Who will be the number one song?
Nogibinko Uresumo Uke
Uresumo Uke
This is the first Uresumo Uke, which was
popular at Assistant MC Gachinko
Audition.
There were a lot of reactions from the
audience, and there were a lot of voices
that they wanted to see more.
Actually, this is a project to decide
the number one song in Omizaka.
This is the first Uresumo Uke, which was
popular at Assistant MC Gachinko
Audition.
At that time, there were only a few
people doing it.
Mr. Akimoto, I heard that the recording
was popular at the Uresumo competition.
How was it?
Karin-chan and I fought, and it turned
out to be surprisingly strong.
I was told that I had no power.
I did it with some people because I had
the power.
Do you have any regrets?
Rime, I'm more interested in you.
You're the one who shook it.
If everyone fought, the possibility was
strong.
It was good.
I think I can win with both hands.
Like a real bird.
I think I can win.
I was confident in the first round of
high-time.
It was exciting, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I see.
Then, let's do such an exciting project
at the dressing room with a special
video today.
So, here is the match card this time.
Here you are.
I made a list of goals.
There are 10 finals, 10 finals, and
finals.
Please look forward to it.
Like "I'm Sawa"
Takayama Kitakome
I feel like I have a lot of power.
I lost to Takayama before, so I'm going
to take revenge this time.
I only did 5.
Minami, do you have a favorite player?
I think Nunami is different.
Nunami, you played bingo before, right?
Yes, I lost to Ame-chan.
I think I'm pretty weak.
My right index finger is weak.
I have a lot of scars.
My nails are crooked.
I want you to throw me.
And this time, as a reward for the
winner,
I prepared something like this.
This is a high-end brand roast steak.
It's in here.
It's amazing.
I'm serious.
This is the match card for the first
round A group.
Will Hashimoto, who is injured, be able
to win?
The first match is
Hashimoto Nanami vs Nakadakana
Congratulations
Nanami, it's your first time, right?
That's right
I was learning baton
I used to use this muscle a lot when I
was a student.
Kanarin also did it on the first day of
6th grade.
That's right. I actually won.
So I'm going to do my best today.
I personally think that Kanarin is a
dark horse.
She seems to have a lot of muscle.
She is also good at dancing.
So I'm going to do my best.
The first match of the first round is
Nanami Hashimoto vs. Kana Nakada.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
The first round.
Ready.
Go!
The winner is Nanami!
I'm happy, but I was surprised.
Actually, I was careful.
I saw you playing the rhythm in the main
story the other day.
Hinachima was really strong.
I'm glad.
Hinachima said she would defeat herself.
I see.
It was a little different from what I
thought.
Great.
Hinachimono lived here.
I lost by a head-to-head battle.
I see.
But, the prize is meat.
To be honest, I didn't have much
motivation.
That's right.
The next match is Itomurica vs.
Horimiyona.
Go for it.
I don't have much image of her arms.
What do you think?
She is muscular.
That's right.
I can beat her.
Really?
Yes.
I've been to the track and field.
Oh, I see.
I've been to Odetate.
I've been to Igaiki.
I've been to Hime.
I've been to Taiketsu.
The second match of the first round is
Ito Marika vs. Horigiyona!
Here we go!
The second match!
Ready, go!
Ito Marika wins!
When I first ran away,
I felt like I was shaking hands with
both of you.
But I think I was the one who started
it.
Why do you look so happy?
I'm happy.
Really?
In the second block, Takayama and
Kitano, who are likely to win, will have
a rematch.
The next match is the third match.
Takayama Kazumi vs. Kitano Hinako.
This is the biggest match of the day.
It's the first round, so I'm a little
nervous.
It was unexpected.
I'm nervous.
Which team do you think will win?
I think Kazumin will win.
I always watch the dance videos of the
members and the dancers.
I see.
I watch them every time I go to the
dance studio.
Me too.
I feel like I'm going to lose.
The third match of the first round is
Takayama Kazumi vs. Kitano Hinako.
I'm nervous. What is it?
I'm under pressure.
Aren't you nervous?
I'm nervous.
I'm grateful for this.
The third match.
Ready...
Go!
I'm sorry.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
It's hard to get the last vote.
It was fun.
You did a good job.
I'll keep up the good work.
Thank you.
The fourth match.
Iketani Erika vs. Sagara Iori.
I don't know.
I've never won in my life.
I can't imagine Iori-chan.
I haven't done this since elementary
school.
This is my first time.
It's amazing.
Which one will win?
The 4th match of the first round, Victor
Erica vs. Kyo Kusanagi.
The 4th match. Ready, go!
The winner is Kyo Kusanagi.
You won.
Thank you.
I won.
How was it?
I couldn't move at all.
I tried to resist, but I couldn't go
this way.
I see.
It's been a long time since we played
arm wrestling.
That's right.
It was fun.
Really?
I'm glad.
The 4 of them will play against each
other in the first round.
Will Akimoto be able to win?
The 5th match. Fukagawa Mai vs. Hoshino
Minami.
Both of them are very soft.
But I have a big body.
You have a big body.
I have a big body.
I'm more like a zombie.
What about you, Minami?
I have a big body.
I was in the gymnastics class when I was
in the third year of high school, and I
had a physical strength of 3400.
That's amazing.
I think that's why I'm strong.
Really?
I'll do my best.
The fifth match of the first round,
Tsukagawa Mai vs. Hoshino Minami.
The fifth match.
Ready, go!
Go!
Tsukagawa Mai.
How was it?
I heard that I was strong, so I was very
determined to do it.
Surprisingly, I was able to do it.
Really?
I thought I was strong at first.
Maybe it's the feeling at first.
That's right.
The next match is the sixth match.
Nishino Nanase vs. Akimoto Konatsu.
Go ahead.
How was it?
This is my first time.
Both of you look weak.
I feel like I'm weak.
Really?
Are you confident that you can win?
I'll do my best.
You have to win.
I have to win.
That's right.
The sixth match of the first round,
Nishino Nanase vs. Akimoto Konatsu.
- Bye. - Bye.
- You're strong. - I'm not.
- You're strong. - I'm not, I'm not.
- You're strong - I'm not.
The 6th match, ready go!
They're a team!
[The second round ends!]
That was amazing.
You were strong.
Yes, I was.
I won.
I lost.
I thought you were weak when you were in
the arm wrestling.
That's not true.
No one was taking care of me.
I'm glad there's no one to take care of
you.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
[To be continued]
Can Higuchi, who showed overwhelming
strength in the last broadcast, show his
strength this time as well?
The 7th match, Ikomarina vs. Sakurai
Reika
How is it?
I was told that I was like a small bird
I came out with a little margin
Really?
I don't think I'll ever win a game like
this again.
[I don't think I'll ever win a game like
this again.]
But Reika is strong.
I don't remember playing Uda-sama that
much
I don't remember winning, so I don't
really like it
To be honest
Round 1, 7th match
Rina Ikoma vs Reika Sakurai
7th match, ready, go!
She's doing it!
I don't know! I don't know!
Thank you!
Which one is it next?
Yeah, next
I can't get the meat
I'll do my best
8th match, Shiraishimai vs Higuchi Hina
This is the last round
Yes, it's the last match
How was it?
I'm confident
Really?
Because Hina is really strong
Hina was strong
But I think Sayurin was really weak
No, no, no
Because she was so strong
She was amazing
I was sleepy and my hands were really
hot
I'm sorry
Round 1, 8th match
The next match is Shiraishi Mai vs.
Higuchi Higuchi!
Ready?
The 8th match! Ready? Go!
Shiraishi Mai wins!
I lost.
I didn't feel like I was going to win.
Really?
It's been a while since we've done this.
I was sweating.
I was confident when I did the siren.
But when I did it with Kazumi in the
dressing room, I lost a lot.
The siren was really loud.
I realized that today.
There are a lot of people like that.
Shiraishi Mai.
I'll do my best to get the first place!
Thank you!
After winning the first round, these
eight players advanced to the semi-
final.
It's a disastrous development that the
winning candidate Higuchi will be
disqualified.
Who will advance to the semi-final?
The first match of the semi-final,
Nanami Hashimoto vs. Marika Ito
Now, the first match of the semi-final.
Ready, go!
She's got it!
Nanami!
Really?
I thought she would win.
I feel like I've gotten stronger since I
came here.
Really?
Nanami doesn't look like she has a
strong arm.
The next match is the semi-final.
Kasumi or Yuri?
That's right.
I see.
I don't think so.
The second match of the semi-final.
Kazumi Takayama vs. Iori Sagara.
Ready, go!
You were pretty strong.
I just did 10 push-ups.
You're already exhausted.
But you were pretty strong.
I was like, "Oh, I'm exhausted."
But then you came back.
I was like, "Let's play."
The third match of the semi-final.
Tsukagawa Mai vs. Akimoto Manatsu.
Ready, go!
You did it!
What was it again?
What was the pressure?
It was 7.
It was definitely 7.
Yeah, you said it.
It was 7.
Try it next time.
I'll try it.
I wonder if I can do it.
The fourth match of the semi-final.
Sakurai Reika vs. Shirai Shimai.
Stop it!
You're just shaking hands.
Are you ready?
The fourth match of the semi-final.
Ready, go!
Amazing!
You were better than when you fought
with Shimai.
I did push-ups.
I thought I could do it.
So I did push-ups.
It was perfect.
The semi-final is over.
Who do you think will win?
Iku-chan!
Mayan.
I've been saying "Mayan" in a low voice
for a while now.
I'll do my best for Erika.
This is a delicious place.
I see.
I want you two to eat meat.
Yes.
How about you, Na-chan?
Eh?
Who do you think will win?
I lost to Manatsu, so I want Manatsu to
do her best.
I'm happy.
That's good.
I'll do my best.
You lost to Manatsu.
I'll do my best for Na-chan.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
Please eat it together.
Yes.
The first match of the semi-final.
Nanami Hashimoto vs. Kazumi Takayama.
It's coming to an end.
It's the semi-final.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
I feel like I'm going to be scolded.
No, that's not true.
Not at all.
It's amazing.
I think I can do it.
I'm nervous.
I want to see this.
Me too.
I'm nervous too.
The first match of the semi-final.
Nanami Hashimoto vs. Kazumi Takayama.
It's coming to an end.
It's a little different at this point.
The first match of the semi-final.
Ready, go!
Huh?
Wait, what?
I'm sorry!
What's wrong?
You're talking, right?
I don't know why you called me
diagonally.
You have an effect.
But it's not like that.
Your fingers are thin, too.
I thought it was casual.
But...
I see.
As soon as you called me, I knew you
were going to take this.
Really?
I don't know how to think.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's strong.
Yay! It's the final!
The second match of the semi-final.
Akimoto Manatsu vs. Shirai Shimai!
Go ahead.
How's this match?
I didn't feel like I was wrestling, but
I felt strong.
I'm a little worried about this.
I was playing softball.
I see.
Muscles.
Well, there was, but I've been watching
Manatsu's matches for a long time, so I
think she's strong, but I want to win if
I can.
I've come this far.
For Erica.
The second semi-final.
The second match is Manatsu Akimoto vs.
Mai Shirai!
The second match of the semi-final!
Ready, go!
Wow!
I didn't know at first, but
I've definitely calculated this so far.
Really?
I knew it.
I thought I would lose, but
I won unexpectedly.
Ikoma-chan...
I can get another score.
You've seen it, right?
You can't be surprised.
Now,
it's a tie.
Kazumi vs Manatsu.
Who do you think will win, Yori-chan?
I don't know.
Takayama-san was really strong.
So, I think Takayama-san will win.
How about you, Ika-chan?
I really don't know.
Honestly, among the four of us,
I thought Manatsu would be the first.
she was really strong.
I don't know.
I think it's a difference in technique.
It's not just about strength.
I see.
Then, the champion is...
Let's decide the winner.
The final match is Kazumi Takayama vs
Manatsu Akimoto.
Let's decide the winner.
Please look at the camera one by one.
I've fought with Manatsu before.
I think I got the meat when she came.
I'll do my best.
I lost when I fought with Kazumi.
I feel like I'm getting stronger when
I'm fighting now.
I want to win the second place with this
feeling.
TAKAYAMA TAZUMI VS AKIMOTO MANATSU
The final match of fate, TAKAYAMA TAZUMI
vs AKIMOTO MANATSU
TAKAYAMA TAZUMI
I didn't expect to win here.
The final match.
Ready.
Go!
It's amazing.
Good luck.
You were strong.
I have fought with everyone so far.
Manatsu was strong without the GUN.
Really?
Yes.
You were strong.
It was fun.
It was a burning final match.
Manatsu lost in the end.
But you won a lot.
I saw a new Manatsu today.
It was good.
I didn't mean to show my strength.
What do you think?
You said you didn't mean to show your
strength.
No.
That's not true.
You are generous.
That's true.
And so, the winner is...
The winner is Kazumi, and she gets a
whole beef steak!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Here you go, champion!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
I can't eat it all by myself, so I'll
either send it to my parents or give it
to someone in need.
I see!
And so, that was the Nagibingo arm
wrestling!
Bye bye!