AISubs
We've arrived at Earth-level Highland!
It's started! Nogizaka Attecoco in Earth-level Highland!
Up until now, the reactions to Fujiyama, Red Tower,
Takabisha, and Nagashimasuka have been the final
episode!
Please vote for the best reactions for each attraction!
The team with the most votes in the first three episodes wins!
The next Nobicoco will give you a reward for making a
project you like!
Here are the results from the last episode!
The third place goes to Team Tenpa! The total number of
votes is 576!
The second place goes to Team Magokakechauzo! The total
number of votes is 953!
And the first place goes to...
Hinachima and Yukaina Nakabatachi! The total number of
votes is 2351!
The total number of votes is...
Hinachima and Yukaina Nakabatachi's total number of
votes is 5593!
Now, the results will determine the winner!
Let's go to the reactions!
The next is...
Dodonpa!
This time it's from Dodonpa!
The theme of the highest speed is 172km, and the
acceleration is over 40km.
The theme of Dodonpa is...
...photo points!
Beautiful face!
How did I look in the photos taken during the investigation?
I want the viewers to judge me!
So, let's choose the members who will judge my face!
What is your face?
3, 2, 1
That's good! That's good!
You are this, right?
This is not Kimigao
Weird face?
Smile Your face Isn't it the same? What's wrong with
your smiley face?
What should I do?
I can't see, I can't see, I can't see I can't see it.
Because it's the opposite!
I'm driving on a highway!
okay, okay It's okay, it's okay.
Good. It's fine.
Eh, I mean, I've been watching all this time. I've been
watching you all the time.
People don't cross each other all the time. Everyone's
been crossing the road.
at all. Not at all.
Good. It's fine.
When are you going to do it?
Guys, really stop. I'm really going to quit.
No! No!
Really, I can't do the Red Coaster. I can't do it on
the red light.
Why don't you go?
We don't have time, so please announce the members who
will challenge. We don't have time, so please announce
the members to challenge.
Please announce the members to ride! Kawago team!
Yes, we are me and Lottie. Yes, we are, me and Lottie.
I can't ride Kawako, but I'll do my best. Kawako. I
can't ride Kawago, but I'll do my best. Kawago.
But, Hiro-chan's facial expression, that, yes, yes, it
may not change. I don't think Hiro-chan's facial
expression will change.
But decide, decide. But, I'll decide, I'll decide.
In a pose that casts magic. I'll do a magic pose.
Higuchi Team!
Our team is Seitan and Hina.
We're good at it.
We have to do our best.
We'll do our best together.
Our team is me and...
I really don't want to do it.
I'll give you a tomato.
I don't want it.
Tomato.
I really don't want it.
I really don't want it, either.
Me, too.
Don't cry.
I'm 18 years old.
I'm not crying.
I'll do my best.
Make a pose that's good for the camera.
I'm eating tomatoes
Tomatoes!
Please prepare tomatoes!
Tomatoes have retired due to lack of tomatoes
Let's choose a replacement
Let's do our best!
Miku-mo is entering instead of Tomato.
Let's start the photo competition.
First, the team that will cast a spell, Hina-chan and
Rotti's challenge.
This is my first time to take a photo.
It's scary.
I heard that it's really fast.
I think it will be a great photo.
I hope I can make a good reaction.
I'll do my best to make a good face.
I'll put my face on your face.
They are taking a photo with a good face in the 172km per hour.
Thank you.
Oh no!
It's bleeding!
What's going on?
If it gets faster suddenly, Mahi will be surprised.
Really?
Launch time! 3, 2, 1!
Launch time!
No!
Wait!
Oh, no!
Ouch!
Ah!
Should I just hit the ground?
Oh, no!
It was much faster than I thought.
Where was the camera?
I didn't know where the camera was.
I was like, what?
Where was it?
It was crazy.
I underestimated it.
It's crazy, isn't it?
It seems that both of them couldn't find the camera.
The photos they are interested in will be released later.
Next, Hinachima and Yukai's friends, Hinachima and
Seitan will challenge.
I'll do my best.
Last time.
Go!
Stop it!
Oh my god.....
I'm not scared at all.
Oh my god, my hands are shaking.
They're shaking so much.
That was crazy.
I don't feel like I'm falling anymore.
I was scared at first, but then I suddenly got into the
camera-like part.
No way!
The cheerful team members.
Seitan succeeded in posing.
We'll take a picture of that later.
The last one is the Deppa team.
Maaya and Mikumo's challenge.
Viewers, we're going to pose like this, so please watch us.
We'll do our best!
Will they succeed in posing with ease?
Please look forward to it!
The last one!
Drift
I am scared!
No!
No, no, no!
My neck hurts!
Maya, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Maya!
Are you crying?
Maya, are you okay?
I was scared.
Did it hurt?
I don't know.
I'm crying because I'm happy.
While shedding tears, Maaya did her best.
What was the result?
Good job everyone!
Good job!
People are laughing at us.
I think we made a good decision.
What do you think?
Let's start with the Kawago team.
Please show us your photos.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
What?
That's not it.
I couldn't tell at all when I got on.
Really?
You couldn't tell?
But the camera is showing the reactions.
I see.
Hina, what's wrong?
She's really worried about you.
It's okay.
The Kawago team's reaction was good.
Yeah.
We might be chosen.
It's okay.
We'll cast a spell on you.
Hina's crying.
I'm going to cry.
Why are you crying?
It's okay.
Next up is the Higuchi team.
Okay.
The photos are...
I'm really sorry.
What?
That's not it.
I want to hear it.
What?
I got the point of the photo.
You got it?
Yeah.
That's mean.
What's wrong with you?
I'm really sorry.
That's mean.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Next up is the Wada team.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
Wow!
That's amazing.
Thank you.
Wow.
That's amazing.
I'm going to forget this.
I decided from the beginning to the end.
I'm so happy.
Maya, you did your best.
This is the only successful person.
Thank you.
That's all for the face-off battle at Dodonpa.
Please vote.
Let's go to the next attraction.
The next attraction is here.
The strongest battle field.
There will be a lot of reactions in the oaki- ashiki,
so I'm looking forward to the reaction of Daigyakuten
here.
So, here is the reaction theme is no, each team is participating.
reaction showdown. The last is the strongest shivering labyrinth.
You will experience horror in an abandoned hospital
with a big turnaround.
First of all, Hinachima and her friends who are
currently number one.
Efforts, gratitude, smiles, 4 PCs in our tall forest.
It's scary because everyone does it so quietly.
Are you going to burst out laughing?
Drop Mars.
Are you okay?
I wonder if the hill is here
We came here without knowing anything
We are looking for a dream
Are you okay?
No! No!
Stop! Stop!
Don't!
No!
They are behind
No! No!
Stop!
I hate you!
Don't leave me alone!
Calm down
I hate you!
Poor you
It's alright
I don't want to be alone
I hate you
I don't want to.
Please stop.
If we are in this close distance, I don't want to do anything.
I don't want to.
Please stop.
Thank you.
I don't want to.
Please stop.
No, no, no.
I think I stepped on something.
It's okay, it's okay.
No.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes, everyone.
Look here.
Look at the umbrella, everyone.
Here, here.
It's okay.
I was surprised.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
We will collect the penlight here.
I was surprised.
I'm scared.
My face feels bad.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
Everyone, slow down.
That's right. Slow down.
Put your feet together.
If you run, you'll die.
It's okay.
The sound is bad.
Are you okay?
No! No!
I don't want to!
No!
No! No!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Is it over?
The cheerful friends clear the stage in a relaxed mood.
What is the evaluation of this reaction?
It's been a long time.
I've been looking down all the time.
I don't know what's going on.
It's been a long time.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Suddenly, I got my feet wet.
I'm tired.
Seitan was amazing.
The ghost is annoying.
When I walked there after the show,
It was so cool.
I was saying, that's my partner.
Next, I'll cast a spell.
It's a team challenge.
Good luck.
Let's make a goal.
One, two, three.
Let's cheer up.
Let's do our best.
I don't want to go.
Bye bye.
I'm scared of being caught.
Catch me too.
I can't be caught.
I don't know.
ahhhhhhhhh
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay, everyone.
Yuna, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I can't do it!
I really can't do it!
Wait! Get away from me!
Okay!
Let's go!
I can't do it!
Are you okay?
Everyone, get away from me!
I'm getting goosebumps!
I can't do it!
I don't want to do it anymore.
Let's go.
This is scary too.
I'm scared that I'll suddenly start crying.
Suddenly?
Wow, this is fun.
Are you guys okay?
Are you okay?
You can do it, you can do it.
This is bad, but I'm laughing.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Mina, you look like a ghost.
It's scary, but it's funny.
I'm not a ghost.
If you're a ghost, hold your left hand.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Your back is bare, right?
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
Mina.
Let's go to the river.
Let's go.
Mina.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
It's scary.
Take care of the stairs.
I can't do it.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you want to go?
Say when you want to go.
No, I can't.
What are you going to do?
Okay, let's go.
Yes, let's go.
FNL, let's go home.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't see it.
Please take a seat.
Okay.
Hold my hand.
Look behind you.
I'm scared.
The party's over!
Everyone is surprised.
Captain Hina and the members were quite in sync, but it
was a nice reaction.
Hina pulled me.
She was walking around saying funny things.
I think it's cool. I think it's cool because I was
laughing the most.
And the last one is Team Depa's challenge.
Are you okay? You should follow the camera.
Hey, hey, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's go home.
One, two, three, let's go.
Hey, no!
Don't come!
I don't want this anymore!
One, two, three, let's go.
Thank you.
I can't do this anymore!
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
Go.
You won't make it.
Don't do that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Clear! Clear!
Clear!
Don't look!
Ok!
Why do you guys have to be here?
Don't look!
Why are you so short?
You have to move forward.
This is the end.
Wait here.
Can I have some experience?
Don't look!
Open your mouth.
It's a running guy, isn't it?
I don't want to go anymore.
I don't want to go here anymore.
What's your name?
I want to be friends with you.
I might not be able to chase you anymore.
These people are normal people.
They're not normal people, they're not normal people.
Should I throw it?
I'll take care of the penlight.
Why are you making that face?
What should I do?
What are you going to do?
Throw it. Throw it.
Throwing it is pitiful.
Hey, go over there and throw the penlight.
Throw it.
It's so pitiful.
It's over. It's over.
It's over. It's over. Hurry up.
Wait, wait, wait.
It will definitely come.
Wait.
It's scary.
It's so pitiful.
What happened to your makeup?
Hey, what happened to your makeup?
I was trying to do my makeup
Maya is crying
Did you live like that?
It's not over yet. I want to go home.
It's really real.
I want to go home.
5 minutes is too long, isn't it?
I don't want to see it!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
I can't do it.
Deppa team managed to get the goal.
It was a nice reaction in a row.
So, Nogikoko who played Fuji-Q Highland.
This is the end of the reaction battle.
Please press the vote button for the team with the best reaction.
Thank you.
Which team won? We will announce it at the opening of
the next Nogikoko.
Please look forward to the next Nogikoko.
Bye bye.
So, everyone, please vote this time as well.
Furthermore, whose reaction was the best through this project?
Please vote for the MVP as well.