AISubs
Let's start cooking.
Basically, it's up to you.
Curry, Yakisoba, BBQ.
If you have high-quality ingredients, use them.
If you want to cook rice, do it by yourself.
By yourself?
Yes, do it by yourself.
Like this?
Wow.
Please do it.
You have 2 hours.
2 hours?
It's 2 minutes.
We have the ingredients.
Please show your cooking skills and cook delicious food.
Okay.
Let's start.
Let's go!
Okay, let's start.
Let's start with the barbeque one.
The air-conditioned beef one.
The sparkling one.
Anything is fine.
Show me.
Curry.
This one.
Is this the only one?
It's fine.
Half?
Let's cut it in half.
We have to light it up with this.
Let's light it up first and then put it in.
That's right.
Let's put it in.
First of all, please cut the vegetables.
Let's start the fire.
Let's do the rice.
Wash your hands.
You guys will wash the vegetables first.
Rice.
Two people cook rice.
I will cook the fire.
Mayaka, you're good at cooking.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
Thank you.
How can you turn off the fire?
I'll turn on the fire.
Isn't it okay to put the charcoal in?
Put the charcoal in and then turn on the fire.
Turn on the fire?
How do you turn on the fire?
With a gas stove?
If you put the firewood in, it won't burn, right?
It won't burn.
Is it okay to set it up?
Around here.
It's done.
Which one is this? A leaf?
Yeah, if there's a tree branch.
We'll light it up.
And light up the corner.
It's like...
We'll light it up with this.
What's this?
I think it's a lighter.
We did it!
It's like a curry room.
It's a lighter.
We did it!
Do your best, everyone.
You're putting in a lot of ink.
I'm putting in a lot of ink, right?
Hina-chan!
What should we do?
Leave it to me.
But I put in a lot of ink yesterday, too.
Maybe you should put in a lot of ink.
Is this okay?
Yume-tan, this is big!
I'll leave it to you.
That's great.
It's a fire!
What are you doing? We have to make a fire.
Let's make a fire.
I'm looking for a pine cone.
There's a fire in the corner.
I'll make a fire with a pine cone.
It looks like it's going to be a very soft day.
I wonder if there's anyone out there.
I wonder if it's going to burn.
Isn't it good?
Thank you very much.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, the fire has started.
Oh, welcome back.
Welcome back.
Hey, how did you start the fire?
Thank you very much.
You can do it with a stone.
A stone?
Are you a primitive person?
Are you from the Yagoyama period?
Are you from the Dōmon period?
I didn't think it was that kind of fire.
There's a fire here.
The fire is getting bigger.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna stick it on, so it's gonna disappear.
It's gone!
Oh, my God! What do we do?
It's not good to put it all in.
Oh, yeah.
I'll do it.
I'll do my best.
Is this okay?
It's gone.
What do we do?
Adults have to teach me.
I started the work.
I have to take it properly.
I can cook unexpectedly.
Really.
It's not fair.
It's a family business.
This is like a man.
I'll do it.
I don't know how to do this.
She's working hard right now.
I don't like this job.
She's working hard.
I'll do my best.
Curry.
Why are you so cute?
That's scary.
I'm scared.
It's cold.
I put it in.
It's hard.
If I leave it as it is, will it go out?
It's okay if you put it on to some extent.
I wonder if it's okay next to it.
It looks delicious, it looks delicious.
I was failed.
It's a volleyball team.
How much water do we need?
This is rice.
Four people are about three cups.
Isn't this the line inside?
No, it's not.
It's like cup ramen.
This? This?
Yes, this.
How about Eihina?
But three cups is usually water.
If we fail, let's boil it again.
That's right.
We have two hours.
Yes, let's boil it first.
Let's boil the rice first.
Where is the rice?
We're going to get the rice.
We have to boil the rice, too.
The rice is over there.
I don't want to be caught by the other team.
This is about strawberry, isn't it?
Don't look at me!
Just open it.
Just use the third one.
There's a mark here.
This is second time use.
Mm, it's delicious.
It's kinda good, it's light and hearty...
You can see it, right?
It's okay.
Which one is strawberry?
This one.
This one is strawberry?
Yes, one.
Strawberry.
Two.
Three.
Four.
I think there are about two here.
Two.
Nothing's written here.
What?
We have to write a script.
The girls are scary.
I hate them.
Who's 20? Who's 20?
No.
I'm scared.
If you want to see it, look in the shadows.
No.
I hate them.
Let's do our best.
Is it working?
I'm going to wash it.
Oh, thank you.
It's okay.
Everyone is going to the toilet.
Toilet!
Let's go!
If the water comes out of the tap...
If it doesn't come out...
If you do it about three times...
From the eyes of the water...
About one joint?
About one joint from the eyes of the water.
Toilet!
This is how you do it.
Put your fingers here, and then you pour the water.
I can't do it.
You can't do it.
This is this one.
Yes, yes, yes.
And this is this one.
And then you pour the water.
I don't know if the coffee is strong enough.
No, it's not.
It's not strong enough.
This is how you do it.
By the way, what kind of curry do you want?
Not the kind of curry I thought.
What kind of curry do you want?
You know, goro goro curry or...
I like smaller meat.
I like the one without goro goro.
You know, I like all the small ones.
What?
I like the small ones.
I see.
The carrots are really small, too.
But barbecue is goro goro.
There is such an image, isn't it?
It's delicious.
Do you want some tea?
Well, for the time being,
I'd like to have a small one that doesn't melt.
I'd like to have a small one.
Have you ever made curry?
Yes, I think so.
With this.
I don't think it's a good idea to take too much.
I don't really participate in it.
But I watch it.
I've never made it before.
You've never made it before?
I like this one better.
When I was a student, I used to bring gloves with me to
practice cooking.
I used to bring gloves with me, but I couldn't do anything.
You always said that.
I didn't touch it, so I couldn't eat it.
Everyone said, Hina, it's okay.
Oh, you're scared.
You know it.
What?
Hina, it's dangerous.
I can't do it.
When was the last time you cooked?
That's not true. I went to a cooking practice this year.
I was just waiting like this.
I didn't do anything.
I put a plate like this.
It's a plate.
There's Hina.
So today, look.
I'm waiting.
It's amazing.
If my friends see this, they'll applaud me.
I think it's amazing.
You can do it even when you're in elementary school.
I always failed.
Everyone was disappointed.
Really?
I put in about 10 times more salt.
You're scary.
I put salt in the salad.
What?
It was a big deal, and I couldn't eat it.
Only our team was able to make bread.
Everyone was looking at our salad.
That's good.
Thanks to Hina.
We don't need that this time.
I don't do it.
That's all.
Is this Mijin-Gi Gai?
Yes, it is.
If it's small, it's Mijin-Gi Gai.
What is it?
Curry Mijin-Gi Gai?
I want to eat it quickly.
I think this is enough.
Wait, isn't it big?
Is it big?
This?
This looks good.
I don't like onions very much.
Potatoes are clear.
I'm hungry.
Did you eat?
No.
Is there anything you like?
I don't like it.
I'll make you a curry.
Is it okay to eat this?
Do you want to eat?
It's better to eat it.
Please.
Which one do you want?
This one.
Don't get schaff, right?
Do I have to take this too?
Oh sorry, that's wrong.
Come on!
Becauseings also could be eaten.
That's really easy to eat.
Here you are.
2 boiled eggs, please.
I'm cutting the onion.
How is it? I cut it all.
You're right.
Isn't this crazy?
They're selling juice!
I made it.
Put it all in.
What kind of curry do you want?
Curry.
Can I have the spicy one?
I'll have the spicy one.
Yay!
They're selling juice!
What kind of curry do you want?
Spicy curry!
I'll have the spicy one.
You don't like spicy food?
I'm fine with spicy food.
So I'll have the spicy one.
What's your team name?
My team name is Team Fire!
Fire!
You're weak.
Fire is weak.
Come on, Fire!
Put it in the curry.
Is 2 potatoes enough?
That's right.
Which one is bigger?
3 or 4?
3 or 4.
It's okay no matter how much.
Put 2 carrots.
And onion.
Is it burning?
What is the name of the team?
It's called ORIGINALITY.
What is the name of the eggplant?
It's a great name.
It's summer.
Summer is coming.
What is the name of the team?
It's ORIGINALITY.
Hey, do you wash the pumpkin?
Well...
It's okay.
The inside is wet.
I don't need it.
It's okay because the seeds are removed.
As expected of Maya.
Eggplant.
It doesn't look like it.
It's rude.
Why?
It's cute.
Really? Thank you.
Maya is cute.
Let's do that.
What should we do?
It's stuck.
Let's make a summer vegetable curry.
Okay.
I can't eat tomatoes and eggplant.
Why?
Let's eat tomatoes.
I don't like tomatoes.
No.
If you don't like it, you can eat it.
I can eat it.
Can I put the pumpkin in?
It's okay to put the pumpkin in.
It's better to put it in.
I'll put it in.
I'll put anything in.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I can't eat it.
The pumpkin.
I see.
Pumpkin.
I can't eat it.
Let's cook something else.
What should we cook first?
Let's peel the skin first.
We can peel the skin with this.
Peeler, peeler.
Can't we peel it with a knife?
Peeling potatoes with a knife is really good.
Really?
Then peel it.
How do you peel it? With a knife?
Peel it with a knife.
As expected.
Then, Nene.
Nene, peel the potatoes with a knife.
I can peel it with a knife.
This.
The net.
It's hard.
Is it okay for me to do this?
I'm cutting onions, right?
When I was working part-time, I was cutting onions a lot.
It's nostalgic.
That's the story.
It's better to eat onions here.
What should I do?
Wait a minute.
One by one.
Just like before.
What are you doing?
I'm making a taxi.
Are you serious?
Are you going to grill it?
What?
Have you ever grilled a tomato? It's really bad.
It's a grilled tomato.
Isn't it really bad?
It's delicious.
Are you kidding me?
What are you going to do?
I thought it was going to be served with curry.
Because there are only three.
What? A tomato?
Are you serious?
Look at this.
I did it.
It's so bad.
Stop it.
Work.
It's done.
What are you putting on it?
The rest of the shrimp.
Leave it.
Where is the pork?
I'm scared. Where is the pepper?
Do you have pepper?
I can cook rice.
You can cook rice?
OK.
I finished my work.
Do you have anything to do?
This.
Wait a minute.
I'm doing it by myself.
I often use a knife.
It's not my knife, so it's really hard to do.
I'll make it, too.
What should I do?
It's hard to do.
I don't have a knife.
I can't do anything.
Hurry up!
Put down 50kg.
Why don't you use a kitchen knife?
Take opportunity.
My refrigerator.
It's ok.
I can't hold it.
No tighten.
Which meat did you eat?
I ate onion.
I did it.
Let's cut this yakisoba in half and grill it.
This is for yakisoba.
OK.
Oh, corn.
Oh, that's good.
I don't have a knife.
Oh, you have a knife.
Where did I put the knife?
Where did I put it?
Where did you put it?
Be careful.
Why is it gone? I put it here.
What?
The knife is gone.
Where is it?
Someone hid it.
It's good.
What are you looking at?
What is it?
Give me back my coat!
Me!
I got it!
I thought you don't use it.
I got it.
You can come in when you get the pouch.
Are you kidding me?
It's over.
I'll wash the peppers and carrots.
Carrots.
Did you get the iron plate?
I didn't get it.
Oh, there is an iron plate.
Really?
I didn't get it.
Liar! Why did you put it on the floor?
Liar!
You!
It's fine.
What should we do?
Let's make curry.
Can we make curry with this?
Yes.
Let's try.
Let's do it.