AISubs
The first match of the second round is Nagashima team
vs. Ando team.
Of course, Nagashima team is famous for throwing and shooting.
Nagashima team won the first match of the second round.
No.1 Yukina No.2 Hoshide No.3 Hina No.4 Sato No.5
Go! Go! Go!
Next, the team name of Ando Churu and Uchiyama
Uchiyama, our team name is...
Ready, go!
Eimaki Ichigo!
Say it, say it!
What is it?
Ichigo?
Our team name is...
Because we're being teased...
Yes!
But actually, there's a power hidden in us.
We're being teased by Eimaki Ichigo.
Yes!
She's being teased.
No, really.
The concept of this team is...
Everyone, I know for sure.
You may think I'm weak, but...
Really, actually...
Each of us has a power hidden in us.
Actually, the concept is that we're strong.
We're being teased.
So, what's the order?
The order?
The order is...
What's the order?
2 points!
Yes!
3 points!
You got 100 points!
Let's check the rules.
One person will throw one ball at a time.
The winner will be free to throw the ball at the end of the game.
Let's get started!
Team Bishoujo Fire Seal vs Team Erimaki Ichigo
Outch, outch!
Don't do that, please!
Ah no, which one it is?
blizzard though!
Do we need to put in clouds in the middle?
Right there?
The scale is 8x8!
If there are clouds in the middle
they will be played as a jakuvian healthy demo Area
OK!
You can do it!
I can't do it!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
What's wrong?
Asuka, what's wrong?
She's a bit weak.
Go, go, Asuka!
Go, go, go!
Stop it!
Ooh.
We did it!
I hope it's not rain.
It's not rain.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I hope it's not rain.
Time up!
What's this?
she is really good
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
I haven't even started yet.
I'll do my best!
Hina, calm down.
Ah!
It's okay!
I'll do my best!
What?
Wow!
You did it!
I can't do it!
Thank you for enjoying!
he's so up
You have to catch it.
You can do it!
I'll catch it!
I did it.
It's a good position, isn't it?
You can catch it!
You did it!
I'll do my best.
Can I practice?
No, you can't.
Yes, yes, yes.
Be gentle.
Do your best.
Yukina, I'm counting on you.
Everyone, calm down.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Everyone, calm down.
Oh No, they missed it, again.
The song stopped because of you that's me?
It's coming!
I passed everything
What happened?
That is amazing
So, why do I lose?
What's that?
Yabai!
Are you okay?
Really?
I'm losing.
I lost.
It's okay.
Yabai!
The last round.
I won!
Yabai!
Miku is strong.
Let's do our best.
Which way should I go?
I'll go this way.
Let's do our best.
Uwhaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
NEO Spy
How many points do you have left?
A lot, a lot, a lot.
6 points left!
Wait, what is this?
It's a big one.
Hang in there.
I don't know what it is.
At least one.
Hang in there.
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
Don't throw it at me!
Someone pushed my pelvis!
I'll do my best!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
I'm trying my best.
I don't know what to do.
Thank you very much.
Good job, Asuka.
Without any hesitation
Please come out!
Wow!
Mami is good!
Please come out!
What is this?
I don't want to do this!
Ahhhh!
Hey!
Ah!
It's a tie!
That's interesting!
experiences
fun
It was very good
It was delicious
There is a captain now.
Good luck!
You can do it!
Are you okay?
No.21, 5 points lead!
I wonder if it's okay.
It's okay.
Curve, curve!
Yabai!
Put down your sword!
It would have been better if you had a temper.
You can do it!
Calm down!
The first day of the competition
Come on, Asuka!
Let's go!
You can do it!
What?
She's going to fall!
Asuka is eliminated!
Asuka!
Ami!
OK Let's go
I like you, Sae but I'm cute now
These people were so smart
She's doing it!
She's getting better!
She's getting better every time!
She's doing it!
She's doing it.
Calm down.
Where are you going?
Yukinon!
We did it!
Thank you very much.
Next.
That is amazing!
Don't stand in front of the camera.
You don't have to stand in front of the camera.
I'm sorry.
Everyone, quick look at the
I want to die.
I really want to die.
It's important here.
You can't lose.
I'm going.
It's beautiful.
It's 36.
It's 45.
I got a nosebleed.
I want to be the ugly five.
jw
be
up
that
It's in, It's in, It's in, Ialdabae!
He's losing!
полностью
He's swimming normal
Thank you very much!
It's 4.44 seconds.
It's still 1.2 seconds.
You can do it now.
It's important.
I'm sorry.
Nami.
Is there no such thing as this?
Finally, it's time for the last round.
The winner is...
44 vs 52
6 points!
8 points!
What should we do with this team?
What should we do?
This is bad.
Next, the last round.
It doesn't matter who wins.
Foul
Move your hands!
Not yet! Not yet!
It's like a magic show.
Oh, it's starting.
Oh, it's good.
It's good.
It's a miracle.
I'm so happy.
A lot of toys fell down.
I can't reach the metal that was Knights's's obstacle.
The spoiled Captain Joined the Nobody Rival.
I tried my best at second attack, but failed.
Ahhhh!
Wow!
That's crazy!
So cute!
This is fun!
That's great!
Awesome!
I ate the last one!
Stop it!
I hate you!
Me too!
I love you!!!
What is it?
It's a lie.
What happened?
Oh, no.
Now,
the mission is
to get the same score as the first one.
The same score.
So,
we will extend the game.
We don't have time.
The game will be decided by this.
Everyone, are you okay?
I'll do my best!
It's all right.
It's really scary.
It's okay.
I think it's okay.
It's a miracle.
It's okay.
Still one more time.
Just one more time.
It's okay.
One more time!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
It's dangerous!
④ worse than 0
It's okay.
The game break.
fürTH
⑤ How many 38
jetzt
Aaaaaaah!
What was that?
I don't know.
You don't know, do you?
Wait!
Aaaaaaah!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Everyone is crying!
It's 4 point half.
Yeah, I can get it in one shot.
My first throw.
she is also dancing
It's really scary.
Amazing.
What are you doing?
Don't do that.
It's really scary.
Aaaaaaah!
Oh no!
You threw it for the first time!
That's what I'm saying!
In the first match of the semi-final, the Mishodo Fan
Team got 56 points and the Erimaki Ichigo Team got 60
points.
The Erimaki Ichigo Team won!
I'm so glad!
Everyone's crying!
I'm so happy!
Waa~~ connection is such that it is difficult to get a picture.
I chose Asuka as my daughter-in-law.
I'm so happy for you.
By the way, how many times did you hit Ami?
How many times did you hit Ami?
It doesn't matter if I win or not.
It's because you won.
BBS46
Let's have fun!
Tamakorodashi!
I'm the first one to do this.
Tamakorodashi
This is not good.
You lost to me.
I lost to everyone.
BBS46
I lost again!
I wonder where the voice comes from on a full moon night
I can hear the voice
Let's put a kiss on the wolf, the melody of love
Rather than picking a fang and biting into someone
Let's put a kiss on the wolf, a gentle song
Just by smiling, the world will change
Yes, what is the meaning of this life?
Now I understand that to live is not to take each other
Even if you don't hurt someone
I see my own dreams
It's a fight, and it's a waste
Let's put a kiss on the wolf, the melody of love
Rather than picking a fang and biting into someone
Let's put a kiss on the wolf, a gentle song
Just by smiling, the world will change
Someday I will understand, in the dark night
I stand by your side and look for the wind
Your voice has changed into a whisper
Wolf, know love, the burning flame
If you look at someone, you will understand
Let's fall in love, let's show a smile
Forgetting the past and living in the present