AISubs
Now, it's started! Nogizaka-te-koko!
This time, we won the last bowling tournament.
We're doing a reward project for One 46!
Yeah!
That's right. We won the tournament.
This time, it's our turn.
And this time, we can do anything.
We made a request.
The request is...
Nogizaka-te-koko BBQ Tournament!
BBQ is good, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
In this hot weather...
Let's do BBQ in this hot weather.
So, this time, we want to do BBQ.
Yes.
But, it's BBQ, so...
It's good to do it with a large number of people.
I think it's better to do it with a large number of people.
So we'd like to invite them specially.
Please!
Thank you.
It's a great honor.
You can call me miss.
Miss?
Yes.
What's wrong, Higashio?
The UV rays are a little...
Ah, nice.
If you have UV rays, your face will be a little tanned.
No, no, no.
You can leave right away.
Thank you very much.
So, the three teams that lost this time will have a
barbecue together.
But, we'll give them a special chance.
Because it's fun.
Thank you very much.
But, in return, we'll have them follow the rules we set.
Okay.
The four teams that won the bowling tournament will be
the leaders.
Four teams.
Four teams will cook together.
The four of us will make our favorite curry, yakisoba,
and barbecue.
We'll make it freely as we like.
That's the rule.
Yay!
Are you ready?
You'll have to follow the rules.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'd like to decide the teams right away.
Just like last time, I'd like to make Nogikoko a draft team.
Yay!
This time, I'd like to choose people who are good at cooking.
Leave it to me.
Yes.
What should we do?
Let's decide the teams right away.
Okay.
Let's decide the first one.
Are you okay?
Wait, you can cook?
It's my first year living alone.
You can cook once.
I know you're not good at cooking.
Wait, I'm not good at cooking.
Look at this face.
Are you okay?
Have you decided?
If you wear it, you'll play rock-paper-scissors like last time.
The first one is MisaMisa.
Good.
I won't give it to you, MisaMisa.
I'm so happy.
MisaMisa is my team.
Please vote for me.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
My favorite is...
My favorite is...Sherry.
I'm Ami.
Ami is correct.
Ami is definitely correct.
I got it.
What should I do?
I'll give you a plate.
You said you can do a number
Okay, it's decided.
I am
Hata Naka
Yay!
Why?
It seems to be an original.
Really?
But I'm good at it.
I drew it when I was a kid.
In other words,
Then,
I'm Nene Koro.
Wow!
I'm happy.
I'll do my best.
Ready, set, go.
Rocky!
Let's do this for real.
Yamato!
Really? I was not motivated to do this.
OK!
Mom!
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best to wash the dishes.
I'm sure you all know this, but there's one person left
at the end.
The last person left will be able to join the team they like.
I'm old, so I want to join the team I like.
Have you all decided?
There's a reason to lower your average age.
Thank you very much.
Good!
Maya!
You can do anything.
I can do anything.
Really?
I'm on a blog.
Next, Murashima.
Thank you very much.
Can you do it?
One, two, three!
Let's go!
You can do it!
I can eat a lot by myself.
You can choose your favorite tree.
Come on!
Can you do it?
Can I go in?
I want to eat a lot.
I'm not confident.
Congratulations!
Thank you so much for saying such a kind thing.
Since the team has been decided, let's do our best with
this team!
Have you decided your team name?
Yes, we have.
Let's start with the team leader.
One, two, three.
Team Fire!
Gamuzo!
She looks strong.
And Iwasetina.
Do you remember?
Yes, I do.
I can't remember it.
We are Anata no Ibukuro Tsukamimasu team.
It's a good team, isn't it?
They look strong.
I think it's Ibukuro.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I don't think you can cook for them at the age of 22.
That's true.
We are serious!
We are tall and young.
Dekoboko Girls!
I'll do my best!
So cute!
She's so chubby.
She's the tallest and the smallest.
She's so tall.
She really is.
She's so cute.
Ready?
Press the button!
I want to be your wife!
The reason is...
We'll sweat it out and do our best.
That's not the point.
We'll all do our best.
No, no, no.
We'll do our best, sweat it out, and make something delicious.
That's right!
Good job!
What are you talking about?
Okay, so we've decided on our names.
We're going to make curry, yakisoba, and barbeque.
Here are the ingredients.
But that's not all.
Something's coming out.
Something's coming out!
Something's coming out, but...
We've prepared this, too.
Ta-da!
What's that?
Shrimp?
Wow!
Shrimp, wow!
What's that?
Shrimp and...
What is it?
It's a croquette!
Wow!
It's a shrimp!
That's amazing!
I didn't expect you to be alive.
It's so cute.
It's so shiny.
I want to eat it.
I'm not that kind.
So, we can eat this high-class food.
Let's play a game.
Only the first and second place can eat it.
What?
Really?
That's...
The first place team is black beef.
The second place team is Isebi.
What?
Well...
That's what it is.
Can I get all three?
You can't get all three.
Why?
You can't eat it.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
So,
High-quality food,
Beach ball rally competition.
The rule is,
Two teams,
Everyone will do a beach ball toss rally.
Challenge twice in total,
The ranking will be determined by the total number of times.
The rally alone will not count, so please be careful.
So,
Which team will do it?
I want to practice.
Are you confident?
Have you ever done it?
I've done it before.
I've done a volleyball.
You're strong.
I've done volleyball when I was in elementary school.
That's why I chose it.
Did you win?
Wow, Yumi.
Not yet.
It's okay.
Let's grab your stomach!
Team!
1st try!
Start!
1, 2, 3!
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21!
So, this is the 21st episode of the team to grab the stomach!
Let's start the 1st round of Water Girls!
Wow!
40 times!
So, this is the first time for Water Girls!
Wow!
That's amazing!
The second time for Water Girls!
So, this is the first time for Water Girls!
Yeah!
Good luck!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Come back, come back
Wonderful
Because it was the real show
Are you still doing the real show?
I'm doing it, I'm doing it
It's close, it's close
It's the first time
What should we do next?
What should we do?
Let's do it one more time
It's no good
Let's do it again
Thank you
Let's start the first round of Team Fire
I got away.
Stop it.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How many points do you have?
I have 46 points.
46?
Team Fire has 46 points.
What?
I have 31 points.
Are you sure?
I have two points.
The first round is over.
The first score is
21 points for Team Fire,
40 points for Supporter Girls,
8 points for Deco Boco Girls,
and 46 points for Team Fire.
Yeah!
You are still in the first place.
Yes.
But you can still do it, right?
Yes, I can.
But Deco Boco Girls is still in the first place.
We gave you a chance.
It's not funny.
Don't laugh.
We are serious.
Next,
we will aim for the 100th time.
We will aim for the 100th time.
Let's do our best in the second round.
We will do our best.
We will aim for the 100th time.
The second round.
The first round is Team Fire.
Let's do our best.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23,
That's good!
So, Team Fire's second attempt was 21 attempts,
46 attempts,
and 21 attempts,
and 67 attempts in total.
The second round is Water Girls, but the first round is
40 times, so it will be the first place with more than
27 times.
It's tough.
Alright, then, Water Girls, start!
Good luck!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 23, 24, 25, 26,
23, 24.
We won!
We didn't win the first place.
The first place is Team Fire, 67 points.
The second place is Water Girls, 62 points.
The team that gets the most stomachs wins.
If you get 47 or more, you get the first place.
If you get 42 or more, you get the second place.
We won't get anything else!
We won!
Good luck!
Let's start the second round!
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26,
23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36,
37, 40, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53 , 54, 55,
56,I can see that the sky is delicious.
It's 39, so it's a total of 60.
But it's amazing.
I did my best!
But I didn't get anything!
Next is the last challenge.
Dekoboko Girls won the first round 8 times.
If you do 60 times, you will be number one.
If you do 55 times, you will be number two.
Good luck.
Let's start.
Let's do it.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19.
We did it.
Don't say that to me!
I'm so sad!
We did it!
The total is
The team that uses your stomach
21 plus 39 is 60 times
Water girls
40 plus 22 is 62
Dekoboko girls
8 plus 19 is 27
And team fire
46 plus 21 is 6 times
Team fire is the winner
It was close
One team is left
So the winner is
Team black
The winner is
It's up to you
Let's get ready
Let's go!