AISubs
Today's MCs are me, Misato Eto, and Yukina Kashiwa.
Nice to meet you.
Compared to the previous MIUMIU, we have to work harder.
Yes, we have to work hard.
This program is to let everyone know the charm of the
under members of Nogizaka46.
It's basically a no-cut recording for 20 minutes, so it
may be hard to see, but please watch over us warmly.
Thank you.
Let's all do our best.
Yes, this program is a program that targets each member
and introduces the information collected from other
members.
From now on, one by one, we will introduce the
information collected in this pipe chair.
Oh, it wasn't a pipe chair.
It's a chair.
Yes.
That's right.
We're going to introduce four people in 20 minutes, so
we don't have time at all, so I'd like to go right
away.
Yes.
Then I'll go to the first target.
Who is it?
It's Nene!
Wow!
Please come here.
It's scary.
There is a witness, but before that, there will be a
drop in the monitor, so here is the first one.
What does this mean?
When I was staying at Nene's house,
If this is the pillow, there is a window on the foot side.
I sleep with my feet on the window sill.
What do you mean?
I'm hot-tempered.
So, especially in the summer, I try to find a cold
place with my feet.
As a result, I ended up sleeping like that.
Do you sleep in your own house?
That's right.
Other people sleep properly.
I want to see what kind of posture it is.
How do you do it?
I sleep like this.
This is also difficult.
Has anyone else seen it?
Hinojima
When did you see it?
When I was sitting next to Nene on the bus, I said, I'm sorry.
Nene is small, so she fits in the head of the previous
person's chair.
So I put my feet on it and said, I'm sorry.
It's a strange way of sleeping.
Let's move on to the next question.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've done it, so I'd like
to do it now.
You want to see it, don't you?
Can I take off my socks?
Don't look at me.
Hurry up.
It's been a long time.
I'll do my best.
Where?
Cute
Amazing
Why can you do Bakuten?
I was learning mechanical gymnastics until I was in
elementary school.
I've been doing it since I was a kid, so I'm used to it.
Is there anyone else who can do Bakuten in Nohizaka?
The only one
I want to do it again
That was Nene Ito.
Thank you very much.
Next is
I wonder if it's okay, I'm sorry, I'd like to go next.
Nagashima Sailor
Don't, don't say it.
Can I sit down?
Then I'd like to go right away.
Here
This is big.
That's right.
I think so.
Nagashima Sailor
I think everyone has probably experienced it once, but
Sailor-rin's voice is really loud at the handshake
party, and it's not the usual loudness, but it's really
amazing, so when I'm next to Sailor-rin at the
handshake party, I think I'm really done.
Is it different? Is it different? Is it different?
Everyone is a victim.
Yes, I'm not a handshake party, but I went to a haunted
house when recording for the movie Nobidoko before, but
I was about 200 meters away from the haunted house.
You had to push yourself too hard
talented
We were scared
hole
Why is Nakashima-san's voice so loud?
I think
Anyway, I'll make a justification
An excuse?
At the handshake event, we were thinking about you in
the first place
All dangerous
The first thing you would say,
Thank you and thank you
and thank you
It's Nacchan!
What about the others?
I raised my hand earlier.
Yes.
I'm always next to Rin.
It's really noisy.
But you're a calm Taisho.
I know how to deal with it, so it's okay.
That's why my fans say,
Hina, you're next to me.
Also, Marika Ito.
She has a sexy voice.
Really?
I want to hear it.
How do you do it?
Everyone says this, right?
For example, Nene.
Nene.
The movement is imitating.
Like this.
Wait a minute.
Even if I say something like,
Hey, hey, hey,
Everyone's going to pay attention to me.
That's why.
I want you to pay attention to me.
I want you to pay attention to me, so...
Hey, MisaMisa.
Even if I stare at Sailor-Lin and
I want you to pay attention to me,
Sailor-Lin won't pay attention to me.
That's because you're a tsundere.
That's fine.
I want you to pay attention to me.
I want you to pay attention to me, Sailor-Lin.
There's another one.
There's another one?
Yes, this one.
A strange posture.
What do you mean by that, Sailor-rin?
There's a person who made that up.
Yukagawa Mai.
I heard Sailor-rin has a very comfortable posture.
When she's tired from a lesson or something,
she stands up and...
I can't imitate it, but...
By yourself?
It's not weird. It's comfortable.
It's really like...
Put your cell phone here.
Put your cell phone in the water.
That's amazing.
Why is that?
Rather than doing it like this,
It's easier to do it like this.
Why?
She's doing it well.
I wonder if it's coming out.
When I was doing my hair and makeup earlier,
I was sitting in this position when I was doing my makeup.
Really?
I'd like to actually put something down.
Can I put it down?
Let's put it down.
Can you put it down?
Isn't it too small?
Should I roll it?
Maybe not.
It can't be a cell phone.
Wait a moment.
It's a little round.
It's amazing that it's not going down.
Awesome!
What did you gain from it?
What did I gain?
Eh, it's easy.
Eh? Everyone's easy, right?
Let's go with something big.
Is it coming?
It's coming.
Sexy.
Eh?
It's coming.
You've decided.
I've decided.
Thank you.
Amazing.
You can do it, right?
You can't do it.
It was such an interesting Celery.
Thank you.
Let's move on.
Next is...
Cowagohina!
Please take a seat.
Here we go.
Go ahead.
This is...
Please take a seat.
What do you mean, Kago-san?
No, it's not like that.
We're getting a lot of responses.
First of all, Ito Nene.
I've never actually been there, but I've heard a lot of
dirty comments from the members.
Who's the first person you've been there?
Me.
How is it?
There's no room for me to step on.
That's right.
But everyone's telling me to stop it.
How dirty is it?
The moment you enter the front door.
The front door.
It's not clean at all.
But that's how it is.
I'm living alone right now.
My mom used to do it for me.
So what do you say?
I feel like I'm back home.
I went to the front door.
It's like a school.
Wait a minute.
I left my chocolate food.
There's a lot of chocolate garbage and snacks.
What?
There are a lot of snacks.
I told her, can I have this?
I'm eating it.
And Mai Mai.
Once it was so dirty that I was a little scared when we
were going to go play at home.
Also, we all cleaned up the mess together.
It was so bad.
We all cleaned up the mess together, but it took about
a week to clean it up.
It's a bad idea.
No, but it's okay.
I'm going to clean it up in a few weeks.
What?
I want you to clean it up and post it on your blog.
It's okay to have a shelf.
There's another one.
This one.
Cute.
I know.
It's cute.
It's cute, but I feel like I'm laughing alone.
The witness is Hime.
I don't have to explain it, but the sneeze is cute.
Hime is cute.
I'll do it once.
What is it?
It's a sneeze.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute, but it's cute.
It's weird.
Can I say something?
I was on the bus the other day, and the makeup artist
sneezed at me.
I thought I was sending it by radio, but it was really small.
Who thinks my sneeze is weird?
It's cute.
I've never seen it, so I've heard of it.
I want to see it.
I prepared it.
I prepared three of them.
It's not that easy for me.
It's not that easy.
Hang in there.
It's hard to see.
Do you have to do both?
Do both.
Hold your breath.
I don't want to see it.
I can't see it.
Look!
Doesn't it hurt?
It's okay.
The sound is so small.
Everyone, be quiet.
Do your best.
It's not coming out.
Is that so?
Don't touch it.
It stinks.
It's coming out!
It's not coming out.
It's cute!
The pressure of the world was too much.
It was a little small.
Let's do our best so that we can keep showing up.
Thank you very much!
Let's move on to the next target.
The fourth target is Ami Ami!
There are a lot of Ami Ami.
Please come here.
Let's get started.
This is Ami Ami information.
Public Opening
Impersonation.
But actually, everyone knows it.
It's like evidence.
First is Anno.
Wow.
You are good at original copy of member.
Your true Nani era is real it the impression you get
maybe it's like that if you do so Well just you see it.
Mr.What killed?
Well, it's not...
I want to know.
I really don't know how to say this, but I think
everyone has a different point of view on people.
I think everyone has a different point of view on
people, so I think I might be good at it.
I heard that you're not good at impersonating other members.
Ami has a lot of impersonations, but if you say it in
secret, it's Hime-tan's impersonation.
Can you impersonate me?
Okay, I'll do it.
I'm Nakamoto Hime. Please call me Hime-tan.
Hime-tan, come out for a second.
We don't look alike.
I want to see if we look alike.
Are you ready?
One, two, three...
Thank you very much!
I wonder what it is.
How was it, everyone?
It was good!
Thank you!
I want you to do something else.
I wonder if anyone is here.
I was just imitated by Ami-ami.
I was imitated in front of everyone.
I was so embarrassed that I told them to stop.
Is it a new story?
That's right.
I don't know what it is.
I don't want to hear it.
Actually,
There's a DVD in the CD of the oil shampoo.
There's a date video in it.
In that...
The first word of Hinachima.
I'm sorry.
Let's do that.
Let me hear your purring.
I came here 30 minutes ago.
One minute left?
Ah, then, at the end...
Thank you!
So, the last part is over.
I managed to get an impression in 20 minutes.
Thank you very much!
Please look forward to the next Nogizaka Tecoco!
Let's meet again!
Bye bye!