AISubs
Go for it!
Goal in the world!
Come on!
This is the second time.
The second match of the semi-final is Team Iwase and Team Eto'o!
Please say the order of throwing and the team name of Iwase team.
One, two!
It's PTA 46!
It's a grandmother.
Only one person?
Everyone is a grandmother today.
It's a poor thing.
So, who's going to throw?
The first one is...
Haru.
The fourth one is...
Miyasawa.
The fifth one is...
The sixth one is...
Wait, wait, wait.
Hira.
The seventh one is...
Miyasawa.
The fourth one is...
Hira.
What is your team name and what do you throw?
Yes, my team name is...
1, 2, 3!
Team...
Nanokorogashi!
Since I'm an idol, I thought it would be bad if my team
name wasn't cute.
If I said my team name wasn't cute, it would be Nanokorogashi.
Nanokorogashi!
I'm not sure.
No!
Who is the winner?
I'm the winner!
Who is the second?
Yes, I'm Misa!
Let's start!
The second game of the first round!
BBA46 vs. Tama-Korogashi Team!
Go for it!
The second game of the second round
I want to go for a strike.
Go for it!
Let's win quickly!
Relax.
I'm going for it.
Don't be nervous.
Go for it!
I'll do my best.
What's the result?
8 points!
So close!
You still have a chance!
The girl who made a strike.
I was surprised.
It was the same as the previous one.
The last one.
Are you all right?
Are you OK?
The last one.
Cheer up!
I'm going to win.
I can do it.
Cheer up!
5 minutes to go until it is fixed to the wall!
Success prediction!
implied win
Welcome home!
Good luck!
Thank you!
Ready?
You can do it!
Oh!
You did it!
Yay!
We did it!
What is this?
It's all black!
Calm down, calm down.
I want to go back.
Is the baby okay?
No, no, no, no.
Please watch.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
It's cute, isn't it?
Good luck!
Just one shot is enough!
Just one shot!
Wow!
Thank you!
Look.
LOL
I can do it!
Of course!
It's the first spare!
Yay!
How was it?
BB-san, do it.
Let's see how it goes.
Seriously?
It's okay.
It was a bit harsh, but it's okay.
It's going well.
I can't use it at all.
It's okay.
Does it hurt?
All good!
This is my last one.
I should be able to do this!
We can skip to the last part after the spares.
You can do it!
It's okay, it's okay.
Gata, Gata, it's okay.
Oh!
Yes!
Yay!
You did it!
number 2
number 3
You can do it!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
The second half of the game
It's just the first half!
I don't get it!
You can do it!
You did it!
I'm scared!
Take it off!
Good luck!
You can do it!
Yay!
It's okay, we can do it!
Look at this!
Amazing!
10.3
10 points difference.
Yeah.
Which one is different?
Amazing!
Rock-paper-scissors technique
before the game
You can do it, Misato!
You can do it!
You can do it, you can do it, you can do it!
I'm going to aim for a spare.
I'm scared.
I'm going to drink the second spare.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're good.
I want a spare.
Check out next strike.
3 points!
Wow!
Good, good, good!
3 more points!
3 points!
You can do it!
Ri?
Are u ready??
This is all pretty good!
You can say whatever u want haha
OKAY!
Bacon, bacon, hey hey, bacon, let's go!
Get out!
I'm lost!
Everyone kept looking at me.
You did it, didn't you?
Are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay.
Is there a meter change or something?
Here we go.
A meter?
Yes, yes, yes!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, right?
It's okay, it's okay.
It's 9 o'clock.
Calm down!
Drive use digital camera
witnessing the actual monitoring
This is the first time I've seen this.
This is the captain's showroom.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
That was great!
Wow!
The bowling ball is cute, isn't it?
Do your best!
Good, good, good!
Replay
We'll prepare bankers
She can do it
So cool
Thank you very much!
How was it?
It's okay.
Let's take a break from now on.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
I don't think so.
I did it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
From the left.
Good, good.
It's okay, it's okay.
You can do it, Yomemi-chan!
Yomemi-chan, you can do it!
We did it!
If you think you're catching up, you can roll the ball
and pull it off.
It's okay. If you get a strike next time, you'll be
able to do it again.
What's next?
Aira!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
You can do it!
Good!
I will do my best not to waste Sei's striker.
Good luck!
No! No! No!
Good job!
Let's see how it goes.
Oh, wow.
It's different from the last time.
It's different.
It's like this.
It's coming.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can do it.
You can do it!
3 seconds
Yes!
Nice!
Wait!
You did it!
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Please make it a little more.
Chiharu will cover it.
Chiharu, good luck.
It's okay to be quick.
It's okay to get everything.
Why is that?
It's okay.
Chiharu, good luck.
Throw it straight.
Legendary
What do you meanRO What?
I think this is W,
Run
I'm scared.
It's 63 to 60.
It's a tie.
Yumi wins.
Who will be the last?
Yumi is the last.
Yumi is the captain.
Good luck.
Good luck, Yumi.
Yumi is winning.
You are winning.
Good luck, Yumi.
Yumi wins.
Yuriko wins.
If we lose, we'll be in the top 5 and we'll be at the
same level as you.
You can't even tell, can you?
I can't do it anymore.
Do your best~!
I can do it!
Yumi-chan, Yumi-chan, Yumi-chan, Yumi-chan, Yumi- chan!
Yubi-tan, Yubi-tan, Yubi-tan, Yubi-tan, Yubi-tan
Good luck!
You're good!
I don't want to!
Yumi, you're gonna win.
Don't make me say I don't want to!
I didn't make you say that!
I don't want to!
Yumi, close your left eye.
Can you do it again?
She did it!
Go, go, go!
Good, good.
Wait, this is amazing.
Amazing.
Thank you very much.
Tama-Korogashi team.
If you get a spare and a strike, you get the same score.
If you get both strikes, you win.
It's the other way around.
If you get both strikes, you get a spare.
It's tough.
Let's do it.
Do you want to do it?
I'll do it.
Can I start the 2nd and 3rd match?
Ye..s
I can do this.
As long as Suzuya scores!
You can do it.
Straight, straight, straight!
I don't want to do it anymore.
I really don't want to do it anymore.
Let's do it.
Ready, set, go.
I'm nervous.
Go!
She did it!
It's a tie!
I'm going to the next one.
Who's going to do it?
I'm going to do it.
2 balls
Strike
Let's go
Yeah
Good luck
I' s so younger than you, Masa.
Oh relate?
I went around, but
is it not cool?
Hey do you want to do it together?
I want to take your'hah...
Yes.
Ah...
Oh Wait a minute.
What did you say!?
I'm in danger of slow down and body election.
I understand.
about fame?
I said through video tutorial
Let's experience Jiangsu
also of videos
I think that ah
I'm sorry.
Wait, wait.
It was close!
It was really close!
Next, we'll have the onee-san 46 win!
That's a good idea!
Then, the onee-san 46 will be the winner!
The best personWhy are you there?
Let's do it together!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Don't do that!
It's okay!