AISubs
Oh, they're selling juice!
Put it in.
What kind of sauce do you want?
Sauce.
Can I use my bare mouth?
You can use your bare mouth.
I'm doing it myself.
That's why I'm good at using knives.
It's not my style, so it's really hard to do.
I don't have a knife.
I'm going to do it.
If you're going to see it, look in the shadows.
It's not a shadow.
No, it's not.
I don't want to.
Oh, my God.
What should I do?
Is it okay?
Because the shadows are gone.
I'm going to do it.
I don't know.
Let's get some yakisoba.
I don't want to eat rice.
Let's get some carrots first.
Let's get some carrots.
Do you want some oil?
Yes, please.
I'm so happy.
Do you need a gun?
No, I'm good.
Hey, hey, hey!
Are you okay?
I opened it.
Oh!
What is this?
There was a lot of oil.
I think the fire is strong.
That's why I told you to be careful.
Yeah.
I think it's half and half.
How much is it?
It's a lot.
It's about half.
I put in this much.
There's no oil.
Oil?
A little bit.
It smells good.
It smells really good.
What about salt and pepper?
I love pepper.
I wonder if there's not enough oil.
Let's put it on the screen.
OK!
Can I put this on YouTube?
OK.
It's still not enough.
Do you need another one?
Water.
I'll take another one.
There's still water.
There's still water over there.
Let's see.
Wow.
Let's go.
There's still a lot of water.
There's too much water.
Since this exhibit was held for two years, it has been
in use for over 20 years.
On May 22, 2014, it was launched with 3S negro system.
this exhibitionN
It's okay if you don't have it.
This team cooks pretty well.
Yes, they do.
I chose the best team.
Chii-chan, you're the best.
Chiharu-shika.
Nene-shika.
Mayashika.
Who's the Yume?
Mayashika can cook.
Mayashika is good.
I'm good too.
Mayashika can cook. Mayashika needs me to cook.
Mayashika must cook Mia-Mah-Fu-Tamago-Yaki. What's in
it? It has onions and bamboo shoots. There are, aren't
they? onion. They are in the dish. I have eggs too.
There are Japanese-style. There are Japanese-style
What's the difference? Don't you say salty? What's the
difference? Taste? All of them are different. All of
them are different. They are not hard bad.
all hard.
Oh, it fell.
It's a grilled carrot.
Will the rabbit come?
No?
Quite a lot of ingredients.
Is it hot?
It's okay.
Thank you.
Where is the seasoning?
It's here.
What's the seasoning?
Salt and pepper?
Yes.
There was salt and pepper.
There's no seasoning.
What are you going to put in?
How are you going to put it in?
Can't I just take this?
It's over there.
Salt and pepper.
There's salt and pepper.
It's convenient.
Salt and pepper, curry roux, sweet and spicy.
It's sweet.
I don't know how to do it.
Can you do it once?
I got it.
Let's go.
I can't help it.
The other side is the opposite.
You should be happy.
Thank you very much.
Grilled! Grilled!
Salt and pepper?
Yes, salt and pepper.
The fragrant smell of pepper.
Pepper.
I'm doing my best.
I'm grilling.
Thank you very much.
I'll go to the other team.
Please come.
Come on.
It's still hot.
Let's go.
Two small people came.
It's getting hot.
I'm hungry.
Really?
Thank you very much.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's a girl.
Girl power.
Heart.
There's a cute bow.
Right?
Who are you going to give it to?
I'll give it to you.
It's been a long time.
Let's go to the potato store.
The potato store was big after all.
I love you.
What is it?
Don't look at me.
I did my best to start a fire.
I'm starting to make curry.
Where is the rice?
I'm already cooking.
You guys came to take out the chocolate.
That's right.
Take it back.
Please don't come.
It's cute, isn't it?
Try to make it.
What are you looking at?
No, no, no, no, no.
I can't see anything.
I can see it.
You can't see it, can you?
Ta-da!
What do you think?
Easy peasy!
You know...
Yeah?
My grandma is a cheater.
She's a fast cook.
And this is...
She's good at making a fire.
But it looks good.
My grandma made a carrot cut.
Yeah!
Don't lose!
What should I do?
Should we put it in?
The meat is still too early.
Is it too early?
The vegetables aren't cooked at all.
What should we do?
Should we put it in after it's cooked?
Should we poke it?
Yeah, the meat is hard.
Yeah.
After it's cooked...
It looks good.
It's not ready yet.
Oh, there's a shrimp next to it.
I heard that tomatoes can handle shrimp.
No way!
That's cool.
I heard that they can handle shrimp.
If it smells good, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm sure they'll understand.
That's right.
I wonder if this shrimp has a good taste.
I know how to do it.
I've eaten tomatoes before in Hawaii.
Oh, that's great.
When it was pan-fried.
It's crispy on the outside and soft on the inside.
It's like butter soy sauce.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
They will be good players.
Can I have one?
Be careful.
Go!
Amazing!
Oh!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's quite sticky, isn't it?
This side hurts a lot.
Wow, amazing!
I did it!
You did it?
It's beautiful!
Amazing!
I did it!
I did my best!
This is amazing!
It's amazing!
Do you want to try again?
Again?
No!
I don't want to do it anymore!
It's already decided that you're going to be in charge
of the shrimps and tomatoes.
You said you can do it!
It was hard to be in charge of the shrimps and tomatoes.
You're going to be in charge of the shrimps and tomatoes.
It was easy to eat, but it was hard to go.
If I could do it...
It's impossible, isn't it?
Let's try it.
I want to eat a lot.
Can I use just the sauce?
Sure.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat a lot.
I can't eat this.
Looks delicious.
Wow!
Smells good.
Taste it.
Give me the sauce.
Let's go.
The color is important.
If the color is good, the taste is also good.
It's definitely delicious.
That's right.
There are few carrots.
Belga cut all the carrots into small pieces.
It's okay.
There are about five carrots.
Do you want to eat meat?
Which one do you want?
It's delicious.
But I'll add a little more.
Really?
It's in the right direction.
Direction?
It's crispy, isn't it?
Yeah, it's really good.
It's good.
It's really good.
I'm going to get off.
The view is really good.
We have to make yakisoba too.
Yakisoba is good too.
I like Yakisoba with salt.
Really?
I like Yakisoba with sauce.
Can I use two types of sauce?
Yes, you can.
I think it's easier to use salt.
Really?
I don't know because I only use salt.
I think it's easier to use salt.
I don't want to listen to their opinions.
By the way, next to it is the sauce.
Then let's use salt.
Let's use salt.
Okay.
It's a little vivid, isn't it?
Isn't it okay to use something unusual?
What do you use this for?
This is a barbecue.
Do you put eggplants in a barbecue?
I don't put eggplants in a barbecue.
Do you put it in a barbecue?
I put cabbage, meat, and peppers in a barbecue.
Hey, you're almost there.
Come on, come on.
I have leaves.
You put it here.
I want a lot.
Shall we put leeks?
Yes
Let's put leeks.
He is so handsome.
Thank you
I'll leave the rest of the rice to you.
This is a pinch.
How do you cut the cabbage?
This is lettuce.
This is cabbage.
Why?
I don't know.
You don't know.
I see.
I'll put the cabbage in.
Oh, Shin-chan put it in.
Shin-chan, do you want to put it in?
Yes, I want to put it in.
I want to give it to the dog.
No, I always eat what I give to the dog.
Don't say that.
But you're eating with a dog in it.
It's the same as a dog. I don't like it.
It's usually in it.
Shin-chan isn't in it.
Shin-chan isn't in it either.
I don't eat it.
Who is Saku-chan?
It's a dog.
I don't know.
Do you want to try the carrot sauce?
Yes.
Oh, it's good.
It's all good.
I'm going to eat sweet.
I like medium spicy.
I can't eat it.
Soy milk.
It's in.
It's okay to put in a little more.
Do you want to put in another one?
And then put in the medium spicy.
I'm really going to put in just one.
I'll put it in.
I can't help it.
Maya, are you okay?
I'm okay with putting in a lot.
It looks good.
What should I do with this?
Stir it.
I'm going to put it in.
Is it okay?
It's quite a lot, isn't it?
You don't have to put it all in, do you?
Can I put it in from the middle?
It's okay.
It might taste too strong.
I'll put it in when it's all melted.
I'll put it in. let's put it in
Is it okay if I don't take action?
Shall we take the aku?
Please don't eat evil.
I don't know which one is which.
I'm getting sleepy.
Where should I put this?
You can't put it here.
It's okay.
The water is coming out.
The curry is coming out from the bottom.
What do you mean?
What is this?
It's a vegetable.
It's a bad ingredient.
I hate it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Salt-grilled soba is...
Only sauce is...
Do you want it?
I'll have it.
Really?
But we have no time.
You can get the sauce.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Do you have a lemon-like one?
What?
Salt-grilled soba.
Yeah.
Really?
We have that, right?
Is there anyone who can do that?
Yes, there is.
Hey, go find a lemon.
Okay.
Seitan, go find a lemon.
What a stupid lemon.
Is there a lemon?
There was something like lemon juice.
Is there a lemon juice?
No, there isn't.
The color is vivid and it looks delicious, but if it is
as it is, it feels good, isn't it?
It was salty, it was good.
Salty?
I was a little lost.
It's salty.
That's right.
Once.
Wait a minute.
Half on the ground.
This is really delicious.
It was bad.
Don't take it.
Do you want to check?
It's good, it's good.
Isn't it good?
You don't know, do you? Salted vegetables are salty.
I don't know.
Make it delicious.
Because salted vegetables are always salty.
Isn't that dressing?
That's dressing.
It's definitely dressing.
No, it's definitely delicious.
It's salty like grilled meat, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Okay, then I'll put it on.
It's dangerous.
It's delicious, it's delicious.
Then put it on a little and try it.
Yogurt is delicious.
Do you have that kind of taste?
No, I don't.
I'm not kidding.
It's really salty and delicious.
One more.
I don't think it's wrong.
I just don't know if that's salt-grilled soba.
Salt-grilled soba is this, isn't it?
I'm still making rice.
It's definitely so.
Don't make fun of us that much.
Pei-chan, this is salt-grilled soba.
It's salt-grilled soba.
Thank you for the food.
Really?
Yes.
This is different.
It's a different dish.
Thank you for the food.
I'm going to taste it.
Are you going to taste it?
I'm not going to taste it.
What did you want to eat?
Vegetables?
Shrimp?
It doesn't taste like shrimp.
It doesn't taste like shrimp?
It tastes good.
It tastes good with the sauce.
Really?
Try it.
Let's try the second one.
The last one.
Is it okay?
It tastes different from the first one.
It's a little hot.
It's too hot, so I'll put a lot of rice in it.
It's hot.
I'll open it a little.
Oh, my God. What should we do?
It's hot.
Is this okay?
It's gone.
Is it okay?
I don't know if it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm going to put oil in it.
I'll do it.
It's a fire.
Your life is in danger.
I don't like that.
It's hot.
It's coming.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, but it's not good.
It's dangerous.
Hime-chan.
Hime-chan is strong.
Hime-chan told me that she had a barbecue before.
She gave me advice.
Thanks to that, I was able to cook various dishes.
Hime-chan team.
It's amazing.
Meat! Meat!
Ah, that's right. I made a mistake.
Let's start with the vegetables.
And the meat.
You can put it in.
Salt and pepper!
I need salt and pepper.
I'm scared, Senpai.
I'm going to eat it.
It's going well with Hime's fire power.
Is it okay?
No?
Who? Other teams?
They gave it to me.
There's salt and pepper.
There is.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Is it okay?
It looks delicious.
It's okay. You can put it in.
I'll put it in here.
Okay.
Leave it alone.
I'll put it in.
Does it look good? Did you put in the roux?
Yes, I did.
You can put in the roux. Tomatoes.
I'll put it in.
Put it in.
It looks pretty good.
How much should I put in?
Are you going to touch it?
Wait.
One by one.
Like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
It's a man's dish.
It's cool.
Do you have sauce?
It may be more Chinese.
Chinese?
I think this is fine.
Thank you.
Thanks to Hime-san, I was able to finish the dish.
The sauce is good.
Oh, salt and pepper.
Oh, it's hot.
Well, it's okay.
Can I put a lot?
Sure, I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.
Good morning.
A little more.
I don't think it's enough.
It looks like it's going to break.
Do you want to try it?
More, more, more, more.
I just put it in the sauce.
Oh, but...
Can I go in?
Yes, go ahead.
Oh, what should I do?
It's pretty heavy.
What?
Why is it so heavy?
Are you okay?
Is this enough?
What should I do?
It's definitely light.
Are they tasting it?
It's hot.
Is it okay to eat potatoes?
Did you eat potatoes?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
If you cook this, it will be delicious.
This is definitely delicious.
Hina, do you want to eat this?
I saw it.
I was surprised.
Why are you laughing?
Are you okay?
Is this enough?
What should I do?
It's definitely light.
It's been a long time since I ate meat.
Ashirin, I'm going to ask you for an egg.
Egg? I don't know how to make it.
It would be delicious if you put it on the curry and eat it.
I'm looking forward to Asuka's tamago-yaki.
Asuka's tamago-yaki