AISubs
I'm tired.
Watch out!
It's good.
Carrot! Carrot!
Is it good?
Can I put fried eggs on the yakisoba?
Yes, please.
I'm sorry if I fail.
It's okay.
Should I wait a little longer?
Yes, wait a little longer.
But the bottom may burn.
That's right.
Is there anything?
If you use a knife, it's okay.
What's that?
I want to put it in.
Get a little closer.
Safe! Next!
Oh, I think I failed.
Yes, I'll eat this.
I'll eat it.
Two of those?
Where should we go?
Yes, let's succeed.
Success!
Curry.
I'll put rice in the rice cooker.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Curry is finished with soy sauce at the Koto family.
It's a hidden flavor.
Hidden flavor.
It's a little out.
It seems to have a hidden flavor.
I'm back.
I'll try it.
Do you want to try it?
It's still hot.
It's delicious.
How is it?
It's good
3. Bird located in izakaya
It's not burnt at all.
What do you want to do with this?
Do you want to grill it?
Really?
I'm not good at grilling.
You can grill it as it is.
I think it's a little burnt.
Let's grill it together.
Do you want to season it with salt?
Yes.
Do you want to season it with soy sauce?
That's right.
It goes well with soy sauce.
Ketchup?
Isn't it good?
It's an original.
Ketchup?
What are you doing with the ingredients?
I haven't put it in yet.
Do you want to eat udon?
Everyone is a challenger.
I'll do it with yakisoba noodles.
I think it'll taste the same.
It's really good.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's a butterfly.
Setsuko likes it.
No, it's okay.
I'll take it.
It's a butterfly.
I don't like it.
I'll put another one in.
It's spicy.
The onions have a taste.
It's delicious.
I'm serious.
It's an Italian dish.
It's amazing. It's my first time trying udon.
It's okay.
It looks delicious.
Really?
You can sprinkle powdered cheese on it.
It looks delicious.
Is it okay?
I don't know. Let's taste it.
Let's taste it.
What do you think, Ami?
It's really good, right?
Is there any sauce you haven't bought yet?
No, there isn't!
It's good!
It's really good!
Let's go!
Good.
I'll give you an egg.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Good luck, Asuka.
Thank you for the food.
It's cute.
Asuka is going to make myanmar-style tamagoyaki.
I think that's better.
I'm going to have a snack later, so it's okay.
I'm going to eat it later anyway.
There are few onions, but let's go.
Don't look forward to it.
Eggs and soy milk, please.
Thank you.
I didn't have any fish sauce.
Asuka, you are so good at this.
No, I can't do this.
You can do it.
My wife is training me.
Do you want to try?
No.
I can't do this.
No, I can't do this.
Because you are noisy, Chiharu.
Asuka is noisy?
It looks delicious.
It's already seasoned.
I don't think so.
Are you going to add salt and pepper?
Yes.
I'm going to do it now.
Really?
It smells really good.
It smells really good, doesn't it?
It smells good.
Shake it.
OK.
I want to flip it over.
I can't flip it over with this heavy frying pan.
How do you flip it over?
I want to flip it over, but I don't have a tool.
I want to eat natto.
I don't have that.
Can I eat natto?
You can tear it with this.
Isn't that okay?
Even if it's torn, I'll eat it anyway.
Wait, this is impossible.
It's impossible.
I can't do this.
We did it!
I want to put it on the grill.
Which one do you want?
I want the one with less oil.
The one with less oil is good.
It's hot.
It looks beautiful.
It's still hot.
I'm sorry.
I want the one with less oil.
It looks delicious.
I made it.
Don't worry about the upper part.
I'm going to eat it.
The second dish, grilled pork belly.
Grilled pork belly
1. Grilled pork belly
2. Grilled pork belly
3. Grilled pork belly
4. Grilled pork belly
5. Grilled pork belly
Let's make an excuse
Okamoto-san, do you want some shrimp?
Thank you
What part is this?
This part hurts
There is still butter.
It looks delicious.
There are three kinds of bread.
Let's go for wheat bread.
Can I make a meniere?
It looks delicious.
I'll go get it.
Yeah, go get it.
There, there, there.
Make sure you don't make a thumbnail for the other team.
Yeah.
Is there still more over there?
Yeah, there is.
I'm sorry about that.
The color is getting better and better.
What are these broccolis?
They're burnt.
Maybe we shouldn't do this.
Let's put these broccolis aside.
The color is bad.
It's okay.
What should we do with the broccolis?
I think it's burnt.
This is bad.
What are you eating?
This is awful!
It looks like a wall.
Oh no, it's falling apart.
It's okay as long as I can eat it.
It's light soy sauce, right?
It's okay with just butter.
Salt and pepper, salt and pepper.
Oh, there it is.
I think it's better to put it here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's light.
Soy sauce.
It's like this.
Is it good?
It's cute.
Really?
It's like lightly frying.
Frying?
Yes, like this.
Like this?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's marshmallow time.
There is a piece of tofu.
Hey, what should we do?
It's getting separated.
It's okay.
As long as we can eat it.
If you put too much, it won't be delicious.
It's delicious.
It's coming out.
It's stuck.
My shrimp is ready.
I think it's delicious.
You can eat it.
Is it delicious?
This is a cherry tree.
Don't worry about its appearance.
Let's eat.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
It looks bad, but it's delicious.
Me too.
I'm a genius.
I can cook.
Delicious.
I'm a genius.
The meat is ready!
Let's grill the meat!
Black pork!
Is this enough?
I want to hold it.
Please take the meat and the sailor.
The fat is good.
How is it?
It's heavy.
Can you do it?
It's amazing.
This is very important.
This is important.
Wait, where is the plate?
The plate.
This is very important.
It seems that it is better to do it by hand.
That's right.
Wow, but it's already colored.
Wait a minute.
I can only smell it from here.
It smells so good.
It's black fried beef.
Can you smell it?
Can you smell it, everyone?
Please take a good look at it.
Look at the color.
This is the black fried beef we caught.
Look at this elegant color.
It's elegant.
It smells good.
What about the vegetables?
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
It's a little different, isn't it?
It's hot.
How is it? Does it melt?
Yes, it melts.
The moment I put it in my mouth, the oil started to come out.
It's sweet, it's sweet.
You can cut it in one go.
It's hot.
The rice is almost gone.
It's gone.
What are you making now?
It's a sea bream.
Is it a sea bream?
Yes, it is.
You rub it with salt, right?
Yes.
A grandma in Hananaka rubbed it with salt.
She rubbed it with salt.
And before cutting,
she rubbed it with salt.
What?
After putting it in, she rubbed it with salt.
When I did it,
she put more salt and shook it.
Let's eat it.
A grandma in Hananaka rubbed it with salt.
How much salt did the grandma in Hananaka put in?
I haven't seen it.
You haven't seen it?
Grandma in Hananaka rubbed it with salt.
It's spicy.
It's too spicy.
It's salty.
It's a miracle, isn't it?
Is it salty?
It's salty.
But you don't want to get burnt, do you?
Grandma will be surprised.
She will be surprised.
Grandma in Satonaka will be surprised.
What's that?
They are looking for the next destination
The next destination is...
...
.........
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I forgot the sauce.
I'm glad.
The meat is delicious, too.
The chef made various dishes.
Amazing.
The taste is Ami.
It's Ami.
It's annoying.
The tsunami is coming.
I ate it.
I ate it when I realized it.
I want to go pick up a snack from the middle.
Next is water girls.
This is it.
I did it. I did it.
It was cool.
The tomato is alive.
Is it alive?
It's alive.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat grilled mackerel or grilled udon.
Lalin made MUNIER.
MUNIER?
It's salmon.
It's delicious.
It's manly.
It's a man's dish.
I want shrimp.
Thank you.
There are only six of us, so let's eat together.
It's small.
I want to eat shrimp.
I want to eat it.
It's the sweat taste of Sailor Moon, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
It's good.
Thank you.
It's absolutely delicious.
It's delicious.
The four of us will eat it.
Do you want to eat with two people?
It's enough to eat with two people.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
It's very delicious.
It was delicious.
Next is Dekoboko.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Isn't it good?
Is this curry?
Curry is definitely the most delicious.
What's in it?
Asuka's Mianma style tamagoyaki.
Tamagoyaki.
It's delicious to eat with Mianma style tamagoyaki.
It's really delicious.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat it too.
It's okay. It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
It's okay.
Everyone, eat it.
I want to eat it.
It's beautiful.
You brought a lot.
Take it.
It looks delicious.
Is it onion?
Is it shiitake mushroom?
There is onion in it.
It's great.
There is curry in it.
The onion is sweet and delicious.
It goes well with the curry.
The onion is sweet.
It is sweet.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
Finally, we...
What was it?
The team that grabs your stomach.
Oh, did you grab it?
We made a lot of it.
Yumenene is a problem.
No, it's not.
I made pickles.
I didn't know it existed.
It was delicious.
I'll rub it with salt.
Did you rub it?
It's surprisingly delicious.
Because it's normal.
Seriously.
I put a lot of salt in it.
But I washed it properly.
It's delicious.
Right?
I don't want rice.
You're kind.
The rest of the yakisoba is salt yakisoba.
Eat a little salt yakisoba.
The salt yakisoba is delicious, but...
Hata put a lot of lemon juice on it.
That's not it.
I put a lot of salt in the dressing.
It was really good.
It's delicious.
I want you to talk more.
Eat a little salt yakisoba.
Don't eat it.
It's delicious.
It's not salt yakisoba.
Say it more clearly.
It's like pasta.
It's not.
It's not salt yakisoba.
How did you like it?
It was fun!
It was awesome!
It was the best, right?
We're the best!
Thank you!
How about today?
How about today? How about today?
Well, let's start with Nene.
What should I do?
Well, Yui and Baba are already...
Wait, wait, wait.
Did you just say thank you?
Thank you very much.
It was so much fun to cook and eat together like this outside.
But the junior high school team got bored and started
playing with the camera.
But I think it was great to cooperate with everyone and make it.
I think it was also a team's unity.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
So, our request barbecue was a success!
Bye bye!