AISubs
We're here at Nagisakka!
Today's MC is me, Nene Ito.
And me, Marika Ito.
We're here at Ito Challenge!
Thank you!
In order for everyone to know the charm of the under
members, we will send it only to the members.
This time, we received 5 people, so we got 25 minutes.
Basically, it's no-cut, so I'm sure there are some
difficult scenes, but I hope you can watch it warmly.
Yes, this project is that other members saw it, so
target one member at a time and send the information
collected from other members.
It's a plan.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Good luck.
We're going to introduce 5 people in 5 minutes, so we
don't have time at all, so let's roll the dice.
The first target is Yumi Wakatsuki.
What kind of trick do you have at the beginning?
Here it is.
The second target is Ayumi.
I really like ice cream, and I love it so much that
it's crazy, but the other day, I went to Namco's Anzu
Town with Hina Kawago, and there was something like an
ice cream kingdom, and the two of us went there, but
there was a normal big soft cream, like gelato, and a
lot of toppings, and I ate four of them.
I ate it with Hina Kawago. I ate four of them together.
I really wanted to eat ice cream, and it took two
minutes to eat one.
By the way, you can finish it in 3 to 4 minutes per
one. I can afford it at all.
How big is it? The size of that one. It's not a normal
soft cream, it's not a small mini.
There's still more, but here's the next one!
Smile!
This is MisaMisa's testimony, isn't it?
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
I think it's gotten a lot better lately, but my eyes
aren't smiling a little.
I often practice like this in the mirror by myself.
It's a little different, isn't it?
It's done.
Then, let's face the camera to the fans.
Let's do it.
Please look forward to it.
Three, two, one.
It's hard.
What happened?
I'm laughing now.
That's right.
I'll keep practicing.
Please go.
I'm laughing at the handshake.
I laugh when I meet you, but I don't laugh when I'm laughing.
There's a picture.
I'm trying to laugh.
Then, someone.
I'll give you a practice of smiling to Wakatsuki- san.
The three of us are fine.
Lottie?
Two people?
One person.
I'll start with Chiharu.
What is it?
It's on the way.
Let's start with Hina.
One by one.
Let's go one by one.
This is a sample, so please take a closer look.
One, two.
Cute.
Asuka.
One, two.
Cute.
One, two. Cute.
Hime-chan Hime-chan.
Hime-chan is definitely cute.
One, two.
Hime-chan Hime-chan!
Who is it?
Ready, go!
It's like this.
That's right.
Her eyes are smiling.
Then, the last one.
Miu Miu
Let's go to the top.
Misami-san
Miu Miu
Cute
Then, Yuki-chan
Yuki-chan
Miku-chan
You're cute.
You're so cute.
OK, Tomato.
Again?
She's cute.
Hina.
You're cute.
Ami.
You're good.
Hina.
Last, Wakatsuki
Wakatsuki Yumi
Please practice like this
We don't have time so let's go
Thank you
Next is Hina Higuchi
There seems to be nothing, but there seems to be something.
Then, Hinatomi, Parikomi, ready, go!
Strange practice.
What is this?
Kumo-chan, what is this?
I think it was probably on my way home from Osaka.
The seats were next to each other.
It was night, so everyone was sleeping.
Ami Ami and... who was it?
Hime-tan?
I was listening to music next to him.
I was listening to old music and I was sleeping.
It was really exciting.
Hinachima was next to me and I thought she was sleeping.
Suddenly she closed her eyes.
Like this.
What?
I thought it was strange for the first time.
I thought, what are you doing?
It was getting faster and faster.
What is this?
This was Setsuko-chan.
That's right.
I felt that Setsuko-chan was taking the rhythm with her
eyes closed.
I thought, what kind of rhythm would it be if I drew
the alphabet S from the top and put it back from the
bottom?
I did it like this.
Did you do it in such a hurry?
Yes.
It's scary.
It's really fast.
Have you ever seen anyone doing such a strange thing?
I've never heard of it.
It's rare.
Hinachima sometimes has a strange way of speaking.
Hinane, you woke up earlier than the crows today.
That's because I have a rule that I wake up early on my
day off, so when I wake up at 4 o'clock and study, the
crows start to cry, so it's amazing that Hina woke up
earlier than the crows, so I said that I wanted to brag
to everyone a little, but I'm sure I woke up earlier
than the crows, so
that's why I woke up earlier than the crows.
that's why I woke up earlier than the crows, so I said
that I wanted to brag to everyone a little, but I'm
sure I woke up earlier than the crows, so I said that I
wanted
It's the first time we've performed in the world, so
it's been a long time.
This is Mikumo-chan's.
Everyone knows.
One more thing I'd like to say is that I like kelp.
Oh, you like kelp.
What was it?
Toro Toro
Bring the one you put in miso soup as it is.
The one you put in miso soup?
The one you put in miso soup.
Grab the miso soup or the one you put on rice.
Like this.
Everyone's into it, right?
I don't know that.
Everyone's into it.
Try it.
Eat it. Eat it.
Overall, it's not my favorite.
It's not.
Kabuki, too.
Yes.
Why do you like Kabuki, Hinachiman?
Why did you learn it?
It was a pamphlet given to me when I was in elementary school.
I wanted to try it myself.
So, I want you to show us a bit of Kabuki.
I want to see it!
Kabuki!
Kabuki-style self-promotion.
Self-promotion?
Kabuki.
As usual.
I want to see it.
Then, everyone, please get ready.
Yes.
Ready, ready.
I'm going to start.
Yes.
May your stride be a
I haven't done it for a long time.
It's amazing.
It's like this.
As expected.
Please polish your Kabuki from now on.
Yes.
Let's talk about it.
What do you use?
Thank you.
Next.
Yamato Rina.
Thank you.
There's a lot of tomatoes, isn't there?
There's not a lot.
Then, the sauce.
The sauce for tomatoes is...
This.
What is this? Who is this? Is this Misami?
You know, tomatoes...
I like tomatoes.
It's not tomatoes.
I like potatoes.
It's a rumor among the members.
I'd like to find out the truth.
Yamato...
What do you mean?
What is it?
Actually, I like tomatoes better.
Really?
A while ago, before the lesson...
Potato...
There was a time when I used to eat it... freshly
fried... I asked you to eat it freshly fried... I kept
eating it and somehow...it got a little bloated... Stop
it, potato No, I started eating tomatoes... Did you see
the time when I used to eat a lot of potatoes? What do
you mean?
Have you always liked tomatoes? I'm sure you like
tomatoes, but...
I eat a lot of tomatoes.
I eat tomatoes and tofu every time I see it.
Everyone buys a lot of tomatoes at the supermarket.
Is there anything else you've seen?
Like Chiharu eating a lot of potatoes.
I have an image of eating it.
I don't eat it at all.
I can't eat it.
What should I do?
It's not a mountain tomato, it's a mountain potato.
It's not a mountain potato.
Let's do the usual thing.
Let's do the potato version.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26,
21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, father, mother,
27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39,
40,ified, 41, 42, livish,
Really? While playing with your cell phone?
While playing with your cell phone?
I'm doing it.
You look quite brave.
It's brave.
Try it.
This, this, this.
I'm doing it.
That's right.
Why?
I'm doing it.
I'm pushing it and tightening it.
I don't know.
Why are you doing that kind of exercise?
Because I learned it.
What did you learn?
TV.
I saw it on TV.
If you do this, it's like...
It has a face effect.
I see.
Everyone has to do it.
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it, but I'm like this.
It's not like this.
It's like this.
It's amazing.
This is important.
First of all, like this.
Do this.
Like this.
Everyone, let's try it.
Everyone can do it.
That's right.
The bones under this cheek.
Like this.
This is it.
It's amazing.
Everyone has a great face.
It's terrible.
Thank you very much.
I'll be a little face.
If I become a little face, everyone should do it.
Let's do it.
Thank you very much.
Next, Fukagawa Mai-chan
I don't have one, do I?
You have a lot
Everyone has one
Here it is
I'm drinking tea
This is miso
It's a strange tea
It's very difficult
I always carry tea that seems to be damp
I'm drinking
It's strange and healthy
I like tea that seems to be healthy
I've never heard of it
Recently, corn tea came out
It's delicious
It's strange
Isn't it dangerous?
It's okay because it's sold normally
I think it's okay
I think it's healthy
Was it effective?
I don't know
I buy it when I see tea with a strange feeling.
I think it's cute if you have such a tea.
It's cute because it's Mai Mai.
That's right.
There are other comments.
Then here.
Wrong answer.
What is this?
This is Wakatsuki.
Yes, it's me.
I've heard a lot of things about MaiMai, but there's
one thing that I thought was a little bad, or rather
interesting.
There was a time when MaiMai was shaking hands with the
fans next to her at a handshake event.
The conversation was waiting for the next one, so I was
listening.
Then the fans said,
MaiMai, thank you very much. It was good up to this
point. After that, I asked what kind of MaiMai she was.
MaiMai, thank you very much.
The fans said, what?
What kind of MaiMai?
What did you hear when you were told what kind of
MaiMai you were?
I couldn't hear it.
I listen to things that I couldn't hear, but sometimes
I make a mistake and I can't communicate with the
members.
Is there anyone else?
I made a mistake and I couldn't communicate.
It's a meeting place.
It's a mistake.
It's through.
I understand.
I don't hear it sometimes.
We face each other and eat together.
When I say MaiMai, I ignore it because I don't know if
I can't hear it.
I say it three times, but I ignore it three times.
Even if I say MaiMai, I ignore it.
I don't know why I can't hear it.
The fourth time, I said, what?
I heard it for the first time.
Really? Three times?
I said three times.
I'm sorry.
Is there anything else?
I was going to play with MaiMai, but I was in a
different place, so I called her and said,
Hello, MaiMai? She asked me where I was, so I said, I'm
on my way to Marukyu.
I said, I'm on my way to Marukyu, and she said, what? Mordabu?
I thought it was Mordabu. There's no way it's in Mordabu.
I was wondering if the phone would connect.
It's like the title of MiuMiu's blog.
Yeah, I do it a lot.
And once in Moldova, it seems that I understood a
little, but I thought that there was such a cafe
because I heard the word Moldova for the first time,
but I don't know, but I looked it up on my cell phone,
and I thought that I understood it once, but I thought
that it was dangerous, so I said it properly
My ears are 21 years old, so it might be a little far.
I wonder if there will be some kind of excuse.
But I'm sorry.
It was noisy outside, wasn't it? If you're
concentrating on something, you'll probably ignore it
I'll be more careful this time next time.I'm sorry.
It's cute. Forgive me.
be careful then what
maima thank you
The next person is Se-no-hime-san, Hime-san.
What is this?
No, I think everyone has probably had a time when they
were showered with Princess Tambiebu, but no, you know
When I thought I was suddenly silent when I was
talking, she suddenly stared at me. If you stare at me,
my skin will turn red and my nose will become bitter
Hime Tambiebu Hime Tambiebu Hime Tambieb
Over there Over there
decided!
Anyone who sees it will be irritated
cute
How many people are there now?
I wonder if it's going to be crazy
Who was it?
i'm more evolved
What is evolved?
I beamed like this
already amazing
really?
You often have a face and take care of it
I've decided, why would you shoot a beam at someone like that?
e?
It's not like I'm shooting a beam
I just had eyes
Are you going to do it to anyone?
What are you going to do? There was something black
I got it from a black princess... eh, that kind of guy!
Black princess, yeah~ Black princess
Would you do it to anyone?
I can see caima
eh wait a minute i was crying
Stop it already~ I'll go next time
Are you doing it yourself?
Thank you very much!
Sure, is this? Loan, who? Is this?
Ah, yes, I wonder what that princess would say.
It's always like this, Cappy... Cappy? Who?
I thought so, but actually, Princess, I once stayed in
the same room as Hime-san.
At that time, when I talked about various things with
Hime-san, in fact, I discovered that Hime-san had a
much more mature way of thinking than I did.
Yes, actually.
What are you going to talk about? What is it?
Eh, I'm really thinking about it. Somehow, I'm going to
do something like Hime-san's beam, but...
But actually, it's not just that, I'm doing it with my own ideas.
wait.
30 seconds ago. 30 seconds ago.
Oh, I got excited from here.
eh?
Come on, let's all say BIM.
One, Two, Three- BIM-BIM-BIM!
We love you!
Bye bye!