AISubs
Now, it has started!
Nogizaka-te High School!
This time, the MCs are me, Wakatsuki Yumi, and Nakamoto Hime-ka.
This is our first time being the MCs, so we're a bit
nervous, but we'll do our best!
Thank you!
This program is to let everyone know the charm of the
Nogizaka 46 under members.
I would like to send it only to the members!
This time, it's basically a no-cut recording for 20
minutes, so there may be some unpleasant parts, but
please watch with warm eyes.
Please!
Members, please!
Thank you!
Yes, so it's already 20 minutes. The time limit is 20 minutes.
The plan this time is to target one member at a time
and introduce the information collected from the other
members!
From now on, one by one, please take a seat in this
pipe chair and introduce the information collected from
the other members!
Ah, actually, I thought we were going to measure the
time, so let's do it in a roll.
Please.
Okay, so we're going to introduce the four of them in
20 minutes, so we don't have any time at all, so let's
go right away.
Let's go.
Yes, please.
Yes, then the first target is Mikumo Ando.
Please.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, please.
It's always from Akara, isn't it?
What kind of information is trapped?
Here is the first information.
The contents of the bag.
This is the witness, Sailor-rin.
Please.
In the bag, Miku-mo is always in a single item.
Do you know? Blueberry, Chikuwa, Chikuwa.
I thought the contents of the bag were amazing.
What do you mean?
What? It's not in the bag.
It's not in the bag.
That's because it's a TV show.
That's not true.
The other day, a single item of the drive number came out.
Everyone said, it's here.
It's like an aunt in Osaka.
It's not only Sailor-rin, but also Hina Kawago.
Hina too.
There's something.
Mom?
Someone made a side dish.
There's a comment.
But I'm eating something I made.
I put it in a tupperware.
I like Japanese food.
That's right.
I speak a lot of English. It's True. Mr. Ando, what are
you bringing in your bag today? I actually have a
battery, so please.
Let's see. what's in it?
Could you introduce yourself? Saylaryn, give me some.
What's in it? What's in it?
It's true! It's true! It's true!
It's true! It's true! It's true! It's true!
I don't want to eat it!
I thought it would be late today, so I wanted to eat
something healthy.
This is different. I'm just addicted to it now.
Ikoma-chan was eating it before.
I'm just addicted to it.
What about this?
I can't do it anymore.
This information about MikuMotti was true.
Actually, there is still more information about MikuMotti.
Let's take a look.
The next information is here.
This is gold.
This and this.
Ami Ami.
Yes.
Well, Miku-mo, I once stayed in the same room as Miku-mo at work.
At that time, everyone was really tired, and I was
tired, but when I was going to sleep,
Suddenly, Miku-mo, um, somehow,
Udita-san magic.
Not shisa magic.
And I did a lot of stretching.
No, really, um, and there was about two times.
Every time I look at it, it's almost, um,
It's almost shisa magic.
It's not shisa magic.
It's cute.
I said something like I wouldn't feel like it if I
didn't do that.
Because it was active.
What does Miku want to do?
I don't know.
Do you want to use your body?
Yes.
Are you aiming for that?
I'm aiming for it.
I want you to know what kind of reaction it will be.
Thank you very much.
There is no time, so please go ahead.
The second target is Maya Wada.
Sorry.
Please hurry up.
Maya's
What kind of information is in it?
The third target is here.
I'm good at English.
It's a little bit of a feeling.
What?
Then, Mr. Kaoga.
Yes.
You always say hello when you can speak English.
But in fact, hello and how are you.
Thank you and bye.
Isn't it just that?
It's a good thing.
Are you good at it?
But it's cute.
When I introduce myself at a live show, I always say
hello and how are you.
I was going to say hello and how are you, but I made a
mistake and said hello and how are you.
That's a little bit.
It's a good thing.
Are you good at English?
I ate it.
You're good at it, aren't you?
No.
You're good at it?
If you're good at it.
I'm going to record it.
Please respond.
Hi, Maya. How's it going?
Hello.
Your voice is shaking.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
I'm good, thank you. What about you?
I'm fine.
What's your favorite food?
In front of the TV?
So, what does this mean?
Yes, I'm the witness.
Oh, please.
I went to Maya's house before.
Maya's house?
I went to Maya's house.
There's a big TV in Maya's room.
There was salt and pepper in front of the TV.
It was in front of the TV.
Why?
What happened?
It doesn't hurt that much.
The reason why there's salt and pepper is that
in horror movies,
horror comes out of the TV.
There's a ghost.
3D.
That's why salt is good for ghosts.
That's why I put salt in it.
Why did you put pepper?
If you say salt, it's pepper.
What?
But that's not salt and pepper.
I put it in a rabbit's box so that no one can find out.
Why did you find out?
If you turn it over, it's going to be a bit of a mess.
If it's going to be a mess, it's going to be a disaster.
Really?
Please put it back in her kitchen.
Yes.
Everyone, please listen.
I'm going to introduce two more people.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the next target.
I'm Yukina.
Yukina, come on in.
Come on in.
Thank you for coming.
Yes, please.
I want to hit her.
What kind of information is in it?
Yukina's information is here.
Everyone agrees.
Let's hear it.
Chima.
Yukina has a strange face every day.
The quality is increasing.
It's increasing every day.
At first, her cheeks were swollen and her eyes were a
little cute.
Recently, the angle of her tongue has increased.
The bottom of her mouth is open.
She had her eyes open a while ago, too.
Recently, her nose is swollen.
Do you want to see that?
Yukina's strange face.
3, 2, 1.
Go ahead.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
Let's hear it.
It's cute, isn't it?
What?
One, two, one, go ahead.
It's cute. It's Yukina's victory.
If there's anyone who can beat Yukina, please come out.
That's it for Yukina. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
This is Lottie's information.
In the toilet.
It doesn't make sense.
What is it?
Chima.
It's my turn.
The other day, I was in the toilet.
Someone came into the toilet next to me.
I thought someone was coming in.
I heard something in the toilet.
What?
I heard a sound effect.
I wondered who it was.
It was a nose voice.
It's not a nose voice.
It's a nose song.
I knew it was Lottie.
Lottie is a good singer.
I thought it was Lottie.
I heard a voice in the toilet.
I heard a strange voice.
Where do you hear it?
I heard it in the bathroom.
I'm singing a lot.
I hear it a lot.
I heard it when I was next to the hotel.
I heard it when I passed through the wall.
What do you mean?
It's dangerous.
I talk a lot by myself.
I'm aware of that.
You sing.
When I press the button, I hear a sound effect.
I hear a sound effect.
It's cute.
Everyone, please check it out. I'll probably say it after this.
I'll sit down and say, I'm ready.
I gave it to you.
There's still more for Lottie.
The next content is here.
The room is round.
It's not round.
When I went to Lottie's room before, the furniture and
carpet were all white and brown.
The color scheme.
Plus, the pictures of the big sunset, the elephants,
the ornaments, and the lights are also orange.
It's like Africa.
It's like an adult.
That's true.
Do you like Africa?
When I look at the magnificent scenery, I feel at ease.
That's why there's an elephant in the African zone, and
there's a sunset in the back.
I put such a picture on the wall.
Where is Lottie from?
I'm Japanese, but when I went to high school and made
new friends, I was like, are you Chinese?
It's not Africa.
After I went to Nogizaka, I was half Japanese.
You always listen to western music, right?
That's true.
Lottie, do you have a bath like Mt. Fuji?
That's not true.
There's a sunset in the back, but there's no mountain
in the bath.
I think the bath is normal.
Please decorate it with Japanese things.
I understand.
Please include Japan.
That's all for Lottie's introduction.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time I've been an MC. How was it?
It was good.
I'm glad.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It's not good at all.
What should we do?
Let's talk about the four of us.
Let's hear more about it.
I want you to take a bath in Japanese Mt.Fuji.
Let's go to Mt.Fuji.
What do you mean by Mt.Fuji in the bath?
I'll tell you when we go shopping next time.
I don't think so.
I'll write it myself.
I don't know how many times I've written it.
I was talking about pineapples earlier.
Where is that?
I brought it from the back when I bought it for the first time.
Bring me some coffee.
You cut it yourself with a knife.
I brought a fruit knife.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Do you know the butter knife?
I can't cut it with that.
I'm going to cut it.
Yukina.
Yukina's weird face is worse.
It's worse, isn't it?
It's not like this.
I heard it a while ago.
My nose was wide open.
I'll put it back.
The weird face that idols put back.
You can put it back.
Can't you put it back this time?
I'm putting it back.
It's terrible.
We had a meeting earlier.
That's right.
I introduced four people today.
I'm watching.
Please listen carefully.
It will be the title of the blog.
Don't do that!
I don't want to.
What do you think?
Let's do a funny face for the last one.
What?
Let's do it.
3, 2, 1, go!
She's so cute.
That's mean.
I guess it's Yukina.
Yukina Shika!
So, we've introduced the four of us.
Bye bye!