AISubs
Who will be the winner?
Harami!
Ah, Kimuchi!
Next, my team.
Chii-chan.
Who will be the winner?
When Mari shows us the peephole...
Mari!
I knew it!
Let's move on to the next team.
It's okay.
What?
What is it?
Let's go.
So close.
It's okay.
It's out.
What is it?
Isn't it live?
So close.
It's out.
I'm not good at playing the guitar, so I don't want to
give you a hint, so I don't want to give you a hint.
That's right, that's right.
Then the next one is the team.
Which one is it?
The answer is rice.
Rice?
It's okay.
Team Hinachima.
Thank you.
Aya team, let's do our best!
Where was it?
I want Nanami.
Nanami?
I only know Nanami.
Nanami is here.
Nanami is here, right?
Is Nanami here?
What kind of conversation is this?
What kind of conversation is being
Hashimoto, Hashimoto!
Nori, Nori!
Did you get it?
I don't know.
Let's do it.
Who is it?
I got it.
This one.
This one?
Not that one.
This one.
That one.
Nori.
I don't know.
That one.
No.
5, 4, 2, 1.
I want to eat it.
Wait.
I got it.
I don't know what it is, but I think it's this, isn't it?
Wow!
Go! Go! Go!
Calbee!
If you remember, just randomly...
Then, that one...
This one?
Yeah.
Arm.
Arm!
Thank you.
Calbee and Namuru.
What should I do?
Oh, I see.
It hurts. It hurts.
It hurts.
Go!
Go! Go!
It hurts.
I want to pull it out.
Oh, great.
This is it.
What should I do?
Do you want to go to the channel?
Let's go to the channel.
Oh, it's a channel.
Oh, is that so?
Rice! Rice! Rice!
Rice!
I know it!
I want to eat rice.
I want to eat rice too.
Let's go with rice.
Let's start with the ones we know.
Oh!
Yay!
Wow!
I don't remember it.
Next!
I don't remember this one.
What was it?
There are a lot of them.
I'm going to pull it out.
Yeah!
Thank you.
This way, this way, this way.
One, two, three.
Good balance.
Let's go.
I want Nori.
It's been a long time since I've had nori.
I did it!
Nori!
I'm so happy!
I'm so hungry!
Let's eat!
Cheers!
Let's eat! Let's eat! Let's eat!
Let's eat!
I want ramen!
I want ramen too!
Let's eat!
It's hot!
It's good!
What should we do?
It's good.
Let's eat!
Let's buy it.
Yummy!
It looks so delicious!
It's really delicious!
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's really spicy!
That's a great joke!
Black Tok.
I'm not good at this.
I'm not good at it.
I don't know how to eat this.
What is this?
Gyuushin Uemiso Senmai Hachi
It's not a no, it's not a no.
Orumon Mori?
It might be delicious.
What about this?
Senmai
The color is...
I'm scared of the color.
I was surprised.
What is that?
I'm sorry.
Senmai
I'm not good at this.
Let's try it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Which one?
Thank you.
Since it's the year-end party, let's talk about the
most important event of the year.
The most important event of the year.
There are a lot of people, so let's talk about it in one minute.
Who wants to go first?
My most important event of the year is that I always
bite when I'm hosting an important event.
It's not this year, is it?
You don't talk much, but you bite.
I bite when it's important.
It may not be so serious, but it's a little bit better.
That's all.
Everyone is not listening to me at all!
Everyone is eating!
Mahiro!
There is a hairstyle that you have been keeping for a long time.
Mahiro is the only one who has bangs.
It was a long time ago.
I cut it this year.
That's right.
Because I have courage.
I haven't had it since I was in elementary school.
You guys!
Hey!
Grilled meat is delicious.
That's right.
Let's go next.
Please listen.
The first discovery is...
Um... what was it?
I was flirting with everyone at school.
What year were you in high school?
I was in the first year of high school.
But it was completely different depending on the area.
Hana happy to sing, first question Hana frustrated to
lose, first question
I miss my chance, I want that girl
let's talk let's do that
similar
Really? Together?
no one is
People in Tokyo wear futons
there is that
Do not know
Saitama but there is
very
similar
I was surprised but, when I was like, don't you do this?
No.
It's long.
Do you do it?
No.
An ending.
Thank you for the food.
Yes!
The way you said it just now was so different!
Well, Hina...
What was it?
About summer,
I bought sparkling water.
And when I drank it,
it wasn't sweet.
I thought it was sweet.
So,
I put sugar in it.
And then it exploded.
Amazing!
I was surprised.
That's how it is.
You definitely didn't listen to that, did you?
I did!
That's good, though.
You were in a hurry, right?
What happened to the bread?
After that, I cleaned it up myself.
Great!
Where did you clean up?
In the lesson room.
I was in the room.
That's bad.
I like it too.
Next.
Next is a happy incident.
I had a lot of people celebrate my birthday.
Until last year, I spent a lot of time with my family,
but this year, I went to eat with Marika, and Marika
treated me with her birthday present.
What did she give you?
She gave me rice.
She gave you rice?
Thank you very much.
You gave her a lot of love, didn't you?
This year, we had a lot of events, and we had a lot of memories.
I got a lot of support from my favorite idols.
My hobby is to copy the choreography at home.
When I was copying the choreography at my apartment,
There was a warning sign at the bottom of the apartment.
I don't know if it's because of me, but when I do it,
I feel like I'm getting paid.
By the way, what kind of dance is it?
I remember a lot of things as an idol.
That's amazing.
No, it's fun.
You can watch it and enjoy it, and you can dance and
enjoy it yourself.
Then, Hina-chan, let's go.
Hina's big incident was embarrassing.
The other day, I went to Harajuku with Hina Kawabono and Marika.
There were three people waiting, and Hina was the first
to arrive at the station.
I've been waiting for a long time, and I was wondering
if anyone would come.
When Marika came out of the station, I thought it was
Marika, so I ran a lot and said,
Marika!
Then it was a completely different person.
But Hina raised her hand like this, so I couldn't do
anything about it, so I said,
Ah!
So I made a mistake, and that was the most embarrassing
thing this year.
What kind of person?
After all, it's Harajuku, so it's a little fashionable.
I thought it was Marika, but when I ran, it was
completely different.
Is Marika fashionable?
That was embarrassing.
Well, it's not an incident, but I was happy to have a
surprise with Nene.
Here it is!
I was surprised because it was a surprise, and it was
like a very fashionable party.
Happy birthday to you!
I learned everything from Rina.
Wow!
It turned dark.
But Rina didn't know about it.
That was her surprise.
Rina didn't know.
Yes, I was surprised at times.
Its was nice.
Thank you.
Congrats.
vortex
Last time
I
I thought it was scary because it was Tokyo and I had a
scary image of Tokyo.
I was wondering what it was, and at that time I was
imagining something scary.
It was scary because I was alone.
The owner of the house had a loud voice, so I could
hear Maya's voice.
It was the voice of Seira Nagashima.
So I was knocking on the door of Maya's room.
When I went in, Maya was like,
I was taking a bath.
I thought it was a suspicious person, but it was Seira.
I had a scary experience.
At that time, I didn't know how to ride a roller
coaster, so I thought I would give up.
After that, I tried to overcome my weakness with a
roller coaster.
However, the staff thought that I couldn't ride a roller coaster.
But I was able to ride it, and that was a big news for me.
I did my best.
I thought I was going to die, so I was ready to die.
But the Japanese roller coaster was really safe.
I hope you enjoy riding on the roller coaster.
The big news of our team is...
When I was in junior high school, I measured my height.
I was 166 cm tall.
And I gained weight.
Recently?
I gained 157 cm.
165 cm.
You gained weight?
Yes, I gained weight.
Why?
You gained weight.
Everyone, look.
They are not listening.
They are listening.
You gained weight?
Yes, I gained weight.
You look scary.
Don't worry.
I'm a teacher.
I see.
I'm growing.
You are growing?
You gained weight.
I gained weight?
I gained weight.
I should say this.
It's like an apple.
I got it.
I'll stand up.
Well,
when I met you,
your eyes were really bad, right?
My eyes were bad.
My eyes were bad and they were below 0.01.
I forgot to contact you when I was doing a handshake.
I asked everyone in a hurry, but they didn't have a reservation.
But I got a reservation from the staff, so I got it and
put it in, and I did the handshake as it was.
There's something more, right?
Why?
Next, let's look for Mariha.
I've been waiting for you.
Is there anything?
Yes, there is.
Everyone, listen.
Everyone, it's a big news, so listen to me.
What is it?
Sailor Moon.
Everyone, let's eat.
This is really good.
In this individual PV,
We met.
Let's talk about it.
I'm really looking forward to it until I stand up.
Why?
During the individual PV shooting,
I was thinking of going to the bathroom before it started.
I was thinking about it.
I was thinking of going to the bathroom.
But when I got to the studio, the camera was already set up.
I saw it.
It was set up, and I had to endure the toilet until the end.
You did your best.
I did my best.
Thank you.
There was a ZEPP concert in Osaka and Nagoya in the summer.
At that time, everyone was in the third campaign.
Do you remember?
When it was hard, Misato Seitan went to Kagoshima.
She went to Nagoya in the morning and said goodbye to
the fans after the concert.
The moment she said goodbye, the staff called her and
took a taxi.
Didn't you go in a costume?
I couldn't make it in time for the Shinkansen, so I
jumped on the Shinkansen with the microphone on and was
in a big hurry.
The staff said,
Let's go to Kagoshima!
I was a little surprised.
It was a behind-the-scenes story.
Did you hear that?
I heard it.
Why did you say that?
Go, Misa!
Is it over?
It's over.
Well then,
Chii-chan.
Please give us a final greeting for the year 2012.
Chii-chan, Chii-chan, Chii-chan.
We'll do our best next year, too.
Let's go, Yuki-san!
Let's go, Kiri-chan!
Kiri-chan, you can do it!