AISubs
Hello, we are Nagizaka and Koko.
Today's MC is me, Hikagawa Mai.
Mai Mai.
And Nagashima Seira.
We will do our best. Thank you.
This program is to let everyone know the charm of
Nogizaka 46 under members.
We will only send it to under members.
It's a no-cut program for 20 minutes, so there may be a
lot of things to see.
Please watch it with warm eyes.
This time, we're going to target the members that the
other members have seen, and we're going to introduce
the information we've collected from the other members.
From now on, one by one, we're going to sit in this
chair and collect information.
So, let's get started.
The first target is here.
MisaMisa.
MisaMisa?
Me?
MisaMisa.
There is nothing, Misa.
There is, there is, there is, there is.
Then, let's go.
This is the introduction.
Here you go.
It's intense!
This is a common thing.
It's a common thing.
This is the witness.
Kawago Hina.
Here you go.
She touches a lot.
I think there are many people who have been touched.
Anyone who has been touched?
Yes.
Everyone.
Almost everyone.
MisaMisa, why do you touch this?
Because it feels good, but the member I really like
recently is MiuMiu.
The part of MiuMiu feels really good, and I've been
touched by MiuMiu for a long time.
I feel so good.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
I don't know.
When I was a child, my mother used to touch my nipples.
I like it. It's calm.
That's why I don't want to be a pervert.
It's proof that I forgive my heart.
I'm glad to hear that.
Other testimony
Asuka Saito
Yes
She touched everyone's chest.
Is that okay?
I'm still in my second year of junior high school.
I don't get touched that much.
Asuka
What?
Rather
He touches my chest well.
I saw it the other day.
Monica
out of the pouch
into the cloth
in the chest
He tried too hard not to take off my ones.
That's too bad.
It's trained to beaufat
Do you know what?
Marika doesn't like that kind of thing.
That kind of story.
So I thought I'd never get it.
That's mean.
But I know you want to bully Marika.
I know.
Why?
If it was a celery, I'd touch it.
Well, well, well.
I'm embarrassed.
It's been a long time, but there's still a little more to it.
Here.
I'm addicted to weird things.
This is the witness, Yumi Wakatsuki!
Yes, it's me.
Recently, I thought I was addicted to literature.
I was reading a book, and I thought,
I'm addicted to literature!
When I looked at the content,
Even beginners can understand!
I read a book called Egypt New Moon, and I'm addicted to Egypt.
Do you want to go to Egypt?
I want to go.
I don't want to go to Egypt.
Is there a reason why you are attracted to Egypt?
I've liked it for a long time.
What is it?
Pyramid?
I don't know.
It's amazing that thousands of years ago things are still there.
And how did you make it?
I think so.
Let's go!
Then, please talk with two more people.
Thank you.
Next target.
Is there anything else you are addicted to?
Hobbies?
Like Egypt.
Like MisaMisa's Egypt.
I have such a strange hobby.
Who?
Everyone.
Who is it?
Do you have a hobby?
Hobby?
Squid Somen
It's not the first time
Then, shall we go to the next member?
The next member is
Chiharu Saito
Come on, come on
Welcome
Then Chiharu
Please
Hurry up
I'm scared
Hinachiman
The other day
I had a job to stay
At that time
I was staying with Hina
Then
I was already sleeping
From the next room
I can hear a lot of work
I thought, what is this noise?
And then
I turned my ear to the wall
Chiharu
I said something
cute
I thought it was the next day's practice
I heard a lot of work
I saw it
At one place
It's a little weird, isn't it?
Please
I'll do my best today as well
Together with everyone
Chihaya
By the way, what time did you shout?
12 o'clock and a half
Chii-chan has a weak sense of humor
I often do strange things with Asuka
I'm laughing all the time
The hotel I'm talking about right now
It was exactly the same room as me
I'm sorry
Because of Asuka
That's a bad influence
I was in the same room as Nene
I heard the same thing from Mahiro and Marika
That's all
No, no, no
But
I'm not doing it
Only Mahiro
There is also a statement from Hina Kawago
The tension becomes strange at night
It's really strange
Isn't it strange at night?
Suddenly
I really started screaming
What should I do?
It's really strange
It's not like that in the morning or in the afternoon
Suddenly at night
It changed suddenly
I think that Chiharunrun is really strange
One day, one day, one day
This time, I will pay attention to Hina's monologue
Pay attention
Because it's a character
Thank you Chiharunrun
The next target is Asuka Saito.
This is Asuka's comment.
I like strawberry milk.
It's cute.
But...
Kawago-san, please.
Asuka says she loves strawberry milk, but she doesn't
seem to like it that much.
There was strawberry milk in the candy the other day.
When I gave it to her, she didn't seem to like it.
She doesn't like it at all.
Is this bad?
Can I be honest?
Yeah.
I don't like it.
What should I do?
At the first event, I didn't have anything to say, so I
thought I'd say something cute.
I didn't have anything to say, so I thought I'd say
something cute.
No, but I like it. I like strawberry milk very much.
You're late.
Asuka still has a long way to go.
Here you go.
She has a bad mouth.
This is it.
Eto-san, the witness, please.
Everyone has a bad mouth, right, Asuka?
That's right.
Misa has been telling me to go to hell recently.
How old are you?
I don't know.
How old are you? 5 years old? 6 years old?
Suddenly...
Die!
By the way, have you ever been killed?
Have you ever been killed?
Other than being killed...
I've seen it.
I don't know.
I've been addicted to it lately.
I'm scared of Asuka.
What should I do?
I was told the same thing an hour ago.
I was told to go to hell.
I'll do my best.
It's mostly Yuttan's fault.
What do you mean?
She says a lot of things, so I'm just saying it.
And she's being taught, so it's Yuttan's fault.
Oh, education?
It's no good if you get caught by Saito.
Saito and Chii-chan are okay, right?
It's okay, right?
But Chii-chan, don't look down on her, either.
Oh, my God!
My hands are shaking.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm in puberty this year, so I can't help it.
Don't say it yourself.
Asuka, how about you?
I was looking at the mail the other day.
I've been looking at my phone all the time.
I got a message from my mother.
She said, if you get to the place you're supposed to
be, contact me.
She said she was worried about her mother, so she told
me to call her when I got there.
She wrote, I'm sorry.
I asked her why she wrote, I'm sorry.
She said, because I hate persistent people.
She said it in a cute way.
I said, because I hate persistent people.
Does that mean your mother is persistent?
That's right, mother...
No no
She said, because she was worried about her mother, she
told me to call her when I got there, but...
I don't know.
Thank you! Thank you!
Let's go to the next one.
Thank you.
The next target is Marika Ito.
Marika Ito.
There's nothing.
Come here.
Let's see Marika's talent.
Go ahead.
Marika Ito.
This is a witness.
Let's ask her specifically.
Asuka.
Asuka, what?
What?
Go ahead.
The way she moves, the way she talks, she's already a
middle-aged man, isn't she?
What's with that face?
Is there any other middle-aged man episodes you have, Marika?
She's too middle-aged, so I call her middle-aged on the phone.
That's right, Marika!
When I changed my email address, I saw her name on it.
I thought she was writing something else, but it was
written as a middle-aged man.
She's not a middle-aged man.
Like, you're sitting on the chair.
You didn't say that!
I didn't.
You don't look like an old man.
You look like you've lost a lot of weight.
Like you've lost a lot of weight.
Do the expression you just did.
Yes.
That's not it.
What is this?
I'm doing it a lot.
And not just the behavior, but also the taste.
Beef jerky.
It's delicious.
I like snacks, but I'm only eating snacks.
Something comes out of the bag.
Yes.
It's not that bad, but it's delicious.
What else do you like?
Jacky Calpas.
Isn't that the same?
But I like all the snacks.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Please eat it all.
It's not that much of a promotion.
Is there any other place that looks like an old man?
Not at all.
It's not.
Just by Marika being there...
Yeah, that's right.
What?
My time was terrible, but...
No, no, no.
I'm an old man just because of that.
Do you think so?
Why?
Marika's face when she wakes up is terrible.
It's because she's an old man.
That's why it's hard to fall in love.
It's hard to fall in love.
Marika still has something to eat.
The next thing to eat is this.
How to eat noodles.
Nene, please explain.
This is when I went to eat ramen with Marika.
That's right.
I went to eat udon after Kagawa's Ion Tour yesterday.
That's why I eat noodles at that time.
Marika can't slurp noodles.
That's right.
Why can't you slurp?
You bite it because it's chopsticks.
What?
It takes time.
I can't slurp.
It's impossible.
I don't have the strength to slurp.
You're a weakling.
What about pasta?
I eat pasta wrapped in noodles.
What about ramen?
I eat ramen with chopsticks.
When I finished eating, there were a lot of noodles left.
I ate it.
That's not a cat tongue or anything, is it?
It's not that kind of thing. I can't suck it.
And when I suck it, I get a runny nose.
It doesn't come out.
Try sucking it.
Why?
It takes time to eat.
I don't know if you're just listening.
Let's have you eat it.
I've prepared some soba noodles.
It looks good.
It's cold.
Here you go.
It looks good.
Let's warm it up at home.
Hurry up!
Let's do a food report together.
If you do this, you'll be surprised.
Try it.
One, two, three.
Why?
I'm surprised myself.
I don't have the strength to do it.
Why?
I don't know.
One more time.
One, two, three.
Throw it away.
Celery is very desperate.
Celery's face is covered.
Wait a minute.
No way.
I'll give it to Celery.
With that face?
With that face.
Let's eat.
Stop it. It's hot.
It's small.
It's not hot.
10 seconds left.
Thank you.
5 seconds 4 3
I can't die.