AISubs
Now, it has started! Nogizaka is here!
This week, we will have a reaction battle from Fuji-Q Highland.
Viewers will be able to vote for the best reactions for
each attraction.
The team with the most votes wins through the first
three episodes.
The next Nogikoko will be given a reward for being able
to make a project you like.
Now, the results of the last week!
3rd place
FUJIKYU-DEMO MAHO-O KAKECHAUZO team 1322 votes
2nd place TEAM DEPPA 1479 votes
1st place is HINACHIMA TO YUKAINA NAKAMATACHI team 2487 votes
The top of the top
The winner is decided by the viewers.
Please vote this week as well.
Please watch this week's match.
The next attraction is here. It's Takamisa.
It's Takamisa.
And we have a theme this time as well.
The theme of Takamisa is to sing the song, Run Bicycle.
It's impossible.
Please sing the song, Run Bicycle while being an attraction.
First of all, the first battle is the maximum angle of
fall, 121 degrees.
The battle to sing the song, Run Bicycle on the monster
coaster Takamisa that appeared in Fuji-Q last year.
Please announce the members to ride.
Our team is KAI.
I love to scream.
Finally, it's my turn.
Are you awake?
Yes, I'm awake.
We will sing and let you hear the echo.
I hate this.
We will sing Vibrato.
Next, our team is Hitomi, Sato and Hanarin.
If you want to be a singer, you have to sing until the end.
Not just the beginning, but the whole song.
We will sing and dance.
Dance!
We will do our best!
And our team is...
Yes!
We came here because we wanted to ride it.
Everyone is saying that they are going to sing out, so
let's do it coolly.
Let's do it coolly with a cool rap.
We did it! We did it! We did it! Let's do it coolly!
First of all, the team to cast a spell, Sailor Lin and
Lottie will challenge.
We'll do our best! Bye bye!
Cut!
Fischer, Fischer, Zaka Fischer!
Fischer, Fischer!
Taka Fisher!
Are you going to sing?
Let's sing
It's black
Taka Fisher
I hear her voice!
I'm going up the stairs of central station.
The bus you got on is the best.
The best supermarket in the sun.
I'll call your name from here.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God!
Yabai!
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Yabai!
I'm sorry.
I had a great time.
I didn't sing.
I'm sorry.
It's so fun!
I got a lot of juice!
Who can sing this song?
There's no way I can sing this song!
Really!
But!
There were a lot of songs.
The attraction itself seems to have enjoyed the song.
Next, Hinachima and her friends, Kanarin and Misamisa,
will challenge.
Hinachima, Misamisa, Kanarin, Misamisa, Kanarin!
No!
Kanarin!
I think this is bad!
My name is друзья!
It's Kanartrenda!
I was killed by a indltry!
Why didn't you all notice me?
I'm a zombie!
I'm the zombie?
This is bad but what's this?
This is...
This is crap.
Wait, from now?
I don't think we should show this.
Hey, wait a minute.
From here?
It's okay from the beginning.
Please start singing.
I'm sorry.
Start singing.
What's the difference between friendship and love?
When did you start talking so passionately?
I was told by everyone afterwards.
Why don't you notice it?
I'm sorry.
Hey, wait a minute.
Somehow, deep in my heart,
a south wind blows.
Run!
Are you okay?
We are fine!
We are sorry...
I want to see you! I want to see you!
I love you too!
I love you!
Are you kidding me?
Are you okay?
What is this?
How was it?
Wait a minute.
I love you too!
What's wrong with this?
There's a lot of things coming out, right?
Wait, if you sing, you'll drool.
You'll drool.
The camera's around here.
Can you sing?
I didn't even dance.
MisaMisa sang a lot.
This is a high point.
What about the last one?
The previous two groups were a little...
It's a little...
We're going to do it.
I'll do it coolly.
Please watch it.
I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
Let's run!
Ready, set, go!
Run, Baishi-kun! Hurry up!
Pedaling with all your might!
I made you lonely!
I want to follow you!
Run, Baishi-kun!
Be a wind and walk ahead!
I want to look back at the sea!
I made you lonely!
Run, Baishi-kun!
I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
Ready, set, go!
Run, Baishi-kun!
What was it? I forgot.
I can't sing.
What was it?
Both are good.
It's over?
That's right.
Why?
It's over?
Ready, set, go!
Yo! Mo! I!
Yeah!
That's the last one!
I can't do this.
This is a pity. I couldn't sing at all.
How about the Kawago-chan team?
I can't sing.
How about Hina-chan team?
warehouse
I Florence.
I always drool.
That's not true.
I can't use this.
I don't think so.
Isn't it a mole?
I thought it was a drool.
I thought it was for the camera.
It's a mole, but it's drooling.
I don't need it.
I'm sorry.
How was our team?
How was the rap?
I knew it when I was stuck here.
I want to go from there.
It's up to the viewers.
Which team did you like the most?
Did you vote?
Please vote for the team with the best reaction.
Now, it's lunch time. Actually, everyone prepared lunch
by themselves.
Who made it by themselves?
Let's eat!
Let me introduce the members' lunch boxes one by one.
First is my lunch box.
The point is homemade quiche that I made by myself.
Next is Hinachima.
Japanese-style lunch box that I always eat at school.
The point is homemade fried eggs.
Next is MisaMisa.
The name is a lunch box that animals are waiting for.
The face made of seaweed is the point.
Seitan's lunch box has a lot of edamame.
In place of tomatoes, the pickled plums are also a point.
Kanarin's lunch box is a salad udon lunch box.
It contains diced pumpkin, a specialty of the Rakadake family.
Next is Nenokoro.
Actually, he is very good at cooking.
The sound of rice is also seasoned.
Next is Himetan.
He is good at cooking with cuteness.
He is also good at coloring.
Next is Rotti.
A lunch box with a good balance such as coloring vegetables.
The point is his favorite black beans.
Next is Rarin.
A sandwich lunch box with a lot of variations.
There is a lot of food so that everyone can eat it.
Next is the youngest Maaya.
A lot of pumpkin, sweet potatoes, grapes and autumn flavors.
And Setsuko's special Soboro bento.
The key point is the seaweed that my mother made for me.
Next is Chiharu.
It's a cute character bento with a lot of hands.
Of course, pandas and tangerines look delicious.
Next is Mikumo.
This is a Halloween character bento.
The key point is the cat's expression made with somen.
After all, tomatoes are the main bento.
Next is Hinapyon. The point is this blue rice ball.
The last one is Yuttan. A lunch box filled with spaghetti.
The point is the 5 minutes and a half microwave.
Ta-da!
Oh, what's that?
Did you make that?
Yes, I made it.
I didn't expect it at first.
I can't make food so that I can understand it at the
camp in Nogidoko.
So, I made a microwave spaghetti.
It's delicious.
The next attraction is here.
Shall we play it?
The theme of this attraction is report with a smile!
Please report with a smile while riding!
Please let us know what kind of situation you are in,
what you can see, and how much fun you can have with
the viewers of NAGASHIMASUKA.
The next attraction is NAGASHIMASUKA.
While enjoying the 18-meter-high curve descent,
this time it's a battle of how to report with a smile.
The two who are not good at shouting will go first.
I was thinking of going to Nagashima Sailor, but I
couldn't get on because I couldn't take a break.
We will do our best with a smile.
Our team is a team of girls and girls.
I'm not good at laughing, but I'll do my best.
I'm not good at talking.
But I just need to say what I saw.
I think you should talk in a good way.
I think you should tell her what you saw.
I think we can do something.
I think we can have a good battle.
Thank you very much.
I'm Seira.
Nice to meet you.
Good luck with your fun report.
The first place goes to Nene and Hina.
This is wrong.
But our position is good.
It's spinning.
We will go from behind.
I'm scared.
We are scared, so it's dangerous.
I'm climbing now.
Do your best.
The angle is dangerous.
What should I do?
It's not scary.
It's scary.
What should I do?
You can see the cat on your right hand.
Yes.
Can you see it?
Can you see the members?
Yes, I can see them.
There they are.
See you later.
It's scary.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ah!
It's wet.
It's not in front of me.
I can see it.
There's a ghost on the other side.
What was it?
It's scary.
No!
It's spinning around.
The water is amazing.
Ah!
It's really wet.
I can see something here.
It's scary.
What was it?
It's a haunted house.
It's famous in Fuji-Q.
It's a rumor that you can't go out for an hour.
Ah!
It's amazing.
It's okay.
It's hard to look back.
It's scary.
The water is coming.
It's spinning.
It's spinning too much.
It's cold.
It's October.
Wait a minute.
Please clap your hands twice.
What should I do?
It's scary.
It's definitely going to be windy.
It's really windy.
I was surprised.
What was it?
What?
I was surprised.
It's over.
It's really wet.
It's definitely going to be windy.
I'm going home.
I can see everyone.
It's okay.
That's it!
It's almost over.
I was just shouting, but it was a thrilling ride that I
wasn't afraid of.
It was fun, but it was scary from behind.
It would be great if you came in the summer.
It's hot, but it's cold now.
It's cold.
I hope you don't catch a cold.
Everyone, please come to play with caution.
We continued our report.
Thank you very much.
It was very wet.
Next is the team with Hinachima and Yukai.
MisaMisa and Kanarin's challenge.
We are now at Fuji-Q Highland Nagashimasuka.
I was looking at this, but it's intense.
But I think it's enough to make a report.
You can do it.
Nagashimasuka's report.
It was reported.
We will continue to report.
We will report with a smile.
We are idols.
We started climbing the hill.
It is like a hill climb.
I can see Mt.Fuji!
It's not Mt.Fuji.
It's not Mt.Fuji?
It's rich in nature.
The air is wonderful.
The wind is getting stronger.
Well, the water is coming down.
The water is coming down, but it's like a water slide.
That's right.
But this is...
It's spinning around.
There's a lot of water coming.
There's water in the water.
I'm sorry.
The water woke me up.
You can see the Senritsu Lake in the back.
That's right.
It's a little scary.
Thanks to this pure water.
Yes.
The haunted house.
You can see it in a different way.
That's right. It's not scary anymore.
It's scary.
Let's go with a smile.
It's coming from behind.
What do you think?
In the water?
Yes.
Over there.
I can't see your face.
There is a cat!
It's only the right half of Misami's face.
I'll show you my face.
Where are we going to end up?
That's right.
No!
There is water between my legs.
In my mother's belly.
How does it feel to be in the water?
Well...
I feel good.
You feel good, right?
Yes.
I heard something.
Fish?
Oh, I forgot to shake my hand.
There are members of Nogizaka over there.
We want to overcome this big wave.
We want to overcome everything.
It was a very fun action, wasn't it?
That's right.
There was a little water.
I think I was able to do it with a smile.
Yeah!
The last team departure, Maaya and Setsu-chan challenge.
The scene now is the beginning of the rain.
It's a heavy rain warning.
It's not raining, is it?
It's a lot of water.
I was attacked by a typhoon.
It's amazing.
We're going to go around like this.
It's my first time, so I don't know what's going to happen.
I'm worried if I can sleep safely.
There's a great sound.
Let's do our best.
I'm back.
It's a mountain.
I'm climbing the hill.
I'm climbing now.
I have to wave my hand here.
There seems to be a member.
Everyone is taking a break.
I lost.
It's cold here.
Is it okay to go up?
Isn't it quite high?
Wait, wait.
What's going to happen?
It's cold.
This is dangerous.
It stopped.
This is...
What is it?
I have never thought that water is scary.
I can calm down now.
What you can see on your right hand is...
On the right...
On the left...
It's Miyazawa Seiran.
It's me.
What?
I'll connect you to Miyazawa-san.
Yes, I'm Miyazawa.
Please, Miyazawa-san.
I'm being washed away.
It's not raining, but the weather is like rain.
I don't know what I'm saying.
I'm falling.
I'm scared.
It's more scary than I thought.
Now I'm in a black hole.
256km
I don't want to do it!
Ahhhh!
Cat! Cat!
Cat!
Ahhhh!
Miyasako-san!
Sorry, I forgot.
Over there, there are a lot of...
Romance for you!
There seems to be a lot of otaku.
I can see Nugisaka46 members.
Everyone!
Thank you!
It's so fun!
I think we'll forget to do the report.
But we did it well!
Please vote for us!
Please!
Did you have fun?
Please vote for us!
It's perfect!
What did you say?
Anyway, did you pray?
Yes!
I saw it!
This is the end of the second episode of the Fuji-Q
Reaction Contest.
Everyone, please vote for the team with the best reaction.