AISubs
Now, it has started!
Nagisaka is here!
Today's program is...
Yakiniku Bounenkai!
While eating yakiniku,
let's look back on this year.
It's been decided that everyone can still eat yakiniku.
You're kidding, right?
I only drank juice for breakfast.
Really? Why?
I want to make sure that the viewers don't say,
Why is Nogikoko just eating yakiniku?
From now on,
I'm going to do a food fight game so that it won't be like that.
Please look forward to it.
Last time, we had a reaction battle with Fuji-Q
project, and the result of the viewers' vote came out,
so we will announce it!
The winning team will receive a reward for the upcoming
game, so please look forward to it!
Yay!
It's a reward!
Fuji-Q reaction battle viewers' vote result!
I'm excited!
Fuji-Q reaction battle viewers' vote
4,638 votes! Fuji-Q will cast a spell on you!
That's not good.
It's reversed!
Let's continue.
The second place is...
Yes, yes, yes.
Hi, everybody.
The second place is 5,509.8 votes.
Team Depa.
I can eat grilled meat.
Let's eat.
I haven't seen it yet.
So, the first place is Hinachima and Yukaida Nakamadachi.
Yay!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy!
You won 7,000 yen!
Wow!
Yay! Thank you!
Thank you!
Let's stop eating yakiniku!
Why?
I'm so happy!
Let's eat!
And everyone,
I would like you to vote for the MVP as well.
That's right.
The 3rd place of the 90th action match MVP vote is...
Saito Yuri!
Congratulations, Yuta!
Let's do it properly.
I'm looking forward to it.
The second place is...
YAKADAKA
You did it!
It's easy.
It's good.
YAKADAKA
What did you do?
It's time to announce the MVP.
The 1st place goes to...
Wada Maa!
Maya did her best.
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
How do you feel?
Eh?
How do I feel?
I'm a member of M-V-C!
Amazing!
Eh?
I'm happy because I did my best!
Amazing!
Congratulations!
What is this?
Wow!
It's Kurogiwagi!
It's amazing!
Of course, there is a prize set.
The prize set for the winning team, please.
It's big!
Please open it.
The prize set for the winning team, please.
What? Wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait.
This is the prize set for the winning team, please.
What?
There's nothing important.
The meat won the game and won.
What?
That's amazing.
The prize set for the winning team, please.
Let's start the game!
The title of the game is...
Shinken Suijaku!
Everyone, you know Trump's Shinken Suijaku, right?
Yes!
In this game, instead of Trump, the name of the
ingredient is written.
It's Shinken Suijaku that uses it.
Shinken Suijaku!
It's Shinken Suijaku.
If the same ingredient is written on the card, you can
get that ingredient.
Let's start with the Higuchi team.
What do you want to do?
Thrills?
I like you.
I like you too, but I'm still in love with you.
I love you.
I love you too.
This is the first one.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
There's too much. There's too much I don't know.
This is fine. This is fine.
I'll go.
I have a weak memory, so I'll go first.
I'll go first.
Ok!
Mihara!
Harami!
Harami and...
Here I go!
Hotateyaki!
That's wrong.
Thank you!
Kawago, let's go.
It's okay.
That was close!
It's so close!
It's amazing!
Amazing! Thank you, Fuyu-chan!
I've been doing this since I was little.
I'm really good at it.
Really?
I couldn't remember when I was little.
Next.
How old are you?
I was born in the year of the rat.
I love you, TOTORO.
Go, YOSHI.
You're going too fast.
I love you, TOTORO.
You can bite it.
Nice!
It's okay.
You can use your normal hand.
Which one is better?
You can bite it.
Pat, pat, pat.
You can use your normal hand.
You can bite it.
Pat, pat, pat.
Team Hinajima, right?
Team Hinajima.
It's not hot.
It's not hot?
What should I do?
Well, I'll just eat it.
It's pretty warm.
It's okay.
I'll take it.
Lemon!
There's such a thing?
It's gorgeous.
Next.
We are.
Who?
Kumatan!
Oh, the famous Kirei-katsu?
Kirei-katsu?
What's that?
Kado-kado-doshi.
Korean green.
Let's do it at a tempo.
Seira is hungry.
I'm hungry.
Ah this is wrong.
It was important to keep our extra points.
I didn't see it.
Over there.
What is this?
It's spicy.
It says it's delicious.
Is it spicy or internal?
I forgot everything.
It's good.
Next.
Do your best.
Ah! Wait!
Everyone is watching, so let's do it.
Let's do a warm one.
This is the warm one.
Next is Team Niigata.
I don't know, but I have a feeling.
If you make a mistake, it's a mistake.
It's okay.
I don't want to hear it.
3rd one! 3rd one! 3rd one!
What is this?
This?
Ah!
Which one was it?
Really?
I forgot.
Then, Hinachiman team.
It's here.
2nd one? 2nd one?
From 2nd one.
It's here.
Ah!
Wait! Wait!
I'll do it!
I don't know how to do it.
It's okay.
I'll do it!
You have good stamina.
I want to eat bread.
Okay, let's go with that.
It's okay.
It's a salad.
I want to eat it.
Oh, wait, wait.
Everyone, don't stick your fingers out.
What was it? What was it?
Everyone, come on.
Setsuko pulled it.
I remember.
Where was it?
I'm sorry.
The team battle is over.
Thank you.
That's all?
Let's aim for the target.
Where should I aim?
It's been a long time since I've played Hanami.
This way.
Let's go.
I got it.
Cute!
I'm coming again!
What should I do?
Thank you.
Chii-chan, Chii-chan.
Everyone is a good girl.
Ah!
I did it wrong!
I'm sorry, everyone.
What is this?
Let's go!
Nice!
The next team is the magic team.
Kimuchi, have you ever played it?
I don't know it at all.
No, I'm sorry.
It's Kimuchi's first time.
Harami.
Harami, Harami.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to the next team, Hinachiman team.
Let's go to the next team.
I don't know how to play it.
I'll play it from here.
Where was it?
The fifth one.
No, no, no.
Where was it?
I don't remember.
No, it's the fifth one.
I think it's the fifth one.
Leader?
Leader's power.
I don't think it's this close.
It looks like it's going to fall.
I think it's the fifth one.
Let's go.
Let's eat.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I'm scared.
It was the sixth one.
I'm sorry.
I don't have to say anything.
Amazing!
Wow!
Are you okay?
Just a little.
Let's move on to the next one.
I'm sure I remember this one.
Next is the Kachan team.
Kachan team
Do you know this song?
Is it the same song?
There's a song like that.
You guys' team.
Tama-chan.
I don't know at all.
I don't know.
Morito, no!
I know it.
audienceاشure
Something's wrong with me.
I can't do it.
Do you guys hate eringi?
I like eringi.
Do you remember eringi?
Really?
The Chima team.
Congratulations.
Do I look like it?
Yes, you do.
Congratulations.
Yay, eringi.
Our team, too.
I want to see eringi.
Thank you very much.
What was the first thing you thought of when you saw it?
It was seaweed.
Seaweed.
This one.
It was different.
What was it?
I thought it was the same thing.
It was different.
Next, Hina-chan team.
Please don't do the same thing.
I'm going to change my name every time.
I'm so scared.
It's scary.
What's scary?
It's scary, isn't it?
It's scary.