AISubs
The 1st place is Mahiro Kawamura and the 2nd place is
Misano Eto'o.
It's a two-top match.
Ready, set...
Oh, you completed it perfectly.
Wow, you're really good.
Ready...
The 1st place is Mahiro Kawamura and the 2nd place is
Misano Eto'o.
Let's start the 1st match of the 2nd round.
We have 0 points. Give us points.
We only have 1 point.
It's okay if we get 0 points, right?
We haven't changed much.
We're all the same.
No, it's 0 points.
If it's 0 points, let's be quiet.
If it's 1 point, let's be quiet.
Let's be quiet for 1 point.
We're all the same.
It's Yuttan vs. Seitan.
Ready?
It's not good!
No!
No, no, no, no!
Eh, I don't want to!
Did you see it? You put your hand out, didn't you?
I put my hand out, but I lost.
It's the same pattern as me.
Did you notice this?
No, I saw it.
Yuttan put his hand out just before he came here.
I can't put it out.
I realized that the left is a disadvantage.
If it's not left-handed, it's tough.
I thought so. It says it's left.
That's right.
I lost.
I lost, but...
It was fun, so it's okay.
It's still 0 points.
What?
Yuttan, you can't do that.
I'll do my best.
Let's move on to the second round.
The second round.
Hina is really fast.
It's impossible.
It's like a slide from there.
How is everyone doing?
Can I do this?
Can we do it together?
Yes, you can.
It's impossible.
It's almost over.
Please look forward to the next video.
The second game of the second round is the battle
between Hinachima and Tomato.
Ready?
What was that?
What happened?
You guys are in sync.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's start the second round.
Hinachima vs. Tomato.
Are you ready?
I won!
One more time.
No matter how many times you do it, you'll get the same reaction.
Hurry up!
Are you angry?
I'm scared.
The second round. Hinashima vs. Tomato.
Are you ready?
Raise your hand. Which one?
Ouch!
My head got stuck.
We can see the replay of the tomato's hair.
Tomato and Hinachi, come over here.
Ouch! My head got stuck.
I saved the second one on purpose.
I saved it to fly at the same time.
I couldn't catch the second one.
It was very interesting.
Please win this time.
Hinachi, do your best.
Are you okay?
The first place is Mahiro Kawamura.
The second place is Misa Eto.
I'm really nervous.
I'm nervous, too.
If I can do this, I'll win.
Leave it to luck.
I'll do my best.
Oh, my God.
It's a two-top match between KAMURA MAHIRO and ETO MISA
in the second place.
Ready!
Oh, look, it's a friend.
It's a friend.
Both of you listen to the sound properly.
If this sound rings, go like this.
Do you understand?
It's a match between ROCKY and MISAMI.
Ready!
KAMURA MAHIRO
Amazing!
It's been a while.
I'm starting to feel a little stronger.
I'm running in the middle of the flag.
Oh, yeah.
And I was already like this.
You went like this, didn't you?
I went like this.
It was a 1st and 2nd match, but it was 1st and 2nd.
But when I did the flying, I was a little scared.
I thought it was fast.
That's a flying dog.
It was easy, wasn't it?
It wasn't easy.
It was fast.
I think it was faster to get up.
The second round.
The last Samba Ichiki Rena.
Ichiki Samba Rena.
Ichiki Samba Rena finally made her debut.
And?
And the opponent is?
It's a farm.
This is definitely going to be fun.
It's your first time, isn't it?
It's my first time.
I got a seed ticket.
It's not such a big deal.
I thought I'd have fun.
I learned from Ami.
I'm pretty merciless.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Do you have any strategies?
Ami?
Yeah, well.
I'm scared.
I don't like it.
Can I quit?
No.
I'll do it.
It's okay, it's okay.
The fourth match of the second round.
Farm vs. Ichiki.
Ready.
Start.
Ami.He is No.3.
At the same time.
Amazing.
I'll give you Samba.
I was shocked.
Farm Samba.
Farm Samba Ami.
That's right.
How was it?
I don't know.
Ami might be able to do better than I thought.
I like this.
It's a pity that the first Samba failed.
Good luck.
I'll give you Samba.
Really?
Can you do it again?
One, two, three.
You've done it perfectly.
I'll give you Samba.
Thank you very much.
The winner will advance to the final.
Isn't it scary?
I won't lose.
Which one is faster? I don't know, but we've never run together.
Which one do you think will win?
Let's try to predict.
It's Hina and Hina.
Hina is doing a miracle today.
Miracle Hata and Naka are in the game.
Hina is fast, so she can exercise.
Even if you ask everyone, you won't know the result.
Let's go to the game.
The first game of the semi-finals.
It's a match between Hata Naka and Hina Chimon.
Get ready.
Hina Chimon
I'm jealous. What is this?
What is this subtle feeling?
It was a great game.
Do your best.
Welcome home.
It was a great game.
Did you take off your shoes?
I'm out of breath.
She's out of breath once in a while to run.
Are you okay?
I'm young.
Miracle Hata Naka
Hina Chimon, how was it?
It was a brave game.
You use difficult words.
I don't know.
I'll do my best for you.
Do your best.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the second game of the semi-finals.
I will play against Nojo.
Are you thinking of a victory pose?
Victory pose?
That's right.
Rena Rin gave me a samba.
She gave me a samba as a gift.
I'll use it.
Misa.
She said she was old.
If you're happy, you'll be like this.
20 years old.
20 years old dance.
Let's ask each other to dance when we win.
That's right.
I'm very nervous today.
It's okay.
Which do you think will win, Nojo or Eto?
I think Misamisa will win.
Nojo was faster than I thought.
I thought it was a good race.
Nojo said it was fun in the comments.
It's all fun.
I want you to do your best.
I don't know what the result will be.
Let's go to the game.
The second game of the semi-finals.
It's a battle between Ami and Misamisa.
Please look forward to it.
The first game is fierce from the start.
The third batter is 怎麼辦.
I'm very sure you'll win.
We did it!
It's amazing.
She's strong.
She knows what she's doing, so she said she likes the left side.
She doesn't hold back.
It's amazing.
As expected of a 20-year-old.
Why are you emphasizing the 20-year-old?
Stop it.
20 years old is different.
You were strong.
Thank you.
Misami, please continue to do your best next time.
I'll do my best.
First of all, it seems that the 3rd place will be decided.
It's a farm and a field.
Really?
Let's do our best.
Good luck.
This is also interesting.
I won't lose.
I completely lost the race just now.
I'm tired.
You've been running many times.
That's right.
Let's take a 15-minute break here.
Let's take a break and then go.
The 3rd place is Ami Ami vs. Seitan.
Get ready.
Seitan won.
I'm so happy.
Ami-chan, tap dance.
Tap dance?
It's hard to understand.
Are you tired of winning in a row?
I'm tired.
Seitan is out of breath again.
Congratulations.
Let's watch the final together.
The winner will be decided by this.
I don't know which one.
But it's 10 points.
10 points is really big.
Because if it's 10 points, it's already.
Because it's already.
Zero people are 10.
That's a simple calculation.
I think Misami is good at taking flags.
I know.
I thought it was the result of my research.
I was studied.
Hinachima's eyes are bigger than this.
Really?
It's because I can catch the prey.
I was relieved when I was told that I was okay.
Did you become a tiger?
Yes, I think becoming a tiger is a brave idea.
Which one?
I will become a tiger.
But if you come this far, I won't forgive you because
you are younger than me.
I understand.
Then I will also forgive you.
What?
Did you think I was going to call you an adult?
I'm older than you, but I won't forgive you.
I'll do my best.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Let's go to the final.
MisaMisa vs. Hinachima.
Start!
MisaMisa wins!
Hina is addicted to this place.
Today, Misa is in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
Listen to Hina.
But Hina is already in the second place.
The two of them are going to win.
The winner is Misa Ito.
Congratulations!
How was it?
Can I be honest?
I can't run anymore.
You can't run anymore?
Hina is the second.
That's right.
There will be some points.
I think the result will be completely different from
the previous one.
Please look forward to it.
I would like to announce who will be the champion of
the under-exercise competition in the spring of 2013.
The third place of the exercise is...
The winner of the first point is...
Hina Kawabayashi!
Thank you very much!
How was it?
I was surprised.
I was the last one, but I lost to Misano.
I'm glad to be able to sign.
I have to say it now.
You have to say it now.
Now is the time.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Let's move on.
The second place is...
Higuchi Hina, who got 9 points.
Congratulations.
How was it?
Please tell us how you feel.
I think I did my best with the last visual act.
That's right.
I'm glad.
I told you that I would aim for second place with my
first enthusiasm.
That's great.
Why did you aim for second place?
Thank you very much.
And the winner of the first Under Sports King is...
The winner of 16 points is Eito Misa!
Thank you very much.
I'll give it to you.
Please tell us how you feel now that you've become an
under-athlete.
I'm so happy!
I'm an under-athlete, but I'm the oldest, right?
If you think about it,
It's amazing in a way.
I'm an under-athlete, but I'm 20 years old.
Wait a minute.
I'm under-athlete, but I'm the oldest, right?
I'm under-athlete.
Right now, I'm 20 years old.
I'm an under-athlete, but I'm in my 20s.
I'm an under-athlete, but I'm in my 30s.
The person who gets the same score from the beginning
to the end is Kawago Hina.
And the other one is Saito Asuka.
There are two of them.
Come here. Let's reflect on ourselves.
Let's reflect on ourselves.
That's right.
Why is it like this?
It's because of this youth.
It's because I was young.
What are you talking about?
You can do better than me.
I'll do my best.
Where do you do your best?
What are you good at?
What would you be good at?
Karate.
Karate?
I'll do my best.
Who can do it?
I'll show you in the future.
Thank you very much.
This is the end of the under-exercise.
I have a report for you.
This is the gym I rented today.
The person who has to clean up and mop.
That's right.
You may not like it.
There are only two staff members.
That's right.
From now on.
No, no, no.
There's only one.
From now on, let's have a relay match with two teams.
Let's have a relay match with two teams.
I'd like to ask Misabisa, who's in first place, and
Kina Chima, who's in second place.
It doesn't matter who's in first or second place.
It doesn't matter who's in last.
The loser will do the relay later.
Yes.
I did it!
Why? Why?
Go ahead.
I did it!
It was great to fight together in the relay.
Appeal!
Your voice is getting smaller.
Asuka!
Really?
Then let's decide on the bet.
On the right.
Who was it?
Hime-tan.
I'm going to hit it on the left.
Let's do our best.
I don't want to do the loop anymore.
Let's do it.
Let's take off our shoes.
Next time,
I'm going to hit it on the right.
That's right.
Let's run twice more than Yuuri.
Isn't that different?
It's because I've been working hard.
Yu-tan, you can do it.
You can do it at the beginning and the end.
You said you wanted to do it.
I didn't say that.
I said it during the break at MC.
I didn't do it.
I want to see Yu-yu.
Let's not do it right away.
I didn't do it.
I'm 15 years old.
Isn't it 15 years old?
It's 15 years old, right?
It's 15 years old.
On your mark, get set, go!
Go for it!
RYU-CHAN, come here quickly!
RYU-CHAN!
Let's go!
As a result, the children could escape.
By saying that we were in trouble, X to Academy will
not escape anymore.
No.1
No.2
No.3
No.4
No.5
No.6
No.7
No.8
No.9
No.10
No.11
No.12
No.13
No.14
N Zoa 2
Awesome!
We did it!
That was good!
Amazing!
Really?
That was good!
What!?
Santa?
What is this?
The goal!
What is it?
It's a bonus!
Wait, I want to apologize.
I'm really sorry.
Why did you run twice?
You should have won the result.
Wow!
Good job, everyone!
Was it good at Lenari?
Lenari?
Lenari was good.
And Marika was good too.
Everyone, you did your best.
You did your best.
Ami? Ami?
Why are you laughing? Ami was good too.
I'm glad I chose everyone.
Don't ever name me as Baba again.
Don't ever!
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Let's do it!
Sorry.
Let's try again!
Let's do it again!
Sorry.
Not at all.
It's not your fault.
It's not.
No, it's really not.
It's really no problem, because it's just a mop.
It was just a mop, really.
It was fun.
It was good.
It's okay.
It was really good.
It's frustrating.
Mahiro, you too.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It was just a mop.
Let's do it again.
But we did our best.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It's okay.
Thank you.
It was fun.
I'm tired.
Today, we came to the final round of the sports competition.
How was it?
It was fun.
We won, right?
We won, but we didn't have anything.
We won.
I was surprised.
It was a tie.
Today was amazing.
We won everything.
But, you know, Reika was the fastest.
I couldn't say much.
Like, Na-chan is good at drawing.
Everyone is good at it, but it's hard to say that I'm good at it.
Like the piano.
Yes, everyone is learning the piano.
So I was a little happy today.
It was fun.
Really, Senpai.
Senpai.
It was fun.
It was thanks to everyone.
No, no, no.
I can cry.
You're not crying at all.
Your eyes were open.
Renalin, how was it?
To be honest, I got the last point, but that was just
the luck of Seed's luck.
My ability is zero.
No, no, no.
It's one out of three.
One out of three.
But, you know, everyone...
But we're all the same.
But it was great to run together like this.
How about Ashley?
Did you do your best?
I did my best.
I didn't seem to be confident.
Wait a minute.
I'm recording right now.
I won.
There's no trash.
I'm scared.
How was it?
The losing team.
Please tell us how you feel.
I'm scared.
What are you holding?
Mop.
It's cute.
What are you doing?
Mop.
Why?
I'm scared.
There's no trash.
Team Mop.
It's the last.
I'm scared.
Let's go home together.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Let's go home together!
Let's go home!