AISubs
And then, the last two lines.
Yes, please.
The second and fourth lines are the first.
The fifth and sixth lines are the last.
The seventh and eighth lines are the last.
There are no two Wakatsuki, are there?
But we're definitely Wakatsuki.
Wakatsuki.
Ah, Wakatanaka is Wakatsuki.
I'm serious.
I'm serious. I'm serious.
I'm the only one who's curious about the shop life
Let's go!
Come on, shampoo
When I take off my clothes
In slow motion, yeah
My hair sways
Come on, shampoo
Your warmth is sweet and painful
Thank you very much!
See you tomorrow!
It's Aomori, so let's all do our best!
Yay!
Thank you for the food!
Let's eat!
It's so good!
Nene-chan, is it good?
I don't know what to say.
It's so funny.
I can't help it.
Look.
She laughs every day.
I'm impressed, but it's not funny.
It's so funny.
Look at me.
Look at this.
It's so funny.
Can you be quiet?
I'm alone.
I'm happy that I got an anago.
I'm happy.
I love it.
Hina.
I ate tamagoyaki today.
This is a tamagoyaki.
I'll cast a spell on you.
Don't do that.
It's coming out of your mouth.
How about that?
I didn't do it on purpose.
I know.
I'm scared.
No, you're not.
Why do you have to come out here on purpose?
Because it's cute.
Don't do that.
Here we go!
Today's guest is this member!
Yeah!
Ami!
I'm 18 years old from Kanagawa prefecture.
My name is Ami.
People call me Jo-san these days.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Next, I'm Chiharu Saito from Saitama prefecture.
These days, I call myself Chi-chan.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mahiro Kawamura, 18 years old, from Osaka.
People call me Lottie.
Money, right?
Money, money, money first!
Nice to meet you!
You're about the same age.
That's why it's called Mali.
Thank you.
It's dangerous.
What are you going to do?
Show me your pajamas.
You look cuter than usual.
What are you talking about?
It's embarrassing.
Show me your pajamas.
I'm a vegetarian.
I'm colorful.
You look different from usual.
I always dress like this.
I'm not cute.
There are a lot of cute girls.
I always dress like this.
My hair style is like this.
To be honest, I chose a cute dress.
Who did you choose?
This is my favorite.
Really?
To be honest, I chose this dress when I was in junior
high school.
This is Hanagawara style.
Hanagawara style is good, isn't it?
I usually wear clothes with Marilyn Monroe's face on it.
It's K-pop style, isn't it?
I want to wear something more blue.
Green?
Blue?
Orange?
I don't wear such a light color.
But this is also good, isn't it?
Chi-chan went shopping with Asuka.
Excuse me.
We went to TETI & CO.
We got this pajama from Novelty.
It looks like ice cream.
I like such a lovely style.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
Why did you put it on your futon again?
I don't have such a thing to record.
This is good.
How about this bra?
Don't do that. It's embarrassing.
Come on.
How about this bra?
This is good.
We made a new song!
It's a song that changes every day.
Let's listen to the song of Mani Mani Manifesto.
Mani Mani Manifest!
Let's listen to Ami's song.
Sing properly!
I'm a little confused.
Why?
This is a quick lesson.
The title of the song is Amino.
Amino is not good?
Amino is not good.
Somebody. Somebody. Somebody.
but I look up at the sky!
remove any
superstitions
I can do everything
Because of such a song, I can do it immediately
If you give me lyrics, I'll do it right away
VISTAs are excellent atBar commentaries
Can you show us your album?
If you were asked to make a title song,
you can make a song called Mani no Hiza
in a short time.
Can I make it?
Whatever you want.
Give me the title.
Mani no Hiza
I'll make it.
Mani no Mayuke
Okay.
It's very sharp.
Ami's eyebrows are always cool.
You can say that much.
Amazing.
Ami's hair is very sharp.
Ami's hair is very hard.
I'll touch you here.
Normally, Ami's hair is soft, but Ami's hair is hard.
I touched it.
Ami's hair is hard.
Ami's eyebrows are also hard.
When did you two become friends?
Disney.
That's right. We became really good friends.
That's right.
Before that, we were just good friends.
Ami and I have been together since the selection of Gurkhan.
The position of Gurkhan was always next to me, so I had
a lot of opportunities to talk at work.
Gradually, what?
It's a little long, but...
With Chii-chan, when we were still sad, we were close
to each other through PV.
Gradually, the distance was getting shorter.
That's right.
But at that time, when I saw the movie Ami took in
private, I was still a little uncomfortable.
I was still wearing a cat.
Chii-chan was still a Brikos.
Brikos. I still had a high voice.
At first, Chii-chan was wearing a twin tail.
I really thought, who are you?
I saw it myself.
Minami, Asuka, and the three of us were in the maid club.
Maid club.
Who are you?
I can't believe it.
This Chii-chan.
This Chii-chan is in the maid club.
When I saw it, Chii-chan was the only one who was really big.
That's right.
To be honest, Minami, Asuka, and Chii-chan.
Chii-chan.
Minami, Asuka, and Chii-chan.
That's right.
Everyone was the same size as the maid's clothes.
There was only one.
I see.
Everyone just came to me and said, it's just right.
Chii-chan was really big.
She pulled out her thighs.
Chii-chan's plump legs.
It's not round.
That's right.
I was surprised.
It's the opposite.
Why?
It's really funny.
I thought about that time.
It changed from the beginning to now.
Let's talk about everyone's first impression.
Let's do it.
Let's take a look.
Do you remember?
What is your first impression?
To be honest, I thought she was a cool girl.
Osaka's...
What?
She was like,
What the hell?
I thought she had a girlish aura.
At first?
I didn't know what to do.
It was strange.
When I talked to her,
she looked young,
but she looked very long.
People often say that.
She looked young.
Yes.
People often say that the appearance and the content
are different.
That's right.
To be honest, I don't remember Chi-chan.
Really?
I don't remember Chi-chan at all.
At that time, Chi-chan was erasing her shadow.
Everyone was saying that she was cute.
So I thought I could stay here and erased my shadow.
At that time, I didn't notice Chi-chan.
What about Ami?
Thinking about ARMY now, I wonder who he was.
What that?
Ami, that's not it.
Ami is kind of quiet, sensual, and I think she's going
to be like this.
gah gah
But it wasn't a healthy pair of pants from the beginning.
He was really shy.
I was shy too.
It's the first time, um,
It was tsuntsun, wasn't it?
But it's true that the other members were also a little scared.
I was scared
Yes, at first
He was the type to get scared easily.
I'm going to go to the middle of the day.
Then, what is your favorite song in Nogizaka?
Oh, I just thought of a good one.
What is it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you want to sing your favorite song in Nogizaka?
Sure.
One by one.
Let's sing one by one.
Okay, let's start with Ami.
Ami is...
What should we sing?
Let's sing Yubibonkyo.
That sounds good.
Okay.
Can you do the hand gesture?
Yubibonkyo
Let's take a look at the distance between our fingers.
The distance between our fingers.
What we are looking for is in our eyes.
What we are looking for is in our minds.
That's right.
That's great.
Next, Chii-chan.
Chii-chan's favorite song.
Ami and I like songs.
We like songs.
Let's show it here.
Chii-chan's favorite song.
Friday the 13th.
That's great.
Friday the 13th. Something is going to happen.
This is bad.
What's wrong with Chii-chan?
She's got a cold.
Mom, tell me about your sadness.
Spread your wings.
The sound of the
rain is falling.
I wanted to sing it, but my voice is not good today.
That was a little weird.
It's rare.
Can you sing one song?
Sing the chorus.
What's your favorite song?
Whistle to the wolf It'll be lively, so are you all
excited? Let's all sing together Whistle to the wolf
One, two, three!
A wolf whispers a melody of love
Hey, come on, be serious!
I'm serious!
What are you talking about?
I'm embarrassed!
I'm embarrassed here.
I like tears, too.
I like Aikawa, too.
But Aikawa's voice is too high.
Really?
I wanted to see you.
It's not that high.
I wanted to see you. Yes!
I...
To you. No, it's not that high.
Bicycle, pedal with all your might.
Climbing up the hill while climbing.
Shirts inflating in the wind.
It's annoying now.
I finally noticed.
My true feelings.
I'm going to the top.
There's only one. Run to the top.
What happens if you dance to the GURU GURU curtain?
Then I'll compete with each other.
I'll give you money.
Sing a song for me.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
As expected of a ninja Kotoko.
As expected.
You are a ninja.
Right?
Like a ninja, I move quickly.
You are a ninja.
I was asked if I was so active on a daily basis.
I blew it after I thought about it.
I blew it deeply.
Like this?
I'm sorry, but I'm acting as usual.
I'm sorry.
I think it's the first time I've ever shown myself like
this on a daily basis.
That's right.
I'm always on TV.
I'm Nogitaka46.
Hello, everyone.
Nice to meet you.
It's like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm like this.
I'm like this on a daily basis.
I'm active 46.
It's boring.
I was surprised.
Now, we are in Kanpei.
We were told to stop talking about serious things.
Let's start!
You start!
Don't be so serious!
Oh yeah!
We've decided the next national tour!
That's right!
I wanted to go to Gyorgi Daichi Park!
I took the first step to Gyorgi Daichi Park.
First of all, I took the first step.
The stage was 180 degrees, but it was about 460 degrees behind.
What are you talking about?
It was like this.
This is Yoyogi.
It's embarrassing.
You have to be careful.
You have to be aware of it.
You're being watched from 360 degrees.
Let's put in more energy than ZEPP.
13,000 people.
Isn't it amazing?
I was surprised.
I'm looking forward to it.
Wow, it came out.
That's it.
I don't think it's a good idea to talk about something serious.
It really doesn't suit you.
I'm thinking about it.
I understand.
Let's make a serious face.
Let's stretch our necks.
What's wrong?
Do you want to show your collarbone?
I'm a little tired.
Let's talk seriously.
How was the tour?
It was fun.
It was really fun.
There were a lot of things.
We were scolded.
We couldn't do it well.
We were clumsy.
At first, when we were in Hokkaido,
we did our best, but we couldn't do it well.
In the afternoon, we were scolded with love.
We were like,
We're not done yet.
Are you sure this is okay?
We got paid for it.
We were like, what are we going to do?
We reflected on it.
We thought about it again.
Everyone was amazing.
The night show in Sapporo was a change of heart.
We had a sense of accomplishment because it was so crazy.
Anyway, I wanted to make all the customers feel happy.
I didn't want to do it.
Ami, it's almost over. Sing the ending theme.
The ending theme is the song that plays at the end roll.
Ending theme.
What about the title?
Give it to me.
Ending theme.
Don't you cry a little more?
A title that suits the ending.
Pajama party.
Pajama party?
Yes, you watched our pajama party today.
So at the end of the song,
we will sing a song called pajama party.
I got it.
Pajama party.
It's always this rhythm.
It's this rhythm.
Our, our pajama party
Always exciting and fun party
Today's members are Nojo Ami
And Saito Chiharu
And Kawamura Mahiro
Pajama party is the best, Pajama party is the best
You and me, we all love it
Bye bye
Let's go to bed
I'm sleepy
Good night
Don't open the door!