AISubs
движение
A Uncle by the name of Faking Kyoto
That's not it
A boy by the name of Shukure
Nooo
Grumpy boy
"...
I'm Marika!
Marika is...
What is it?
Marika is nothing!
You're annoying.
You're always saying that.
Marika is...
Kawabata-san is...
You're overestimating my hobbies.
I'm overestimating your hobbies.
Your hobbies are good?
Yes.
I think your clothes are also cute.
I like your clothes.
What do you like?
Your clothes are cute.
What do you mean?
Your clothes are really cute.
Marika is...
What is it?
Marika is nothing!
I forgot what I was thinking.
Marika is...
Marika is nothing!
What is it?
I'm going to cry.
Then...
What is it?
You're annoying.
You're overestimating my hobbies.
You're always saying that.
I'm not overestimating your hobbies.
I'm overestimating your hobbies.
Then...
What is it?
I'm overestimating your hobbies.
The next is Mayan!
Yay!
Hello!
This is a video of the actual performance.
Thank you very much.
The nickname has been decided for a long time.
Oh!
It's a goddess.
Thank you very much.
It's the best, isn't it?
It's the best.
Thank you very much.
I've been loving Hina lately.
Hina?
Look at the camera.
Mayan is the best.
Thank you, Hina.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me, Mayan.
Say something.
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
Mayan X Shingo
Mai Mai!
Mai Mai is here.
I'm getting excited every time.
Mai Mai!
I'm so excited every time.
I can't forgive you.
Mai Mai is the best in the world.
She is so cute.
You don't think so, do you?
I really think so.
I don't think so.
Hina's live and rock videos are also Mai Mai.
Hey, hey.
Mai Mai is special.
Ta-da.
Mai Mai is so cute.
What are you into recently?
Eating.
Eating is cute.
It's not cute to eat.
It's the size of your mouth.
Why?
I don't like it.
Anyway, the nickname of Mai Mai is Seigo.
I'm glad you like it.
You didn't hear it, did you?
I heard it a little.
Next is KANARIN.
KANARIN is fluttering.
Fluttering.
KANARIN is the cutest.
KANARIN is cute.
Really?
I love KANARIN.
When I saw everyone earlier, I fell in love with KANARIN.
I only saw you.
KANARIN was 100 times sexier than everyone.
Really?
KANARIN is good at dancing.
KANARIN is cute.
KANARIN's nickname is...
What should I do?
KANARIN is cute.
KANARIN is sexy.
Sexy?
KANARIN is sexier than anyone.
KANARIN is sexy.
KANARIN is good at dancing.
KANARIN is the best.
KANARIN's face is blue.
KANARIN is cute.
KANARIN is white.
KANARIN is black.
KANARIN is so cute.
That's right.
KANARIN is Sexy.
Resemble KANARIN.
This is SIYULIN.
She is cute.
Her nickname is...
I am making painful characters.
Painful characters!
But,
Sayori is making a character desperately.
No, I'm not.
This is me.
Sayori, how old are you?
13 years old.
You've been doing it for a long time, haven't you?
Oh, it's been a long time.
Really?
Can I make it?
Yes, you can.
I heard a lot of rumors about you.
No!
But there's nothing.
What should I do?
Let's make an apple.
What?
Let's make a painful character 21 years old.
No!
Let's just make it a tentacle.
It doesn't matter.
I'm sure there are fans who call it a tentacle.
Really?
So, let's make a painful character 21 years old.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to do it.
I'm scared.
This is how a party looks like.
No, no, no, no.
This is not how a party looks like.
Take a picture first.
Hello, I'm a complete professional.
Thank you very much.
We did it!
Na-chan and I are together today.
Yes.
It's our first time.
Yes, it's our first time.
It's our anniversary.
Yes, it's our anniversary.
It's our first time to be together with Kina.
Yes.
Thank you.
Next is Yuku-chan. Yes, I'm Yuka. Nice to meet you.
Yuku-chan is perfect at everything except cooking.
Am I a genius? No, you're a pervert.
Pervert is always perfect.
Am I perfect? No, you're a pervert.
Am I a pervert? No, you're a pervert.
You're perfect and you can do anything, but you can't
do normal things.
You're not good at painting, you're not good at
cooking, and you can't do normal things.
I'm not good at housework.
You're not good at painting, you're not good at
cooking, and you can't do normal things.
So you're a pervert.
That's it?
You can finish it in two letters.
It's like Terumae-Romae.
What?
Terumae-Romae is strange.
Terumae-Romae is here.
Yay!
What about you, Riku?
I'm a pervert who doesn't know common sense.
Then you're a pervert who doesn't know common sense.
That's it?
I'm a pervert who doesn't know common sense.
I'm really a pervert.
You're a pervert.
Riku is a pervert who doesn't know common sense.
Who's next? Kawaguchi.
What's this? Why did you put it here?
How much is this?
I'll put it on the tripod.
Then Reika.
Next is Reika.
Yay!
Hello.
Well, let's get started.
The first letter is...
Your face is noisy.
Yay!
I've been thinking about this for a long time.
You're lying, aren't you?
Do something noisy.
Okay.
Do a hop, step, and flip.
I'll do it.
Hop, step, and flip.
You're always sliding.
I don't think everyone cares about this.
What?
When I introduce myself at school...
Did you do it?
No, I didn't.
I was surprised.
I said, I did it.
And when I asked how it was,
Most of them said yes.
That's right.
Slippery cap?
Which do you prefer?
Slippery cap or noisy face?
Slippery cap is better.
No, I'll choose noisy face.
Why?
It was a noisy face captain.
The second letter is...
Your face is noisy.
The next letter is...
The fourth letter is...
Yay!
Thank you.
Ayu-chan.
Sayonara's nickname is...
It's decided.
I'm a fake angel.
I'm really cute in clothes.
I'm white and fluffy.
I'm fluffy.
I'm an angel.
I sometimes write strange pictures on my blog.
I used to write a lot of pictures.
Do you write a lot of pictures these days?
I want to commercialize it.
Which one?
There are a lot of scenes.
Really?
I want to commercialize it.
I'm thinking of making it a T-shirt version.
It's a strategy.
I'm a fake angel.
I write strange pictures.
I'm good at drawing pictures.
I sometimes write strange pictures on my blog.
I'm a fake angel.
I think it's a good idea.
Are you a fortune teller?
I'm a fortune teller.
The fifth letter is...
The sixth letter is...
The seventh letter is...
The eighth letter is...
I don't care if it's 5,000 yen or 80,000 yen.
Stop it.
At first, I thought it was an act.
But before I knew it, it had changed to Getsukue.
I'm so happy.
Maybe that's why...
What?
I'm surprised when I see the fans.
Why?
They don't know you make so much money.
No, I don't.
Oh, I see.
So, Naomi is an individualist.
Bye bye.
Stop it.
I'm an individualist.
This is Na-chan.
So cute.
Na-chan is so cute today.
I'm so happy.
Na-chan, I told you.
Na-chan.
Na-chan is cute.
It's a perfect video.
She's so cute.
Highlight.
Na-chan is a perfect video.
I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
Which one is the hint?
What is it?
Well...
It's Doiya.
Oh, Doiya.
What should I do?
It's difficult.
It's so difficult.
Because...
I don't know what to do.
It's a phantom.
A phantom?
Yes.
When I was told that I was cute,
I always said it's a phantom.
A phantom?
No.
It's a phantom.
Na-chan is a weird girl.
She touches my elbow.
Na-chan really touches it.
She touches it.
What is it?
Touching.
Touching Nishi is cool.
It's cool.
Everyone is crying.
Next is Lenarin.
I'm scared.
Lenarin is...
What is it?
It's close.
It's like Ichiki-sensei.
It's Ichiki-sensei.
Ichiki-sensei is normal.
Normal.
Ichiki is Kazumi-sensei.
Ichiki-sensei.
I think it's Ichiki-sensei.
San-barena.
I think it's San-barena.
It's something San-barena.
Chia-kun and Kazumi's gaia meeting.
It's amazing.
What is it?
He uses a fan.
He goes up his toes.
I know.
It's finger-sensei.
He uses fingers.
You're being ignored.
Don't stand up. We're having a conversation.
I'm sorry.
This is a show.
I'm sorry. I was standing on my toes.
Did you notice that I was standing on my toes?
Yeah, you stood on your toes.
The fan was like this.
I was standing on my toes.
That's so cool!
Tsumasaki Rena?
It doesn't matter.
Tsumasaki Rena.
It's decided by Tsumasaki Rena.
She's laughing.
Next is Manattan.
It's decided from a long time ago.
What?
Manatsuri City.
It's not a city.
I want another one.
Manatsuri City.
It's like Pokemon.
Devil.
Did you see it now?
From the camera's point of view.
It's scary.
It's a new information.
What is it?
I don't know.
Tennei City.
Tennei.
From the age of zero.
Tsuritan.
Everyone calls it Tsuritan.
Can I call it Tsuritan from the age of zero?
No.
It's Tsuritan from the age of zero.
Try it.
Three, two, one.
Everyone.
What should I do?
Hurry up.
I'll shoot your hearts.
I thought it was Tennei style to say Tsuritsutte.
I'm making it.
Next is Asuka.
Asuka's head.
Tebasaki?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Tebasaki.
That's all.
I know what you mean.
No, no, no, no, no.
Tebasaki.
I'm Asuka.
No, it's not cute.
It's heavy.
Tebasaki.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Then what is it?
One more.
One more?
Then why don't you do tebasaki?
Why tebasaki?
Somehow tebasaki.
Loli tebasaki.
Loli.
Isn't it cute?
It's cute.
Loli tebasaki.
Isn't it good?
I was told it was good.
Loli tebasaki is good.
Next is Seitan.
Seitan is a little Yankee.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's kind of small.
Wait a minute.
It's not a Yankee.
It's a Yankee.
It's a little Yankee.
It's a little gyaru.
It's not a gyaru.
It's a little Yankee.
Is it a Yankee?
Yes, it's a Yankee.
Is it okay?
Then it's a little Yankee.
How is it?
Thank you very much.
And Minami is the last.
The last member is Minami.
Minami looks sleepy.
Minami's nickname is...
What should I call you?
It's okay.
It's okay if it's hard.
Why do you say that?
I'm M.
Really?
It's like a whisper.
I want to put a devil in it, too.
Devil like a crow.
Don't sleep.
I'm sorry.
I'm sleepy.
Minami is the last.
It's like a whisper.
I'm thinking about what to do.
There's a whisper and a devil.
A whisper and a devil?
What is it?
It's a fat whisper.
It's not fat.
It's a demon whisper.
Demon whisper.
I'm sorry, Minami.
It's like a whisper.
It's like a crow's voice.
It's not a crow's voice, it's a crow's voice.
It's like a crow's voice, it's like a crow's voice.
I'm sorry.
I was a demon whisperer.
The last one is over!
Behind the scenes
Hina suddenly appears
A present for these 3
7 points, what's the next party?
Hey wait
I'm telling you that I've never seen Hina pose this
gesture to anyone
What?
When everyone can pose she won't pose
You can Τake pictures until the end
You have to pose!
What about like from Chirio Hara'maaaa
That's good.
Magical girl Haraguro.
When I saw Hina's blog, she wrote something like
Konnichi Pyon, Hina Pyon.
She wrote something like that.
Then, from today...
Magical girl Haraguro.
Look at the camera.
I'm going to cast a spell on your hearts.
Yes.
Magical girl Haraguro.
That's not it.
But when I was casting a spell,
I wrote a spell like this.
All the Nogizaka members are cute.
She's a beautiful girl.
I'll do my best.
That's not it.
You can say it because you're close.
Do you know what a spell is?
If you're not close,
You can't just say it.
That's why I was able to say it because I was close to everyone.
So, please.
Yes.
What are you writing?
Magical girl Haraguro.
What was it?
Magical girl angel?
That's not it.
For some reason, it's decided.
For some reason.
That's not it.
You can say it because you're close to everyone.
Why?
Magical Girl Haraguro.
Magical Girl Angel.
I wrote it like this, but the Nogizaka members are
cute, so please come and see them once! Thank you!
Please support me! Bye bye!