AISubs
Yabikko-ko Aki Festival!
MAHIRO!
Thank you so much!
We won the game!
MAHIRO, please don't spill it here.
I don't want to spill it.
I'm really going to do it.
This is...
No, no.
If you hold it, you'll know.
If you hold it properly, it's like this.
That's right.
Do you understand?
If you hold it like this, it's 46 degrees.
That's right.
That's great!
We won the game!
Super stage
Ready, set...
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's do it again!
You can rub it on your back.
I don't know how to do it.
Rub it on your back.
I'm going to take a picture.
Ready, set...
Super stage
Wow!
Wow! Very good!
Good job!
There will be one chance out of two, so it's plus 1 point.
OK, OK, OK.
Now, it's good!
Replay
Well, if we can move like this,
when he get his finger up fully like this,
I'll put it by the screen
How about Lane …
Can he teach you how to move with only new one?
Let's try!
With my experience
Wow!
Very good!
You're the best!
I don't need your dance!
Actually, she is my experience.
She said she was taken by her dad.
It's quite possible to expect.
I'll do my best!
You can put it in.
Amazing!
I went too far!
Nagashima-san is not a free-spirited girl, right?
She is also a free-spirited girl.
I'm not an easy girl.
I'm confident about it.
I'm not like Nene.
I have been to Uchipparashi.
I've been to the Uchippa Lodge.
Oh, then you've been to the Uchippa Lodge, right?
You've been to the Uchippa Lodge, right?
If you've been to the Uchippa Lodge, you can go to the 35th hole.
You can go to the 35th hole.
Let's go!
No!
Wait!
I can't do it!
No!
Nice!
It's so fun!
I can't do it!
Let me show you.
It's coming out.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
I want you to finish it.
Yuri!
Yuri, don't get your teeth out.
I'll pull out my teeth.
Your teeth will come out.
I can't do it.
Don't pull out your teeth too much.
Let's go!
Good luck!
No!
Wait!
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Don't look at the camera.
So good!
Wait, wait!
Next one will be included.
Akachi will be dancing from there.
As expected, it's difficult to dance from there.
It's really difficult.
Yuuri team, do you have something?
What is it?
I got it.
There are many words that will be popular this year.
There are many words.
Like a representative of English?
Just do it.
Let's try it.
If you do it, please show us.
Show us with your hands.
With your hands.
I'll go.
It's a speech from the Tokyo Olympics.
It's a speech.
It's a speech by Mr. Takigawa Crystal.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
Is it OK?
Wait.
Do your best.
It's amazing.
You can do it!
Who's next?
Let's go!
You can do it!
S light
No way...
yup, we did it!
What's going on?
I fell!
It's over.
You can do it.
The last game.
F3.
I can do it.
I'm ready.
Go.
It's over.
You can do it.
The winner of this golf match is the Yurii team!
So, you will receive a penalty game.
You will pull the paper inside the box and play the penalty game.
What is it?
Ta-da!
Please show it to us.
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
Bibi Philippines!
We did it!
You did it before, didn't you?
There are seven members in the Chiharu team, so only
one of the seven will get a penalty.
Even if it's a penalty game, the one with the worst
luck in the Chiharu team is the penalty game.
How many times have you done this?
Let's all take a pen.
This is a direct feeling.
I'm scared.
No, no, no.
Wait, I'm scared.
It hurts already.
I'm scared.
I can't push it because it's chicken.
Push it.
Everyone, please put your hands in front of you.
Please push it at the same time.
I'm scared.
This is the penalty game of the Chiharu team.
Bilibili pen, one, two, three.
I'm scared.
The person who got Bilibili is Yamato Nina.
I'm glad.
How was it?
This is bad.
By the way, is this Yamato's first experience of Bilibili?
Yes.
How was it?
My hands are getting bigger.
This is really bad.
Can you check the salary?
I'm really scared.
I don't know if I really got Bilibili.
This is strange.
Please push it.
Let's move on to the next video.
The last theme is the art of autumn, so I would like to
draw an illustration on this mug and make an original
mug.
Why are you doing this in the conference room?
Actually, I couldn't make a hand strap because of the time.
I wanted to do it.
When I played golf, my friend didn't do it right away,
so I was embarrassed.
I was worried about it.
By the way, there is a person who put the ball somewhere.
It's not that person's fault, is it?
I will make it.
Let's do our best!
All the cups I made earlier have been completed!
I haven't seen it yet, but let's turn around and see it.
Let's go!
One, two, three!
Wow!
It's done!
This is the easiest to understand.
This is Maaya.
Didn't you draw a picture like this before?
What did you draw?
The design of the T-shirt.
The sun, clouds, and tulips are always drawn.
I think this is it.
What is this?
Is this an image of autumn?
Isn't this different from humans?
Halloween pumpkin?
What?
I was surprised.
I thought it was a little dangerous.
What?
Was this Halloween?
Just a little.
The theme is autumn.
Is it only autumn here?
What is this?
Halloween halloween?
That's not it.
I didn't know.
Hello.
You are a masterpiece.
Thank you.
What is this?
I'm going to be cursed.
You are going to be cursed.
What is this?
I was surprised.
This is a fact check.
You often say,
Nakadakara Nakadakara Nakadakara Nakadakara.
I'm scared.
I was surprised.
I wanted to read my name from above.
I'm Nakadakara.
I'm going to go around.
Nakadakara Nakadakara Nakadakara Nakadakara.
I want to go around.
But if you're not careful,
I don't know if it's cute.
I'm cursed.
I'm going to be cursed.
I'm cute, right?
I've been cursed in the theme of autumn.
I'm cursed.
I'm going to be cursed.
I thought it was Halloween.
It's Halloween.
It's so cute!
It's Halloween!
Wow!
It's amazing!
I've never seen anything like this before.
I'm jealous.
I don't want to look at it.
Stop it.
Look at this. It's the same Halloween.
It's totally different.
It's so cute.
But...
It's so cute!
Everyone is amazing.
It says,
Yuu-chan.
It's so cute!
It's cute!
It's rare for Minami to have a cat.
It's always like this.
It's so cute!
It's rare for Minami to have a cat.
It's nice that there are so many colors.
I can feel how she feels.
It's a little thin from a distance.
It's Nagashima-san's.
I'm curious about the back.
It says, Aki-love.
It's the most beautiful.
It's Aki-love.
Yutan's is really cute.
It's a three-part.
It's cute!
I can't think of something like Aki.
I thought it was a check because I didn't have a check.
It's cute!
It's like a 100-yen coin.
Yutan's.
Who do you think is the best at this?
Chiharu.
Chiharu?
Who could it be?
For real, I think it's Chiharu, Sayuri, or Minami.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Sayuri.
You're actually wrong.
Now we'll have 3 of us close the costume show with
Minami, Sayuri, Chiharu.
Actually, we were going to do a felt costume.
Oh hai, I'm showing my passports again.
It was a great memory to be able to make Shizuoka- Fu together.
It was a serious conversation.
Minami, close your eyes.
I don't really like drawing, but...
What is this?
At first it wasn't fun, but...
What?
Wait a minute.
When I said I was going to draw, I thought it was weird, but...
But, but, but...
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun.
Sayuri.
We were able to enjoy the fall together.
Today...
I think I enjoyed the fall the most in the world.
It was a lot of fun.
That's all.
Shizuoka-Fu together!
Today, we've been doing a lot of things since the morning.
How was it? How was the Bilibili pen?
How was the game?
It's not a game, it's crazy.
It's a bad game.
How was it?
The Bilibili pen itself was the first time you've done it, right?
It's the first time in my life, and I've been avoiding it.
I don't like it because it's chicken.
I'm not the kind of person who does things like that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But next time, I won't do it.
Well, that's a punishment game, so I don't know.
That's true. Thank you very much.
How about Sen-nyan?
Sen-nyan?
How was it today?
How was it?
I'm looking forward to it because it's my first gift coin.
I got a fish from the beginning.
It was fun.
Thank you.
For the first time, the person who held it was only Sayu-nyan.
I cried when I saw her face.
That's right.
I think I got a good result.
That's good.
Well, look forward to the next Nogikoko.
Bye-bye.