AISubs
Now, shall we start?
Nogita Kaze, here!
This time, I, Tan-tan-tan, Yu-tan-tan, and Yurito Saito
and the Saito Combi will be the MCs!
Nice to meet you!
So, we're here in Sagamihara, Kanagawa Prefecture.
What exactly are we going to do here?
Chiharu-san, please tell us.
Let's enjoy the best of autumn!
Nogizawa-kun...
Are you okay with your first line?
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm worried about being the MC today.
I wonder if I'll be okay.
Take 2! Ready, action!
Let's enjoy the best of autumn!
Nogikoko Autumn Festival!
Yay!
That was good!
So, speaking of autumn,
there are many things like the autumn of sports, the
autumn of ability,
and many other things.
So, let's enjoy the best of autumn!
So, Seitan, what is the best of autumn?
Autumn?
You know what it is, right?
What is the best of autumn for you?
I'm sorry.
Everyone is saying, one, two, three.
What do you want to eat?
Meat.
Meat?
That's good.
Hinachima.
Thank you.
What is the best autumn for you?
Autumn?
Autumn for readers.
That's a serious answer.
That's a different answer from Seitan.
At first, Seitan said it was the autumn of food.
So we all cooperated.
Catching fish!
Fish!
We all cooperated.
We caught fish with our hands.
That's amazing.
It's not fun to just catch fish.
I'd like to set a rule.
If you can't catch a fish before the time limit,
you can have lunch prepared after this.
Lunch!
We're all into it, so we can have lunch.
That's right.
So let's all catch fish.
Let's think about each other.
All or one.
One whole or one.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Are you all ready?
Do you want to have lunch?
Yeah!
Okay, let's go.
In five minutes.
Ready?
Go!
Fish!
You guys are all bad at fishing.
You're bad.
Eh? Eh? Yamato! Yamato! Yamato!
Yamato! Yamato!
What was that?
But you did it just now, didn't you?
Yamato! Yamato!
Look! Look!
You did it!
You're so cute!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Rina! Rina!
You have three minutes left!
You did it!
Are you okay?
I want to be caught.
I'm holding it.
Wait, wait.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Isn't this big?
Wait, wait.
How is it?
I can't even touch it.
I might have died.
I did it!
Shinkan, do you want a small one?
This one, this one, this one.
I got it.
I can't see the snake anymore.
Look, look.
It's a unicorn.
10 seconds left.
10, 9, 8, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, time's up.
Time's up.
So, I will announce the result.
Sakano's catch.
The result is 5 out of 14.
I'm sorry if I licked you a little.
Sae-chan, come here. What's wrong?
What's wrong?
She's crying all the time.
Don't you need lunch?
It's okay. I feel sorry for her.
Please don't do that.
What should we do with this feeling?
What should we do?
I don't know.
Ready...
Start!
Gently, gently.
Hold on, hold on.
No, no.
No, no. Move.
No, no, no.
Everyone, push the fish.
Is it okay?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
What should I do?
Everyone, everyone, surround me.
No, no, no.
It's impossible.
Seriously, it's impossible.
I'll show you.
You're almost there.
You touched me.
You look like a parent.
Ah! You're so cute.
Ah! Don't touch me.
I'm sorry.
Ah, I was caught.
I was caught.
Ah!
I hope you like the video and see you again.
Everyone, where are you?
Please come here.
It's a little bit more.
No, this has nothing to do with the army.
It has nothing to do with the army.
See you later.
No way!
It's a very unfortunate result.
What? No way!
Then, then, then.
Everyone, lunch is...
No way! No way!
I feel like I'm going to die.
Yuuri, you did your best!
You grabbed the fish, but it fell.
There's no point in falling.
There's no point in leaving a result.
So, everyone.
It's not easy.
Saya-chan.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
There's a program like this.
Next is the autumn of sports.
It's a real golf competition in Nogizaka.
It's golf.
We're going to be captains here.
Team Akita will receive a punishment game.
I don't want to.
Please don't give me a punishment game.
I will announce the team.
Nene Ito.
Kawamura Mahiro.
Yes!
Urakawa Kana
Hatanaka Seira
Miyazawa Seira
Wada Maaya
Nice to meet you!
And the Chiharu team is
Inoue Sayuri
Higuchi Hina
Nagashima Seira
Nojo Ami
Hoshino Minami
Hina!
Now, I'd like you to decide who will be on the front line.
Everyone, over here!
Team Tantan!
We'll do our best!
Let's start with the first hole, Yuuri team.
Ready, go!
I'll do my best!
Let's start with the first hole.
Eh?
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Where did it go?
It went somewhere else.
It fell into the sand.
Sorry.
The next day
Chii-chan?
You said it before, right?
That's so hard.
Chii-chan!
I'll do my best.
She'll do her best.
Then Eri-chan.
Eri-chan!
Please do it!
She's a beginner, but...
I'm worried.
Do your best!
Thank you!
This is all?
I didn't have this before.
No.
Thank you!
The next day
Spread your legs and cross your legs
Cross my legs?
A little bit
Like this
The next day
It's like this.
No, it's not like that.
It's totally different.
It's like this.
You can't bend it.
The way you hold the net is weird.
The second one is Minajima.
It's a flying fish.
I'll pull it out.
Go for it.
I will...
Are you serious?
Please stop...
I'd like to make magic today too.
Here you are.
One is good.
I'll hold it.
There is a big one...
But I do not.
I do not.
Actually, it's like this.
Like this?
Like this.
Was it good like this?
The surface of the hit is wide.
Ah, it's a little...
I don't think it's a good idea.
But it's better than Kana.
Please don't touch her.
I'm hurt, too.
I'll do my best.
I'll aim for the red flag.
Don't throw the ball.
Don't throw it.
I'll throw the ball.
Good luck!
Amazing!
Practice! Practice!
Like this, right?
It's a practice!
I was surprised myself.
Thank you!
I've been playing around here.
I was so full of energy.
I've been practicing.
The advantage team got 3 points, so the advantage team
gets 3 points.
Even if we get 3 points, the rest of the game will be over.
The advantage team got 3 points, so the advantage team
gets 3 points.
Wow!
It was so fast!
This is bad!
Wow!
Awesome!
Wait, there was a strong one.
A strong one!
Wait, this is difficult!
It was a strong one!
Now, since Rina was out of the game,
it's a plus one.
That's right.
It's a plus one!
If you keep hitting the ball, it's a plus two, three, four, five.
So it's a tie.
I think I saw the ball.
That diagonal.
What diagonal?
46.
Let's go.
Good luck.
How do you do it?
Really?
It's difficult.
You did it.
Please.
Go, go, go.
It's like a car.
You just hit the car.
I'm sorry.
OK, OK.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
I'm sorry.
Good luck.
It's a lie.
It's difficult.
Tell me how to hit it.
Everyone was amazing.
It's a lie.