AISubs
discovered that elite position
the zrobi got an annual salary, 15,000 yen
Here we are at Nogizaka!
I'm going to be in this video!
I'm here at Wakari Messe!
Let's go to the dressing room!
I am often called by the members, so I would like to
give a nickname to the members.
What are you talking about?
Ok, next is Okatsuki.
Yes, I was called.
Ok, Okatsuki's nickname is a professional of facial expression.
Can you stop it?
Why?
Why are you doing that?
Because you always have a funny face.
No, I don't.
It's funny.
Do a funny face.
What?
I don't intend to do it.
Really.
No, it's funny.
Tell me if you want to say it.
I'm a person who wants to express my facial expression.
Yes.
Let's take a look!
Ready, set, go!
Hey, you did it!
I didn't do it!
You made me do it!
I always make this face.
Hey, seriously.
Are you really going to do that?
Okay.
That's good.
I don't want to!
Are you a pro?
No, I mean, that?
I don't want to be in front of you.
Then why are you doing this?
No, I'm a pro.
I'm a young pro.
A young pro.
What kind of pro are you?
A handsome pro.
Okay, the next one is Hinachima.
Yay!
It's double Hina.
Oh!
Well, the name of Hinachima is...
A fake Kyoto person.
Wait, wait, wait.
Say something in catchphrase.
I'm waiting for you.
No, it's not.
Why?
It's different from Oide Asu.
It's Tokyo, isn't it?
Yes, Tokyo.
It's always Tokyo, isn't it?
What?
Why?
No, it's not.
I like matcha, so I chose Oide Asu.
Even people who want to shake hands ask me to tell them
good things about Kyoto.
Everyone misunderstands.
I think everyone misunderstands.
At that time, I want you to shake hands with me.
Wait, you don't want to be a Kyoto person.
Yes, but I want to be a Kyoto person.
What?
Kyoto doesn't exist, does it?
Secretly Kyoto character.
Yes, secretly.
What?
I don't like it.
Why?
I don't like fake Kyoto.
If you say it in the standard language of Tokyo, what
does it mean?
Come to me.
I dare to say Oide Asu.
Certainly, Oide Asu sounds better.
If you say Oide Asu, I will be surprised.
No, I'm scared.
Next is KAZUMIN.
KAZUMIN is fluttering.
KAZUMIN is saying something.
KAZUMIN and KAZUMIN are a match made in heaven.
Yes.
Recently, I was going to say something different.
We were going to make our voices cute.
Yes.
We practice in the middle of the night.
We stay at a hotel.
At 3 o'clock in the evening, we practice to make cute voices.
And the next day, our voices are fluttering.
KAZUMIN, I don't know what you're talking about.
I know what you're talking about.
You're going to make me dance, aren't you?
Well, then...
Grandma...
Hey!
What kind of grandma are you?
I'm your relative's grandma.
No!
Wait a minute.
I'm an idol.
What should I do?
Grandma beauty?
Do you want to be my grandma's beauty?
What is it?
Grandma's beauty?
No!
What is Grandma's beauty?
But it's a little thin.
But the way you've been talking until now is like this.
No, it's not.
If it's a mushroom, it smells like a mushroom.
Then I'll make you my grandma's beauty.
I really don't want to.
Then I'll make you my relative's grandma.
No! I'll make you my grandma's beauty.
What is Grandma's Beauty?
It's a fake Kyoto girl.
I've met her too many times.
Isn't that too much?
But I know.
You're a fake Kyoto girl.
I like Kyoto.
Really?
Well, it's Tokyo.
Yes, it's Tokyo.
It has nothing to do with it.
I was wondering what you were doing.
When I said that, you said I was a fake Kyoto girl.
Next is Nene.
Hello.
I'm Nene Koro.
Nene is small, but she is sexy.
She looks like an adult.
What is her nickname?
I don't know.
I'm 46 years old.
You're 46 years old, right?
Yes, I'm 46 years old.
I'm looking like a 46-year-old girl.
Thank you!
If you say it well, you look like a 46-year-old girl.
Because I'm a little bit like this, so I can't show my age.
How old are you?
Are you not popular?
I'm not popular.
I'm not 146 cm, I don't have any.
You're always popular, aren't you?
I don't have any.
I always wear high heels and hold them in secret.
I'm always small, so I'm really small, but I look like an adult.
Thank you very much.
Next is Rarin.
Serarin's nickname is a desperate girl.
Desperate?
I'm really desperate, and I'm doing my best to dance.
I'm doing my best.
How old are you?
I'm just a cheerful girl.
It's like there's no other way but to be cheerful.
Then do something else. Do something good.
What's good?
Do something idol-like.
I want to be cheerful.
Then say your catchphrase like an idol.
I always bite my hair.
Say your catchphrase.
I'm always in your heart.
I'm always cheerful.
Serarin.
You have to be cheerful.
Do it again.
Cheerfully?
As usual?
I got it.
I'm always in your heart.
I'm laughing.
Your voice is loud.
I don't have time.
Yuki is impatient.
An impatient girl.
I don't like it.
I'm always impatient.
Next is Yuttan.
Hello.
Yuttan is as cheerful as Serarin.
She is the loudest in the dressing room.
I'm not.
It's noisy.
You are a pervert.
I'm a pervert.
There is no such thing as a pervert.
In fact.
Everyone around you is laughing.
You are not a pervert.
I'm scared.
Hina chan.
A manatsu girl.
Manatsu.
Stop it!
What should I do?
Make it cute.
I feel like I'm being watched.
It's cute.
It's cute as it is.
Isn't it cute?
It might be the best.
It's the best.
Next is Ami.
Hello, I'm Ami Noji.
Ami.
Ami Noji again today.
What should Ami's nickname be?
Everyone has a nickname.
There's a nickname on the back.
It's not filled in at all.
Ami, what should it be?
Ami, I don't know.
Isn't it easy to think of?
I just thought it was easy to think of.
Then, Rouge.
Rouge Ami.
Really.
You always have a rouge in your hand, right?
Please listen to me.
If I don't apply rouge,
I don't know where my mouth is.
It's so complex that
the color of my mouth is the same as my skin color.
It's so complex.
That's why I always apply it.
I want to be a healthy woman.
I always wear rouge.
I wear it all the time.
I always have it in my right hand.
Rouge Ami.
Hello. I'm Rina Ikoma. I'm Rina Ikoma.
I'm Rina Ikoma.
Hello. Hello.
What's your nickname?
I don't have many nicknames.
You have many nicknames.
But it's hard to call me Rina Ikoma.
Really? Then I'll call you Rina Ikoma.
Rina Ikoma!
Then I'll call you Rina Ikoma.
Really? Then what should I call you?
What should I call you?
Stop it! Stop it!
I really don't want to.
Then...
What should I call you?
You look like a boy.
Yes.
So...
I'll call you Minanshi.
What should I call you?
Minanshi. Minanshi.
Bi.
Bi shounen.
Shakure shounen.
Shakure shounen is terrible, isn't it?
Really?
Really terrible.
Shakure shounen was good.
This is the worst.
Next is Lottie.
Lottie.
She is really good at singing and dancing.
She is perfect.
I don't know what to choose.
What do you think, Kazumi?
Me?
She looks like a Shiba Inu.
I know.
But she looks like a dog.
She looks like a dog.
What should I choose?
Shiba Ken.
What about Shiba Ken?
What should I choose?
Shiba Ken.
People often say she looks like a dog.
She looks like a dog.
Shiba Ken of Kansai.
I can't find the worst part of Lottie.
She is in trouble.
Really?
Yes.
What should I choose?
She is in trouble.
It's rare to see her in trouble.
She is wearing Shakure shounen.
I think there is something like that.
Shiba prefecture in Kansai.
Shiba prefecture in Kansai is fine!
Shiba prefecture in Kansai
I'm Rina Yamato.
Hello.
I'm Komoto.
The name of the tomato is...
What should I name it?
Then...
Moegoe's potato.
That's mean!
What kind of potato is that?
Potato.
That's mean! That's mean!
Well...
Tomatoes always work hard in the ecosystem.
Right, everyone?
Why do you say that?
I'm going to introduce you to Rina next time.
Because I'm familiar with it.
I'll introduce you.
It's like a beauty antenna.
I always know a lot of things.
Like clothes.
Beauty products.
Makeup tools.
Massage.
I know a lot about it.
It's a potato.
You don't need it at the end, do you?
Then I'll name it a potato.
Shiba prefecture in Kansai
Next is Chiarun.
There are a lot of names for Chiarun.
Helmae Romae
Aladdin
The people of Egypt.
Chii-chan, nice to meet you.
Everyone, be quiet.
Chii-chan is...
What is it?
You have a strong face.
Hina-chan has a strong face, too.
I can't say anything.
You two have a strong face.
We have a strong face.
But you're beautiful.
You can be a star.
Kamen?
You're called the world's three most beautiful women.
That's amazing.
If you're the world's three most beautiful women,
Kuryo Patra.
That's right.
Kuryo Patra
You can do anything.
I can do anything.
Which one do you like?
Can I choose?
Terumaeromae?
P
Chii-chan's nickname is Terumaeromae.
I have that at home.
Terumaeromae.
I like it.
It suits you.
It suits me.
Next is Maaya.
Hello.
Maaya is...
What should I do?
I can speak English, but I can't.
What should I use?
I've only heard hello and how are you.
I remember the word stupid of me.
What does it mean?
I'm a fool.
That's right.
Then what is it?
I'm a fool.
Wait a minute.
I can only use hello.
That doesn't make sense.
What should I say?
English conversation?
English conversation.
What is it?
I don't know.
I don't have a word that comes to mind.
What is this?
Aisare Maaya.
Do you want to say Aisare Maaya?
Let's do it.
Maaya is Aisare Maaya.
Next is Hime-tan from Nakamoto Hime.
Hime-tan.
Hime-tan's nickname is Bakarimon.
What?
It's Bakarimon.
I'm not a fool.
I always wear a big, dirty ribbon.
No, it's dirty.
It's dirty.
It's not dirty.
Do you know?
I've been told that it's dirty lately.
What did you say?
I'm a little embarrassed.
There is a beautiful ribbon.
Really?
I always wear dirty things.
That's right.
Then shall we buy it soon?
I'm going to buy it again.
Hime-tan is often said to be an idol of Tensei.
Hime-tan.
I always imitate it, but it's not similar.
It's similar.
It's similar, isn't it?
So, often said to be an idol of Tensei.
My nickname is Bakarimon.
Thank you.
It was Bakarimon and Kawaguhina.
Bye bye.
It's beautiful.
Next is MisaMisa.
It's MisaMisa.
What is the nickname of MisaMisa?
What is it?
Is everyone thinking about it?
Yes, everyone is thinking about it.
MisaMisa is like an older sister.
It's like an older sister.
So, it's okay to be a sexy older sister.
It's normal.
Why?
I was expecting it.
What are you expecting?
Then, what is it?
Older sister.
Shut up.
It's Bi-damababa.
Older sister.
Bi-damababa.
It's a lie.
It's okay.
She said it's okay.
Then...
I'll do my best.
You're already turning yourself in.
I don't want to.
How old are you? How old are you now?
I'm 20 years old.
20 years old? 20 years old?
Then, your eyes are really like a bee ball.
I can really see that.
So, I'm a bee ball grandma.
Thank you very much.
I'm a bee ball grandma.
What's the difference between a bee ball grandma and a
bee ball grandma?
You!
It's okay.
It's because I denied the sexiness.
I see.
But, it has an impact.
Yes.
It has a strong impression.
But, if the fans say,
I'm not a grandma,
I'll be told the opposite.
I'll be told that I'm not a grandma.
I see.
I'm not a grandma.
I'll do my best. Bye bye.
Mai Mai is here.
What? She gave up her position.
Mai Mai is taking pictures.
Sayori is in the way.
I haven't decided Mai Mai's name yet.
But it's Seibo.
It's Seibo.
Have you decided your name?
Yes.
Hichike Joshi.
I know that name.
Why?
I'm a professional of facial expression.
Ringo Baba.
Why?
When I was 13 years old, I was always called Baba.
That's true.
I was always called B-dama Baba.
B-dama Baba.
What about you, Hinachi?
Nisekyotojin.
That's terrible.
I know that name.
Oide Yansu is a lie.
It's a lie.
I was worried about Hinachi Manishi.
I was asked if I was from Kyoto.
That's terrible.
And the recommended place is Kiyomizu-dera.
That's a lie.
It's a lie.
I was asked if I was from Kyoto.
What kind of food do you recommend?
It's a lie.
It's not a food.
Bye bye.
Shut up.
I'm Hichike.
I'm Ikki.
I don't need a Tsubittan.
I'm Yumittan.
Yumittan is cute.
Everyone in the second generation is nervous.
This is the first live show.
Please do your best.
And the members of the first generation.
Let's do our best not to lose to the happiness of the
second generation.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best not to lose to the happiness of the
second generation.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
I'm Lenonin!
I'm going to eat a lot of drugs!
Thank you!