AISubs
C.C Wasabi
One, two, Nogizaka-te, here!
Yay! It's started!
This time, Maaya Wada and Asuka Saito are going to the
handshake event in Kyoto!
We'll do our best!
Then, we'll go to the front.
We'll go to the front.
Do your best, Maaya!
How do I do this?
Turn around.
What should I do?
Should I go with this hand?
Like this?
You can change your hand.
Do your best!
Wait.
Do your best, Maaya!
Like this.
Let's go!
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
Let's introduce ourselves.
Why?
Asuka, please introduce yourself.
Really?
Yes.
Let's do a hand shake.
That's good.
How about you, Maaya?
Have fun, everyone!
Let's go to the members' waiting room!
No one is allowed to enter!
Let's go together!
I'm Mayan!
Mayan, what are you looking forward to today?
I'll do my best because it's the first day of the month!
It's the first day of the month, so I'll do my best!
Today's clothes are also cute!
Mayan's hair is short today!
Actually, my hair is short!
You're lying!
I won't be fooled!
I'm a chatty bob today!
Good smell!
Good luck today!
What is this project?
Today is Nogikoko!
Nogikoko's...
Infiltration!
It's an infiltration!
It's an infiltration investigation!
Bye bye!
Thank you for your hard work!
Nanami!
This is my wife, Nanami!
Good morning!
How do you feel today?
I'm in a good mood!
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
It's a little push camera!
It's up!
Yeah!
It's nice!
It's cute!
I found Kawago P!
Kawago P is here!
Bye bye!
I haven't finished my makeup yet!
You haven't finished your makeup yet?
Even if you haven't finished your makeup, it's cute!
You're lying!
I'm in a good mood!
Thank you for your hard work!
Next to me is Kazumi!
Kazumi!
What I want you to see today is Ichigo-chan's clothes!
That's right!
Please stand up!
It's cute!
Yeah!
It's too close to the camera!
Why is it so close?
It's okay!
I don't know!
Good luck today!
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
Kazumi is in a good mood today!
I'm in a good mood!
That's why!
Today is amazing!
It's amazing!
Positive!
Oh!
I got it!
Bye bye!
I'm looking at you!
Fish wink!
I got it!
Good morning!
Can I take a picture of you?
I came from the water!
Your heart!
I love you!
Yeah!
Who can tell me the fashion point of today's clothes?
I was brought to the Gia today!
Thank you very much!
That's enough!
Wait a minute!
Good job!
Manatta!
Beautiful legs!
I'm a little tired!
What do you mean tired?
I'm tired!
Cut is the point!
That's nice!
Please don't look at my legs too much!
Why?
I'll zoom in!
I zoomed in!
I'm being stabbed by Buyo!
Manatta was stabbed by Buyo!
That's right!
It's a waste of beautiful legs!
Bye bye!
Wakatsuki!
Oh!
People of R's!
Wakatsuki!
It's a little dangerous today!
Yeah!
It's a dangerous feeling!
I'm wearing it!
I'm glad!
I was wearing it!
I was a little surprised!
Cute!
Akira is ahead of me!
What? Ikoma?
I'm sure!
The boy was a little late!
I was late!
Boy!
Ikoma is here too!
Don't drink it!
Cute!
Yes!
Everyone!
It looks fun last night!
It looks fun!
Then from now on!
I would like to see the members going to the handshake meeting!
Yeah!
Now, the first one who is on standby is!
Duren!
It's Nacchan!
I'm the only one!
Nacchan is the first!
Everyone is late!
Yeah!
Today is cute!
Oh!
From today!
You are from Osaka!
I'm from Kyoto!
Huh?
Kyoto?
I'm from Kyoto, but I'm from Osaka.
Oh!
I don't know a little bit!
I know!
Do you know?
OK!
It's a great hairstyle!
Yeah!
It's like braids!
What is this?
It's the same hairstyle as the character Kirigiri- san
in the anime, Danganronpa!
Oh!
Nacchan likes anime!
Yeah!
Everyone is here!
Everyone is coming!
Everyone!
It's a handshake meeting from now on!
Yeah!
What's your enthusiasm?
Like Maya!
What? What? What?
I'm going to be good at it now!
Oh!
Maya!
Thank you!
Thank you for praising me!
Maya!
Like Maya!
I'm going to be good at it!
What?
Then I'll cut Reika's part!
Why?
That Maya!
That Maya is good at it!
I'm in trouble!
No comment!
Oh!
It's just to concentrate!
Maya!
Do you have a handshake meeting tomorrow?
Yeah!
That's it!
How about Kanarin?
Uh, I'm looking forward to it!
I know!
You're like Maya, and you're enjoying it!
Oh!
Thank you!
Well, I've been to Kanarin's handshake meeting once.
Uh!
Do it again!
Congratulations!
That's good!
You're going to be good at it!
I'm going to move now!
Good luck!
Bye!
Yukata is wearing it!
It's cute!
The season is different.
That's true.
I bought this today.
It's August for me.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye! Good luck!
Bye bye!
Iku-chan is still here!
You are late!
I'm not late!
Good luck!
Bye bye!
Now we are going to start the event!
I'm going to infiltrate as a cameraman!
I'll do my best!
Let's go to the goods section!
Goods section!
Everyone's goods are on sale!
Oh, Nogizaka Towel!
You can't drop it!
Yes!
I'll do my best!
It's dangerous if you drop it!
I want it!
Towel!
T-shirt!
Bag!
Clear file!
There are a lot!
The movie version of Bad Boys J is coming soon!
Please look at Naramin's Getsuke!
I'm going to talk to Nikisei!
Yay! Oh, you're eating!
Yay!
How is it?
Is the food good?
It's good!
It's good?
You're always taking care of me!
You look like you're enjoying it!
Thank you!
How is it?
Are you going to do a handshake after this?
I'm going to do a handshake!
I want to have fun!
How is it?
It's my first time eating Twintail.
It's your first time eating Twintail.
So...
I want to do my best!
You want to do your best because it's Twintail!
I don't know what you're talking about, but...
I don't know what you're talking about, but do your best!
I ate croquette, too.
Did you eat croquette?
Is she natural?
She's natural.
How about you, Mai?
It's hard to meet you all today.
I want to have fun!
Mai has changed into a camera!
But I don't know what to talk about when I'm on camera.
Please tell us what you're going to say today.
What I'm going to say today is...
Please look at my eyes!
What's wrong?
It's a monomaniac.
What a shame!
Please take a look at my eyes!
It's rare!
It's beautiful!
Beautiful?
Beautiful!
Is this a bad place to take a picture?
I'm a middle school student!
It's a bad place!
Is the camera a good place to take a picture?
No, no, no, no, no.
Look at my eyes!
I got a middle school student shot.
Yay!
It's so good!
We're done with the first part.
Now we're going to take a break.
Let's go!
Now it's Mai Mai's turn.
Hello, Mai Mai!
Good morning!
How is it?
It's delicious!
What are you eating?
I'm eating fish, beef suji croquette, consomme soup and salad.
It's good.
You're eating fish, meat and salad.
That's right.
I ate carrots that I don't like.
You can't eat carrots?
I don't like carrots.
That's surprising.
What about you, Maya?
I can eat them.
You can? What do you hate?
Broccoli.
You can eat broccoli.
That's right.
I'm 22 years old.
What about you, Sayulee?
I don't have anything I hate.
But you always eat anything, right?
I eat anything.
21 years old!
Stop it!
Don't exaggerate.
That's right.
I'm 13 years old.
You're a real beauty.
What's wrong?
I got a compliment.
You got a compliment.
Thank you.
Your flowers are cute today.
You wear them often, right?
I wear them every time for our individual handshake.
You do?
That's right.
Good luck!
How was the handshake event?
It was fun.
How was it?
There weren't many people who overslept today.
There are a lot of people who overslept today.
That's right.
I overslept.
You overslept today.
I wanted you to wake me up earlier.
I'm always ready.
I wake up at the last minute.
It takes hours for you to wake up.
I can't wake up that early.
I can wake up 3 hours earlier.
It takes a lot of time for me to get ready.
Is it that long?
What are you doing?
I'm getting my bangs done.
That's important.
I have to dye my hair again.
My bangs don't change no matter how many times I do it.
Does it change?
You're cute from now on.
Thank you very much.
Are you done with Twintail?
I'm not making Twintail.
I'm making a flower.
Are you making a flower?
I'm going to see the finished product later.
I don't want to.
Why not?
I won't show you.
I'm going to see Twintail.
OK.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
There's still time.
Why are you so embarrassed?
I hate cameras.
Why?
Let's take a picture together.
Why do you hate cameras?
I don't think it's good.
I took a picture with Maya.
Let's take a picture together.
Don't be shy.
Maya, be shy.
Are you in the picture?
Can I go?
I'll take a picture.
You're bad at it.
You're wrong.
It's a video.
I'm not a character.
Close, close, close, close.
Okay, then.
Ranze, take it.
Bye bye.
Good luck.
I'll give it to Kawago P.
Maaya has to go to Nibu.
Good luck.
I'll leave it to Hina.
I'll have it.
Please.
Good luck.
Bye bye.
I'm Kawago Hina.
Maaya went to the handshake event.
I'll take over and turn the camera.
Please.
Nogikoko.
Recently, I was on the show.
I'm Kawago.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
There are a lot of goods here.
Choose what to buy here.
I'm selling a lot.
What should I buy?
What should I do?
Goods.
There are a lot of goods.
What should I do?
What should I buy?
Bad boy.
What should I do?
Key holder.
Key holder. What should I do?
This is the official Nogizaka goods I bought earlier.
I bought a key holder that I like very much.
I think I'll put this on my cell phone or Mac.
I always carry it with me.
And...
It's a goddess key holder.
I bought a KANBATCHI from YAN.
And I'm sorry, but I bought my own.
I'm sorry.
I can't buy it myself, but I bought it.
And the problem is here.
It's a random live photo, so I don't know who will win.
This time, it's a theme of a literary girl.
Then I would like to open it.
First of all, Mei-chan and Hime-tan.
Bakaribon, this is also a stable bakaribon.
Next, Reika.
She is a captain.
She is beautiful, very beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Hinachiman.
Cute.
This looks good on her.
This serious feeling looks good on her.
Then, Ikuchan.
Ikuchan.
Does it really smell? cute!
cute!
What's next?
Mayer! I love Mayer!
cute!
Mayan!
Unfortunately, I didn't win if Fuka was good.
But I really like Mayan.
I'm very happy.
Everyone is cute!
I really want to go to the handshake event more and more.
I'm sure the people who are watching will want to buy
goods at the handshake event.
Please come.
It's so cute.
I'm going down now.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going down and reporting.
I'm going.
5 minutes.
Okay.
I'm going.
Nene-chan!
You're so cute, Nene-chan!
I'm wearing a yukata!
You're so cute!
Nene is wearing an overcoat!
Thank you!
Look at me!
Chii-chan!
Chii-chan is shy!
Before I go to bed, my character has been following me
lately, so I'm probably enjoying my days.
Bye-bye!
Ami Ami is here!
Ami is a beautiful girl.
I always forget about her, but she's cute.
Oh, look over here!
Ami Tamu!
Ami Tamu is cute!
Nene-chan!
She is so cute! What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do?
What should I do? She is so cute!
Mouth information.
I recently got along with Na-chan.
I always get nervous when I talk to Na-chan.
Recently, the distance between us has been shortened.
I think so.
Nanami!
I love you, Nanami!
You are so cute!
She is my wife.
The last one is Mayan.
Recently, I have been trying to find Mayan's weakness.
She is waiting for me.
She is looking for Mayan.
It's over.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
So while looking at it like this,
I feel like I'm being treated like this.
I learned a lot.
Yeah, I learned a lot.
Next week, we're going sightseeing in Kyoto!
Let's go!
I want to eat a lot of delicious food!
So please look forward to it!
See you next week!
Bye bye!
See you soon!
Thank you so much!
It was so much fun!