AISubs
Why?
Fight! Fight!
It's so hard!
I feel sorry for them.
Next is 105cm.
I'm not good at it.
I'll do my best.
You'll do your best.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
It's 105cm.
Can Marika Ito jump?
Let's go.
It's a 105cm challenge.
Good job, Marika!
Wow, amazing!
Well then, I'd like to challenge Misa!
Ready, set, go!
Amazing!
She's pretty good!
She's got a lot of room!
Wow, it's a new one!
It was cool!
It's a missile, right?
Missile?
It's a new one.
Ah, missile.
Ah, I see.
Next is...
Mahiro?
That's right.
I'm going to challenge Kawamura Mahiro's 105cm.
Ready...
Ah...
Oh!
Wow, I did it!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Yeah!
Congratulations!
I hope I can jump like this.
Next is Hime-tan.
I wonder if she's going to jump in that cool way again.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, it's Hime-tan's 105cm challenge.
Ready, go!
Wow!
So close!
It's so high!
Hime-chan, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Hime-chan, calm down.
Hime-chan, you can do it.
This is Hime-chan's second attempt.
Ready...
Hime-chan, you can do it.
Hime-chan has fallen.
I'm satisfied that I was able to jump 100 cm.
What was the reason why you couldn't jump that high?
I don't know the reason.
She was the most professional among the members.
Really?
Why couldn't you jump?
I also wanted to jump 100 cm.
You can't give up that easily.
I can't do it.
Let's do our best in the next competition.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Next is the 105cm challenge of Hinachima.
Ready...
This way?
Hina-chima, what's your way of jumping?
It's like swimming.
I can't say anything.
This is impossible.
Hina-chima, this is your second try.
Ready, set, go!
I succeeded in sex.
Higuchi, what did you try to do?
What did Higuchi try to do?
I was thinking about what to do.
No, no, no.
No, why did you try to go to the back?
Come back, come back, come on.
You know, this was impossible, so I thought I'd jump to the back.
For the first time in my life.
For the first time in your life here.
It was impossible.
Because it was amazing.
I threw everything away.
Really?
I couldn't do it.
Next is...
I think I'll stay until the end.
I think I'll stay until the end too.
The difference in the length of your legs is amazing.
This is Setsuko's 105cm challenge.
Ready...
Setsuko's 105cm challenge
The only remaining member hasn't rolled yet.
Really?
Everyone was desperately rolling.
Only Setsu was rolling.
Please look forward to it.
It's too easy.
It's cool.
Setsu is too easy.
I don't want to say it's cool.
Next is tomato.
I'm worried about tomato.
She hasn't rolled yet.
It's okay if she doesn't roll.
She can't roll.
It's a challenge of 105 cm of tomato.
Ready, go!
Seriously, what should I do?
I don't have energy.
Please look forward to it.
What should I do?
Do your best!
What is it?
Please look forward to it.
You are so cool.
It was cool, wasn't it?
Why don't you roll?
It was cool.
I was surprised.
I thought it was over.
It was amazing.
The result was good.
Next is Maya.
Maya's challenge of 105 cm.
Ready, go!
You touched it with your hand, didn't you?
It would have been better if I didn't touch it with my hand.
Please look forward to it.
Maaya, you can do it without your hands.
This is Maaya's second try at 105 cm.
Ready...
Oh my god!
That's amazing!
Maaya, you did it!
I did it!
You did it!
Wow, amazing!
It's like this, but it's quite high.
It's over 105 cm now.
It's so high!
What?
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Oh my god!
What?
Eh? Why?
Eh? Zero! Zero! Zero!
ZATSURAKUSHA ZERO!
Wow!
The level of ZATSURAKUSHA ZERO has increased!
Next is 115cm.
The average age from 16 to 18 is 110cm.
So, all the members here are over 110cm.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ito Marika's 115cm challenge.
Ready!
She's so close!
But I think I can do it next time.
You can do it!
I'm sure I can do it next time.
Even though her body is so flexible.
My way of jumping is so hard that my butt is already on
the ground.
I have to change my way of jumping.
Marika, you can still do it!
I think you'll be okay on the second try.
You can do it!
I have to watch her.
I have to protect her.
This is the second challenge of Ito Marika.
The third challenge of Ito Marika.
Marika, you must be frustrated.
Good job.
Good luck.
Marika, come here.
115 cm.
Come here.
She can't jump.
This is the only thing I can do.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
Everyone was in good condition today.
That's right.
She is very obedient.
The next challenger is Misa Eto, but she is the coolest
among the members.
Misa, do your best!
Misa's challenge is 115 cm.
Wow!
That was amazing!
I don't need the gravure pose!
Thank you very much!
Amazing!
It's not shaking at all!
If you participate in a competition...
How is it?
Can I apply?
I can participate in a competition.
Good luck, Mahiro!
This is Mahiro Kawamura's 115cm challenge!
Ready...
I'm so frustrated!
I'll do my best one more time.
This is the second challenge.
Ready!
The third challenge
The fourth challenge
Thank you very much.
Mahiro, come here.
Mahiro, how do you feel now?
I'm so frustrated.
Setsuko is going to challenge.
This is the first challenge.
Setsuko is going to challenge 115cm.
Ready, go!
She did it!
Amazing!
You did it in one go!
I'd like to be called a master.
You were so close.
Thank you.
I'm ready.
You can do it, right?
Let's start the first challenge.
Let's go!
You can do it, right?
The bangs! The bangs of Inochi's life!
I'm a woman now.
I'd like to pay attention to the next way of jumping.
I don't like it if it looks very manly.
I'd like to see it.
This is the second tomato challenge.
It's a butt, isn't it?
It's a butt.
Lightly.
It's a shame.
But I did my best.
I did my best.
I did my best. I was a woman.
I was a woman.
Tomato.
Are you okay?
I fell off.
I have a little pain in my back from the
Are you okay?
Yeah.
But I did my best.
You did a great job.
I didn't think you'd be able to fly like this.
I thought I'd fall off the tomato right away.
I did my best.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much!
Next is Maya's challenge.
I want Maya to jump, too.
Maya's 115cm challenge.
Ready, go!
Don't break it, Maya!
Maya, don't break it!
Maya!
Maya, one last time!
One last time?
That's right!
Maya's second challenge!
Ready, go!
Maya's third challenge!
It's really delicious.
Maya still has a long way to go.
It's a shame.
The stick fell off.
If the stick falls off, it's no good.
I'll do my best next time.
But Maya is amazing.
Because she's young.
It's not good to be young.
Tantan is only 5 years old.
The camera isn't looking at me.
It's terrible.
Please hug me.
I want to decide on the first try.
You can do it!
You did it!
We have to decide on Yutaka.
That's right.
Misa-senpai, you can do it.
Please do your best.
120cm.
It's Misa's challenge.
Ready!
You can do it!
Misa-senpai, you can do it!
I think it's better to be a professional player.
I think it's a fairy.
I'm aiming for this.
Olympic?
I'm going to take a break and aim for the Olympics.
That's okay.
Idol vs. Olympic player
Great! Thank you very much.
This is a new star.
That's enough.
Do you want to go to the Rikujoka house?
Don't just do your best.
Isn't that crazy? You can still fly, can't you?
It's still like this.
The next challenge is Miyazawa Seira.
If you fail, you'll be second place.
That's right.
But I want to get to second place.
I can get points, too.
What?
That's not true.
In a high place.
It's Setsuko's 120cm challenge.
Ready.
You can do it!
How's it going?
Just a little bit more!
You're hitting the bar!
Your back?
Your butt?
You can do it!
This is the last one.
This is the real final.
You can do it!
This is my second try.
Ready?
You can do it!
I'm scared.
I can do it!
Wow!
Kawaii!
Just a little bit more!
So, the winner is Misa!
Congratulations, Misa!
You did it!
You're the winner!
Thank you!
You won the first prize!
Congratulations, Misa!
Thank you!
What's the next activity?
Sit-ups!
Do you guys know what this is?
We will do the abs exercise.
Everyone will do the abs exercise at the same pace as the signal.
If you can't keep up with the pace, you will fall.
What?
No, you can't.
We will do it with the survival awareness.
If you can do more than 30 times, you will increase the pace.
What?
If you can't keep up with the pace, you will fall.
We will do it in three groups.
Let's start with Team A!
Ready, set, go!
My stomach hurts a little.
It's hard.
Everyone is amazing.
20.
Good luck.
21.
I have a stomachache.
22.
Good luck.
23.
24.
I can't believe it.
25.
Who's the old man?
I heard it.
28.
29.
Isn't it crazy? It's going to be 30 times.
I'm going to speed up from here.
31.
32.
Mari is not following.
Mari is out.
Let's go.
What? No way.
It's still going on.
This is bad.
Someone.
I can't put my strength into it.
Everyone, do your best.
Hina is out.
Wait, Rena is out as well.
Everyone is out.
Misa and Rottie are in a battle.
Rottie is relaxed.
Misa is a little behind.
Misa is out.
The winner of Team A is Kamuran Mahiro.
Please record it as it is.
My neck hurts more.
90 seconds
I'm still smiling.
It's amazing.
Don't let go of my hand.
I'm feeling sorry for him.
I feel sorry for him.
He is bullying me.
Mahiro.
I feel sorry for him.
Mahiro, hang in there.
I'm scared!
I love you.
I did my best.
The result of the A team is...
The 3rd place is Marika Ito.
The 4th place is Hina Kawago.
I'm scared.
The 3rd place is 41 times.
The 2nd place is 46 times.
The 1st place is 122 times.
Thank you.
I did my best.
I don't know the dimension of 122.
Yuttan, Misa is 46.
Did you touch 46?
Yes, I did.
It's a little different.