AISubs
The next day...
Go for it!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ready...
Go!
Wait!
Go for it!
Sit-up Challenge
Now, it's time for the sit-up challenge of Team B!
Ready...
Start!
Yutan!
Yutan, you are so funny!
Yutan is laughing at me!
Yutan is eliminated!
No way!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Yuta, what's wrong?
Yuta, you're alone.
I can't do it.
It's too close.
Yuta, don't do that.
Don't mess with my face.
This is funny.
Help me.
Yuta.
The rest of the four are a little relaxed, aren't they?
You're in the way.
What are you doing?
Ami, hang in there.
You can still do it.
The 20th time.
Yuta is in the way of everyone.
I'm a coach.
What kind of coach?
Use your abs more.
Is that all you can do?
Yuta, hang in there.
You're in the way.
It's already the 30th time, so I'm going to speed up.
Hang in there.
Asuka! Asuka! It's Asuka! It's painful!
Why? Why?
Ami-san! Ami-san, your voice is hoarse!
Ami, Ami, your pace is...
Ami!
Go for it!
All three of you, keep up with the pace!
Chiharu!
Chiharu, your face is dead!
Go for it!
Hime-chan, your legs!
Ah, the young lady fell down!
Now it's Chiharu and Hime-chan's turn.
Hime-chan looks so relaxed.
I'm not relaxed!
You're not relaxed!
Oh, it's the 50th time!
Listen! Pollen-like people stop flowering!
I'm already full! I'm going to have trouble breathing!
keep it up!
Match the pace with the two!
Decided! Falling out!
Good luck, Chi-chan!
I'll do my best!
Good luck!
Kihiro Kihiro Kihiro
What?
She's trying to get a good score
Good luck!
70!
Chii-chan got 70
The high score is
Let's go over 123
What?
She's trying to get a good score
90!
Go for it, Kana-san!
You're right.
She's really good at this.
Go for it, Chii-chan!
Everyone, cheer for Chiharu!
Go for it!
99!
100!
100?
She's 23 years old!
You can do it!
It's spinning!
Chiharu, it's spinning!
Is this okay?
It's spinning!
My heart...
You can do it!
Go for it! Go for it!
What? Something started.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26,
So, let's announce the results of Team B!
The 3rd place is Saito Yuri!
Yay!
Saito Yuri was in the way, so I think it's okay to write 0.
Saito Asuka, 33 times!
Huh?
That's quite a lot.
Right?
Saito Asuka, 34 times!
And Hime-tan, 56 times!
And the best, Chiharu, 129 times!
You just passed Mahiro's 122 times.
I'm so frustrated!
Mahiro!
Let's move on to the C-tube!
Please look forward to the next episode!
Now, the highest number of times is 129 times, so
please do your best so that you can overcome this.
Let's do it together!
Maya, you can do it!
Maya is out!
I know how you feel.
I know how you feel, Maya.
Maya, I know how you feel.
Are you tired?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
Good luck!
The tomato is doing a fence zone, so do your best.
Really?
The tempo is different.
Look around you.
Next to you.
Fast, fast.
I'm looking at you.
It's not easy.
My head hurts.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
I'm scared.
I won't lose.
I'm doing it.
Oh, I feel like my pace is going down a little.
30! I went to 30, so I'm going to speed up.
Oh, I don't want to do it anymore.
It's hard!
I don't want to do it anymore.
Isn't it Hinachima?
This is amazing.
I don't know.
I'm tired.
Everyone, let's do it together.
Tomato is down.
It hurts.
A woman's fight of will.
A woman's will.
Seikun and Hinachima are fighting now, but who will win?
I don't want to.
I had enough energy.
Wait a minute.
Seikun is down.
Why?
Hinachima is first.
The C team is over.
Good work.
The result is out.
How was it?
It hurts.
It's hard.
You can speak louder.
Let's see the result.
5th place.
Eto, Misa, Hatanaka, Seira.
46th place.
2nd place.
3rd place.
4th place, Hina Hibuchi, 53rd place.
Congratulations!
3rd place, Hina Hibuchi, 53rd place.
2nd place, Nakamoto Hibuka, 56th place.
2nd place, Kawamura Ohira, 122nd place.
Next, 1st place, Harui Saito, 129th place.
Congratulations.
Do you practice at home, Harui?
No, not at all.
It's been six years.
I haven't done it recently, so I thought it was dangerous.
But Chi-chan's wasn't that good.
It's easier to do than I thought.
After making a record of Makiro, I started to revive again.
Did you enter the room?
Yes, I entered the room.
Then, I would like to announce the overall ranking of
the two items so far.
Mahiro got 3 points in the first round and 4 points in
the second round.
So far, Mahiro got the first place.
And the second place is...
MisaMisa got the second place.
Chiharu got the third place.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Don't give up.
There's a big change in the final round.
Everyone, let's do our best until the end.
I'd like to move on to the final event.
The last event is Beach Rock.
I like Beach Rock.
We're going to have a one-on-one tournament this week.
The best eight got one point.
Fourth place got three points.
Third place got five points.
Second place got seven points.
And the winner is...
10 points!
Let's check the ranking with the whiteboard.
The first place is Rotti.
With this, you might be able to turn the tables.
So all the points up to now have nothing to do with it.
The second place is Rotti.
With this, you might be able to turn the tables.
So all the points up to now have nothing to do with it.
Who is confident?
Me!
I love it!
I've never done it before.
I've done it once in a gym class.
What?
That's so bad!
Why did you ask that?
First, let's decide the tournament.
There is a number here.
Let's draw in order.
Let's start with Renarin.
I'll be the one to stick this.
I'm scared.
There is a seed ticket for the 15th place.
The person who draws this is a winner.
I'll be the 15th place.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21,
I didn't see it.
You didn't see it.
I saw it.
I didn't see it.
Well, it's a luck.
Thank you very much.
Nene is number 25.
It's nice.
We are having fun.
It's a shame.
I'm with Kuchii.
I'm with Nara.
What number are you?
I'm with Ruki.
If I can, number 4 is good.
I think so.
I think I can.
Number 13.
I don't know yet.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
Number 8.
Nene said that.
So I got it.
That's right, let's play Maaya.
Let's play Maaya.
I don't know what number I'll get.
But 14th is out.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
There's only one left.
Maya, Maya, Maya, Maya.
I don't know yet.
14th.
Wow!
Wow 14th is amazing.
Wow 14th.
That's all.
The tournament is like this.
Remember this, everyone.
So, let's roll the beach flag!
I'll do my best!
Let's start the first round!
First of all, Yuttan vs Chiharu!
Please show us your enthusiasm!
Enthusiasm?
It's impossible!
What should I do?
First of all, I don't want to lose.
My heart is beating so fast right now.
I'm most nervous about this game.
I was checking my heart earlier.
I don't know where Chiharu's heart is.
It's alive.
I don't know.
Let's do our best!
I want to run.
I'm looking forward to it.
Get ready!
I did it!
Yuta won!
Amazing, Yuta! You got it!
It was fun!
Yuta was simply having fun!
I'm so frustrated. What should I do?
I was in 3rd place!
10 points?
It was fun!
I'm so frustrated!
But it was fun.
We're in third place, so we don't know yet.
Is that so?
It's a match between Ashurin and Seitan!
I'll do my best!
I don't want to lose to Seitan.
I think I can beat an adult.
But Seitan seems to be slow.
Seitan, you said it yourself.
Let's do our best.
I won't let you win.
No, I'm scared.
Ready, set, go!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm going!
I'm going, I'm going!
Why did you say that?
I'm too nervous.
Oh no, I really forgot.
Ready, set, go!
You did it!
You're so fast!
I don't know why Asuka is so good at this.
I don't know either.
Asuka, why did you do that?
I don't lose to Asuka.
Congratulations.
Next is Hinachima and Mari.
I heard that Mari is fast.
It's not a rumor, it's true.
I'll do my best.
Do you have a strategy?
I have to win at the speed of my feet.
I'll chase you.
I'll give you a spurt at the end.
I'm scared.
It seems that the preparation is ready.
Higuchi, Hinata, Ito, Marika.
Let's go!
Which one?
Wow!
Yay!
Hina-chan just put out her hand.
Marika!
I'm sorry!
Well, I did it.
That's why it was good.
I think everyone saw it.
I don't know what happened.
It's a little bad, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hina-pyon?
I don't know.
Surprisingly, I was able to cast a spell.
I may fall.
I may be taken by the power of potatoes.
Let's do our best.
That's right.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Now that we're ready, let's go to the fourth match.
Kawago Hina vs Yamato Rina.
Ready.
Go.
Yamato Rina vs Kawago Hina.
I'm sorry, I was too serious.
Tomoto's way of falling was brilliant.
Her hair was all over here.
Congratulations, Tomoto!
You know, we're all getting old.
I've never seen Kawago's desperate face.
But I can't see Hina-chan's running as if she's running
seriously.
I can't see it at all.
That's right. She's running like this.
She's running like this.
It's a girl's run.
I thought I'd be able to do it, so I thought I'd be
able to do it, so I thought I'd be able to do it, so I
thought I'd be able to do it.
No, it was a beautiful run.
It was hard to live.
I think I'm getting older.
The 5th match is the battle between the 1st Kawamura
Hiroto and the 4th Miyazawa Seira.
This is amazing.
And you two are close friends, so I wonder what kind of
match it will be.
You said it.
We play a lot in private.
That's right.
How are you feeling?
The most important thing is to have fun.
Winning here is the most important thing.
That's right.
What should we do?
We're close friends, but...
Let's do our best.
It seems that the preparation is ready.
The 5th match is the battle between the Kawamura Hiroto
and the Miyazawa Seira.
Ready, set, go!
Not again!
Rocky won!
Vacuum!
At first...
Ah...
Sessan was...
She stumbled.
Sessan didn't say anything.
She didn't say anything.
She stumbled.
I was like, oh my.
From there, Mahiro...
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Nice.
I hid it.
It's a friendship.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
The 6th match will be the match between Hime Nakamoto
and Eto Misha. Let's listen to their enthusiasm.
Hime-tan, your eyes change when you start running.
Eh, is that so?
I'm doing it seriously, but it's not like that.
Don't say that.
You say you can't do it, but you're really fast.
I really can't do it.
Let's do our best.
I'm hiding my real ability.
I'm doing it seriously.
I'll do my best too.
This is an important match.
That's right.
But I'm older than you.
Age doesn't matter.
The 6th match will be the match between Hime Nakamoto
and Eto Misha.
Hime Nakamoto vs Eto Misha
You mean she teased you...?
It was funny!
I took it without jumping in.
And I think I saw something like a serious pose.
It was a senpai's relaxed win.
Did you run seriously?
I ran seriously.
No, I didn't see much.
No, I ran seriously.
But he was the last one to jump in.
At the mat over there, MisaMisa kept saying,
No, I'm going to win.
What? I was scared.
No, don't do that.
I'm scared.
I'm not scared at all.
Next, we'll go to the 7th match.
Nojo vs. Wadamaya.
Don't laugh.
This is kind of funny.
They're going to do something funny.
Stop it.
Can I do it?
We're serious.
We're going to sleep together the day after tomorrow.
But we're rivals now.
We're fighting now.
I want everyone to have fun.
I want you to do that.
What are you talking about?
By the way, how are your legs?
I don't know.
But if you're serious, it should be fast.
If you look at the way you run, it might be like this.
The more serious you get, the weirder you run.
I'm serious about this.
Soon.
No, no, no.
Not soon.
I'm taking a dream.
Take a dream.
Now, the 7th match.
Nojo vs Wada.
Ready.
Wada wins.
It's hot, it's hot!
How was it?
It was super fun.
It's like...
It's really like...
I can't help it when I'm younger.
Everyone is like that.
I can't lose to you.
It was really easy.
I'm sorry. It was easy.
Thank you very much.
The first place is Mahiro Kawamura and the second place
is Misano Eto'o.
It's a duel between the two top players.
Ready?
Oh, it's a fly.
It's a fly.
Ready?
She completed it perfectly.
She's really good.