AISubs
Is it a bad thing to fall in love?
Let's dive into my hands
Lightly, always
I like anyone
Always together
Everyone is a treasure
Let's dive into my hands
Wow!
The event is held in the city of Tokyo.
The venue is bigger than anything.
The people in the back feel that we are far away.
They are worried about us.
This time, we will go out of the city.
I want many people to see my face.
What I want to say to my fans is to look at each and
every one of their faces.
And also, if I get eliminated in my singing part,
I would like to do something like a wink or a kiss.
Please pay attention to that.
Since the venue is so big,
at ZEPP LIVE, I was good at acrobatics.
But I couldn't do acrobatics.
Since Yoyogi is so big,
I've been given permission to do a lot of things.
So I think it would be nice if I could do it at my own timing.
Since it's so big,
I might not be able to see it because it's so small,
but I'll do my best to show my presence.
Since this is the last Yoyogi Live in Japan,
I'd like to do my special skill,
which is a weird face,
when the MC starts.
I'm going to do it now.
I'm going to do this during the live, so please remember it.
Here we go.
3, 2, 1.
This is a game where you have to make a square face.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
This time, at the Osaka concert of ZEPP TOUR,
I made a promise that I would wink once for each song.
But I completely forgot about it.
I'm going to wink as much as I can this time.
I'm going to wink once for each song.
Hi, I'm Hina Kawaguchi.
The highlight of the other members this time is
the deco pins of MY and MYMY that I like.
Both of them are so cute.
They gave me lessons during the rehearsal.
They were really cute, so I'm paying attention to them.
The highlight of this live is
the dance of the song from another planet.
I really like Kanari's dance.
It's really good.
Please pay attention to it.
But the highlight is MISAMISA.
Please watch it.
I want you to watch the melody of the song.
Please look forward to it.
I'm Marina Ikoma. I'm doing my best for the Yoyogi live.
I want you to see the other members.
It's a unit of five members of DECOPIN.
It's a unit of four members by accident.
The dance and the song are my personal favorites.
It's really cute and I think it's a highlight.
Please pay attention to that.
I'm Marika Uchou.
Everyone has their heads up and down.
I didn't think I'd be able to dance in such a big place.
I shouldn't talk about my anxiety, but even if I write
a note, it doesn't get into my head, so I'll try to
relax my brain a bit more.
Asuka is really young, but she's very confident, and I
think that's good.
So, you're checked!
That's good!
Bye bye!
I'll do my best, so watch me too!
This time, it's number one, right?
But I really can't decide.
All of them.
The reason is...
Until now, it was just dancing before, so there was a
certain choreography.
But this time, it's all crazy, so the formation and the
dance are a little different for each song.
Maybe it's a formation that can only be seen in the
first half of the show.
So I like all of them.
So I want you to pay attention to all of them.
My favorite song is...
I'm just saying it by chance.
There's a place I want you to see.
There's a free place for dancing.
And that's where...
I want you to see it, too.
I don't usually do idol-like gestures, but I'm going to
show you my free style.
Please watch it.
Why? Why? Why?
It's so embarrassing.
I didn't do it at all.
Did you get it?
Whether this is a two-point or a one-point or a wink,
it depends on the day.
That's how I feel right now.
My recommended song for the summer national tour final is...
A melody of spring. I can't go out this time, so please
let me dance here.
Can you hear me?
This is the toothbrushing core rhythm that I always do at night.
It contains the letters of the soiled waist.
I don't have it this time, but I want you to see it
again someday.
Recently, everyone has been brushing their teeth, so I
think everyone is getting pretty good at it, so it's a
sight to behold.
My favorite song from the setlist is Friday the 13th.
Well, I think I'd like to take a group photo here.
My point is that I dance a lot in the chorus.
I think I'm the one who dances the most.
I'm confident about that.
I'd like you to pay attention to that.
Here we go.
On Friday, the 13th, I'm going to give you my hand.
I'm going to give you my heart.
I'm going to give you my world.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ta-da!
That's it.
What do you think?
Ta-da!
I'm from Osaka.
My name is Mahiro Kawamura.
The rehearsal just ended.
My favorite song is...
Okami ni Kuchibue wo.
I'm going to dance.
It's a little embarrassing to do it alone, but it's like this.
Actually, I just laughed, but it's a cool song.
When I'm nervous, I stay at home.
My movements get smaller, so I'll do big movements in
front of a lot of people at the Yoyogi live.
I'm just a little bit, but I'd be happy if you could
see me grow up.
When I was given the zip last time, I didn't make any mistakes.
Now that it's Yoyogi, it's going to be a bigger stage.
I want to do my best so that I can meet a lot of people.
I'm Hori Miona.
I'm going to change the atmosphere of this live to suit
each song.
I want you to see my facial expressions and actions.
Thank you.
It's the first big Yoyogi live of Nogizaka46, and
Nikisei is going to be there, too.
I'm going to make the fans who came to see me think,
Oh, Nogizaka46 is good. Nikisei is good.
I'm doing my best in the lesson right now, so I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
I need a lot of energy and power.
But if I don't keep calm, I might make a mistake.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
It's my first time doing it in a big place.
I'd like to do my best so that I can meet a lot of
people on the first and second floors.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll do my best.
I usually do ZEPP.
But this time, it's a very big venue.
I often remember the position more than usual.
I'm having a hard time with that right now.
It's a test period right now.
I'm going to focus on the rehearsal and do my best.
I'm having a hard time.
I need to memorize a lot of things.
It's from another planet. I'm happy that you chose the unit song.
I've done it many times in the last Zepp live.
The content of the Yoyogi version has changed a lot.
There was only one stage for Zepp.
I could only show it there.
I think I can go here and there.
I'm going to surprise you all from another planet.
The number of the stage is up to 38.
It's usually 13 or 5.
It's written there, but it's 5.
There are a lot of numbers in the Yoyogi version.
I have to remember that.
I'm going to be far from the members.
I'm a little worried.
I'm full of anxiety.
I'll do my best.
I'm Asuka Saito.
I'm struggling with the rehearsal of the Yoyogi live.
The venue is too big.
I can't remember where to go out and where to change clothes.
It's over.
There are a lot of songs.
It's a big venue called Yoyogi.
It's great that there are people everywhere.
It's hard to remember everything.
It's very difficult to express myself during the rehearsal.
I'm not good at winking and kissing.
As you can see, I'm not good at it.
I'll do my best and challenge myself.
I'll be happy if the reaction comes back.
This is the first time I'm performing on a big stage.
I know the atmosphere of the venue.
I'm worried about my position.
The venue is small during the rehearsal.
I can only imagine it.
I'm worried about my position.
I'll do my best.
I'm getting a lot of work.
I'm looking forward to the day before the rehearsal,
and I'm a little worried.
Hello, I'm Inoue Sayuri.
The point that I want you to see here is that I'm
always fluffy, but from other planets, I want to show
you a little bit of dance, so I want you to see my cool
side as well.
Thank you.
Yes, I would like to fly a lot of beams at this live.
I'm waiting for the beam. Bye bye.
I'm Mai Fukagawa.
At this live, my goal is to make eye contact with everyone.
There are 360 degrees, which is very wide, but I really
run around to various places.
If you think that Fukagawa is watching, please wave your hand.
Thank you.
I think the feeling of the stage is different from when
I was in Japan, so even if I think it's a distant seat,
I think there are opportunities to see it closer, so
don't miss me.
What I want you to see at the live is the hair style of
the live. Recently, there is a hair style that is
popular with braids, so please take a look.
Yes, this time I'm going to make a peace, so I'm going
to raise my little finger at that time.
Please notice that.
Maya, shut up! Maya, shut up!
What?
I'm Maya Hoshino.
Well, I just finished the rehearsal of Yoyogi.
What I want you to see is that there is a part where I
sing with Hina-chan, so I want us to do something
together, so I want you to pay attention to that part.
Yes, I'm Mai Shirai. This is the first live performance
of Yoyogi, and the venue has become the largest, and
there are many different performances, but I think it's
fun to pay attention to that, and I think it's fun to
see everyone's various expressions.
It moves a lot from end to end, so I think it would be
nice if you could find out where Shirai is. I hope you
can see me with your own eyes.
Kaigan-sen wo basu wa susumu The bus goes along the coastline
The sky is high pressure
This is... Kore ga... This is...
Since it's the last summer,
Oh yeah!
The members of the club
Riding on the salty wind, the sound of the waves is
getting closer
I wrap a plastic towel around me
And change into a swimsuit in 10 seconds
Isn't it like we're showing off something?
1, 2, 3, 3, 2, 1
Girls fall in love in the middle of summer
And graduate
Girls fall in love with him
We always cry together
He makes us happy
Girls fall in love
We're going to have a live show soon
It's going to be a 360-degree view
I'll do my best to make it a live show that will make
you fall in love with the world of Nagizaka from start
to finish
Please come and play
I'm waiting for you