AISubs
Nagisakatte Koko is about to begin!
Here we are at Nogizaka!
This time, I, Ami Nojou, will sneak into the back of
the members with the camera in one hand.
And this time, the reason why I'm going to sneak into
the back of the members is because
I came to the practice room of the Nogizaka 46 national
tour in the middle of the summer.
So, I'd like to show you the back of the members who
can only be taken by the members.
Let's do our best!
So, let's go to the members' place!
Let's go!
Hello, I'm Nojiwami again.
Today, I went into the rehearsal room of ZEPP.
Everyone is very excited.
I'm sure I won't be able to enter this room.
I'm taking it easy now, but everyone is very serious
during rehearsals.
Everyone is doing their best.
Good morning!
How about you, Marika? Are you looking forward to the
live performance?
Yes!
Good luck with your skits.
I'm wearing a pinball perm today.
Marika is wearing a pinball perm today.
Ami recommended it to me, but I can't see the result.
50,000 yen!
I can't show my forehead.
Hide your forehead.
It's okay.
Aren't you sleepy?
No, I'm not sleepy.
Listen to me. This is makeup.
Me too.
I was told that I have to put on makeup at the fan meeting.
I can't do it, but I want to say it here.
When I appear on TV, I want to say to professional
makeup artists.
Ami!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
I got it very well.
The concert is coming soon.
Everyone.
How do you feel?
Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you really looking forward to it?
There's something I'm looking forward to.
For example, the content.
This get-up.
Get-up.
In the yukata.
I think it's amazing.
Really?
Chii-chan.
I'm just looking forward to it.
Please dance a lot.
Yes.
I'm just looking forward to it.
How about you?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's work.
Where?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's okay.
It's a little blurry.
It's not that bright.
That's good.
I'm wearing it today.
Today, too.
I'm wearing my new work.
Here.
My hands are shaking.
Don't say your hands are shaking.
I'm wearing this today.
I'll do my best.
Ami.
Se-chan's here.
Hinachiman is here, too.
Is it a log?
It's a log.
It's a live rehearsal.
That's the title.
I'll do my best.
I'm doing my best today, too.
You do your best, too.
I'll do my best.
It's raining.
I'll sweat a lot and dance today.
See you later.
Thank you.
Are you going to eat again?
Yes.
What are you holding?
I'm holding milk and milk.
It's raining.
Is milk and cookies one set?
It's definitely one set.
This is my full course.
It's gorgeous.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
I'll check the microphone.
Bye-bye.
The voice lesson is about to begin.
I'll go first.
Good luck.
Bye-bye.
I'll do my best.
You're good.
Everyone is working hard.
Everyone is working hard on their voice lessons.
I got it.
Sayu-chan!
Fuwa-tan!
You're not recording, are you?
I am!
What are you recording?
Tantan's camera
Sayu-chan
Sayu-tan
Fuwa-tan
Sayu-tan's rabbit pin
The one I always wear
Amitabha!
The one I always wear Amitabha!
I'm practicing.
I'm like Yutan-tan's camera now.
Yutan-tan's camera.
Yutan-tan, you don't show your face today.
Yeah, because I'm bare-faced.
Huh?
Yeah, Sayu-nyan is wearing it.
Because it's cold.
Wait, I'm doing the same thing as Nanase.
No, no.
It's because we're a break team.
Oh, yeah.
Wait.
I was surprised.
I wasn't looking at you like that.
You were cute.
I was surprised.
I can't see Maya.
Maya.
I was surprised.
Are you filming?
I'm filming a video.
If you take Maya after Hinachiman,
Maya is black.
Na-chan.
Sayu-nyan's camera.
Ami-san, Ami-san, I'm taking a picture of you.
Ami-san!
I'm in the middle of a voice lesson.
I'll do my best.
Ami-san! Ami-san, you're so cool!
I'm on my way to the next place.
I watched porn today.
What did you do when you woke up?
I watched porn.
I didn't go to the singing lesson.
Too bad.
But I did my best.
Really?
I did my best.
You did your best.
Let's do our best.
Tanyan is doing her best.
Roti is doing her best.
I'm Roti.
Like this.
You are very enthusiastic.
Roti is doing her best.
You are very energetic.
What are you wearing, Yusa-chan?
I'm Yusa-senpai.
Ami, you are amazing.
Me?
I think it's amazing that you record during the rehearsal.
Really? Thank you.
I'm a cameraman.
If there is anything you can do, please tell me.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Yusa-senpai.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Yeah.
Nana is doing her best with the microphone.
Yes, nothing.
Nothing.
Yes.
Nagashima-san.
It's Sari-chan's lip.
Don't listen.
It's Yusa-senpai's lip.
It's sexy.
Yusa-senpai.
I made you popular.
Sayulee is not losing.
Sayulee's lips.
No one can say that.
Wow.
You got a great picture.
Are you writing a note?
It's white.
I thought you were writing a note.
Because you look like a person with a face.
Yeah.
I love you.
I love you too.
What's next?
The white one.
Let's move on to the next one.
Then, turn your body to the back.
One, two, three, four.
This is my favorite face of Asuka.
Isn't it gross if I do it with my eyes covered?
My mouth.
I'll do my best.
I can't see anything.
The two of them are practicing dancing.
Oh, she noticed me.
I was going to continue, but I was approached because I
was being filmed.
As expected of an idol.
Right now, we're practicing for Under's song called
Tears of Sorrow.
Serialin is doing well today.
Ame-chan.
Ame said that my face is different today.
You look like an adult today.
Really? When I woke up this morning, my face was like
this. What do you mean?
It's okay.
Let's do our best at the concert.
Let's do our best.
Everyone, we're practicing for Under's song called
Tears of Sorrow.
You can really see it.
Do your best!
We're going to do a get-up practice.
What's this called? Towel?
I'm Chii-chan in charge of the cloth.
I'm Hinata in charge of the umbrella.
There's a bright red umbrella in the center.
Ami is in charge of the cloth.
Amitamu is also in charge of the cloth.
Maya is also in charge of the cloth.
Toma is also in charge of the cloth.
The umbrella is Renarin.
The umbrella looks good on you.
What about Amitamu?
Amitamu is in charge of the cloth.
Wow!
It's so powerful!
I felt the smell of history.
Thank you very much.
Ikoma-san, show me your beautiful face.
I was in charge of the cover.
Really? Did you do that?
I thought you were filming me when I was doing it.
Really? Then I'll see you later.
See you later.
Spins! Spins!
Yeah!
I exposed the spin.
It's almost over.
Only Ami's face is on the screen.
You're overreacting.
Yuri, Hinachima told me that I look terrible without makeup.
I'm sorry.
You look terrible without makeup.
My glasses are...
Please take a picture of me.
You look terrible without makeup.
Cut.
Misa is massaging Kawago.
Kawago is massaging Sayu-nyan.
Can I say something funny?
Mahiro is massaging Yuri.
Say something funny.
I always go to the student body, but the student body
member told me that I was a person who gets angry.
I was very sad.
But I was told to come once a week.
It's funny, isn't it?
If you're told that, you'll be in trouble.
Yuri looks comfortable.
Who is Hina?
They are completely off-mode.
You look good.
You have to come down.
How was Sayu-nyan? Was it good?
It was good.
Hina is popular.
You're good at massaging.
Hina was massaged by Rina.
Rina massaged me.
It's not a waste.
It hurts.
It doesn't hurt.
Let's change Mahiro.
Change.
Yuri is massaging Mahiro this time.
Everyone is working hard.
That's how hard they're working.
That's good.
It was a relaxing time.
So, the rehearsal for the national tour is over.
The concert is about to start, and the tour is about to start.
It's our first national tour, so we're going to go to
many places and eat a lot of delicious food.
That's all. I'm Ami Nojyo. Bye bye.