AISubs
Don't say such kind words
You're always so cool, you're not like yourself
You don't get along with anyone
If you're the loneliest in the world
So, here we are at Nogizaka.
I, Seira Nagashima, will be shooting the first episode.
This time, we're shooting with this member.
Please come over here.
It's raining.
The moment we got to the train station, it started raining.
She's a tomato candy lady.
Oh, no! I'm supposed to be sunny.
Why are we in Miyagi this time?
There is an event to celebrate the resumption of the
Great East Japan Earthquake.
I was chosen as one of the runners.
This time, we will run tomorrow, so we are here the day before.
Yes, we have finished the live shooting.
Then we will enjoy it a little, so we will go.
I will go.
Bye-bye.
Well, since I came to Sendai, I want to go to various places.
That's right.
I want to go too.
I bought it.
Wow.
Right?
There's something like this.
Let's see.
I'm hungry.
Gourmet?
Beef tongue?
There's a lot.
Are you famous for Rikyu?
I've been going to Rikyu.
Really?
Rikyu is the best.
I'm famous for Rikyu.
I was able to take a picture.
Is it in the middle of the two of us?
It's in the middle.
That's why I came here.
Rikyu!
What is this store like?
If you come here every time, you can come to Rikyu.
Is that so?
When I was in my hometown, I came here.
That's right.
Let's order some tomatoes.
Which one did you order?
Beef tongue,
and...
This one.
3 pieces of beef tongue.
I thought this was 5 pieces.
I thought so, too.
I was told that this is 3 pictures.
4 pieces of beef tongue.
That's right.
So we ordered 3 pictures with cute mini salads.
You can't see it, right?
Let's toast.
Let's toast with grapefruit juice and melon tea.
Cheers.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Let's eat.
It's amazing.
Look at this.
Please show it to them.
I'm so hungry.
How is it?
Let's see how it tastes.
How is it? Is it good?
Here it comes.
This is also what Kono-chan likes.
Can you see it?
This is beef tongue sushi.
Here it comes.
Yay!
Bon appetit.
I can't eat it.
You can eat it.
Is it good?
It's very juicy.
It's good.
I have never eaten such a thick beef tongue.
It's really delicious.
Rikyu is the best.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's a store that only recommends tomatoes.
It's time for the long-awaited night.
The beef tongue was very delicious.
Tomato, be quiet.
First of all, our...
First of all, let's start with our pajama check.
Let's start with Tomato's pajama.
Here we go.
Wait a minute.
Tadu Tadu
Oh, oh, oh.
You were wearing it.
Do you have a cat?
Tomato! What kind of pose is that?
A mountain tomato.
Don't you think you should stop being a tomato character?
How was it? Do you like it?
It's cute. Look.
Let's put it together.
No, no, no, wait. Introduce my pajama.
Please take it, Toma-tan.
Oh?
This is weird.
Hurry up!
I'll express it with this face.
Te!
So cute!
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's night, so I have a suggestion.
Let's go to bed.
What is it?
I don't know.
It's night time.
Let's go to the room together.
I've been thinking a lot.
Girls talk.
Girls talk without girls rules.
I want to do it.
Look.
Ta-da.
Great.
I made it like a lottery.
What is it?
Let's play a game.
I don't know how to do it.
I don't have a good sense of it.
First of all, let's do an impersonation.
Is there anything I can do?
Let's do an impersonation of the members.
Let's do it.
I think I can do it.
Let's do an impersonation of Kazumi.
Where are you going?
Oh my god!
Daaamn!
You look like Jimin.
Really?
Let's imitate Rina and Ayama.
Rina is good at imitating birds.
That's right.
You have to tighten your neck.
I'll try it.
Here we go.
I can't do it.
I'm 18 years old, Rina Yamato, and my special skill is
to close my neck and imitate a tiger.
Then I'll do it secretly.
So, let's move on to the next topic.
Nogidoko Nogikoko, a memory of when I first appeared on the show.
Did you get it?
No, I didn't.
First of all, Nogidoko.
Our first appearance.
Nogidoko Nogikoko
It's a touching story.
It's a recent story.
Why did I say something similar to Kimura?
You hesitated during the program, didn't you?
You really hesitated, didn't you?
Why did you say that there?
And the timing is bad.
Why?
The timing is bad.
It's like that.
No, it's not.
You know what?
It's like that.
The timing is bad.
When I go to the theater, I have to do the timing.
That's right.
I'm okay now, but I can't go to the theater in front of
the camera.
That's a problem.
I don't know.
What should I do?
I want you to calm down and talk to me.
I think everyone wants to know about this.
That's right.
I don't talk much, so I get asked a lot by my fans.
Is that so?
Is it a secret?
It's not a secret.
Please reveal it here.
My current goal is...
I want to go somewhere.
I often dance in the back.
Because of my height and back,
But my current goal is to dance in the front row.
I want to go to the front row.
In the front row?
Yes, in the front row.
My current goal is to dance in the front row.
It's easy, but I want to dance in the front row.
I don't have to think about many things.
I also want to stand in the front row.
That's right.
I want to work as an actress.
That's great.
I want to be a multi-talent who can be an actress in the future.
I'm very interested in acting.
You're good at acting.
I'm good at acting.
I want to be an actress in the future.
That's right.
I want to be an actress while I'm alive.
Is that so?
That's right.
I've worked part-time before.
Oh, you've worked part-time before?
I've never worked part-time before.
Oh, I see.
I want to take a picture like this when I take a
picture of other things.
I want to take a smooth picture.
I'll let you do it at home.
It's not a dream, but I want to go to Hawaii.
I want to go to Hawaii.
Don't you want to go to a bm shooting?
I want to go.
I want to go to Ghana.
There seems to be Maldives, too.
Maldives?
Oh, I see.
I want to go to Hawaii.
I want to see the sand of the sun.
The beach is covered with sand of the sun.
I want to go.
I want to travel abroad.
This is the last one.
This is...
I want to know everyone who is standing in front of the camera.
The ideal prince.
The last one.
The ideal father.
I like someone who can pull me.
For example, there is a manga called Hanayori Dango.
I like Uresama.
I like someone who can pull me.
I like someone who has a shadow.
Someone who seems to be thinking.
I like someone who seems to be thinking.
I like someone who looks like Koizora no Uta.
I like the uniform.
I want to wear the uniform at the handshake event.
I know.
If it's the uniform, I like the school uniform.
And the suit.
The suit is cool.
What do you want to be told by the ideal person?
There are a lot.
I want to be told I like you.
That's funny.
I want to be told Tina.
I want to be told I like you, Tina.
I want to be told I like you.
I've always avoided it and now I want to be told
Apostasis Shitaro.
I'm so happy!
I wonder what it is.
If you don't want to do it,
Nogimen-san,
everyone says it,
Kabedon.
If you don't want to do it,
That's crazy.
Kabedon.
I'm embarrassed to look at you.
I like you.
Like this.
Nagashima fat.
Kamedon was beaten.
Let's sleep.
It's early tomorrow morning.
Let's sleep on the futon.
3.6kg.
Good luck, Tomo-chan.
I'm cheering for you.
OK, let's do it.
Motomato, put on your arm pillow.
Put on your arm pillow.
Leave it to me.
Good night.
It's dark.
Don't touch anything weird.
I'm not touching anything.
Good night.
Good morning!
Finally, we came to the show.
How do you feel?
It's really fast.
I'm so excited.
Really?
You'll do your best to run.
I'll do my best.
I'm rooting for you.
Actually, I'm also a staff.
Look at this.
Wansho.
There's a wansho.
I'll wrap a towel around it and cheer you on.
I'll do my best.
It's about 300 meters from here.
Good luck, Tomo.
I'll follow you.
It's good to run.
Even at that pace, he told me to wave my arms, and I
just waved my arms and it got really fast.
When you're tired, you can wave your arms like this.
Wow!
Do you want to try again?
Yes!
I didn't think I'd be chosen as a representative of
Miyagi, so I was really surprised when I heard that.
I feel very close to Miyagi.
I was really happy.
My grandmother was the most affected by the quake.
I think it was about a week.
I couldn't use all the electricity.
I was reminded of how terrible the tsunami was.
That's right.
There is still a lot of work to be done, so I think
everyone's cooperation is necessary.
I hope that everyone will do their best to connect from
Aomori Prefecture.
My grandparents will come to see me, so I'll do my best to run.
I'll definitely make it to the finish line.
Are you scared?
It's okay. I'll do my best.
Can you move your back a little?
Sure. From now on?
I'll do it.
Okay.
Do your best.
5,4,3,2,1
Start!
Good luck, Tomoto!
5,4,3,2,1
I'm rooting for you.
Hang in there.
He's running forward.
You're going to be tasty.
It's going to be a lot of work to do the skating 16ive square.
Don't do that.
Please do your best.
How is it? Are you tired?
I'm tired.
Are you sweating?
It's a little hot.
Do your best.
There was an old man on the street.
A real old man?
Really?
It's so hot.
I see.
Good luck.
You're moving your legs.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Here you are.
Last one.
Good luck.
I am so happy.
Let's all go home.
It's over.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ladies and gentlemen, please give them a big round of applause!
Then let's receive the help.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help.
Please give a big round of applause.
Hello, I'm Rina Yamato from Nogizaka 46, from Miyagi Prefecture.
Thank you very much for letting me participate in the
reconstruction of the Great East Japan Earthquake
Reconstruction Event, which was held on the 2nd day of
the 1,000 km.
I also work in a group called Nogizaka 46 in Tokyo, and
I want to be a presence that can give a little energy
and courage to people in the Northeast through singing,
dancing, and performances.
So everyone, please continue to watch over me warmly.
Thank you very much for inviting me.
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Good work!
How was it?
It was good!
I was really nervous before the race.
To be honest, I was worried that I wouldn't be able to
run 3.6 km.
But thanks to the runners who ran with me,
and thanks to everyone on the track,
I was able to finish the race safely.
I was relieved.
I was there, but did you notice me?
I noticed you!
You were the first to notice me!
I heard a loud voice in the car.
I thought to myself, let's do my best!
Did I sound like a child?
You sounded like a child!
Really? Thank you!
I've been with you since the practice.
There were a lot of ups and downs, right?
Yes, there were.
So I thought maybe it was because of the practice.
There were a lot of ups and downs.
Yes, I'm glad.
You did a great job today!
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
Is that so?
Yes.
Okay, go ahead.
Itadakimasu.
Is it good?
Yeah! It's good!
I'm going to eat this too.
It's so good!
My eyes got bigger.
It's good, right?
It's sweet.
Tama-chan, please do a river walk.
Put it on properly.
Yeah, it's cute.
It's cute.
Please show me your face more.
It's cute. It's really cute.
You don't have it, do you?
It's really cute.
Toma-chan, are you being laughed at?
I'm being laughed at!
Don't say such a thing!
Okay, I'll do it.
Oh!
Lali-tan, go!
Show your face!
Oh!
So cute!
Wait, really?
What is it?
It's not that!
It's a rock!
It's so cute!
It's really cute!
It's so funny!
It's so cute!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
In the winter, it becomes a page of light.
Can I take a picture of it at night?
Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
Oh, there's something.
What is this?
Summer memories.
That's right.
Toma-chan is in the same pose.
Put your butt out more.
This way, this way, this way.
Oh, that's good.
Good, good.
It's so amazing!
It's fully loaded!
So, did you enjoy it?
Did you see it?
It was so much fun, wasn't it?
It was so much fun!
Today, we did it in Sendai for two days.
Please tell us how you felt.
I was really anxious.
I was really anxious about running.
But I was able to run safely thanks to everyone's support.
I was really happy.
I think it was thanks to everyone.
Really, thanks to everyone's support.
I was able to do my best.
I feel like I'm the parent.
I've never been with Tomoto for two days.
There's nothing like it's our first day together.
It was really fun.
I'm glad I was able to run with Tomoto.
I'm glad to hear that.
So, let's meet again!
Come to Sendai, everyone!
Bye bye!