AISubs
We are here at Nogizaka!
The second round has started!
Last time, we entered the Akshikai.
Yes, the individual Akshikai.
This time, we are going sightseeing in Kyoto!
We are not going sightseeing, we are going sightseeing!
Akshikai
By the way, there is a girl who always says that she
wants to go to school with me.
Is it Kyoto?
Yes!
Here comes the fake Kyoto people.
Stop it.
I'm sorry, Hina wanted to go too.
Yes, Hina wanted to go, but she can't go because of the
handshake event.
She can't go.
That's too bad.
She said she wanted to go forever.
What is the recommended food in Kyoto?
Yatsuhashi.
This is a little dangerous.
I'll get angry.
Why?
But Hina wanted to go too.
I wanted to go too.
But the handshake event is waiting for you.
Have fun.
Come here.
Good luck.
Bye bye.
Let's go.
We're going to rent a car.
We're going to take a taxi.
It's a big taxi for three people.
That's right.
We're going to take a VIP.
We're on the move.
Where are we going now?
Kiyomizudera.
There's a bridge called Gojo Bridge.
Gojo?
What's famous?
Eight bridges.
Bravo.
Why?
I'm your senior.
You have to give me a different answer.
I know.
I don't expect anything interesting.
It's Gojo Bridge, isn't it?
Say it.
Gojo?
Gobo?
What?
It's where Renkei and someone fight.
Yes.
That's where they fought last night.
I think it's where they fought last night.
Is that the right answer?
You got it right!
I'm sorry, I just found out that I'm smart.
It's been a while since our last trip.
I'm so embarrassed that I have to hold the camera in this crowd.
And it's raining.
I know it's a bit embarrassing.
I'll do my best.
Look at this.
Wow, there's a lot.
I'll do my best to climb this.
Wait, there's soy milk and whipped cream.
Oh no!
Wait, Baben!
Baben! What should I do?
This is your first cake! Thank you!
It's good!
Let's eat!
It was a mistake to eat ice cream before it started.
I thought so.
My mouth is blocked and I can't do anything.
Here we are.
Look, Caesar is here.
This is not Okinawa.
No, this is Kyoto.
Let's take a picture together.
Hina looks beautiful from behind.
She looks beautiful, but how about looking back?
Why?
This is called looking back beauty.
I'm a double beauty.
Let's go up.
I want to go up.
This is the first step to commemorate.
Everyone, from the right foot.
We were cute just now.
It was really cute.
It was cute just now.
We have arrived.
Have we arrived?
Great!
But this is still a gate.
What is the real thing?
The real thing?
I can't see Kiyomizudera yet.
Look.
Jin Omon.
Jin Omon?
This is Niohmon.
Maya will not say what she can read.
I'm sure Maya will read it in the editing.
I will not.
This is the place I often see on TV.
I often see it on TV.
I'm the only adult, so I'm a little sad that the size
is different.
Thank you.
Middle school students are small.
I'm still a junior high school student.
Do you know this?
This is the one to lift.
I did it.
Do you want to do it together?
Let's do it.
If you lift it up, it will come out.
This is important.
There is something very good.
It's important.
Let's lift it up for the time being.
It's amazing.
Asuka can do it.
Asuka can lift it up.
Asuka is amazing.
There are various princesses in Tebasaki.
Do your best.
I think I can do this.
I can't lift this.
I can't do this.
I don't have a grip.
I can't lift this.
I don't think so.
I really can't lift this.
Is it difficult?
It is difficult.
I lifted it.
Asuka is amazing.
I'm sorry if I made a mistake.
I believe in you.
Do your best!
Next, the three of us are going to go buy some scents.
I told you before.
Scents.
Sounds good.
It's the first time we're doing it again.
That's right.
Scents.
Everyone wants a cute scents.
A cute scents.
I'd like to choose one.
Choose one.
We'll be arriving at the store soon.
Yeah.
I want one.
Let's choose together.
Let's choose.
We're going to choose.
Bye.
Please wait for us.
I bought a fan.
Are they the same?
Yes.
It's cute.
Isn't it nice?
The bag is also cute.
Yes.
They are all the same.
Isn't it cute?
It's pink and has butterflies.
It's cute.
I bought a girl's eye-catching one.
What about Asuka?
Asuka is a little small one.
The shape is cute.
It's cute.
It's like Asuka.
Yes, it's like Asuka.
It's cute.
It's nice.
You two are too fast.
Please look back.
It's beautiful.
We did it.
You look good today.
The city is very beautiful.
It's very beautiful.
I want you to take a lot of pictures.
Kyoto is very beautiful.
Yes.
Arabi mochi?
Matcha mochi.
I ate it before.
Please say ah.
It's delicious.
It's chewy.
It's very chewy.
It's delicious.
Can I eat it?
Thank you very much.
Everyone eats vinegar.
I eat it.
I eat Nogikoko.
Nogikoko is delicious.
It's really vinegar.
I'm hungry.
I eat lunch with everyone.
This is a tofu shop.
Yes, it's a tofu shop.
It's a tofu shop.
This is a tofu shop in Kyoto.
That's right.
The water is so clean.
That's right, Maya.
Do you know Maya?
Maya is quite famous.
I knew Maya a few hours ago.
Wow, amazing.
It smells really good.
It smells good.
It feels kind.
Wow!
Look!
Amazing!
This is amazing.
Beautiful.
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
I wonder if it's okay.
What?
I can't open the door.
Because now everyone is doing their best at the handshake event.
That's right.
We're enjoying it.
Let's enjoy it.
The handshake event is just coming back.
I can't go sightseeing.
It's indoors because it's inside the handshake event.
I've never been to Kyoto.
It's the first time in the world.
This is Koji-san's hot food.
Please enjoy it in the hot water.
This is tofu.
Please enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Tofu is ready.
Let's eat.
It smells good from the beginning.
It's a lot of food.
It's warm.
It's very delicious.
The miso on top is delicious.
I'm glad.
It's delicious.
Thank you for the food.
How do you eat this?
Oh, it's good!
I've never tried the real Tororo.
There's Tororo soba at the convenience store, right?
Tororo udon? Tororo soba?
I've only had Tororo soba.
It's different, isn't it?
Is it good?
I thought it was different from the real one. It's good!
It's jiggly. It's so jiggly.
It's like Hina's belly.
Oh, you're praising it.
Let's eat.
It's good.
It's really good.
How does it feel?
It looks good.
It's like warabi mochi.
Tofu is beautiful and shiny.
It smells good.
It smells like tofu.
Let's eat.
It has a strong taste of soy.
It's good without anything else.
It's good.
Pumpkin.
Do you like pumpkin?
I love it.
I don't like broccoli.
It's hot.
Be careful.
How do you feel?
Are you full?
I'm very full.
It was delicious.
The staff at the restaurant were kind.
They were kind.
Don't show your teeth.
Thank you.
They are kind.
Are you in the frame?
Maya is not in the frame.
Maya, you're in the frame.
I'm interested.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
It smells good.
Maya
It reminds me of HINACHI.
Maya is always in the frame.
Show me your cute face.
Don't close your eyes.
Is it dazzling?
I love this.
Is this a bracelet?
It's cute.
I will check your lucky seat for free.
What month and date do you have?
Let's start with ASUKA.
Let's start with KAWA.
I was born on March 22nd.
I remember your birthday.
Really? Thank you.
Do you know your zodiac sign?
I'm a tiger.
If you are a tiger,
what is your zodiac sign?
Is it the same?
I was born on August 10th.
I was born on April 23rd.
You are an idol.
I'm actually an idol.
We are the official rival of AKB48.
Please support us.
Please.
Do you appear on TV?
Just a little bit.
Everyone is modest.
You have a small face.
No.
Look at her face.
I'm a tiger.
I was born on March...
I am an idol.
The tiger is me.
We are not twins.
I enter the class on January 13th.
I'm small.
I don't have an adult mother.
I'll give birth to some young girls.
Is there any question to be asked?
I see.
I'm the main character.
The first SE or I'm cute!
Out of all of them,
Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy it.
So cute.
Look, there's a gum shop.
I like gum.
Gum shop?
So cute.
Let's go inside.
Put your hands together.
Please calm down.
It's cute. It looks like Kyoto.
It's beautiful.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's cute.
It's all cute.
Here comes the trouble.
No, I can't. I'll decide in 10 minutes.
I can't spend 10 minutes.
There was a mirror, so I'll fix my bangs.
One-micro unit.
I can't do it right now.
No, I can't.
You can't decide, Maya?
Hina is thinking about this one or that one.
Ah, Hina-ish, Hina-ish.
It's the same pattern.
Is it a little in the way?
Is it a little in the way, Maya-tan?
Maya-tan, is it a little in the way?
Ah, there's a girl.
It's true. I can't see.
It's close, it's close.
It's like Marika.
It's amazing.
Yellow is cute.
What is the meaning of Hanna-ri?
It's written on the wall.
Oh, sorry.
Maaya-san, don't look around.
The meaning of Hanna-ri is...
What?
Hanari is a word that expresses the state of being
gorgeous in the heavens and earth, yet unpretentious,
layered with elegance and preciousness, and ready to
perform.
Hanna-ri, in Kyoto, there is a variety of beautiful fabric.
Every time a product is imported, the pattern of the
fabric changes.
I don't want to use this part.
OK.
I bought it.
So fast.
Ta-da.
Everyone has their own taste.
Kawatan loves candy and lemon.
This pattern is the best.
Everyone has their own taste.
Maaya-san is like Maaya.
I bought a rabbit, so I made it a rabbit.
It's cute.
It's pink.
Asuka.
Asuka, strawberry?
Strawberry?
I like strawberry milk.
Please stop it.
Asuka loves strawberry milk.
I often see pictures like this.
It's a good picture.
What are you doing?
Maaya, did you do this to the leaves of the strawberry?
Maybe it's a plum flower.
It's different.
I did it like this.
It's beautiful.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
This is a pancake.
Wait a minute.
This is a white pancake.
This is a white pancake shop.
What should I do?
It looks delicious.
Oh, no, no, no.
I want to eat everything.
What should I do?
We've been eating all day today.
This is the most popular.
It's a white pancake.
I have to eat a white pancake.
This is the most popular.
This is the best.
That's right.
Oh, my God. It's really white.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat. Let's eat.
Let's eat. Let's eat a lot.
It looks delicious. It looks delicious.
Itadakimasu.
It smells good.
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
It's warm.
It tastes like coconut.
Is it hot?
Is it that hot?
It's hot.
There's something I wanted to say.
I went to Fuji-Q at Nogikoko and ate yakiniku.
I also went to Nogidoko.
I didn't go to either of them.
I didn't go to Nogidoko because I was in Under.
I didn't go to Nogikoko because I was in Senbatsu.
I thought the timing was really bad.
I've been talking about it with Ami.
I think it's a good project this time.
I'm happy to be here.
I'm sorry to the members.
It's fun.
I've never been to Nogikoko before.
Even if I go on a trip to Akshikai, I can't go outside
of that place.
I felt like I was sightseeing for the first time.
Kyoto was a lot of fun.
I ate ice cream and crepe in Kyoto.
I ate tofu, too.
I also ate rice cake.
I ate white pancakes, too.
I was happy today.
I'm so happy.
I want to share this happiness with everyone.
That's how happy I am.
I'll give you a little.
Let's buy everyone a souvenir.
Let's buy it.
Let's buy a souvenir.
Let's go.
It's a candy.
It's cute.
I want to buy a candy.
Which one should I buy?
Let's buy this.
Let's buy a small candy.
I'm waiting for a souvenir.
Everyone, I bought a souvenir.
Thank you very much.
It's a candy.
It's cute.
Thank you very much.
Everyone chose this.
Everyone who chose this is cute.
Everyone is smiling.
Thank you very much.
I bought a lot of things today.
It was fun.
Let's put it all together.
Why?
I just got it.
Please put it all together.
I had a lot of fun today.
I bought a souvenir.
I was able to tell the story of the first time.
It was fun.
If you have a chance like this, please call me again.
I want to do it again.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.