AISubs
Let's go to Nogizaka!
Today's MC is me, Marika Ito, and the cutest girl in
the world, Yubi Saito.
Please go ahead.
This time...
It's starting.
Are you okay?
MC, please do it properly.
I'm not in pain.
Please go ahead.
This time, I'd like to find out who has the highest
ability to exercise.
Who is it?
Under-exercise finalists!
Yay!
From now on, we will challenge speed, power and super power.
We will challenge these three things.
And we will decide the under-exercise.
I'm going to appeal to my grandmother.
I was going to tease you later, but I didn't think you
would come.
I was meeting my grandmother.
I'm going to appeal to my grandmother.
I'll do my best.
I don't have such a person.
Yutaro is also my grandmother.
I want you to do your best.
Let's go.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's start the first event.
Good luck.
The first event is...
Hide-and-seek.
Who will be the first to jump?
I will jump in order of attendance number.
The first one is Lena.
There is no one else but me.
So I'm scared from this morning.
I came here with only fear.
Lenaline will challenge first, but is it advanced
unification? Let's hear it. there's movement in you
Isn't it still better to praise
Let's fly it and decide it Renaline let's fly and decide
I'm going to raise my hand.
Failed!
The first try of Ichikirena is a failure.
Renari, come back.
This is your last chance.
If you fail this time, you'll be in trouble.
Good luck.
The second try of Ichikirena is a failure.
The third try of Ichikirena is a failure.
The first one to fall from the high jump is Rina Ichikawa!
What a shame!
Rina, how do you feel about falling from the high jump?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
How did you feel at that time?
I thought I was going to fall from the high jump, but I
couldn't raise my legs.
Rina, thank you for your hard work.
Let's do our best in the next competition.
I'm pretty confident.
I did a bodybuilding test for a long time ago.
I was first in high jump.
So I thought I could do it this time.
First place means you can do this, too.
That's easy.
I got it.
It's my first time.
Ready?
Wow!
That was a beautiful shot!
This is the first time I've seen this!
I passed!
I might be able to get 1st place in this condition
Let's move on to the next challenger
Eto, Misa, please!
I'm the oldest
Unfortunately
But I'm confident in my athletic ability
Is it okay if I do my best?
I want to prove that I can do my best even at the age of 20
This is the first challenge of 90cm
I'm scared.
Really?
It was close.
I think I was a little higher in high school.
I'm sorry.
Next is the challenge of Hina Kawago.
Hina-pyon, what are those shoes?
It came in from the appearance.
Hina-pyon's 90cm challenge.
Are you ready?
US top 1
Congratulations!!
You can still do it!
Next is Lottie!
I don't think there's anyone who can beat my athletic ability.
I'll do my best with Lottie power!
It's a 90cm challenge!
Ready!
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Congratulations.
Next is Asuka Saito's challenge.
I'm not good at sports.
You're not good at sports?
I didn't work out at all because I was in the brass band.
How much do you aim for the first place?
But even if I go, there are a lot of people who are not
good at sports.
So I'll aim for the third place.
This is Ashley's first attempt at 90 cm.
That was a tie, wasn't it?
If you do it again, you'll fly.
Really?
Asuka, this is the last time.
Do your best!
This is Ashley's second challenge.
Ready, go!
You can do it!
The second one has left.
Asuka, please come back.
What happened?
I was scared.
Asuka.
I almost cried.
Did you cry?
I thought you cried like a crybaby.
Don't cry.
You can do it.
I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
You can do it.
Don't cry.
Don't be scared.
When I was in elementary school, I played basketball,
and when I was in junior high school, I was in the
track and field club, but I was always in the last
place, so I don't have much confidence, but I'm doing
it.
I'm doing it.
How many points did you get today?
Well, I think I can get the first place.
Ready!
lol
Ah!
Wait!
His seed!
How did he get this seed?
Mine is longer!
Write it down!
I'm more surprised than anyone.
What?
That's crazy.
Don't lie!
I can't believe it.
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
Did you jump?
I jumped.
There's a red mark on my knee.
I think Chiharu can jump the best.
What's wrong with your smug face?
I think I can do it.
This is embarrassing.
Let's try again.
What's the next challenge?
What if you have a smug face again?
Yes.
I'm not good at jumping.
I'll practice the first time.
I'll try the second time.
What do you think?
Isn't that a land job?
It's a land job, right?
What's wrong with you?
Show me your real ability.
The second challenge is 90 centimeters.
Ready, go!
Don't do that.
Just a bit more!
Please don't do that...
Shut up!
I want to do it like this.
I was trying to look cool.
I've been able to fly before.
I thought I could go to the back.
You can't. Everyone might fall out of this flow.
It's okay. Everyone can go.
Let's move on.
I was in a club when I was in junior high school, so
I'm in junior high school, so I don't know how much my
physical strength has decreased, but there are a lot of
female members, so I think I can keep up with that, so
I think I'm a good athlete, so I'll do my best.
I'm 15 years old, so I can't fly at all. Don't call me
a grandmother.
15 years old is 15 years old. I don't know what 15
years old means, but I'd like to start now.
This is the first challenge of the 90cm button. Ready!
It's Chigohime!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
It's shaking a lot.
Next is...
Next is Hime Nakamoto!
I did takatobi when I was in junior high school, so
I'll do my best.
I can do takatobi.
I don't want to do it again, so I'll do my best to avoid it.
I'm sleepy.
I can do it.
Really?
Hime is always like, what should I do?
No, I'm not very excited in the morning, so what should I do?
I can't say too much.
I'll do my best.
Hime's first challenge.
Ready, go!
Go for it!
It was like a pro.
Yeah, it was like a pro.
I feel like I've lost weight.
Amazing.
It was so easy.
Hime-chan, it was so easy.
I can't do it at all.
I can't do it.
Hime-chan, you can do it.
Why?
Next,
Go, Ami-san.
Yes, Ami-san.
I think I can do it in 5 minutes.
I think I can do it in 3 minutes.
You don't want to win?
Well, I'm modest.
That's it.
But, Ami,
I think you can do it better than that.
Please watch me.
Before you know it,
you're going to be number one.
That's right.
I think everyone can't beat Ami.
I think I'm a little bit like that.
I think I'm betraying you.
I'm thinking of betraying you.
Hey, everyone.
I can't hear you.
Hey, Nojo-san is farther than everyone else.
The distance.
Oh, the distance. Oh, I made a mistake.
It's my own run, so I made a mistake.
It's an Ami-Ami 90cm challenge. Ready.
Nojo-san.
I was blown away by the whistle.
Please look forward to it.
What was that?
Wow, you were able to fly, Ami.
It was a new way of flying.
You were able to fly with that kind of way of flying?
It was amazing.
Next is...
Hata Naka.
Do you have any sports experience?
My sports experience...
When I was in the first grade of junior high school,
I joined a table tennis club for a moment.
I quit there.
But that has nothing to do with my sports experience.
But I'm really good at dodgeball.
I did it at a table tennis club.
That has nothing to do with it.
Seitan, how was it?
You've been saying that you're really good at it.
I can't do it. I really can't do it.
I'm going to fly.
I'm a little worried, but let's do it.
It's Seitan's 90cm challenge.
Ready...
Go, Miracle!
Hata Naka, go!
I want to see other people's performance.
What? What? What?
What are you talking about?
What?
It was a great jump.
With both legs.
Congratulations.
Let's move on to the next round.
The next challenger is Hina Higuchi.
Everyone in Nogizaka can exercise.
I'll do my best.
I'll aim for 2nd place.
There is still room for improvement.
Actually, I jumped 110cm in the shower.
So I'll do my best.
Next is Miyazawa Sailor.
I love to move my body since I was a child.
I've been moving my body.
I'd like to show you my good sportsmanship.
This is Setsuko's 90cm challenge.
Oh, I'm scared.
Next is Rina Yamato.
I have a sore nose, but I'll do my best.
Wait a minute.
It looks like Mt. Fuji.
I can't see it.
It's a 90cm long challenge.
I don't know what just happened.
She fell down.
Are you okay?
This is the second time.
I have to go to the second time.
What happened?
Are you okay?
This is the second time.
Ready.
Let's go.
Next, Wada Maaya!
I'm a junior high school student, so I'd like to do my best here.
It's like that.
It's the third year, right?
That's right. It's the third year, so it's more like
this than everyone else.
I don't want to let you down.
Please look forward to it.
It's Maya's 90cm challenge.
Ready, go!
Wow!
Nice!
You have long legs!
Wow!
Next, the first try!
100cm?
100cm from Itomari!
Ready?
Wow!
MisaMisa, can you change your position?
I think it's easier to jump from the left.
Really?
Then please trust yourself.
This is the first time.
MisaMisa, 100cm challenge.
Ready, go!
What's going on?
It's so beautiful!
She jumped and went back up.
Amazing!
She jumped in a strange way.
She probably jumped from the right side.
She's showing her skills.
Next, it's Kawago Hina's turn.
Ready?
What?
I thought you said Namitsu.
I thought you said Hinamitsu.
What did you say?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Hinamitsu.
Hinapyon.
This is the last one.
This is the second time of Hinapyon.
This is the last challenge of 100cm.
Ready?
What?
I couldn't jump.
That was close.
Hinapyo.
Too bad.
What do you think is the reason why you couldn't jump?
Well, I don't know.
The wall was too high.
It's Lottie's 100cm challenge.
Ready.
Go.
Lottie.
Amazing!
Let's keep going!
Next up is...
Saito Yuuri!
Oh, it's me!
I'm sorry.
She's a strawberry princess.
Strawberry princess!
Now, it's 100cm Yutta's challenge!
Ready...
Go!
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no!
What about the power?
I haven't eaten a strawberry, so I don't have any power.
You just shook it perfectly, didn't you?
Yuta, the second time.
I don't know if the strawberry princess is okay, but let's go.
The second time is Yuta's challenge.
Ready, go!
Failed!
I don't want to!
Yuta!
What about Ichigo?
Ichigo-hime!
Are you okay?
Saito is over.
Finally, Saito is over.
I don't want to!
Yuta, come on!
Saito is about to fall.
Saito is over.
Hime-tan's first 100cm challenge.
Ready, go!
As expected!
And it was cool.
Did you really jump on your back just now?
Great!
What should I do if I jump?
I'm happy to be able to jump.
I'm excited.
Let's go!
I'm getting ready now.
Next is the challenge of Ami Ami!
Ami Ami
Ami! Ami! Ami! Ami!
Hey!
What was that?
Are you okay?
That girl's face was so fierce.
No, the way she jumped was amazing.
Like this.
The way she ran.
Well then,
I wonder if I can jump again.
Ami, are you okay with that?
Let's hope so.
Okay.
This is the second Ami Ami challenge.
Ready, go!
You can do it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's higher than I thought.
I was always curious about you.
But before you fly, you look like you're in a hurry.
What happened to that?
You have to be calm before you fly.
But I couldn't fly.
I'm sorry.
Let's do our best next time. Thank you.
Next is Seita's challenge.
Miracle Hatanaka.
I don't know if I can do it.
Ready.
I can do it, I can do it.
Miracle Hatanaka.
She's getting closer, don't you think?
She's getting closer than I thought!
It's hard, isn't it?
She's gotten 6 cm, but she's getting closer to the first time.
That's right.
Seira is...
I've become serious.
I'm already serious.
Seita, there's still one more time.
Hang in there.
You're going to decide who's going to get the miracle hat, right?
I can do it, I can do it.
Oh, you can do it, you can do it!
Seita's serious.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
Then, Seita's second try.
It's a 100 cm challenge.
Ready, go!
I'm going to lose it.
You're really good at this.
There's a little bit left.
You did a good job.
I want to go in.
I'm going to go back.
Look at this hair.
You did a good job.
You're this tall.
I'm sorry, but I thought you were serious.
If you're serious, this is it.
Really?
Next is the 100cm challenge of Hinachima!
Ready...
The 100cm challenge of Hinachima!
You can do it!
It's beautiful!
There's no one who can do it so beautifully in the first try.
That's amazing.
Thank you. I'm looking forward to the next one.
I'll do my best!
Next up is Setsuko's 100cm challenge.
Ready, go!
A mysterious peace sign.
Setsuko's 100cm challenge.
I'm jealous!
This is definitely the length of her legs.
It's a bit of a disadvantage, isn't it?
The length of her legs.
Setsuko's 100cm challenge.
I can't do this. I'm already out.
I can't lose this.
Let's get the tomatoes to do their best.
Next is the tomato.
Here comes the Pokemon.
Let's go.
The length of her legs.
You can fly, right?
The first 100cm challenge of tomatoes.
Setsuko's 100cm challenge.
Wait, Rina, I'm really serious.
I have eyes on my butt now.
You're a pervert.
One more time.
Tomato, do your best.
That girl is also comfortable to touch.
I feel uncomfortable.
Why?
Tomato, don't you go with that style?
Let's get through it, Tomato.
I'm getting embarrassed.
This is the second time for Tomato.
Ready.
I think it would have been better if you didn't use the whistle.
It would have been better if you didn't use the whistle.
It's definitely because of the whistle, right?
Next up is Maaya's 100cm challenge.
It's the last 100cm challenge, so I hope you succeed.
Let's do this!
Ready, go!
After all, it is better to have a narrow space here.
Next!
I'm gonna cry!
Ahhhhh!
Good luck!