AISubs
Maki-chan!
It's time for our new program, Nogiten!
In this program, we'll challenge ourselves to improve
our idol abilities.
Let's do our best to become idols loved by our fans!
Let's do our best!
Let's take a look at today's program!
Let's do it!
Nogiten, let's do it!
You're an adult, aren't you?
Thank you.
What should I do?
I don't know.
That's not right.
It was taken.
Everyone!
This program is a program that challenges various
projects to improve your idol skills.
The first theme is girl power.
Girl power.
It's essential for idols, isn't it?
Yes.
So, this time, I'd like to check who has the highest
girl power among these members and who lacks girl
power.
Let's see who has the highest girl power among these
members and who lacks girl power.
That's not true.
Please look forward to the next program.
The lid of the drain hole was a little off.
The rain that still won't stop
Wasting my time
You're killing my emotions
Staring at me with jealousy
I don't care what you say
If you put it in your mouth, it will be easier
Are we doing this forever?
Can't we move together like this?
Love is an illusion
More than this
There is no reason to be here
Even though we know each other
Is there anyone who cares about the coordination of
other members?
I like Mahiro
Thank you
Stand up once
All white
Only one
Is it a skirt?
Is there anyone who cares about other than Mahiro?
Hime
Thank you
Baburi
Audrey Hepburn, too.
Today's theme is the day off in Rome.
Why?
The top is like this.
Only the socks are like this.
Oh, I see.
Banana, banana.
The clothes on the top are also popular.
Skeleton.
Skeleton?
Marika's badge is so cute.
It's so cute.
Is this handmade?
This is handmade.
It's amazing.
I'm jealous.
This.
One point.
I've heard of that.
It's not common.
I've heard of spice.
Spice?
What kind of spice?
Thank you.
Asuka and Hata Naka.
It's cute.
That's good.
The names are completely different.
Hata Naka.
The body.
The stomach.
It's not coming out of the stomach.
It's coming out of the stomach.
That's true.
It's a trend now.
Show me a little.
Asuka is wearing a dress.
Is this good?
It's a dress.
Oh, is that so?
She's always wearing a dress.
Is that so?
It's cool.
Oh.
Doesn't it look like a senior?
I'm saying that to myself.
Asuka is also wearing a dress.
That's right.
Now that we know the appearance of women, let's check the inside.
Let's take a look at the women's items of the members.
The top batter is Nagashima Seina.
This is an organic body spray.
It smells like honey.
It's a body mist.
It smells really good.
It smells like honey.
It's a honey scent.
Yes, it smells really good.
It smells really good.
It smells like honey.
I brought it.
Honey and lemon.
This is my womanly charm.
It's a womanly charm.
I think the fans who are watching this will think that
Nagashima has a womanly charm.
Next up is Himeka Nakamoto.
I thought it would be a good one.
You know, I put it in a case like this a while ago, but
it's overflowing, so I've been incinerating it a little
lately and it's about this big.
This looks big.
Is it that big?
Give me a cushion.
It's about this big.
This? This?
I have the image of wearing a different ribbon every day.
I have a different ribbon almost every day.
I'm 96 this time.
Actually, I brought it today.
Here, Hime-tan-ryu Ribbon Technique is taught to the members.
Who wants to wear it?
I want to wear it.
Let's wear it.
Which one do you like?
Which one looks good on you?
This one.
It's cute.
As if the ribbon adds fragrance and excitement,
if I wear the ribbon the word stands out.
・・・
Next up is Seira Hatanaka.
Mario, cute mama bag and a new hat, pink hair and a
special heart 5 star
She got that from her friend remember?
Haha!
She also got strollers
It's a candle.
It's cute.
There's a bottle.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
I've been to Seita's house before.
I think it was vanilla.
They gave me an aroma candle.
It smelled really good.
Nami and Asuka went there too.
It was an incense stick.
It wasn't an incense stick.
What was it?
It was an incense stick.
I heard that you cook.
Why do you know that?
What's your specialty?
I like fried food.
I also make hamburgers.
You can do it yourself.
That's right.
Have the other members ever eaten hand-cooked food?
Yes.
That's great.
How was it?
When I was with Asuka,
I said I was hungry.
I said I'd make it in a minute.
That's great.
I made it in about three minutes.
Eggplant and cheese.
Seitan's original.
I love eggplant.
It was delicious.
It looks delicious.
Now that we know the unexpected woman power of Hatanaka,
Next, check out the farm items.
What is this?
It's an omelette.
Ami made it?
I made it!
No way!
It's true!
This is for my mom's birthday.
My mom is late for work, so I made this for her.
I thought I'd wait for her.
It's cute.
I thought she'd be back soon, so I made it for her.
It has flowers and bears.
It's so cute.
I wrote Happy Birthday in English.
Is this right?
No, it's not.
It's B.I.
Please show us the picture.
B.I.
It says A.
Really?
No, it's not.
Happy Birthday.
It's B.I.
Really?
Am I wrong?
No, it's not.
It's a bit difficult.
No way.
There's a flag on the omelette.
It says Happy Birthday, but it's wrong.
You made it yourself?
Yes.
That's amazing.
It's cute.
I made a flag.
That's amazing.
It's the edge of a notebook.
How is it?
It looks good, doesn't it?
It's amazing that you can make flags with a toothpick.
It's cute.
I was surprised that Ami could make an omelette.
Did you bring any items?
I think everyone knows what it is.
I don't know.
I brought it.
What is this?
This is the next important thing in my life.
It's rouge.
Rouge?
Yes, it's rouge.
What color is it?
It's pink.
It's orange.
Why is the next important thing in your life rouge?
I've been doing this since I was in high school.
I don't have any color on my lips.
On your lips?
Yes.
So I have to put it on.
Sometimes I don't have any color on my lips.
When I see that, I can't forgive it.
It's like using paper.
Really?
I can put it on.
Hime put it on earlier.
Yes.
Hime didn't have any color on her lips.
I couldn't forgive it.
You couldn't forgive it?
So I put it on.
What do you think now?
Is there anyone you're interested in?
If there is, can you put it on for her?
Marika is sweating a lot.
She's sweating a lot.
Can you put it on for her?
Ami, you're not good at putting it on.
I'm not bad at it.
Ami is good at putting on makeup.
Yes, I'm good at putting on makeup.
I'm not good at it.
I'm good at putting on makeup.
I have to do it like this.
Ami always gets up in the morning without makeup.
But her lipstick is perfect.
She only put on lipstick.
Why?
It's perfect.
See?
I really like this lipstick.
Who are you talking to?
I can't put it on even though I put it on.
She's very particular about her lipstick.
There seems to be a member who is not convinced.
She has a lot of lipstick, but her cell phone case is very dirty.
She uses cellophane tape to fix the screen.
I've never seen anyone use cellophane tape to fix a screen.
She's good at makeup, but she's very good at makeup tools.
Don't do that.
You have to raise and lower it nicely.
It seems that Ms. Nojo is not a lazy person who can cook.
Next is from Nakada.
What kind of candles do you have?
What is it?
Candles.
I like candles.
I collect various things.
This is a real thing.
This red thing.
It's a flame.
The pattern of the flame is swaying.
It's amazing.
It's really healing.
What kind of time do you burn it?
I'm tired from work.
When I come home.
Before going to bed.
I put it in the bath.
I can't put it in the bath.
I can put it in the bath.
Thank you very much.
How is your breakfast? I often have breakfast at home,
so I make it myself, but I thought the colors were
beautiful.
This is a French bread with tomato and basil on top.
It's fashionable.
Have you ever eaten Nakata's food?
No.
Kana, you can cook.
To be honest, I don't cook much meat, so I don't say I
can do it, but this kind of breakfast is quite
delicious, so I want everyone to eat it.
Are there any other members who make breakfast?
I don't make breakfast.
I eat natto rice.
I didn't make it.
I just mix it.
I mix it 30 times.
I mix it 100 times.
It's different from mixing it 60 times.
It's delicious.
What are you talking about?
From the story of breakfast, it became a story of natto
for some reason.
Shin-uchi, a member of OL, arrived here.
Shin-uchi, are you okay with your work today?
I came out until about lunch today.
Good job.
Let's go to the fashion check.
You came.
Is it for commuting?
It's a little for commuting.
It looks easy to move.
It's not for commuting, is it?
It's definitely different.
Tell the truth.
The upper body is not for commuting.
It's a little tight.
The lower body has long legs.
It's not for commuting.
The legs are long, so don't wear high-waisted clothes.
Marika, please stand next to me.
This reaction!
Marika looks like a child.
Marika-san, please show us the difference of your body
type with a girl power item.
I put necklaces, my favorite postcards, and cards from
the exhibition.
I liked collecting them, so I put them up.
This is also from Marika World.
I want to display all of them, but I can't keep them
neatly, so I thought it would be better to show them.
This is a work of art.
What is this?
It's a piece of furniture.
Candles.
I put a small desk on the edge.
I put candles and kimonos on it.
It's cute.
Do you use that candle?
I'm already using it.
It's gone down a lot.
When do you use candles?
...
When I'm really tired, or when I don't want to go out
on a day off, like on a rainy day.
You know? On a rainy day.
I want to be healed.
I light a candle, read a manga, and listen to music.
That's my favorite time.
Your favorite time?
More than when you're working?
It's fun when I'm at home.
I really think so.
When I'm at home, that's my favorite time.
It's different between work and private time.
Is there anything else you do to improve your woman power?
I improve my woman power.
My hobby is calligraphy. I also draw pictures.
You're good at it.
Did you bring something today?
I'm looking forward to it.
This is a brooch.
It's cute.
Is it all handmade from the beginning?
Yes.
It's dirty, but it's like this.
It feels like handmade.
What kind of image do you have of it?
It's sold and there are cute ones, but it's expensive.
Then I feel like I should make it myself.
That's great.
Then you can make it according to your design.
Your parents are designers.
I was born among designers, so I'm good at it.
I want to be able to use that machine next time.
I haven't been there yet, but I want to make clothes next time.
If you have a second one, please wear it.
I'll wear it.
I'm looking forward to it.
What is GEN-KOL's women's power?
This is a lunch box, but I always pack the leftovers,
so I was going to make it a little smaller, but is it
okay?
It's a pretty messy lunch box.
Is this all handmade?
I feel like I really packed all the leftovers from yesterday.
Do you cook properly?
I don't eat dinner if it's late, so I pack it and take
it to lunch because I feel sorry for my mother.
Mother?
I'm packing it, but my mother is making it.
That's not true!
It's pretty messy.
I packed it more neatly, so that everyone can see it.
I don't think you need a rain jacket.
Next, let's check Kawamura's woman power.
Kawamura's woman power.
Kawamura's woman power is cute and stylish.
Off.
Next is Asuka's woman power check.
What is this fluffy thing?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's a manicure.
I don't know what's in it.
Why are you moving it?
There's a manicure.
It's a manicure and a doll.
The macaron one is a candle.
I have it.
Really?
It's cute, so I'm decorating it.
The one on the left is a necklace.
It's a necklace.
Thank you.
It's a Valentine's box.
It's amazing.
I want that.
I wanted to give chocolates for everyone on Valentine's Day.
There were many years when I couldn't give chocolates.
Last year, I had no choice but to throw away the box.
I thought I'd put it in my accessories, but I can use it.
It's convenient.
You can use it more.
I have many necklaces, earrings, and rings.
This time, Asuka checks the pouch she usually carries.
What's that?
It's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's so fashionable.
Reika also had it.
Really?
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute.
It's so cute.
It's sparkling.
Lipstick.
I always put lipsticks in it.
I always put in a comb.
It's a must.
Tissue.
Tissue and eye drops.
I also carry a bandage every day.
You have a bandage and a tissue.
That's all.
It's important.
Asuka, who is young and has a high girl power, what is
the item of Mr.Tawago?
Wow, that's amazing!
I really like collecting materials like this.
I'm a magician.
What?
What did you say?
That's amazing.
First of all, calm down.
And for that, you need a compact to transform.
That's why there's a lot.
Don't push yourself too hard.
If you don't push yourself too hard, you'll hurt yourself.
It's really hard.
16 times.
It's too hard.
It's okay.
I love you.
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
Ami read the magic book.
Yes, I read the magic book.
It's amazing.
It's fun.
There's a spell.
There's a spell list.
Yes, I'm a magician.
You can't trust me.
I'm scared.
What kind of magic is it?
It's like open sesame.
It's written open sesame.
I'm scared.
What other spells do you have?
It's difficult.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is it really like Harry Potter?
What happens if you ask that?
I don't know.
Because this is the real world.
A little happiness for everyone.
Stop it.
There's a tarot card in there.
There's a feather in there, too.
It's amazing.
I really like magic.
By the way, if you can really use magic.
Can you use it?
I'm sorry. I didn't believe it at all.
I'm sorry.
Can I cast a spell?
Who will you cast a spell on?
I want to tell you who's watching.
I'm going to cast a spell on your heart.
What the hell?
Stop it.
Yubi's really going to do it.
But I hid it.
I'd make a reason.
I don't think so.
Let's do it.
Metal beam!
What does this do?
The person who sees it will be excited.
From your personal life, you may have understood the
power of women, but in the second half, we will go into
the practical part.
Lastly, we'll have you do the practical part.
What is it?
It's a test of women's ability with gestures.
This is really embarrassing.
We'd like to see how natural it is for the fans who are
watching the show to be able to make a gesture that
looks like a woman without thinking.
We'd like you to listen to the situation from the box.
Please tell us a gesture that fits the situation and
comes without thinking.
It depends on the girl's character.
Let's be fair.
If I do it, I'll definitely laugh.
I'll do it seriously.
It's easy to be that kind of target.
Let's be serious.
Let's forget the character.
It's okay.
I know you're cute, Rin.
It's not funny.
The topic of the top batter is Kawago.
The topic of the top batter is a word to make up with
your boyfriend.
I'm sorry. Let's make up with each other.
If she said this, it would be annoying.
The topic of the top batter is a word to encourage your
boyfriend who caught a cold.
Are you all right?
Please get well soon.
It's Bukki.
It's cute, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
The topic of the top batter is a word to encourage your
boyfriend who caught a cold.
What should I do?
I forgot the textbook, but I want you to show it to me.
Thank you very much.
I'm embarrassed.
I want you to show it to me, not show it to me.
I was embarrassed to see it.
I want you to show it to me.
I made a mistake.
The topic of the top batter is a word to encourage your
boyfriend who caught a cold.
Where are you going to meet?
Shibuya.
Where in Shibuya?
Hachiko.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I'm late. I'll treat you later.
No, you're laughing.
Let's have a matcha sushi party with Hachiko tomorrow.
I'm sorry. I'm late. I'll treat you later.
Mr. Nakamoto came to eat his favorite cake.
It's delicious. Have a bite.
The topic for Mr. Nakada is 〈Wake up from your slumber〉
You appeared in my dream!
Amazing! Thank you very much.
Next is Nojo-san.
The theme is a word when you find a lost person on a date.
Huh? What did you say?
Oh, you're so kind.
Don't cry.
Let's find a house together.
A house?
It's hard to find a house.
A word when you say goodbye on a date.
I don't want to go home yet, but shall we go to another one?
I see
Shall we go to another one?
Katanaka-san's answer when she tried to take the same
book and her hand hit it
I got it! Shall we read it together?
So cute!
The last one is from Nagashima-san.
The question is, what do you say when you pick up
something you dropped?
I'm sorry, I dropped this.
You can't drop it next time.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're too serious.
I don't know what to do.
I told you to be serious.
You're cute.
This gesture is cute.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work for the first recording.
This is sudden, but we have an announcement.
What is it?
Do you know that Nogizaka46 will appear at the Japan
Expo, a Japanese culture event held in Paris, France,
in July this year?
I don't know.
Wait, where is the announcement from?
If anyone doesn't know, Nogizaka46 will appear at the Japan Expo.
However, only the selected members will appear.
Unfortunately, Kyoryukuri-san can't go to Paris.
I want to go.
Do you want to go?
Yes.
But you can't go.
What is it?
Actually, in this program, we would like to deliver the
pattern of Japan Expo in detail.
Therefore, if you are an under member, I would like to
send a local reporter to Paris.
There are only two people.
Two people?
What is it?
So, next time we will go to Paris and have a real bowling match!
But for some reason, an unprecedented situation has occurred!
The spirit of this battle that can never be defeated!
Who are these two going to Paris?