AISubs
Green!
Ha!
Okay, we've started!
Let's go to Nogizaka!
Yeah!
It's started!
I didn't want to start, but I wanted to do it.
So, the first one is the 8th single.
Then, the second one is the one-way ticket.
We are at the event special.
We are at Makuhari Base.
Makuhari!
Yay!
The back side.
So, this event and the handshake event, of course, are
very important for us.
It's the 8th single for Nogizaka.
Please look forward to the live performance of the members!
Thank you so much for today!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Thanks to you,
we were able to have this concert.
Who was it?
It was all thanks to you.
Why did you do that?
I won't forget you because you attacked me.
Then, I'll go first.
I don't care about Kana.
I won't forget you.
Can you do something to make the customers happy with
Rakuten Cards?
For the members of Rakuten Cards, I want to hold a live
concert with the under members.
I want to do it!
That's a good idea.
Do you want to do it?
I want to do it!
Let's do it.
I think we've done a lot of rehearsals so far.
How about you, Marika?
How do you feel?
How do you feel about the live show?
It's my first time doing a live show by myself.
I'm sure you're all worried.
I'll do my best to make you feel better.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, Mana-chan.
Sorry. Sorry.
I couldn't hear.
Seitan is so nice.
Seitan, you are so, so nice.
Seitan is nice.
I thought they wouldn't come.
No, no, no.
I've been doing a lot of live shows with the Under
members, but it's my first time doing it, so I want to
do my best, so let's do our best!
I'm going to show you a lot of live shows with the
Under members, so please look forward to it!
Before I knew it, I fell in love with one-sided love
Every time I think of you, it hurts
How many encounters have people had since birth?
I always believe that this is fate
But for some reason, I hurt myself
I decided from the past that I would definitely fall in love
More lonely, lonely, lonely
I'm going to abandon him and go to me now
It's not that I didn't believe it
I'm going to shake off all the bad luck
Danke schen, danke schen, danke schen
Meeting is fate
Parting is also fate
Meeting is fate, parting is also fate
The past and the future, until now, thank you
One, two, three, four, five!
Twinkie, shake your heart
Just spit it out slowly
That's right, so you can continue to dream
Twinkie, shake it all off
Let's change the mood
Yeah, a new me
Suddenly I woke up
As if I were running on electricity
I fell in love with you for the first time
Suddenly I woke up
It's different from before
An exciting encounter with you
The start of our romance
I like the delay of moving around.
This one is better.
You can change the position of your body.
Your right foot should be on the left foot first.
After this, it was the first time for me to perform
under the stage.
Now, it's...
I'm just so nervous.
But I want to show the colors that only Under can show,
and the energy that I have.
I want to show this to the fans.
I want to make this the best concert that will make them think,
Under is so energetic.
I'll do my best!
I'm so nervous!
A lot of my fans told me that they were coming to my
concert today.
My voice was louder than I thought.
There are a lot of people in my head right now, but I
want to confirm it with everyone during the break.
If we enjoy it, I think everyone will enjoy it.
There are a lot of people, but I want to do my best
with everyone.
I have only one student, so I have less dance
experience than everyone else.
I want to do my best today, so please pay attention to my dance.
Also, during the rehearsal of Under, I was able to get
along very well with the people of Under, so I hope
that the goodness of that relationship will also
spread.
Thank you very much.
I'm going now!
Bye bye!
This is MaiMai Daifuki Konbinen.
This is a team of old people and young people. Bye bye.
Who are you talking to?
Shut up! Shut up, old lady!
Bye bye.
I'll do my best at the handshake event with Maiyan.
I'm going.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Bye.
Please come on board.
Thank you very much.
Ok, we're going to Unit A.
Yes, see you.
Please give me some.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best.
This is the members' practice room.
Well, let's go.
How long does it take?
Wait a minute.
I'm quite nervous.
Are you nervous?
When I went to the make-up shop, the make-up was worse
than usual.
They told me to dress up a little better.
I'm embarrassed by this.
Are you okay?
I usually dress up in a fashionable way.
My make-up is falling off.
That's true.
I have to fix a lot of things.
It will work out somehow.
I wonder if it will work out.
I don't know if it will work out.
That's right.
I'm going to fix my make-up.
It's cold!
Who is it?
It's cold.
and I heard the birthday song too.
Happy birthday to you!
Congratulations!
What should I do?
I was surprised, what should I do?
What should I do, I will cry.
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Did you get cold?
Bim!
Thank you!
Are you going to do Bim this year?
I was asked,
How long are you going to do twin?
I said, I'm going to do Bim again.
It's okay.
I'm going to do it.
Even if you're 40 years old, you're an idol.
It smells bad.
It's dangerous.
It's okay.
I want to stop my age.
It's still a long way to go.
That's right.
We're going to be younger.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much!
OK, pose.
One more time.
I think all the members are very happy that this is the
first attempt at UnderLive.
Rehearsals were also short, so I didn't do it for a
long time, so I was very anxious to be able to do it
all by myself.
In my case, I couldn't participate in the rehearsal
because I had to go to college and I had a fever, so I
couldn't participate in the rehearsal as much as I
wanted.
There were times when I had to watch the video and take
back the late part, so when I did the rehearsal, I
still had a lot of anxiety.
When I was on the stage, I wasn't sure if I could
perform well, so I was still not confident.
I was still not in my best condition, so my voice
didn't come out as I wanted.
I was still not in my best condition, so I was still
not confident.
I want to bring my best condition to the best of my ability.
I will do my best to bring my best condition to the
best of my ability.
I want to bring my best condition to the best of my ability.
This concert is a concert where UNDER members think of
a set list.
Please pay attention to it and enjoy it with everyone.
I'm in the middle of the show and it's my first time
doing an under-live.
To be honest, I'm really nervous.
The highlight is that it's my first time doing an under-live.
I'm really grateful to Rakuten-san.
Most of all, there are a lot of energetic girls in the
under-live.
I think I can see their powerfulness.
I also do all the under-lives.
So, I hope you'll watch it too.
It's almost time, but I'll do my best!
This time, I'll be doing an under-live.
I've been practicing a lot so that I don't waste this
opportunity.
I hope it'll be a live that everyone can enjoy.
I'll do my best!
The day before the live
And do it like this …
Are you OK?
Well then...
We're going to perform at Rakuten's Under Live.
Let's do our best!
It's OK.
Under Live and...
It's OK if we do it slowly.
We're on the same team.
Let's do it!
One, two, three!
No!
You!
One, two, three!
Let's smile!
Kimi no te no hiro Mune no ue
Tato to oshiattete
Myaku wo utsu kono kodou
Shikari kikunda
Donna kanashi ni deatte mo
Nikiteba natto ka naru
Nakedo ni nattara
Yuuki wa hibari no mune ni
Katten no naka, soyokaze to hana no kaori to nukumori wo tsutsumu
Inside the curtains, the scent of flowers and the
warmth of the breeze
Shikure, dare ni koishita no ka? sou yo
Secret, who did you fall in love with? Yes, if it's a girl
Onna no ko nara, itsu datte shikaku ni naru basho kurai
I'm always ready for a place that's right in front of me
Konna toki no tame ni takuho shiteru
Please listen to it.
Namida ga mada kanashimi datta koro
Mune no oku ga shime tsukerarete kurushikatta
Sou iu toki dousureba ii no ka
Gakkou ja nani mo oshiete kurenai
Butsubutsu ni nagara maerimichi no shousen gai
Senryoku de hashiru shikanakatta
Haru no Melody kikoete kita
I heard the melody of spring
Sotto utaitakunaru kimochi
I want to sing softly
Me wo tojite omoidasu no
I close my eyes and remember
Kare to hana no kaori
Hatsukoi no hito wo ima demo zutto sagashiteiru I'm
still searching for my first love Hatsukoi no hito wo
ima demo zutto sagashiteiru I'm still searching for my
first love I'm still searching for my first love Hiro
wo atteita you ni koe wo kaketai yo I want to talk to
you like we met yesterday
My heart is throbbing
Recently, I've fallen in love with someone
For some reason, everything is going well
Ah, I want to meet you
Thank you very much for today!
Thank you very much!
Sayu-nyan, how do you feel?
At first, I was really anxious and nervous, and I was
really nervous at the first UnderLive.
I was really happy that everyone was so kind and
excited. Thank you very much.
Yes, and now that we're all excited, there are only two
songs left to sing!
Thank you very much.
I'm tired of my current self
When I realized it, I fell in love with one-sided love
Every time I think of you, it hurts
I don't know why, but my heart is so fragile
Everyone, thank you so much for today!
Thank you so much!
Silence, silence!
All the best! All the best!
Let's push each other
Let's make a promise
Listen carefully
No matter how we meet
If we live, everything will come true
If you feel like losing
Courage is in the heart of the left
Everyone, thank you very much for the encore.
Thank you very much.
Actually, we didn't think at all that there would be an encore.
I was surprised.
I didn't think of it as an encore.
It's sudden now.
So I don't want to end it as it is.
Can you still go?
Let's go.
We started with this song.
Please listen.
Gurgle curtain
Everyone, please sing with me.
In the curtain
The sun and the girl and me
Gurgle wrapped
I want to tell you what you're talking about
I somehow calm down
I'm in the classroom
With a good friend
The world of two people
That's right
I want to tell you
If you become one
I can't understand
In the curtain
The scent of the wind
Gurgle
Who did you fall in love with?
That's right
If it's a girl
I'll always be blind
That's right
I'm preparing for a time like this
Please listen
Until the end of the concert, we had rehearsals and...
I'm about to cry!
The rehearsal didn't go well, but there was a lot of
action in it, and I had a lot to think about.
But it was so exciting, and I was really happy to be
able to do the encore. Thank you very much.
Everyone, thank you very much for today.
I was going to do a basic MC today, but I feel like...
I was so nervous I couldn't talk at all.
It's not like that.
It's okay.
I was really excited today.
I'm sorry, Yurin. Thank you.
It's okay.
Everyone gathered here.
And we, under, too.
Thank you.
We under are more active.
We work hard every day.
We don't want to lose to the members.
We don't want to lose.
We want to do our best together.
Please continue to support us.
Thank you.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
Thank you! Bye bye!
Thank you!
I thought I would do my best, but I can't do it alone.
It's okay.
I want to touch everyone.
Why are you crying?
Why?
It's okay.
I said a lot of good things.
I'm really grateful.
It's okay.
Thank you.
It's just over now.
You're crying.
I'm about to cry.
Let's talk about me.
Minami, please tell us how you feel.
It's my first time doing an event alone.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best to make you feel good.
I don't know what to do.
Personally, I'm still a little sad.
That's what I thought.
I want to improve it during the live show.
I want to do something better.
I thought it would be nice.
That's right.
Thank you.
Hina.
Yes.
First of all, this is the beginning.
It's the beginning of the Under.
It's just the beginning.
I want to grow and get bigger.
I want to do my best today.
I want to be better at talking.
Yes.
As you said,
I want to continue to do the Under members' live shows.
Next time will be May 3rd.
Please see the details on the official website.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.