AISubs
No! No! No!
I can't get down!
Everyone, please listen to the song.
Thank you for the food.
Do you want to eat?
It's delicious.
It's delicious. You can eat it right away.
Thank you for the food.
It's so good!
I've been here for about a year.
I've been here for a year and I've grown up.
I've grown up since you started raising your hand.
I've grown up here.
How was it?
It was amazing.
I can talk at a handshake party.
That's right.
I can talk now.
Before, I couldn't talk at all.
That's right.
I've been getting excited lately.
That's true.
You've worked hard.
What else?
It's getting more and more fluffy.
What?
Wait a minute.
You look like a twin girl.
I'm a twin girl.
But...
You've grown a lot.
You're heavy.
When I first came in, I was a little nervous.
Nervous.
You've grown a lot.
I haven't changed since I was a kid.
You haven't changed?
I haven't changed.
I've been sitting down lately.
It's a little different.
It's a different meaning.
What do you mean?
I don't remember.
I remember the live performance.
I've been to that kind of live performance recently.
I have a lot to remember.
I think I've grown up.
I think so.
Anything else?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I think I've improved my dancing skills.
But you've been dancing since the beginning, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
You haven't?
At first, I didn't even do a live performance, so I
didn't know how to show it.
Now, I'm doing a live performance.
I don't know where to start.
You have to do it at your own pace.
You have to learn.
At first, you have to dance a lot.
You can't do it now.
But you're doing your best.
Little by little, little by little.
Let's do our best.
One year has passed.
Tagara-san is here.
Really?
She's here for a full-fledged activity.
We're here for the full-fledged activity.
How is it?
Is it fun?
Yes, it's fun.
Suddenly, we've been working together for a year.
Isn't it hard to work with us who've been working
together for a year?
It's hard.
It's hard, but everyone is teaching us how to dance.
Everyone is teaching us how to dance.
It's fun.
Everyone is working hard.
That's good.
We have to do what we have learned in the past year.
I think it's going to be hard, but everyone is working hard.
It's hard.
Yes.
But when I teach,
I want to teach 2nd graders.
Because the other day,
at my favorite girl's house,
I learned how to dance.
Did you get better?
I don't know.
You don't know?
But you learned how to dance.
Yes, I did.
You taught me how to dance.
That's good.
I learned how to dance.
We still have a long way to go.
I'll do my best.
You're a graduate student.
You gave us a chance like this.
It's a long way to go.
I didn't think so.
I thought it would be nice.
I thought I wouldn't be called.
Finally, I was called.
I can see it.
I'm going to be a graduate student.
I've been dancing and supporting a lot of things.
But a year has passed and I've grown up.
I want to show myself.
I'm going to be a graduate student.
I'll be a graduate student.
I have a lot of qualifications, but I'll do my best as
a graduate student.
Let's do our best!
The next attraction is Crazy Stone!
Yay!
Ayane Suzuki and Ange Teradara will challenge this attraction.
How is it? It's high, isn't it?
It's high, but...
It's high.
How is it? Are you not good at high places?
I'm not good at it.
I'm about to cry.
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
Please do your best.
This time, we're both lonely, so let's take a picture together.
But this time, we're going to take a picture of someone.
What? What? What?
I'm so sad.
We're all crying.
No one can help us.
Oh, wow!
It's okay.
I'm so happy.
How about the high part?
It's okay.
Cheer them up.
It was so loud.
I don't have any ham here so I don't have anything.
Faster.
I didn't see this coming.
You don't want to eat it, huh?
Shut the door!
Shut up!
No! No! No!
Aya-ne!
Are you okay?
Come back!
Aya-ne!
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
You can do it!
You can't make that face.
I don't like that face.
I don't like it.
You look like an idol.
Bye bye.
Please come back alive.
Please don't leave me alone.
What should I do?
What's the momentum?
It's a balance.
What should I do?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23,
24, 25, 26,
Stop it!!!!
Stop it go away go away....
I'm scared.
It's inside.
I'm scared, I'm scared.
Welcome back.
You're smiling.
Good job.
Are you okay?
I tried my best to sing and dance at the same time, but
it was so hard.
But it was delicious.
Is it okay to sing high notes?
Yes, it's okay to sing high notes.
It's okay to sing low notes.
When I was climbing up, my legs were stiff.
I was scared because my legs were stiff.
Lena was next to me, so I was scared.
I'm scared.
And Ayane, who did her best.
Ayane, come here.
Ayane is retreating.
Are you okay?
Thank you for your hard work.
When I finished climbing, I was surprised and wanted to walk.
Are you okay?
I'm glad.
I was scared.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm not good at high places, but I was able to climb.
Shall we go to the last place?
Let's go.
I'm not good at climbing.
My legs are stiff.
Thank you for your hard work.
The last one is bungee jumping!
The challenger for bungee jumping is Iori Sagara.
It's your first time to do bungee jumping for the first time.
You don't hate it, do you?
No, I don't hate it.
Then, I'd like you to jump with a smile.
And if there's anyone who wants to do it, please do it.
Anyone?
Good job.
Go ahead.
Lydia and Lena, aren't you scared? Are you good at this
kind of thing?
You're not good at it?
You're not good at it, though.
Well, I couldn't get on the ride earlier, so I got on the bungee.
Oh, that's great.
Let's do our best.
What about Lena?
But I've never been on a bungee before.
Oh, really?
I wonder if I'll be scared when I get on it.
I wonder.
If I'm alone, I'll do my best.
That's your goal for this year.
That's right.
It's one of the 100 goals.
Oh, this is it.
Then, one of the 100 goals can be achieved.
That's right.
Also, in the individual PV,
Mr. Nakada used to be the principal of the school, but
he was able to do it.
Iwari and Nina may be good at it, but I'm sure Miria,
who is not good at it, can do it, so I think three of
you can do it.
Good luck.
Good luck!
Oh, I'm scared.
Wait, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Wait, no one is watching.
Rena!
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
Go!
My legs are shaking.
What?
Really?
Yes.
What?
I've never been to a place where I can go out of the
city by myself.
It's amazing.
I've never been to a place where I can go out of the
city by myself.
Thank you very much.
Cut!
I'm scared. What should I do?
I think it's dangerous.
What should I do?
Which is safer?
It's safe for me, but it's not safe for you.
Then, please push it.
Please push it.
It's okay to use light force.
I'll wait for you.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!!!!
It's so scary!
Are you enjoying this?
You are enjoying this, aren't you?
I mean, this is the most important thing!
Please be careful not to catch a cold.
I don't know. I have to show you.
Number 13
Doesn't look wild
nament
?
What seems to be the case?
There is a
thing
...
Clean feel
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job!
You did your best!
I was scared.
Don't cry when you see a crying person.
Don't cry.
Good job!
Were you tired?
But you were brave.
Did you push?
Yes.
You did your best!
Thank you for your hard work!
I was scared.
Can't I tie this around my neck?
Where is it?
What should I do?
Let's go!
I'm scared! Help me!
3,2,1
What should I do?
Please get off
I'm scared!
You can do it!
You did it!
You didn't cry, did you?
I thought I was going to cry, but it was okay.
You did it pretty fast.
But you pushed me.
I couldn't do it alone.
You were shouting, but it looked a little fun.
Do you want to do it again?
I want to do it again!
You're so strong!
This is the end of today's Nogizaka.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
There were various things, but it was fun.
It was fun.
As a result, it was also an experience for the students.
I worked hard with tears and laughter.
Thank you for your hard work.
Everyone who watched this time.
How was the reaction of the students?
If there is a reaction, I will do my best to appear in Nogizaka.
Please look forward to it.
Please look forward to the next Nogizaka.
Bye bye.