AISubs
Chii-chan, you look so young today. What is this? Earrings?
Ribbon!
Baka-Ribbon!
Baka-Ribbon is Baka-Ribbon!
Oh, my God.
Well, it's this opportunity.
We're in Yokohama right now.
So, Yokohama Arena.
I won't talk about my thoughts or reflections.
Let's talk.
So, who will go first?
I'll go first.
Well, then.
I'll go first. Then.
Do you want to join Nanase?
You want to join Nanase, right?
Let's join Nanase.
It's Nanase-maru.
This is Yokohama.
Let's talk about our impressions of Yokohama Arena.
How many stages are there?
Let's talk about the most impressive scenes.
I didn't see it at all, but when Ikoma-chan sang
Mizutamari Moe alone, Nana was desperately moving at
that time, and I only listened to the earmuffs, so I
knew that Ikoma-chan was crying there, and I thought
that Ikoma-chan was crying while running, so I knew it
later, but at that time it was amazing.
I thought that Ikoma-chan was crying alone, and I
thought that Ikoma-chan was crying while running on a
blog, but at that time it was amazing.
It was amazing.
We are also wolves, so when we were wolves, Ikoma was
standing on top of us, and we were waiting here, and
Ikoma was like,
Are you there that day?
I thought there was still Ikoma.
I thought Ikoma was crying.
I was impressed by Nanase.
I put all the vlogs in the video, but it was like,
I'm going home in the middle of the summer.
I came here, too.
I came here.
I was told a lot by my fans.
I was standing by for the mannequin when the mannequin
was about to fly by.
And the mannequin was right in front of me.
It was so close, wasn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I didn't know what kind of reaction I would get.
I hadn't told anyone about it.
When I was looking at the mannequin's reaction,
the mannequin started to cry a lot.
So I started to cry.
I didn't know what to do.
We've been together for a long time, so we understand
each other so well.
I'm glad we got to know each other better.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want to go?
I don't want to go.
Good luck.
Bye.
Thank you for your comments.
Bye bye.
You're so cute.
Sayuri, do you have any memorable moments?
Memorable?
It doesn't matter.
Do you have any fun doing this?
It was fun.
It's the whole song.
If you're sure you can do it.
I was so impressed by all of them.
I don't remember the last one.
We've been doing it for about five hours.
I think the first song was completed about three days ago.
That's true.
I don't know how you feel about that.
Who is the best dancer?
Sayulee
I'm the worst dancer.
It's not a shark, it's a fish.
Fish.
It's a fish.
It's so cute.
I want to have some too.
It looks fun.
I want to use the same studio.
I want to be the MC.
I want to be the first or the second.
We made it ourselves.
I really wanted to try it.
It's like the first and last time.
That's right.
It's been a while since that.
I think I want to try it for the first time.
You've done a lot.
I've done a lot.
I always try my best.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to take the camera myself.
I want to do it.
That's right.
Yamato and Sendai.
Yamato runs and I support him.
That's right.
That was fun.
Thank you very much.
I want you to look at it again.
It's all bare.
It's bare now, but it's a different one-sided flower.
That's nice.
I don't have any impression of Chii-chan.
I wonder what it is.
But that's not it?
Hime-tan is...
The beam is...
I think it came out with that style.
That's right.
Hime-tan Beam
That's where I was named.
That's where I was born.
The second one.
Right here, in the studio, Asuka is...
Don't lose, don't lose!
That's right.
But from there, it goes up.
Can I do it for the first time?
I've grown up.
From the second.
I got it.
You're kind.
I'm Imei-kyun.
Why are you acting like that?
Wait!
That's cute!
What about you, Chi-chan?
What was impressive?
There was a barbecue and bowling.
There was a bowling.
Fuji-kun was there.
At that time, there was a strike.
Chi-chan was good, wasn't she?
There were a lot of strikes.
I thought it was amazing.
I didn't know I could do that for the first time.
I didn't know that.
It was my first time.
It was amazing.
It was like a new discovery.
I didn't have to do it.
It was like a game.
There were a lot of stories.
It was fun.
For me...
For me, it was...
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
For me, it was Yamato.
Yamato.
The one you showed me.
Ah, there was that one too.
There was that one too.
What could it be?
Fuji-Q is Fuji-Q.
It's really fun.
It's all good memories.
I can't sleep.
Please look forward to the next video!
I can't do it.
Nagashima is so cute.
Please do it.
Everyone.
Next time, let's say goodbye.
Let's do it.
Please do it.
Say bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
I can't hear you.
Hi, we just started our talk show here in Nogizaka.
This time, I would like to talk with these members,
Nakada Kanna, Misa-senpai, Asuka Saito, and Yuri Saito.
What should we talk about?
We have a guest today, right?
I heard about it, but was I wrong?
I think it might be the first big guest in Nogizaka City.
Everyone, please be careful.
Wait, I'm nervous. What should I do?
Everyone, please stand in line.
Please put your bangs up.
Who is it? I'm really curious.
I'm really curious.
I wonder if I can talk properly.
Please put your bangs up.
Cute.
I'm nervous.
I'm looking forward to it.
Everyone, please stand in line.
The big guest is here.
Oh! Big! Big! Big!
It's really big!
It's so big that there's a lot of flamingos!
So, the real big guest is...
Well, well, well...
The one who's alive is Miho!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
Miho, you were the 7th guest.
You suddenly became the center.
How was it?
I learned a lot!
Miho-chan, make your voice louder!
Thank you very much!
You've grown up, haven't you?
You're proud of yourself, aren't you?
When I was chosen, I was like,
I thought, is this going to be okay?
I thought I was really nervous.
Nanase is a star, isn't she?
She's not here.
She's not here, but...
I wanted to talk about this.
I wanted to talk about the fact that I often cry.
That's what it means.
So when I was called, I cried a lot.
You were shaking, weren't you?
I wanted to say, is this going to be okay?
You've grown up, haven't you?
Yeah, I'm a sweet potato.
That's a lot.
There's something we're doing here.
Miho, are you watching?
I'm watching!
Let's listen to it.
It's like you've prepared an answer.
I'm watching.
I remember the scene that was good.
I'm watching!
Wait, wait, wait.
Sorry!
I didn't say anything.
Kyoto sightseeing is pretty new.
Yeah.
I didn't say Kyoto sightseeing?
I did.
It was the end of the year.
Oh, I see.
I think it was the fan.
How interesting!
The atmosphere is getting better.
We're under the sea.
Yeah, yeah.
I love you under the sea.
We're under the sea.
I want to go to the sports festival.
I think I've done it before.
You've done it before, haven't you?
I've done a lot of sports.
I've done a lot of live shows.
I've done a lot of DVDs.
I've done a lot of CDs.
I love Nogizaka Sports Festival.
I've done a lot of sports.
Did you watch Nogizaka Sports Festival?
Yes, I did.
She said she's watching Doki Doki, so can I ask her a
difficult question?
What is it?
Who do you like the most among the members?
It's hard to answer
I know
Miyu-tama
Please be honest
Close your eyes, put out your hand, and ask the person
you chose to shake your hand.
This is so embarrassing!
Ask them to come up to you.
Kana-san!
Wait!
Sorry! What's wrong?
Something got on my hand.
Wait, wait, wait!
I thought you might come up to me.
I didn't come up to you, so...
I thought you might say,
I can't choose this corner.
I'm sorry!
I'm always surprised.
My feet hit my knees when I stood up.
I knew it before I was called.
Kana-san!
I'm so happy!
She's the same type as me.
Why are you so annoying?
What's wrong with Kana-chan?
I don't know much about boys.
But Kana is good at it.
She's good at it.
That's weird.
Why do you like Kana-san?
She's been telling me about it lately.
I'm hungry.
Why?
Riku-senpai is really...
It's different, isn't it?
That's right.
Really?
But it was really good.
That's right.
I came all the way home.
On the contrary, it's hard to think about it.
It's a little hard.
What about Yuri?
Yuri is always smiling and funny.
That's great.
If you talk to me, I'll be happy.
Then the bad part.
The bad part?
Why is it bad?
I don't like it.
I didn't choose it because it was dangerous.
I'll take it back.
Atsuta said she wanted to get along with me.
It's easy to talk to her, so I'd like to be friends.
I want to be close to you.
You mean, I want to be close to you after I deeply love you.
I love you so much.
I have a question. I don't look at people at all.
It's a very personal question.
To get along with people who don't look at people and
people who don't look at people,
People who don't look at people should go.
If you come in a hurry, you'll get sick.
I'm happy.
I look at people a lot, so I don't have time to come.
I should have come in a hurry.
I'm glad I experienced it.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I wonder if there are people who don't look at people.
There are a lot of people who don't look at people.
I'm going to attack.
Attacking attitude.
I don't want to be pulled.
Attacking attitude is important.
I haven't said yet.
Don't say it yet.
I don't have a haircut.
That's the problem.
It's hard to say.
Are you okay?
We are under 18.
Miu is the last one.
I want you to tell your goal to the camera.
Who will go first?
What is the best part of Kana's 8th album?
Best part?
My brother's...
Your brother?
I said your brother.
It's the best part from my point of view.
It's the best part.
My brother loves dancing.
I don't know how much he dances in the music video.
The song is good and the dance is good.
It's a song that makes you cry.
That's why.
I want you to see me dancing.
I want you to copy me.
I want you to come to the concert.
I want to do my best at the concert and the handshake event.
It's a little difficult, but there was a curfew, right?
I think the 8th album will change how Gizaka will be.
I hope you don't miss it.
I'll do my best.
I'm very serious.
I want to do my best at the handshake event.
Misa-senpai, you've been hanging out a lot.
I haven't been hanging out.
You just saw the cameraman, right?
Azuka's mouth was so red.
I said, ah.
That's right.
I hope you enjoy it.
Misa-senpai wants you to come to the handshake event.
I want you to come to the handshake event.
I'm underage.
I hope you enjoy it.
I want you to come to the handshake event.
Ash, please come.
You were just listening to me.
I meant to say the handshake event.
You were told that before.
Ash will be a high school student.
That's also a good idea.
First of all,
The number of handshakes has increased.
Congrats!
It's a little different.
I'm really lonely when I think about it, so I want you
to wear it.
I want to wear it.
Is there any change?
There is, there is.
Say it, say it.
What is it, Yuri?
I've been emphasizing that I'm a high school student
for a while now.
Because I'm a grandma.
Hurry up and make me a higher person.
Don't you think so?
I followed you a lot.
I'm definitely not going to follow Asuka anymore.
Stop it.
I told you to say it.
Is it you?
I didn't say it.
Yu-san is also a grandma.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's talk about grandma.
Calm down.
Unfortunately, we're having a handshake event in
Yokohama right now.
The 5th part is about to begin.
It's already started.
Misa and Hana will be in the handshake event in the 5th part.
Everyone is waiting for Misa, so I'll go.
Don't hang up at the end.
I'm going.
I have to go.
Hurry up and go.
Bye bye.
Hana and Misa.
Have a good time.
I'm going.
I'm leaving.
See you later.
It's probably going to be Nogikoko after 4 months.
Nogikoko! Thank you!
Bye bye!
Thank you, guest!
This is the last one.
Let's continue.
The 8th song is...
I think it's a song for high school girls.
The lyrics, the melody, and the dance...
I want people to sympathize with it.
I think it will resonate with girls in high school.
Seitan has been saying that this song is too good.
Seitan loves sad songs about love.
The song has been playing in the car all the time.
I hope many girls in high school listen to it.
I think the generation is the same.
Do you have a favorite phrase?
My favorite phrase is...
What was it?
There it is.
The one that comes out early.
It's like Christmas and Valentine's Day.
It's lonely, but it's not lonely.
It's strong.
It's like a modern girl.
I didn't know that.
I heard the song title.
I heard it, but the lyrics are too fast.
It's like this.
It's flowing.
I'll listen to Miyotam's point.
I want you to listen to Miyotam's point.
Bye for now.
I wonder what it is. Even if you say it's the end, suddenly.
Probably Nogikoko will be held in four months.
I think it's been four months.
I want you to check it out by looking at the homepage.
That's all from Yokohama Pacifico.
It was Nogikoko. Bye-bye.
Sui-chan's shoes aren't broken, are they?
I'm Sui-chan.
It's amazing. Nogizaka.
It feels like Nogizaka around Heroniko.
Thank you very much.
Do we have a live performance today?
Wow!
Actually, we have a surprise one-on-one performance for
the 8th single.
It's a solo performance.
The chosen members will perform.
And this is the special stage.
This is it!
We're the first to perform!
Wow! What's going to happen with this?
What do you mean?
Isn't this going to open up?
This is going to open up.
It's hard to understand.
It's really hard to understand.
Okay, I got it.
This is going to open up.
And this is going to be the floor.
Wow!
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
The first single, which will be released on April 2nd,
has finally been completed!
Today is the first performance, and...
That's right, today is the first performance.
I'm really nervous.
It's not a normal stage.
I'm a little nervous on this track.
Everyone, please watch with warm eyes until the end.
Thank you.
When I realized it, I fell in love with you at some point
Every time I think of you, it hurts
Love, love, love, love, love, love
How many times have I been rejected?
I always believed that this was fate
But for some reason, I hurt myself
I decided from the past that I would definitely fall in love
I pretended not to be interested when I was rejected
I grew up for myself
Birthdays, Christmas, and Valentine's Day
The strength I can spend alone
I finally found it
I'm curious about your reason
I want to make a phone call and hear your voice
The days I suffered so much
Even my tears dried up
When I realized it, I fell in love with you at some point
Every time I think of you, it hurts
When I realized it, I don't want to admit it
Maybe my heart is fragile because I'm in love
I tried to think that I was alone
If I try to be normal, I don't feel good at all
Until the day you introduced me to you
I'll be jealous of you and make you love me
The only thing I didn't notice
I didn't know how to say it
But I can't tell you
I was looking for you in the mirror
I knew from the beginning
Someday I'll fall in love with you
When our eyes met
I didn't say a word
I knew from the beginning
You were a special person
Love is something that can be given
I couldn't resist
Even if I hold back my emotions, my breath hurts
Even though I love you so much
If I put it into words, it seems to disappear
When I realized it, when I realized it
Someday I'll fall in love with you
Every time I think of you
I feel sad
When I realized it, I don't want to admit it
Maybe my heart is fragile because I'm in love
Maybe my heart is fragile
I have no choice but to accept it
Thank you very much.
Please take care and go home.
Bye bye.