AISubs
Yeah!
It's been a while since I've seen you all!
It's been a while.
It's been a while since we've been to the No-Gi- Go-Go.
Since last time's NAKI HATSUI,
I didn't know, but it's been 4 months!
That's early!
That's so soon!
I didn't think this would happen.
No, that's not it.
4 months is probably a bit too soon.
You're almost there.
That's right.
Today is the day of the release of the 7th single,
VALENTA, in Pacifico Yokohama!
That's great!
We're having a fan meeting right now!
We're filming here with the colors.
What are we doing today?
We're having a fan meeting today.
Today, we're having a talk show with the members of Nogizaka!
We'll be reflecting on our 2nd anniversary live in Yokohama.
We'll be talking about the future of Nogizaka and also
about the various members' Marifujo.
We'll be having fun with the members.
So we'll be talking with everyone!
Is everyone okay?
I'm a little nervous because I'm the MC.
I'm worried about everyone, but I'm going to the
handshake event today, so I'm going to wear my school
uniform.
I'm interested in the 3rd grade of high school, so I'm
wearing my school uniform.
What?
Did you change your clothes after work?
No, I didn't.
I changed my clothes and ran away because I was too embarrassed.
Why are you embarrassed?
I was so embarrassed.
It was because of you.
I gave you a
What did you do at the end?
What is it?
The venue got bigger and we could see 360 degrees.
We could turn around.
Wasn't it really scary?
It was scary.
When we did it for the first time, it was really scary.
We were spinning, and the round stage was spinning too.
It was really scary.
I don't know which one is which.
It's been a while.
Is it cold?
Which one is which?
I'm from Japan.
Oh, I forgot about MC.
Oh, that's right.
We were on the same team.
I made a mistake before the MC.
I couldn't get out.
I got nervous.
I was in the next song.
I was in high school.
I was in the same team as Shira.
So I went to the practice room.
I thought it was bad.
I forgot about MC.
I forgot.
It was like a script.
My mom came to see it, too.
Minami, I thought it was a script.
I was surprised.
That's right.
Please enjoy the wonderful music video!
I don't remember what it was, but I forgot to wear a
small item in the song.
What is a small item?
I don't know.
I forgot to wear it, and I was caught by the fans.
I'm sorry.
Was it fun?
Yes.
I had a hard time turning around.
That's right.
What was it again?
Minami, what was it again?
I don't remember.
Well, you know.
Whisper the demo.
Whisper the demo!
The demo is really good.
I was told to do it at home.
I'm influenced by this kind of thing.
I'll do my best.
Here you go.
By the way, are you going to do it at the handshake event?
Wait, wait, wait.
I was just going to talk about doing it.
What?
I'm done talking about doing it.
Are you going to do it?
I'm done.
That's enough.
I'm done talking about it.
What's tomato?
What was mine?
What was it?
It's like a tomato.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't it a burnt potato?
It's a burnt potato.
That's right.
It's a small-sized potato.
It's perfect.
I've been told forever since the day the video was broadcast.
I'm so tired.
I'm always told that's okay.
What was it?
Mental age.
I'm not happy at all.
I'm really troubled by this.
What is this?
Close it properly.
Close it? What do you mean close it?
From the bottom?
Then let's all do it from the bottom.
Let's do it from the top.
From here?
Is it around here?
What is this?
If you go down from the bottom, you can see it.
I'll go.
Ah, it's closed.
I don't know.
Is it okay?
It's popular.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Please do it properly.
Are you okay?
I will tell you about it.
My name is Shinji, and I will be working as a member of the team.
Thank you very much.
My name is Shimae Shin, and I am a junior high school student.
I would like to do my best with a sense of
responsibility, so I look forward to working with you.
Yes.
We never worry about the fans or those who are out in
the country.
We always trust our members.
NiziU's debut world champion, NiziU's debut field,
I'm really happy to be able to work with you.
We've finished all the music for the music video.
We've already finished a great song.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
We worked together this time.
It's amazing.
I'm proud of you.
We'll continue to work together.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much.
...because I am also fond of their woes, the sensuality
of their songs.
So, the last special performance of Barretta is over.
First of all, Mai-Chu.
Mai-Chu has been promoted from the second generation to
the second generation.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time I've been here.
What do you think, Nugikoko?
I've only been on the show once before,
but it was about 10 seconds long,
so I'd like to do a little more this time.
Thank you.
I'm going to introduce myself now.
First of all, let me introduce myself.
I'm Shin Uchimai, 22 years old and the oldest in Niki.
Nice to meet you.
She is 22 years old.
Excuse me.
I'm Hinako, the daughter of Rikisei.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say that.
I want to introduce you to Mai-chan.
I want to introduce you.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
I want to introduce you to Mai-chan.
Mai-chan is...
Twenty...
I was a little surprised.
How old are you?
I'm 22 years old.
You're 22 years old.
You're very young.
Young?
Yes.
I'm 22 years old, but I'm still too young.
I'm 16 years old inside.
Really?
The other day, I was really drunk.
I'm not in the mood to wear a 13-kilo outfit, so I'm
excited to wear it.
It's cute.
It might be unexpected.
I'm still a little confused about that kind of style.
I didn't know much about it until now.
I was shooting a PV with under members.
I'm not used to it that much.
I was really busy.
It was a music video shoot that was packed in one day.
Are you busy?
Busy?
It was pretty tight on that day.
That's right.
I did my best.
How was your first music video shoot?
It was more than I expected.
I thought I was going to shoot a lot of scenes.
What do you mean by that?
What did you imagine at first?
I thought it would be more like dancing through one
song and editing it.
I thought it was simple.
I thought I was going to shoot a lot of scenes.
I didn't do it many times.
I did it many times.
I threw it like this.
I threw a piece of paper and made it look like it was falling.
I ran all the time.
I ran with all the under members.
There are about 50 times, right?
About 50 times.
Did you do it too much?
I didn't do it too much.
I thought it was hard.
From the front and from the side.
Well, well, well.
It's like riding a bike.
It's going to be hard.
Do you know me?
Wait a minute, I know you!
You didn't know me?
You're Hinako Kitano, right?
That's right.
Yes.
I know you, I know you.
In detail?
In detail.
You're called Ki-chan, right?
Ki-chan.
How old are you?
I'm 17 years old.
I remember you well.
Ami doesn't remember people very well.
Don't say that.
I'm shy.
I'm sorry.
We're not used to each other yet.
I'll get along with you.
Thank you.
Wait, you are quite aggressive.
You tease me a lot.
Lenarin is wearing a mask.
What's wrong?
I have a cold.
I'm wearing a mask.
I feel uncomfortable.
I'm sorry.
I have a cold.
Lenarin is wearing a mask.
There were so many people born in 1994, and there were
about eight of them.
That's why we all wore uniforms last year.
It's kind of nostalgic.
That's right.
It's amazing.
It will be cosplay in April, right?
I'm going to cosplay, too.
Really? Cosplay?
I've been cosplaying for four years.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
We've shown all the units songs for free.
Like Kourmei.
It was the first time I performed on a big stage, so it
felt really good to sing.
It was really good.
When I was an MC, I was like,
Oh, I'm an MC.
I did it a little bit, but
I was just...
For some reason,
There was no scene where I came out as a farm girl.
I don't know what it is.
Ashida Mara-chan, Kouda Kumi-san,
Inoue Yousui-san.
I don't know which one.
But
It's not a priority quality.
It's a priority quality.
Really?
It was good.
On the contrary, everyone said that the quality was low.
What should I do?
It's been a long time since I've done it, so I'm
wondering if I'll be told again.
But it was great.
I was accepted.
No, no, no.
Mr. Ashiyama.
That...
It's Ashida Mana.
But it's a little better.
That's right.
I'm really not good at dancing, so I'm not good at
dancing like this.
I'm not good at dancing like this.
But you can do it.
It was really good.
I was in the middle of a break.
That's right.
It was really cute.
I was in the middle of a break.
I was the last one to appear in the surprise.
I danced Marika in the center stage.
Were you nervous?
It was crazy.
We were taking a break.
The audience was taking a break.
I didn't think they would come out.
They were drinking water and taking a break.
I thought there would be few people.
I was worried.
I was confused.
But I did my best to switch on and dance.
When I saw the dance, I was excited.
It made me happy.
It was easy for me.
Yes.
After the dance, I was very angry.
That's good.
That's all.
During the break, it was the most difficult for me.
After that, I calmed down and made a lot of mistakes.
That's right.
How was it?
I was taking a break.
Standing on the stage of Yokohama Arena alone is really amazing.
It's amazing.
There are few people going out.
I could see everyone.
Akari was also in a state where she could see the audience.
I could see that she was dancing with her eyes focused.
That's terrible.
What should I do?
When I was taking a break, I was seriously taking a break.
I thought it was real.
Really, really.
Did you run away?
I wanted to run at full speed.
I made a mistake with the cake and the cake
I don't care about the little things
The contents of my wallet
I wonder if I'll get it someday
A long list of
Sword and sword
At the same time
When you're in trouble, use the magic of words to transform!
Marika, Marika, Marika, Marika, Marika, Rika, Rika, Rika, Marika
You can call me Marika
Marika Rika
Marika, when you're feeling down
My, my, my magic
I'll cast it on you in the black town era
Marika Marika Marika Marika
Marika Rika Rika Marika
Marika, it doesn't matter if you're feeling down
Marika Marika Marika Marika
Marika Rika Rika Marika
It doesn't matter if you're feeling down
Kari kari marika
SE7EN London
Please look forward to it!
So, I'm going to be a member of UNDER, and I'm going to
be a member of MIGHTY.
Please look forward to it!
It's my first time to be a member of MIGHTY.
I'm going to be a member of UNDER, so I'll do my best
to let more people know about me.
Thank you very much.