AISubs
It has started!
Ready, set, go!
Let's go!
Yay!
You are looking like your lips.
Wait a minute.
Don't you want to lose weight and go to bungee jumping
competition?
Really?
You're saying the truth?
I can do it.
For the time being, for the time being,
We, Miria and I will challenge Bandit.
I can do it.
Junna and Kotoko are going to ride a roller coaster
called Momonga.
And we are going to ride Crazy Stone.
We are going to the haunted house Mukuroya.
I'm going to jump from a height equivalent to the
seventh floor of the bell.
Let's go to the haunted house.
I want you to challenge the haunted house.
How is it?
I can't laugh.
What?
It's hard.
It's hard?
I can't laugh.
You have to do your best.
I haven't been to haunted houses since I was in kindergarten.
You haven't been?
I haven't been.
You're a senior.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm scared.
How about you, Yuzuru?
I'm not good at dark places.
Really?
That's the worst.
What are you going to do?
Hang in there.
I want you to challenge one by one for the haunted house.
Don't cry.
It's just a word.
You can decide which one to enter.
It's okay. Just go ahead and do it.
Didn't we just do it?
That's right.
Let's do it first.
Isn't it too easy?
Isn't it scary?
That's right.
Ah, but...
It's okay. It's okay to play rock-paper-scissors.
It's not okay to play rock-paper-scissors.
Is there a cameraman?
A cameraman?
I thought there was a cameraman.
Isn't it okay?
Yone-san.
Ah, I don't want to.
So, more or less, is there a prince? Let's go out!
Let's go! Let's go! Since it's Three, I'll go with
you.). Is it a deal then. Mandarin English is a big
deal! Yone- Liar. It's a deal then. Okay? First, Yone's
house. Which means we choose Yone. After that, Yamazaki
will take on the challenge. Let's do our best! After
this, it is Yamazaki who will challenge us.
I'm going.
Good luck!
Bye!
What?
No way!
Oh no!
Scary, scary, scary, scary...
Oh, no!
Where, where, where?
Oh, that's the camera man.
Ahhhhhhhh!
Scary, scary, scary, scary...
Scary...
Eh?
I'm scared.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What?
I found it.
I think something is coming.
Hello.
This is the magic brush.
Thank you.
I'm brushing.
Not yet.
I can't do it anymore.
Thank you.
Get rid of the
I was surprised.
Oh no, oh no.
Good job!
I was really scared!
Oh no!
How was it?
Scary!
I can't hear you.
Oh, it's coming down!
My sweat is coming out.
I've never heard a girl's voice.
I was really surprised.
Good job, good job!
Well, the pre-recording is over.
It's over.
The pre-recording is over.
Next, I want Lena to go.
Good luck!
Oh, no.
Wasn't it better before?
Are you okay?
Good luck!
No! Don't come this way!
There is a monster!
I can't see the front.
What? What?
I was scared.
I can't see the front.
What? What? What?
Oh, this is magic.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Who's this?
Eh? Ah, this?
Eh? What should I do?
It won't eat me.
Let's go home!
Thank you!
You saved our friend!
She's shaking so much!
Ah, this is bad.
Welcome back! Welcome back!
How was it?
Was it scary?
I was scared. I thought she was going to cry.
She was crying without screaming.
I couldn't hear her voice at all.
She said to take off the tooth pick, but she didn't.
I couldn't take it off.
I couldn't get out.
I didn't see anything.
Calm down!
I was scared.
I hate it.
You hate it? Do you want to go in again?
Do you want to go in?
Eh? Do you want to go in?
I was scared. I got carried away by the guide.
Then, here.
Raise your hand if you haven't entered the haunted house.
Come forward.
Including me, though.
The person who loses by rock-paper-scissors will enter
the haunted house.
Eh? That's not true!
That's not true!
The person who loses by rock-paper-scissors will enter
the haunted house.
Ready, set, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
You're my idol!
I won!
Ready, set, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won!
Kotoko-chan!
The person who loses by rock-paper-scissors will enter
the haunted house.
Don't say it!
Do you want to confirm it later?
I'm saying it.
I don't think she said it.
I didn't hear it.
Let's do our best!
It's okay!
You can do it!
Do your best, Kotoko!
Are you afraid?
Are you not good at it?
I've never been in the haunted house.
It's your first time, right?
You can do it!
Let's do our best!
Let's go!
The person who loses by rock-paper-scissors will enter
the haunted house.
I'm sure you're nervous, but do your best!
Go for it!
It's okay! It's okay!
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm scared.
There is a monster ahead.
Who is it?
There is a monster that the big fish has summoned.
What is this?
Something is coming.
No, no, no.
Please don't come.
Are you ready?
What should I do?
This was the dance after this!
The person who danced wakefully
wants to run away…
But he didn't take running away so much so…
Why do I have to do this?
I don't want to do this!
Who is it?
No, no, no
No, don't come, please
I don't like this
This is it, isn't it?
Is it okay if I put it in like this?
Cute, cute
Thank you
No, no, no
I'm tired
What was the last one?
Was it okay? Was it scary?
But it was cute
Was it cute?
Was it scary?
It was like a plan
The voice was cute
But I heard the scream
The scary part was scary
Was it scary?
The scary part was
No, no, no
It was like a plan
I'm glad I was able to challenge
The first Bakiyashiki
It was clear
Thank you for your hard work
Next, I would like to challenge Bandit
I will challenge Bandit this time
How is it? Are you good at roller coasters?
I'm not good at it
I'm not good at it either
This is amazing
It falls
What are you going to do?
The angle of death
We will do our best at the angle of death
Please cheer for us
Let's go
I'm going to sing
I can see it from far away.
At a baseball field near my house, I hit the ball and
scored a goal.
I just need you to fly to where we are.
No, it's too late.
If you don't take the first step, nothing will happen.
Don't give me an answer in your head.
Is it a bad thing to fall in love?
I can't do it anymore.
I know I can't do it anymore.
Our mark on the court is that your marriage will be
canceled as a matter of fact.
I can't do it anymore.
I know you can't do it anymore.
I can't do this! I can't do this anymore!
I'm gonna-
AAAAAH!
I'm gonna die!
Ahhhh!!!!!
?!
Wait..
I thought it was a little sweeter
I can't sing
Does he sing that scared?
What what!
The waist. Is your waist OK
Hey, hey, hey. Are you alive?
I'm laughing.
I'm scared. Do your best.
Don't do that.
Look at this.
Well,
Have a nice day.
I'm going.
I'm going to climb.
I'm scared.
I'm under so much pressure.
I'm going to climb.
What should I do? I'm all alone.
I'm scared.
Oh, no! I left a note!
Well, I'll sing a barrette.
Ready, set, go!
Until the end of the school year,
Girls are going to the park to have a meeting.
Oh, it's high!
while calling the
one on
and
the
It was a coincidence that our eyes met, and I felt as
if my heart had been peeped at.
I thought my heart was getting peeped at, but it wasn't.
It was a coincidence that our eyes met, and I felt as
if my heart had been peeped at.
I thought my heart was getting peeped at, but it wasn't.
It was so cold!
I didn't notice it!
I'm so scared!
Ah!
Oh my god!
What is this?
Ah!
Ah! I'm wet!
I'm so scared!
Ah!
Oh my god!
I'm so scared!
Ah!
Is it over?
I'm so scared!
Ah!
Wait!
You're all wet!
What?
Good job!
I sang!
You sang?
Yes!
You're not going to stand up, are you?
What is this? It's scary!
It's scary, isn't it?
How was it?
Everyone's wet.
The first one to get wet was Naoko.
Yeah, we all did our best.
The second one to get wet was Naoko.
It was an unobstructed version.
How many times are you going to fall?
It's long!
Karin is the front and Miria is the back.
Both are scary places.
It was scary, but we did our best.
Thank you!
Let's go to the next attraction!
Let's go!
The next attraction is Momonga!
I can't imagine standing on a roller coaster.
Yeah, standing on it.
And if you look at the back, you can see that it's a
little rounded.
That means?
It's going to be like this, right?
It's going to be like this.
It's scary that it's going to be like this.
Are you okay? Your face is still there.
Don't you ride a roller coaster?
I don't ride it.
I can't ride it.
But I want you two to do your best, so I want you to
go, but I have an announcement to make here.
I want you two to do your best, so I want you to go,
but I have an announcement to make here.
It's not bad, it's not bad.
Ready, set, go!
The first one is Keiichi-chan!
Yes, let's go!
Oh!
The second one is Keiichi-chan!
Ok, now Kana's turn.
Ai Kojisho! Ai Kojisho! Ai Kojisho!
You did it!
The next day
Oh my god!
Oh my god! I'm scared!
Bye bye!
The next day
Oh my God!
Run away!
I'm scared!
I think I'm going to throw up.
I'm scared.
I can't use my strength.
Is it different from standing?
My pants...
Is it better to sit down?
I want to sit down.
This is crazy.
Can't you see it spinning?
It's crazy.
It's like a mummy.
It was hard.
This is no good.
This is not a mummy.
The Guys Who Can Do It
I'm scared.
I'm going to die.
It's so high.
Why is it so high?
No! No! No!
I don't want to!
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
I did my best.
It was so hot.
I'm scared.
Are you alright?
Wait! No!
No! No!
No!
Yada, yada, yada, yada, ehehe.
I'm scared! I'm scared!
3 parts tank
Really?
Thank you very much.
It's all right?
It's all right.
Are you ok?
Standing straight?
No, just standing up.
Standing straight, huh?
I got it in my head.
I'm sorry, mom.
How was it?
Was it okay?
I couldn't see anything.
You couldn't see anything?
Good job.
Any other impressions?
No? You couldn't scream?
I don't want to.
You won't scream?
You were just pretending.
The three of us are done, but...
Out of the blue...
Iori and Yonezawa-san...
We're going to ride it!
I love it!
I'm watching it and it looks fun.
It looks fun.
It's amazing.
There's even a girl without a waist.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
We're going to ride it.
Oh my god!
Wanko!
Also, an animal will appear as soon as he gets close to mother.
isn't a bonus news from the
Internet?
I said there was a bonus news from the Internet.
What should I do?
I think he'll say something and come back.
I'm a little scared.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna fall!
What should I do?
ah ah ah Take me oh oh oh oh
ah ha ha
Ah, how did it go?
I'm scared!
Help me. Please help me.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
I'm so scared!
Thank you for your hard work.
I was more scared.
But...
After the show, I didn't feel any strength.
I was scared.
When I saw you from the outside,
I couldn't feel any strength in my legs.
I felt like I was a crab.
How about Kotoko?
Well... 360 degrees.
I thought I had centrifugal force, but I didn't have it at all.
It's dangerous.
It's going to fall out of your head.
I don't know why.
My neck is sore.
Ayane, thank you for your hard work.
How was it? Were you scared?
Ayane, didn't you cry?
I didn't cry.
I was crying.
I'm okay.
I can't walk after the show, so I crouched down on Junna's belly.
I didn't crouched down.
I was standing properly.
I wasn't standing properly.
Let's see.
But I did it.
I'm glad.
And at the end,
I only saw you two having fun.
I was crying.
Both of us are already speechless. I laughed so hard.
But I wanted you to raise your hand at this level.
We both went too far.
I was asking for reactions. I'll ask
But you did your best, both of you. Thank you. good work.
Let's go to the next attraction.