The song you copied this time is a
famous Christmas song, "Last Christmas".
The singer is WAM, a British duo.
The song you copied this time is a
famous Christmas song, "Last Christmas".
First of all, don't be shy.
I thought it was "Pressure" at the end.
It's like "Pressure" when you don't have
a partner.
I listened to "Pressure" at the end.
I'm a person who can't have a
girlfriend.
But because you don't have a girlfriend,
you're the pressure of a lonely man.
She was excellent last time, too.
Is she a typical優等生 type?
That's right.
I don't know the word "modesty."
(Singing "Save Me From This" by M.I.C.)
No way!
I'm sorry, but there's no lyrics at all.
The lyrics are correct.
I'm in a good mood today.
I see.
It's like a party.
I don't like parties.
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart.
This is a serenade from Jesus.
I felt that someone special.
Amazing!
It's slightly different, but the sound
is almost perfect.
That's right.
That's amazing!
This is already 95 points.
This is...
The expression "Give me five" that was
introduced in this show before
What does it mean to high-five?
The answer is...
Akimoto-san?
Yes
I'm confident
I don't know
Yes, please
Yes
Give me five
Yeah
Awesome
The expression "Give me 5" means that
you have 5 fingers, so you have to say
"Give me 5 fingers", which means "Let's
high-touch"
cute and
Big size
Black black, okay. Oh, thank you
Hats
Big black hats
Why is your head so big?
That's right
I didn't know
I asked Santa
That was a cute wish.
By the way, "just size" is a Japanese
English word.
In this case, you can say "perfect size"
or "perfect fit".
Next up is Ms. Kitano. Here we go.
I'm Santa Claus. What would you like for
Christmas?
Please give me...
Um...
A lot.
It's English. English.
Please give me...
Huh?
Please give me "Iru-don"
What?
"Iru"
What's "don"?
"Don"
"Iru"
And...
"Hakumai"
"Hakumai"?
"Rice"
"Rice"?
"Iru" and "Rice"?
"Alive"
"Iru"
"Iru" and "Rice"? "Cooked eel"? "Rice"?
"Cooked eel rice"?
"Grilled eel" and "Grilled ball"
Next is the question about the word
"Irasuto"
(meow)
and a lot more
What is it?
Number 2 is carrot
It's a carrot
Let's see
Kitano-san's answer
Kitano-san
Correct!
As a robot
The bottom is a car, the top is a robot,
and the bottom is a robot car.
Do you think a robot car will come out?
I think a lot of things will come out.
I think it will be mean.
So I think there will be something.
You have to change it.
You have to change the car and the
robot.
Didn't you know the meaning of the
carrot?
Thank you for watching.
I couldn't read "carrot". If I was told
"carrot", I would answer "carrot".
Oh, I see. You couldn't read the "c".
Next is Miskitano.
Ant is an ant, but what is Miskitano's
picture?
What is it?
Ant.
What is this?
It's an ant.
It's an ant pumpkin.
From my point of view, it only looks
like a joke.
I don't know.
There was a movie called Ant-man, right?
I haven't seen it.
Are you angry?
I have another question.
Hoshino-san.
What is this?
What do you mean?
It's an interpretation in my head.
It's a word like a confession.
The art of love.
Your...
It's really difficult to make a
confession into a picture.
If it was an ant, I'd draw it.
Let's look at Hoshino-san's answer.
Wait, what is this?
What is this?
It's like a festival.
What are you trying to draw?
It's like a hippopotamus.
Native American.
It's like an American.
Is this a limbo dance or something?
Next is Akimoto-san's answer.
What is this?
Is this a circle?
This is a hippo.
This is a hippo!
You're not good at drawing.
Next, we'll check out the questions from
the test.
This is the first question.
It's a basic question.
This is Hoshino-san's answer.
Sensei, did you play baseball?
It's the first time I've heard of it.
But the name "Yasukouchi" is rare.
I thought "Yasukouchi" would be more
fitting.
So that's why you chose "Kouchi".
I didn't know you were so good at
trading.
That baseball team is going to be
strong.
Next is this English sentence.
This way of using "life" is something
I've been taught by Nogiego many times.
If you can't do this, I'm a little sad.
Kitano-san.
It's long, it's long, it's long.
I know how much he loves me.
That's amazing.
That's totally different.
He, that man.
Well, he.
And, woman.
When a man and a woman come out, I think
it's a relationship between a man and a
woman.
And, looks. I look at looks. I like
likes. Ah, it's a relationship between a
man and a woman.
Ah, so when I look at him, I can tell
how much I like her.
Suddenly?
Next is this question. If the
conversation is successful, it will be
correct.
There is a building that looks like a
school.
Is that a hospital?
He is asking if that is a hospital.
Normally, he would say, "No, that is a
school."
Mr. Kitano.
OK.
OK!
He said OK.
He is very confident.
He is going to participate in the
Olympics, so don't give him
irresponsible answers.
First, the 4th place.
37 points.
Mr. Ikoma.
Amazing!
4th place.
But, but...
Amazing.
4th place, but still 37 points.
3rd place.
It's the highest in the past test.
It's more than 30 points.
Amazing.
3rd place, 58 points.
Kaogo-san.
2nd place, 68 points.
It's almost 70%.
Takayama-san.
Wow, amazing!
The winner is...
92 points!
It's almost perfect.
Akimoto-san!
Thank you very much!
I did it!
Now, here is the announcement of the 4th
place.
First, the 5th place.
The 5th place has two people with the
same score.
36 points.
Kitano and Hoshino.
The rest are 7th and last.
Now, the last announcement.
8th place is...
27 points.
Wada-san.
You can react so well.
So...
Among the top 4, there are 3 guests.
Sensei, what have you been doing for the
past 6 months?
I'm trying my best to teach you.
Here are the final 10 places.
Regular people, let's do our best a
little more.
From now on, I would like to play a game
to make you more familiar with English.
Thank you very much.
From now on, it's game time!
Of course, all the games will be played
in English.
Let's have fun and learn English.
First, the team will be divided into
teams.
Ms. Maaya and Ms. Nojo will be the
captains.
The members will be chosen by rock-
paper-scissors.
What is rock-paper-scissors in English?
This is a paper.
What?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors, go.
If it's Aiko, it's go.
Go.
Okay?
Are you ready?
One, two.
Rock, paper, scissors, go.
Oh.
The winner, Nojo-san,
Let's see. It's an English game.
That's right.
It's an English game.
The winner is...
Hirari-san.
That's good.
Takayama Kazumi-chan.
Why?
Isn't she a devil?
Why? Isn't she a devil?
There's a bit of a tricky part
It's a bit like "let's go"
I'm scared because I'm going to be low
on points
I see, so you're going to be serious
I'm going to be serious
[Rock, paper, scissors]
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
Well, Minami
Why? Why?
Wait a minute
Why? Why? You're number one.
No, no, I have a cute person here.
No, no, no.
It's Hina.
It's really funny.
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
Alright!
Ikoma-chan!
You can do it.
You can do it with your head.
I'm sure it's a fake.
I'm going to think about it
realistically.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
That's amazing.
Why?
I want someone who can speak English
here.
I want Natsu-san to do it.
Yay!
Isn't that a bit too much?
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's worse than that, Kitami-san.
It's starting to change a bit.
What do you mean it's changing a bit?
No, it's not. I love you.
What did you say?
Nakanishi-san!
It's a game!
Look, she's crying!
I'm the one who's crying!
It's a lie!
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
Suzuki-san!
No, no, wait!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I'm sorry!
That's amazing!
You did it!
It's a joke!
Kitano, you can do it this way.
Which way?
Wait a minute.
You did it!
Kitano, come here.
But I was the one who was hated the
most!
Cheer up, Mesquitano!
As you can see, there are 3 games in
total.
The team with more than 2 wins is the
winner.
The first game is...
The English game!
In English, you have to tell your
teammates about the topic and they have
to guess what it is.
The team that gets the most correct
answers wins.
Of course, Japanese and gestures are not
allowed.
Rock-paper-scissors. Team Nojo is
leading.
Come on, everybody. You can do it.
3, 2, 1, go!
Um...
Isn't it slow?
Four legs.
Lion.
No.
Slow, slow, slow.
Slow?
Slow, um...
Your movement is slow.
Big, small.
Small?
Big, small?
Turtle.
What should I say?
What?
Puzzle!
Next
Small
Mouse
People
People, small
Uki, uki, what?
No!
Pee-po!
Pee-po?
Child!
No, no!
Small!
Baby!
Hurry up!
It moves.
Drive.
You drive it.
Red.
Red fruit.
Apple.
Cold. Very cold.
White.
Snow.
Sit!
Sit down!
Chair!
Wow!
You're good!
Ah!
Ah...
I was going to order...
Ah, you're so cute!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Hurry up!
Soba!
I'll help you.
Mua.
Uu.
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
This is...
Sparkling...
Ah, so cute!
He did it!
So cute.
Thank you!
Wow!
[Literally, what a cutie]
Ah, so cute!
What was the first question?
Cat
Why slow?
I wanted to say slow
You got 6 questions right
Team Wada is in the lead
Will they be able to beat Team Nojo?
Are you ready?
Here we go
3, 2, 1, go
Lead, lead, lead
Book, book
Note, note
Read, read, read
Sorry, sorry
Shop, shop
Book, book
Read, read, read
Dictionary, stationary
If you don't know what it is, just pass
it.
Pass, pass, pass.
Ah, um, um...
Ah!
Wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
That, that, that.
Cold, cold, cold.
I don't know.
The sun!
"Water"
"Walking"
No!
"Umbrella"
Third single
That's right!
Is that okay?
I like people
People
I
Me
Grandmother
Love
Family?
Mother love
Mother of love
What?
Me
Small
White.
Black first.
Night star? No star?
No star!
Moon!
What is that shape?
Big fish?
Shark!
Time's up!
It was a big fish!
It's amazing that you came here.
Good job to both teams.
So the first game is a 6 vs 6 draw.
The next game is...
In English, Shiritori Game!
The rules are the same as the Japanese
shiritori.
You will do shiritori with the alphabet
of the English word.
However, the answer is to hold a balloon
that is getting bigger.
If you do shiritori three times in a
team before the balloon explodes, you
will clear it.
If it explodes, it's over at that point.
As a result of rock-paper-scissors, the
lead goes to Team Nojo.
OK, Team Nojo, are you ready? Let's go!
Ready, New York's K
Color
Kick, kick, kick
King Kong
Green
S?
Nine!
Eat!
Toe!
Elephant!
Te!
Ten!
"T"
yes yes
good good
"T"
Really?
again good?
true
ah, wait
the teacher is wearing it
ah, it's inflated
bring it
good good
go for it
quickly
hint hint hint
"H"
"A"
Apple Apple Apple
"E"
"G"
What did you say?
She's calm!
She's really calm!
Wait, isn't this paused?
It's moving, it's moving!
Hurry up and answer!
Can I?
G!
Anything is fine!
Eating!
G?
Grandmother!
Real!
3 weeks clear!
In the middle, Takayama-san was like,
"If you can't do it, it's fine, it's
fine."
I did it!
You did it!
Next up is Team Wada. Here we go!
Are you ready?
OK!
Ready?
Yeah!
OK, let's go!
Here we go.
Japan!
No!
One! One!
Fake! Fake!
Guitar!
Light!
Transparent?
Onigiri!
Onion!
Onion...
There's no onion!
E,E,E,E,E,E,E,E,E,E,E
Don't bring that one!
E,E,E,E,E,E,Eat!
Tiger
You're getting better!
Run, Run, Run!
More, more!
N,N,N,N,N,N
No, No!
Nose, Nose!
She is calm!
You can do it!
That was close!
8, 8, 8, 8
8, 8, 8
That was close!
3, 2, 1
Sonic!
That was close!
It was like a punishment for this team
Cain!
Clear!
If it's like this, you have to split it!
Do you want to split it?
No!
This is definitely not a trick!
Really?
(Screaming)
You idiot!
(Clapping)
What are you talking about?
This is scary.
I didn't say it, but I said "hey"
several times in the middle.
While I was saying "wow wow", "choro
choro" came out.
This time, the members received a final
test in advance.
Today, we will check not only the
results, but also the answers of the
members.
It's 100 out of 100.
It's a close battle.
This is the first episode of 2016.
We will have the members talk about
their plans for this year in English.
"I'll _____ this year."
"I'm going to do _____ this year."
That's what they will say.
Next up is Miss Kitano. Here we go!
I will...
English...
Study...
Study English...
Over...
Towards 2017...
Season...
Go!
What are you talking about?
Don't put Japanese in it!
What I want to tell you is...
For 2017...
For 2016...
Let's study English together and go
abroad!
That's what I wanted to tell you.
I'm glad.
No one has said that so far.
I was a little lonely.
You studied English.
The second half is "overseas".
Overseas.
Overseas?
Go abroad, go overseas, and use English.
Yes.
You're not laughing, are you?
After this, I couldn't join the public
recording special.
I'm going to show you the unreleased
scenes.
Study fight, start!
From here, I'm going to show you the
unreleased scenes of the Christmas
special.
First, the unreleased scenes of the
final test.
There were too many new answers, so I'm
going to show them all at once.
This is the first question.
This is a very basic question that you
have to write in English from 1 to 10.
This is a question for the first year of
junior high school.
It's a question that I'm licking quite a
bit.
But this is...
If I can't do this, I don't think I can
go abroad.
First of all,
Takayana-san.
I think it's definitely correct.
Well then, Takayana-san's answer is
this.
No, it's correct.
1, 2...
Torte!
It's wrong! It's wrong!
Wait! I made a mistake!
It's wrong!
It's true!
I made a mistake!
It says 1,2, Torute
Torute?
Even if you make a mistake, it won't be
like this
Why?
Because the back of T is R
I'm really shocked
Really?
This kind of simple mistake
Simple mistake?
Simple mistake
That's pretty flashy
I'm shocked
Next is Ness Hoshino's answer
1,2,3
I did it! I got a 3!
You did get a 3 though
I got too excited
Here is the next question.
Do you answer each body part in English?
I don't know.
There are people who do something like
singing.
I didn't want to sing.
Let's see Takayama-san's answer.
Takayama-san's answer is here.
Ah, it's true!
Tooth!
Fruit! Tooth!
Do you know the meaning of Tooth?
You know the song "Utare"?
Ah, I know!
It's Toes! Toes!
Ah, Toes! Toes!
The toe is called Toes.
This is Tooth.
Tooth is Tooth.
To be continued
That's why Tooth is here.
Next is Ms. Kitano's answer.
Let's take a look.
Ms. Kitano, it says "Kou".
What about the foot?
Foot means "Kou".
Tooth.
The part you're pointing at is weird.
I know!
Don't make a fuss about the problem.
You can't tell if it's a knee or not,
can you?
I mean, you can't tell if it's a leg or
not, can you?
But if I think about the part where I'm
being stabbed,
It's like this.
You can't feel it's like this.
It's Japanese.
But my hands are like this, and my legs
are like this.
So it's like this, right?
The back of your hand?
The back of your hand.
What?
You're just going to leave the bad
kanji!
Huh?
This?
What is this?
This is a elbow.
I also did it with a song.
Elbow.
So the knee part is also "knee".
"Knee"?
"Knee".
In English, what I came up with was
"shoulder, knee, shoulder, knee,
shoulder".
"Knee" isn't in Japanese, is it?
That came up, so "knee".
So this isn't the Japanese "knee"?
"Knee".
What is it?
"Shoulder".
Next, let's look at the illustration and
see what it means in English.
I'd like to see what you guys are
interested in.
First, the word "rice".
"Rice" means "rice" in English.
Hoshino-san, what is your answer?
"Japan White".
It's not "Wakabane".
It's not "Wakabane", but it's a bit
different.
But when it comes to Japan, when it
comes to white things, it's rice.
Next is the question about sheep.
The correct answer is "sheep", but...
Well then, Takayama-san's answer is...
Lamb? Hey, that's meat!
Even though it's so cute, if you look at
it as meat...
Well then, let's move on.
Ah, that's right.
Next is this question.
Well then, this is Hoshino-san's answer.
Oh, Hoshino-san. You're coming out,
Hoshino-san.
You did your best this time.
City
That's wrong
I thought it was "Tanpin"
"Tanpin"?
What is "Tanpin"?
"Tanpin"
"Tanpin" is an island, right?
I was wondering if it's "world" or
"city"
"City" is fine, but the spelling is "S"
It's actually "Sui"
"City" is also "C"
If you study the spelling a little more,
you can read the lyrics of the song
I think it will be useful for your work
Next is the hole in the conversation
It is correct if it is established as a
conversation
Let's start with this conversation
What are you doing?
I'm listening to music
That's right
From this situation, I'm listening to
music
I think there is no doubt about this
This is Kitano-san's answer
It is correct if it is established as a
conversation
What?
Wait a minute
This is...
I'm listening to music
Wait a minute
That's right! You can't hear it if
you're wearing headphones, right?
Yes, that's what I thought!
That's right!
So there's no reason to answer!
There's no reason!
I think the question wasn't good.
I think it would have been better if you
had said it.
There's no way to get a penalty for
this.
That's right.
Because...
It might be the best answer.
That's right!
You can't hear it anyway, so whatever
you say will be the answer.
So I think there might have been a
mistake in the question.
Yes, so...
Thank you!
It's amazing, but it's kind of
frustrating.
Japan is Shikoku?
Does this look like Shikoku?
It looks like Shikoku.
That looks like Shikoku.
I can't see it.
But is it a country? Is it okay because
it has a country? Shikoku.
Where is this country?
No, that's no good.
And here is Akimoto's answer.
Akimoto-san, please read it.
Akimoto-san, when you came as a guest,
you were in perfect condition.
If you didn't sing, it would have been
amazing.
Next, we learned "Give" from the song
"Last Christmas" by Wham!
Actually, we also learned the word
"Save".
"I save money for _____" means "I am
saving money for _____".
Let's use this phrase to announce what
you are saving money for.
"I am saving money for _____"
Oh!
I want you to use it for yourself.
Do you live in a junk house?
I heard that you are worried about
_____.
Everyone is realistic.
It's not an image of an idol.
It's not an image.
It's like a book house.
That's right.
It's not that I want to build a palace.
There may be people who don't know.
I want to build a good house for my
grandmother.
That's great.
Is Nogizaka not so profitable?
Maybe.
More and more.
From now on.
If you say something, a great person
will move to the other side.
I'm scared.
Let's stop.
I won't do that.
I'm so sorry everybody. I know that it's
such a personal question.