"Simon and Garfunkel - The Sound of
Silence"
It's a meaningful title, but it's also a
big hit in the 1960s that became the
subject of a movie.
Let's listen to it one by one.
Next up is Ms. Hori. Here we go!
Don't be afraid of mistakes.
Sing in a loud voice.
You practiced a lot, didn't you?
I practiced, but I got confused when I
heard everyone else's.
I got confused!
The point is not to listen.
If you crazy so
But I don't know that
Red, white, yellow, green
Someday
I was singing in Japanese all of a
sudden, and then I started to sing in
Korean.
I was so surprised.
And I became completely white.
Wow.
I had memorized it.
But I became completely white.
You became completely white.
And at that time, you decided to sing in
Japanese?
I thought I should speak in Japanese.
But your face color hasn't changed, so
you don't have the energy to sing in
Japanese.
I'm sorry.
Next up is Miss Hitano. Here we go.
Excellent!
The silence was right.
Didn't you say something like pizza
crust?
Crispy.
Then, let's warm up a little here.
Sound of music.
Instead of "music", put another word and
announce your favorite sound.
What kind of sound do you like,
Mizukita?
I like the sound of...
Animal voice
I like the sound of animal voice
I like the sound of cooking
You like cooking sound
You like the sound of cooking
Do you cook often?
Yes
Are you busy?
What is the sound of your mother
cooking?
I don't like it
You don't like it?
You only like the sound of your own
cooking?
No, I like it
You like it
Now, let's learn how to say "I like it"
If someone says something positive, you
can say "sounds nice" or "sounds good"
The members will tell you a good story
about what happened recently, and then
you can say it
Kitano-san, you can tell us what
happened recently
Yesterday
Eat
I like it
Very very...
Delicious
Sounds good
Eel
Very very delicious
Very very good
Yummy
Yummy, good
It can be delicious
Very good
Sounds nice and delicious, Miss Kitano
But you can't say that in Japanese
In this case, "Yesterday I ate eel, it
was very very good"
Next up is Miss Hori
Please tell us about "sounds good"
Miss Hori, what happened to you
recently?
Yesterday, I like roast beef
Eat
Roast beef
3, 2, 1
That's right, if you can hit this
signal, the conversation will be very
smooth
Miss Kitano and Miss Holly are talking
about food
Yesterday I ate roast beef, I liked it
and I'm happy
Next up is Miss Kitano, here we go
When I was washing my hands, I dropped
my ring down the drain
I was washing my hands
I dropped my ring down the drain
What? I'm on camera!
But you're the one who got it right,
right?
You didn't do it on purpose, did you?
I didn't get it.
I said, "Did I get it right?"
Well, Suzuki-san's reaction was kind of
sad.
Did you see that?
It's Suzuki-san's fault!
I wasn't looking at anything.
Suzuki-san, did you get it?
I didn't get it at all.
Did anyone get it?
Since no one got it, Ms. Hirata, one
more time please.
I'll do the gesture.
I washed my hands.
And I dropped my ring down the drain.
I dropped my ring!
That's correct!
You got it now.
You were just guessing.
You got it now, right?
I got it now.
You were just guessing.
"Let It Go" by Idina Menzel
Everyone's long-awaited hit song.
This famous song has been heard once.
Can you expect it this time?
Gold button, anyway
Partially, I thought Ray-chan was
amazing
You could pronounce it like a native
Partially, I thought it was amazing
But mostly, it wasn't good
You cheated a little
I cheated a lot
Are you okay?
Your voice is husky
Thank you
Okay
Real voice
It's like "We are strong"
What are you doing?
Something went in
He was influenced by Anayuki, so he's
trying to get out of here.
He's accepting everything.
Is this okay? Isn't this impossible?
I don't care what you're going to say.
Let the story jump.
It's going to be funny to anyone.
That was the best you could do.
Sensei, what do you think?
But you were able to do it.
That was the best you could do?
That was the best you could do.
The last part was really good.
If your voice was ok, it would have been
really good.
That's right. To be honest, you didn't
hear anything up to my part.
You didn't hear anything up to my part.
So here is a warm-up using "Let's".
Everyone, please try to do what
Takayama-san said.
Ok, go ahead.
Anything is fine?
Anything is fine.
Let's dancing!
Okay, everyone understood.
But you made a gesture.
If you dance by yourself, everyone will
understand.
We don't say "Let's dancing".
"Let's dance".
We say "dance" normally.
You just have to put the word "dance" as
it is.
Then, next.
I'll do as you say.
Don't make a gesture.
Let's sing!
Let's dance!
Let it go! Can't hold us anymore!
Correct!
Okay!
There was one person who didn't get it.
What did you think I said just now?
Let's see.
"Think about it."
Ah, I see.
That's why you didn't say anything and
just thought about it.
I see.
I thought you said "Think about it."
"Think about it."
This one is "Think about it."
And this one is "Think about it."
If it's "Let's think," you think about
it.
If it's "Let's sing," you sing.
By the way, what were you thinking
about?
I wonder why I was singing.
You were thinking about that?
Ah, I see.
Your voice is getting better, isn't it?
You're getting better.
Yes.
"Don't worry, let me warm up"
Thank you!
Amazing!
In one go!
"Let me warm you up"
Even if you say "warm"
The other person can understand
Just by saying "let me warm"
You can understand, right?
Yes, I can understand
And your movements
If I had to say, Takayama-san's
movements are colder
Right?
"Let me warm you up"
Ms. Takayama, that's pretty good!
Just by adding the verb "Let me" after
"Let me"
You can help her in English
Okay, next up is Ms. Kitano
Here we go!
Okay, here we go!
I need love, I'll let you hug me
Correct!
Wow, everyone can do it!
Amazing!
There was no love in the hug.
That's why it's the second time we've
met.
You're really emphasizing that.
It's the second time we've met.
We're just getting to know each other.
That's why.
Wow!
It's like, "What the hell?"
So you were expecting Jin Kaito?
Yes, yes, yes.
This time I was able to do it.
Next time, I have to level up a little
more.
Level up!
The level is getting higher and higher.
Let's go.
Start.
I love you.
I like your face.
You are pretty.
I love you.
I can't you.
No, I love you.
I love you.
I can't.
You're right.
I want to hug you.
I love you.
No more chances for you.
It was a little too tough for Miss
Kitano.
Please tell her the truth.
I can't love you anymore.
This song is one of the most popular
among Michael's many hit songs.
It's a little difficult, but I wonder if
you can copy it.
(singing)
How was it, Sensei?
It seems like you got it all right.
Bige?
That's what you said, right?
Hige?
Right?
Right? Bige? That's Bige, right?
Bige.
What did you say? Say it slowly again.
Thank you for watching!
Wait a minute.
You said "Bige".
No, I didn't say "Bige".
I don't know anything other than "Fu".
I can only hear "Pei".
(singing)
Last up is Miss Takayama. Here we go!
How's your voice?
Oh, um, it's loud.
Loud?
Nice, nice.
Very, very, very good.
Good, okay.
You're ready, right?
Here we go.
What's wrong, Takayama-san?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Here, yes.
The things I've learned.
But you can't cheat.
Yes.
I want to stay here, so it's okay.
You're an idol, right?
Let's go!
You remember it?
Didn't you say "soy sauce and salt"?
Soy sauce and salt.
I remember it with this sound.
Amazing.
Soy sauce and salt.
Now, practice.
In the episode Ms. Hirata will talk
about,
try to express your feelings by saying
"How~".
So, first up is Ms. Hirata.
Next, Ms. Akimoto. Here we go.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
The other day, I bought a shampoo and
conditioner, and it's really expensive.
It's about $100, and I lost it in the
train.
How?
I lost my $100 shampoo and conditioner
in the train.
I left my expensive shampoo and
conditioner on the train.
How...
How interesting?
How amazing?
No!
Sorry!
It's okay?
How interesting is when you say "I
forgot" to someone who is sad and you
say "Oh, that's funny"
That's funny.
No!
Akimoto-san, you have that side of you,
don't you?
No, I don't!
Ms. Akimoto, that wasn't too bad.
But in this case, it was better to
express sadness, such as "How sad!" or
"How terrible!"
Be careful in the actual battle after
this.
By the way, let's review a little from
here.
Do you remember what you did in the last
3 lessons?
Do you remember?
Yes, yes, yes.
"Like this"
What does "Like this" mean?
It means "Do it like me"
In the first lesson, we learned "Like
this"
It means "Do it like this"
Let's brush up
"Like this" to Mr.Suzuki who is crazy
about foreign tourists
Use this to teach her how to eat sushi.
Wow
Wow?
Like this
This
Dish
I don't know how to eat sushi
One more
Like this
Soy sauce
Hmm
Oh
Eat?
Eat
Delicious
Are you ready to go to the city?
Are you ready?
Yes
Alright, let's go to the city and use it
Let's go
This is the stage for the autumn
homework class
Foreigners
This is the most popular tourist spot,
Asakusa's Kaminari-mon
This time, two foreigners who don't
speak Japanese will guide us around
I would like to introduce the foreigners
who will guide us around
Please come in
What do you think? Are they good-
looking?
That's all
Perfect!
First up is Miss Kitano. Okay, here we
go!
Who are you?
Yeah!
"Who are you?" is quite rude, isn't it?
Who are you?
If you say it in front of me, "Who are
you?"
Right, teacher?
What's who?
What's you?
You, right?
What's your name?
My name is Alicia
My name is Sean
Miss Kitano, you can't say "Who are
you?"
It would be nice if you could say "Nice
to meet you"
My name is...
My name is Hinako
I like eels
Eels?
You don't know what eels are?
You can say "gesture"
Eels are...
That's dojo school, isn't it?
You like dancing?
Dance
Eels are mistaken for dancing
Eels are not eels
Eels
I like you!
Next up is Ms. Takayama. Here we go!
I'm Kazumi.
I'm from Japan.
I'm 21 years old.
I hope...
Many friends.
Please!
Friend!
Please, my friend!
Do you want to be my friend?
Yes.
I said "my friend".
You're almost there, Ms. Takayama.
I hope to make many friends.
Please be my friend.
We will be your friends.
We want to be your friends.
Yes.
Let's go.
Miss Kawago, Miss Nojo, and Miss Akimoto
are shopping at Nakamise Street.
There is no route called "Sanpai" in
Sensoji.
First of all, let's get to know each
other more and more.
Where are you from?
America
Where do you think she came from?
Where are you from?
Please try to guess
Where?
Is it close?
Canada
Where do you think?
Where I am from
Australia
Can you praise me?
The color of your eyes
The color of my eyes
Very cute, very
Thank you
What do you like Japanese food?
What kind of Japanese food do I like?
I like curry
Curry?
You like curry?
I like curry
Wait a minute
Curry?
You said curry
And that's the curry
He said curry
Curry?
Yes
It's curry
It's totally different
Can we go to this shop?
What?
Go to this one?
This food is Senbei
Is it sweet?
No, salty
What is it made of?
Soy sauce
Rice?
Rice
What is Senbei?
Rice cracker
Soy sauce
Dip soy sauce
Grill
Party Party
It looks so good. Is it good?
Good
Rice cracker, soy sauce, salty
and rice crackers.
Mr. Kimoto, good job!
What are these?
Are these rice crackers too?
No.
Different.
These are Japanese sweets.
Doughnuts.
Doughnuts in Japanese food.
Anko.
What is it?
Mr. Hirata, Mr. Inatsu, what is anko?
Do you have it?
Sweet red bean
Sweet, because it's sweet, sweet
Red bean because it's red bean
Sweet bean paste
Sweet bean paste inside
Inside donut
Perfect
Girls, nicely done
If you compare it to a donut or a cake,
you can explain the taste of Japanese
sweets
Do you want to try this? Ask her
Would you like to...
Not like
What? Eat?
Eat?
Eat
Try?
I would love to try
Let's eat
Yeah, let's eat
Thank you
Thank you very much
Thank you so much
Here's a question that we didn't expect
to see from the two of them.
Why is your face angry?
Ask the clerk.
Nioh-san
Nioh-san is the face of Nioh-san in
Kaminari-mon.
Nioh-san has a scary face, so it is
called Nioh-san.
Nioh-san
Nioh-san is the face of Nioh-san in
Kaminari-mon.
Gate. This face looks like gate.
It's the same as the one on the gate.
It seems that Akimoto's gesture has
conveyed the point.
Ms. Hirata, how would you say it in
English?
The face on this is the same face as the
one on the statue in the gate where we
came in.
Is it like an angry face?
Yeah, it's an angry face.
Angry man.
Now, let's ask them if the "Ningyo-yaki"
was delicious.
The way to ask for the taste is to use
the word "How" that I taught you today.
When you combine "How" and "Like" and
ask for the taste...
Oh, I got it.
You haven't taught this yet, have you?
How do you like?
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
How did you like it?
Ah, how did you like?
Don't look this way.
Yes, yes, yes.
Because we are Japanese.
Yes.
How did you like "Ningyo-yaki"?
It was delicious.
It was so good.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
I ate it very quickly.
It was so delicious.