Today's theme song is "Holding out for a
hero" by Bonnie Tyler.
It is the theme song of a Japanese TV
drama.
Miss Kitano, who is your hero?
My hero is Mr. Tak Suzuki.
What?
What's going on?
Last year's Christmas special recording
Mr. Tak Suzuki
You are my hero
I remember a bit, but Kitano-san, you
weren't crying?
That's right!
You were, weren't you?
She made me cry.
Who made you cry?
It looked like there was something going
on between the two of you.
Yes, Maaya and I had a bit of a fight.
At that time, the one who saved you
was...
I was the only one left, but I ended up
crying, so Suzuki-san...
Oh, well...
I was the only one left, but I ended up
crying, so Suzuki-san...
That was a bit cool!
But why did you end up crying in the
first place?
I just wanted to make people laugh.
"Aho ni nagure hi no dubi banana nai"
"You gotta be corn, you gotta be cedoli"
"You gotta be fresh, bon papai"
Bon papari?
Bon papari
The part where you get hit by a fool, I
did hear it like that.
I was like, "Is this a trick?"
"I get hit by a fool, I can hear it!"
The song was really good.
Your voice...
My voice came out.
It's a matter of course.
It was pretty good.
I see.
65 points.
I did it!
Wow!
Now it's time for practice!
Let's practice using "hold" for a short
period of time.
Please explain why you want to use
"hold"
My...
Grand...
Mother...
You can't remember!
That's a good one!
That's not it!
My grandmother got...
I got a present from Hokkaido
What's Hokkaido?
Fish
She said it so easily
Don't give up, Miss Kitano. Could you
hold this box? It's a package from my
grandmother.
How about you, Miss Kitano?
Tight pants
Keep a tight figure
Slim
The game that was very popular during
the Christmas special
I would like to challenge this
Today's game is to play "Counter" in
English
"Counter" is a well-known game in Japan
Today, we would like to play it in
English
Among the cards lined up randomly,
the card that corresponds to the hint
read in English will be the winner
There are some questions that you have
to listen to the hint until the end, so
be careful
This is the second half.
Ms. Hirata, Ms. Nojo, and Ms. Kitano are
the players.
Ms. Nakada will read the hint.
I'm red and I have seeds all over me.
What about the others?
Please show us.
Ms. Nojo.
I heard the word "red" so I thought it
was "apple".
Speaking of "red"...
Hirata-san, you don't hold back at all,
do you?
At first, I thought I'd do my best.
Why "red"?
Because "red" is a seed.
It's easy to say.
But this is not a seed.
This is a meat.
I saw it on the news this morning.
It's an orange.
You're studying something else.
Let's make it a leaf.
So the answer is...
Strawberry!
It's not "Maya"
I didn't know that
You've learned a lot
The hint reader has changed
Next is "Mess Maya"
Here it comes!
Wait, this is...
We might be able to win
This is really...
I'm Glen and I'm very...
Glen...
That's good!
People make salad with me
One more time
I'm Green and I'm very...
That's good!
People make...
Salad with me
What is this?
Carrot
Why carrot?
I heard it's a vegetable
Vegetable?
It's a salad
I said two colors
Gray and...
And green
Gray is grey
But it's two colors
It's true, it's two colors
It's almost two colors
For me, it's green
There's green in it, so
The rest is in the salad
Oh, I get what you mean by "crazy"
I thought it was crunchy
I heard "crunchy"
Crunchy?
You said "crazy"
I thought it was "crunchy"
I thought you said "crunchy"
You didn't say "peepo" either?
Peepo?
It's a salad that people make
So I thought it would have lettuce in it
I see
So I chose lettuce
Wada-san, please announce the correct
answer
Red hose
The answer is lettuce
The last question
The reader of the hint is Nescawago
I'm purple outside and gold inside. I
make people fast.
No, it's not like that.
First, let's find out the rules of the
cards.
There's no rule that you have to take
back what you took.
What is this?
Eggplant.
How is it?
It's purple after all.
Everyone said "Pan", so I said "Panji"
You said "Panji" as soon as you heard
the word "Purple"
It was fast
She was so calm when she came here
but she was so aggressive when she came
here
Did something happen in February?
I don't think so
Inside gold?
Gold inside
Yes
But it's still this
The yellow part
Yes
The second part is
I make people fart
Fart
Fart and fart?
You guys do it a lot right?
Just a little bit
So the correct answer was sweet potato
And the result is?
Nagata-san got 2 points
And Nojo-san got 2 points
Thank you
Yay!
I'm glad you didn't lose.
We always let our guests win.
Mojo-san, you did your best. Thank you.
Yay!
Today's song is "Destiny's Child -
Survivor".
It's a representative song of Beyoncé's
popular R&B group, Deathjah.
To be honest, it's pretty hard to copy.
Next up is Miss Kitano. Here we go.
3, 2, 1, go!
I am a diver, I am a giver, I am a
father, I am a mother, I am a umai, I am
the father, I am the son, Imoabata!
Imoabata!
Until the first 2 or 3 lines, you sang
it almost perfectly.
Wow!
Thank you!
From the middle, it's like "Father"
Yeah, everyone started saying "Father"
The story has changed
From now on, it's a fun game corner to
learn English
This time, following the theme song
"Survivor"
We will play several games
Only the winner will survive
We will play a survival game
The first game is
Fruit Basket in English
First, a fruit basket using English.
The person who answers to what the demon
says
must stand up and move the seat.
As a result, the person who didn't sit
down becomes the demon.
If you become the demon twice in total,
you're out.
By the way, there are two losers here.
The first demon is Miss Kitano, who lost
in rock-paper-scissors.
Today, eat lunch!
It's definitely a lie!
Did you eat?
You didn't eat, right?
Wait a minute, Nojo's expression is
strange.
It's definitely a lie!
You ate, right?
I eat breakfast, lunch, and dinner all
at once.
You ate, right?
By the way, who came here and ate lunch?
That was lunch.
Nojo-san ate it!
Wait a minute!
This is a snack.
Stop it, everyone.
Please be serious.
OK, are you ready?
OK, let's go.
Like food is...
Clap.
What is it?
Stop it!
What does that mean?
My favorite food is crab.
Crab person?
Yes.
Crab?
You said crab!
I didn't say that!
Crab!
You said crab, didn't you?
Unfortunately, this is not a normal
fruit basket.
It's an English fruit basket.
So, communication skills are tested to
see if it works.
It's a shame, but Nojo-san is out of the
game.
Nojo-san is out of the game.
There is only one person left to be
eliminated.
Once again, Miss Kitano lost to Oni with
rock-paper-scissors.
It might be an advantage to start from
here.
Now, can you do it according to your
topic?
I like chocolate.
To be continued.
Kaho-san, 3, 2, 1, go!
Hair is shortcut
What is this?
You two...
In the end, the one who came out was the
one who pushed her out
It was like that, right?
When you two were about to go
We should have exchanged each other
It's getting more and more intense
It's a battle
Yes
To be continued
Next up is Ms.Maya
Brown hair color
Next up is Ms.Hirata
Someone that can shoot a Himetan beam
Ms.Nakamoto is the target
Next up is Ms.Nakamoto
Hi, student!
What? What?
So, Kawago is...
Disqualified!
What does that mean?
She's a high school student.
So, she's disqualified.
I'm not a high school student.
What?
Wait a minute.
Unfortunately, Kitano-san is out of the
game.
That means everyone gets 1 point.
This is amazing. It's really a survival
game.
Everyone reaches the goal.
Who will be eliminated?
Let's go.
3, 2, 1, go!
Wear stockings.
Ah, Kawago-san.
Everyone is so excited.
So, Kawago is disqualified!
He survived the first game.
What's the next game?
The second game is...
Voice recognition game.
This is a game using the smartphone's
voice recognition.
If you can pronounce the word "A" and
pronounce it well, it's okay.
However, the smartphone's English
recognition level is set to "Negative",
so you have to pronounce it as
"Negative".
By the way, the answer is here. If you
succeed twice, you will win.
Let's get the first question.
Here it is!
It's a girl.
If you don't say it like a native
speaker, they won't recognize it.
Say it like a native speaker.
Girl
God
Go ahead
Girl
It's God again.
Really?
You can hear it in your ears.
Girl.
All of them are God.
So far, everyone has summoned a god.
Who will it be, Ms. Hirata?
Girl
Wow!
Good luck!
It's a native
As expected of the real thing
Make a hole at the tip of your tongue
Girl
Everyone says god
The second question is about the rhythm
Rhythm
It's a hat!
What?
Rhythm
Ah, little
She can't pronounce the word "little" at
all
She's starting to speak!
She's angry
Rhythm
Megoman
That's amazing
Rhythm
I knew it
I knew it was wrong
Since you got it twice, Hilary is out
The other three
Let's try
The next question is "Rock'n'Roll"
Rock'n'Roll
Can you do it?
What's that?
Rock'n'Roll
It's your favorite song
It's a foreign artist's song
Rock'n'Roll
Look at me now
"Look-a-like"
This is difficult
The difference between "L" and "I"
Everyone failed
Miss Nojo will try
"Look-a-like"
It's totally different
I'm shaking
You were so cool, but it was totally
different
It's embarrassing
It's really embarrassing
The rules have changed
The chances of getting it right are too
low
The person who gets it right next will
be the winner
The next question is about curry
Curry
Curry.
Ah, it's curry.
That was a bit close.
Yeah, it was close.
If you get this one, you've come a long
way.
Curry.
Ah, that was close.
You got an A.
I thought I could get it this time.
It was close.
Curry.
You got an A.
That was close.
Curry.
That was amazing.
Now that the regular members have all
been eliminated, let's move on to the
final round.
The final round is still the two of
them. The game they will be playing
is...
The complex guessing game.
In this game, you have to answer the
questions in English in order, and the
one who gets the correct answer first
wins.
If you don't get the correct answer
quickly, you'll have to keep saying bad
things about the other person.
Team? Group?
It's different.
It's just right.
That's why it's just right.
You have to say it here, and that's it.
And later, when you say, "Who is the
entertainer you hate?"
You have to say it, and that's it.
By the way, I'm King Kong, I'm King
Kong.
I told you, I told you.
What is the complex of each other that
you are curious about?
Nakamoto-san's complex is this.
This is difficult.
It's difficult.
But surprisingly, everyone is not
convinced.
It's different, isn't it?
I'm convinced now.
I know, I know.
It's nothing.
On the other hand, what is the complex
of Miss Hirata?
What is it?
I don't know.
Really? When I saw Nojo, I smiled.
No, it's not.
Let's go one by one in order.
Miss Nakamoto will go first.
Ready? Fight!
Now, please tell us the complex in
English.
Eh?
Well...
Japanese... difficult.
No, very good Japanese.
Very good Japanese.
You only have one dimple.
The only thing I have is a complex.
That's what I thought.
I thought you only had one.
I don't want this.
No, no, no.
Well, here's a hint.
First of all, Hirata-san's complex is
her appearance.
And Nakamoto-san's complex is her
talent.
It's a talent relationship.
That's right.
Appearance?
Her forehead is wide?
Her forehead is wide
Your forehead is...
Large
I thought it was the same because I have
a wide forehead
I'm sorry
I don't need an excuse
Teacher is the coldest
Everyone is getting sick of your Himetan
beam
It's close, but everyone is getting sick
of your Himetan beam
It's close!
Sensei!
The hint is...
Something is too big
Too big?
Shoulder width?
Shoulder width
Is my shoulder wide?
No!
But it looks like you're thinking about
it
By the way...
If I give you a hint, it's about a
person's inner side
It's about a relationship
Which one is it?
I might be right
You don't have many friends
I'm right?
I'm right, what should I do?
Hirata-san, you've been thinking about
it for a long time, right?
"She doesn't have many friends"
First of all, I have a friend in this
beam
Stop it!
This game is over
If we continue like this, we won't be
able to see each other
So this is the end
So this time, these two are the
survivors
Let's sing a song together