Special Expansion Ball!
First up is the Kouhaku Uta Gassen Document.
Unreleased video that was not broadcasted in the 60-minute special broadcasted the other day!
30 seconds left!
Thank you!
After Kouhaku's appearance, Captain Sakurai called out his members.
Why didn't you tell me?
That's right.
I think it's good.
This is absolutely good.
Just once
It's absolutely meaningless.
Excellent.
Unexpectedly, the members' true feelings burst out!
Furthermore...
Last December, they entered the Under Live held at the Nippon Budokan.
Complete report behind the scenes!
Furthermore,
Daihankyou's Maid Conto Series, the latest work!
Thank you very much, Master!
Tadio Live will perform two songs!
Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop!
Ladies and gentlemen, it's about time for the real show!
Nene
Do you remember the lyrics of POPPY POPPAPA?
Of course, POPPY POPPAPA is perfect.
Wow, I still don't remember the lyrics of POPPY POPPAPA.
POPPY POPPAPA is good, but last year's KOUHAKU was really fun.
The last boss, Sachiko Kobayashi's costume was amazing.
Don't you think so too?
Mmm!
That's POPPY PAPAPA!
I was saying it in a tone that was amazing, but I don't think that's what Poppipappaba means.
Could it be that if you convert Nogizaka to Pagyo, it comes from the part where it becomes Poppipapa?
Look at Bubi-papa!
She said it in a tone that she didn't know, but that's also different, isn't it?
Oh, that's right!
Maya, have you eaten your lunch?
I haven't eaten yet!
Oh, I see.
You haven't eaten either, have you?
No.
I haven't eaten anything since this morning.
Popi-Papapa...
I said it in a tone that made me hungry, but
that's not what popi-papapa means.
I can understand that, Maya.
No, no, it's not the time to be impressed.
It's our important situation, so
shouldn't we use it in a rough way?
Well, well, well, calm down.
I've been having stiff shoulders lately.
I want to get a massage, too.
I've been having stiff shoulders since I was over 20 years old.
I also have stiff shoulders.
Again?
Oh, I got it!
I'm getting old!
Correct!
Yay!
Stop!
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
Pop! Pop! Pop!
Piano, guitar, 46
Pony Pony Six
Piano Guitar Pony Six
40, 46
Miyano Kizaku 46
P-P-P-P-P-P-P-46
If it's a person who understands, it's fine to understand
It's a pure word
Close the door that you don't want
Thank you for watching!
You're dead
Piano Kisaku 46
Hey! Let's have some fun
No one can beat us
Even if we don't know each other, we can understand each other
Let's fall in love
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
Piano guitar for 46
Thank you!
What is what is shit?
We don't know what is that
What is shit?
What what what what what what is what is shit?
Thank you for watching!
He made it to the semi-final!
The truth is...
Please take a look at the unreleased scenes that couldn't be aired last time!
December 21st
The members who performed at the Budokan on this day
Even after a full-fledged live,
These six went to NHK in a hurry.
Kouhaku is waiting for him as a challenger.
I don't do anything like this, so I'm going to jump out.
I admire you.
What? It's a live broadcast.
Oh, my God.
There are a lot of live broadcasts at night, but I don't think I've been on TV much.
I think it's my first time.
Really?
Since I turned 18, I've never been on a live broadcast at midnight on TV.
I suddenly started to sleep.
Let's take a nap.
Suddenly?
Here?
That's all for today.
Here comes the unreleased scene!
Kazumi Takayama went to the same high school as a famous artist.
Isn't it cool?
It's like Kailanba
Kazumi Takayama said he was scared.
They collected money and gave us flowers.
I got a message from my mom.
That's good.
There will be four of us this year.
Four of us?
From X JAPAN.
The two of you and...
Yusuke-san and Toshi-san
Takayama is the same as Yoshiki and Toshi.
And there are 7 strange things about this high school
It's a clear color.
The piano is sleeping somewhere in the room.
It's like a crystal ball.
That's what you choose, right, Nanako?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
There's a lot of events.
Arriving at NHK at 11 p.m.
The live broadcast is about to begin.
will appear on the show Kouhaku Sendenbu.
Don't look back!
Amazing!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
Then, here too, a message related to X JAPAN was discovered.
Takayama-san can't be here or not.
It's a failure!
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
December 28th
3 days until the show
These 6 members are...
He will perform as the back dancer of Ayako Fuji.
Thank you very much.
Reset.
Today's choreographer is Natsu Mayumi-sensei.
Thank you for watching.
Natsu Mayumi-sensei also taught Morning Musume and AKB48.
I'm going to kill you!
The choreography uses sense.
The members who can't get used to the movement
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
This is the front of the chest.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
They have to finish it in three days from today.
Thank you for watching.
And then...
This is how it was broadcasted last time.
Here's a scene you won't regret!
The members who are desperate to learn from Natsu-sensei
I'm ready.
But...
Let's go.
I don't know
Thank you very much.
Back, back, back, back!
That's it!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Did you catch it?
No, I'm fine.
It's like this.
Thank you for watching!
He's trying to dance as he was taught.
See you next time!
Bye-bye.
Let's go to the left.
Ta-da!
What are you doing?
Peace!
It's a good place to dance, isn't it?
I understand that you're going to try it.
It's difficult.
It's my first time dancing with a sense of dance.
I'm trying to figure out what it's going to look like.
I won't close it.
Keep it open
I'd be happy if you could make it for me.
I will do it!
Mmm.
Hmm.
Ta-da!
Yes
It's gotten a lot better now.
We are Nobizaka48
I'm doing it like this all the time
Your face is going to be a mess.
Because it's the most visible part
properly
Do you want me to show you my face?
Yes, please.
What do you think?
O.T.6
O.T.6?
Yes.
What did you say?
I said O.T.8.
That's strange.
I'm sorry.
How many times did you make a mistake?
Twice.
I'm sorry.
The choreography is gradually coming together
This person is...
The left side of the screen.
Yes
I'm going to eat this
1, 2, 3
I don't know what to do.
Ta-da!
Sakurai-san always messes up the shape of the circle.
And then, the 4-hour shake-off is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I used to like Moose very much.
I was very nervous from the beginning to the end.
But he was a kind person, so I was glad.
Sakurai was moved to meet Natsu-sensei, who was more worried about dancing than about dancing.
December 29th, 9AM
Two days left until the main event.
The first rehearsal at NHK Hall.
If you want to enter, please enter in the position of the intro.
Please watch one by one.
I think it will become a investment as it is.
This is the only time you can do it with sound.
One more time, please.
Thank you.
Nogizaka 46 can use the stage for about 10 minutes.
He checked his standing position and his eyes.
Next, MC interview.
While doing a schedule of minutes,
there is also a surprise from the members!
Actually,
Ta-da!
It looks like this.
it has a lot of crackers
IKOMO is today
It's my birthday, so I want to celebrate it with a surprise.
And this is the end of the last episode.
A scene that won't be revealed from here on out!
The members are waiting for Ikoma-san
Hooray!
It's a surprise.
That's right.
It's for you.
Magic
You have a good sense of humor.
Mine is a little short.
Really?
Let's do it!
Thank you very much.
3, 2, 1
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Among them are...
This kind of member is also...
This is...
Thank you for your viewing.
I feel like it's going to be really messy.
I should make a stamp card.
I think I'm going to eat a lot.
It was my first time.
Happy birthday to you!
Happy Birthday to you!
It seems that the surprise was a great success!
Next is the rehearsal of Ayako Fujii's song, but she is worried about her outfit.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I don't have a lot of clothes that I want to wear,
but I think I'm going to compete at the end of the year.
This is how it looks.
I'm still hiding it, but I can see it when I dance.
Here comes Ayako Fujii.
Ms. Fujii is from Akita Prefecture.
Long time no see.
You did it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Kawaii kawaii
This is what Akita's uncle and aunt are proud of.
And this is the end of the last episode.
From now on, it's an unreleased scene!
Thank you for watching until the end.
After checking the choreography
Sakurai has a problem
Thank you for watching!
Why are there so many people?
Why?
I'm not good at it.
You are good at it.
Actually, you should do this on the top.
I'm not good at it.
I can't do this anymore.
I have to do this.
I told you
It's so curved
I was surprised
This is the first time I've seen such a curved one
If you try not to bend your stomach, you will make a mistake in your sense
If you pay attention to the direction of your sense, your stomach will bend.
I don't know if my body is stiff, but I don't have a good sense at all.
Of course, not only Sakurai-san but also Hashimoto-san struggled with the choreography.
I was so nervous that I almost forgot about it.
I make a lot of mistakes every time, but as a result, I often make mistakes because I'm nervous.
What is it?
She's a number dancer and an OED dancer.
Yes, I did.
I liked it.
Do you still remember it?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Thank you.
Please don't give me a sudden expression of excitement.
It was the moment when Sakurai-san, who was depressed because the choreography didn't go well, changed his mind.
And for the first time, they rehearse with Ayako Fuji.
See you in the next video!
Yup!
Start!
After the rehearsal, the members check the choreography immediately.
Before the show
I only have 30 minutes left, so let's concentrate.
The one in the back
Um...
The light is red and it's really strong
If you think about it,
I'm burning
If you don't release something, it will be a little hazy, so take a little more accent.
I'd like to practice putting my emotions into it.
I'm a 30-year-old kid.
Basically, you step, step, and take the accent from your hand.
But...
It's not about the technique of the body, but how do you get it out of here?
Hey, please, more, so, like that
Beautiful.
If you think, please, more, that's why, you might get a little emotional.
Now, if you say, step and stretch, step and stretch, step and stretch, this will stop.
Please tell me that you understand
I'll talk to you.
With Natsu-sensei's guidance,
The members' movements have changed.
You're older than me, Hajimoto-san.
I'm starting to feel a woman's passion.
You have a good sense of humor, too.
I'm going to make it look more powerful.
There are some parts that come off easily.
What I'm good at is very beautiful, but
Wait a minute!
If you think you're good at it, it makes you feel a little bad.
So...
Even if you watch it, you'll understand.
They were the members who taught Natsu-sensei very important things.
The day has finally come.
When the members gather,
Checking the choreography immediately
This is good for both legs.
I'm getting nervous now.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You don't look nervous.
Right before the show.
The engine unites the hearts of 37 people.
Today, all the members will be participating in the karate class.
We've been through a lot, but we've all done our best, so I think we can go home like this.
I'm having so much fun today that I'm going to give it all I've got!
Seiji
Let's stand!
No!
Yeah!
It's finally time.
Kabate! Kabate!
Here's the unreleased scene!
Trouble occurs just before the main event.
A penlight was given to the members waiting for the opening.
Thank you.
This!
Everyone, it's not on now, but it's automatically controlled.
In other words, the color will change automatically, so please enjoy it.
This is a penlight that glows by remote control.
I'll do my best.
This is my color, Chika-san.
Lanin color.
Thank you for watching!
Trouble occurs 30 seconds before the main event!
It's not enough for one.
Let's go!
Sakurai-san is in trouble again.
Only her penlight is broken.
The real show is coming soon!
Thank you very much.
He replaced it with a new one just before it appeared, and was able to safely get to the opening.
Thank you for watching!
After the opening, you have 15 minutes left.
It will be ready soon.
It's the 4th song now, so the 5th song is the first stage of us, Nogizaka46, so let's go!
The behind-the-scenes talk channel of this Kouhaku Utagasusen was carried out by the two Bananaman.
Koushiki Onii-chan's BANANAMAN cheered him every time he saw his face.
This time, please listen to the song with the sound of the song.
This is a great song.
The name of this song is KIMIKA, which is the mother of KIMURA.
Why is this song the 5th single?
This is a great song.
I can't believe it's all of us.
There are 37 of us.
IKUMA is the center.
That's right.
Everyone has a good face.
This is the color of Nogizaka, so it's purple.
Next year, I heard that purple is good.
Is that so?
It's a lucky color.
Red and purple.
Nagizaka will be more and more active.
There's no one here.
Thank you for watching!
What kind of song is this?
Why are you so serious?
I love this song
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
It's lonely to get used to it.
Oh, Takayama.
Nagashima is here.
Nagashima announced his graduation.
Thank you for your hard work.
Everyone is here at this stage.
Yes!
Thank you for watching!
Everyone is singing with pride.
Everyone has a very good expression.
Everyone has worked hard to achieve this goal.
Yeah!
That's good.
The fact that I was there
Thank you for watching.
NAKATTA KOTO
Thank you for watching!
It's always new
トキメキと出会いのバス
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Did you know that?
I didn't know.
Wow, that's great!
Nogizaka!
It's cold!
It was really fun.
Did my fans and family watch this video?
It's not too fluffy.
Was it good?
I'm not happy because I'm not a fan.
I haven't seen it yet, so I can't laugh at all.
I got a lot of messages from my friends.
Thank you for watching!
I didn't come here either.
No, no, no.
I'm coming from here.
I thought you were coming.
What?
I can't get in touch with you.
I'm watching you.
No, no.
How can I follow you?
Help me.
Personally, I think...
For a year.
It's quite tiring.
DEMO
On this stage today,
All of them.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
I think it will start in Nogizaka too.
Next year
I hope I can do it again in a new year.
The next scene is with Ayako Fuji.
Oh, Manju!
lol
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
The members are taught to dance with emotion to Natsu sensei
But it's easier to express than to be sexy.
And Sakurai-san has been struggling with her sense for a long time.
Finally...
Good evening.
Please pay attention to the 6 people's facial expressions.
Thank you for watching!
I wonder why I'm so happy
So, from now on
A letter to that person
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Two or three people fell down.
I was like, I can't take it anymore.
I think I've become a better woman than I was when I was a camera man.
I want to be a good woman like this.
Let's watch the DVD.
Thank you very much.
And the Kouhaku歌合戦 will end here.
The red team won for the first time in 4 years.
The members and a large number of staff gathered together
The big stage of Kohaku's first appearance was a great success.
And now, we welcome...
Let's look forward to the future of Yuzaka 46!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
If I live alone, my room gets messy.
It's a cute maid house cleaning.
I asked for this, but I wonder if it's okay.
Oh, hi!
Here you go
Excuse me.
Thank you for watching!
Ready?
Nice to meet you!
Master!
Eh?
You guys are cleaning the house, right?
Yes, we will clean the master's house.
Wow, such cute children came.
We will not only clean the room, but also clean the master's heart.
Yes.
I don't know what you're talking about, but I'm so excited!
Obviously, we'll clean up a room that women have never been to before, like a trash house.
Is that my room?
Ping-pong!
Correct!
Come on!
Tell me where to clean up.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Well, first of all, that area...
Can you clean it up for me?
Certainly, Master!
What a good response!
Thank you for watching!
Excuse me, why aren't you guys moving?
I'm sorry.
There's one thing I forgot to tell you.
What?
We are...
You don't like dirty things, do you?
It's your job to clean it up, right?
We are...
You don't carry heavy things, do you?
I don't know.
It's my job to clean it up, right?
What? It's not a house cleaning at all!
Is it better for us to go home?
NOOOOOO
You don't have to change!
Because it's cute!
Master, I am a man who can clean the room cleanly.
I love it!
Me too!
If there is such a person, I want you to be my boyfriend.
Is that so?
When the living room is clean
I want to live in this room!
The man's room is...
When it's dirty
It's the worst.
Yes!
What are you doing?
I'll clean it up myself right now.
Good!
Hooray!
M-Mama!
That's right!
It's really beautiful, isn't it?
Aaaaaaah!
You guys don't know anything.
Master, what should we do next?
Can you clean this up for me?
Certainly, Master!
That's a good answer.
Master, I have something special for you.
Eh?
What is that?
Thank you for your viewing.
Let's go!
Oh!
Thank you for watching!
What is this?
He cleans the room by himself just by leaving it in the room.
Amazing!
You don't need it, do you?
I'm rooting for you!
A robot?
Hang in there!
It's cute.
We've been cheering for you guys for a while now.
Master, this robot costs 350,000 yen now.
That's expensive.
What are you trying to buy?
I'm not trying to sell it.
It's a rental fee.
That's too expensive.
It costs 350,000 yen per hour.
I don't know the price, but it's very expensive.
Wow, you are...
Not only the room, but also the money is dirty.
It's good!
No, that's not what I meant. I was about to be taken aback.
Master, is there anything else you'd like to do?
There's nothing else for you to do.
Can you clean it normally?
Ta-da!
Oh!
That's...
I was finally motivated.
Can you clean the dirty part of this room?
It's cleaning from a dirty place.
Understood, Master!
I'll give you 100 points for your answer.
The dirty part is...
I can say almost everything.
Thank you for watching!
Hmm?
What's wrong with your face?
This is the best I can do.
You stop too.
Ah...
I can't take this off.
It's your chin.
That's it!
Your hair will grow.
Can you do it properly?
Do you think it's better for us to change?
No, I don't remember such a thing!
Don't change! It's okay! It's cute!
Anyway, please throw away what you don't need.
It's around there.
I'll throw away the things I don't need.
I'm in the way of cleaning.
I told you to throw away the things you don't need.
Do you mean I don't need it?
Yes, I definitely don't need it.
No, I asked you to throw away the trash.
I'm not trash!
Oh, I see! You're not trash, you're trash!
You're terrible!
And you're good at it, too!
So it's not like that.
It's about saying, please throw away what you don't need.
Can I get rid of this camera?
Wait a minute, I haven't used it much lately, but it was expensive.
That's why you can't clean your room.
Master, do you know Danshari?
I've heard of it.
It's a way of life to get rid of things you don't use and refresh your room and mind.
Oh, it's Donshari.
Got it!
I'll get rid of this camera.
Thank you for watching.
Nice to meet you, master.
Yes, who are you?
I'm in charge of the fashion department.
Yes! Then please dispose of this camera!
Yes!
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
What was that?
It's creepy and cute.
I just got rid of it.
That's fast! Wait a minute.
Eh?
You sold it, didn't you?
What?
You sold that camera, didn't you?
What did I sell?
So the money you have is the money you sold the camera for, right?
No, it's not.
Then what is that money?
There's a strange old man, and that camera and money...
I said I wanted to exchange it.
I thought I didn't need it anymore.
I've exchanged it.
That's what you call selling!
What are you doing with someone else's stuff?
Master.
Yes?
You can dispose of this trash can as well, right?
It's not a trash can!
It's a savings box!
But I...
You have clothes you want, don't you?
What are you talking about?
That is
I saved 500 yen and finally got 100,000 yen.
Please get rid of this, too.
Okay, I'll get rid of it.
Did you hear what I just said?
It's a robbery!
What you're doing is a robbery!
Thank you for watching!
You've done both, haven't you?
You're going to make a big deal out of it later, right?
The way he stutters is old-fashioned.
And he doesn't make any whispers.
Master, please get rid of this car's key.
Why are you trying to sell your car?
I don't even have a girlfriend to sit on the passenger seat.
It's a waste to have a car.
You're terrible. That was the best.
Please get rid of this, too.
Okay, I'll get rid of it.
Wait a minute.
I have a lot of memories.
It's the worst.
I think I've put a girl on it once.
You only brought the key. What's wrong?
The car was too bad.
I couldn't sell it.
You just said you couldn't sell it.
Master, do you have anything else to do?
I lost both my camera and money.
Thank you for watching!
Ah, well...
Can you clean up this dirty place?
I understand, Master.
You have a lot of answers.
Master.
May I borrow your chair?
Oh, that's right. It's expensive, so I'm sorry.
Let's eat.
Ready?
It's so funny!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
Wait wait!
What are you doing? You're so cute.
Hey, don't look at me with that weird look.
You're the worst.
I don't want to clean anymore.
Do you hate me so much?
You don't like it?
I didn't mean to do this.
I'm not wearing it.
It's a tsundere!
It's so cute here!
Master, there's something on it.
Yeah.
Thank you for watching.
It's my chin!
My chin!
It's sticking out
Master, is there anything else you'd like to do?
I see.
Well, then...
I think I'll have the floor all decorated.
Certainly, Master!
Thank you for watching!
Then, I'm going to put a band-aid on you.
Okay.
Ah, no, no, no!
Miya-chan! Miya-chan!
Then I'll do it.
AHHHHH!
What?
Master, this is the purpose, isn't it?
No, it's a misunderstanding.
It's a pervert.
Stop it, don't throw things.
Don't throw it away!
What? What?
Who hit you?
What?
Wait a minute!
What the hell is wrong with you?
It's time!
It's on
And the important thing is that the clock isn't on
What? What?
Wait a minute
Is this the end?
The fee is 2.6 million yen.
It's high!
Thank you for watching!
But I'll pay for it! It's cute!
Thank you very much, Master!
I can't do it this month.
I can't do everything
Translated by Vortex
Nagizaka 46!
Next is Captain Sakurai's lecture room.
Who will come today?
Excuse me.
It's here!
Erika-sama, I'm a little confused about the door.
I was wondering where it was, so I'm sorry. It's my first time.
I see, it's your first time.
Here, please sit down.
It's like this, isn't it?
It's like this.
It's called a lecture room, so I thought you were staring and waiting.
I see, that's what I should have said.
Have you forgotten anything about the concept of this room?
It's not that I've forgotten, but I feel like I'm in a chat room.
First of all,
Since it's a Kouhaku special, this year was the first time you participated in Kouhaku. How was it?
I was so nervous.
So...
When I realized it, it was already over.
That was quick.
Were you nervous?
I was.
I've been doing it for a long time.
The position when you're waiting is...
It was always close to midsummer, but I cried in midsummer too.
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous that I said Iku-chan in the middle of the summer.
I was relieved of my nervousness while supporting each other.
You were nervous, weren't you? I was nervous too.
Really?
It was crazy. You knew I was nervous, didn't you?
I didn't really look at Reika.
So you weren't interested.
Yeah, I wasn't really interested.
I was so nervous.
I relied on you a lot.
Oh, really?
Did I drop something?
I was relying on you. I was looking at your face.
No way.
Really.
Eh? From far away?
From far away.
That's scary, though.
When I say Iku-chan,
I have to touch that
8 photo albums!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Erika, you're finally here.
That's right. I'm surprised.
And you're in Germany, right?
That's where you're from, right?
What was it?
Düsseldorf.
What is this?
I can't believe I'm hearing Düsseldorf.
Düsseldorf, right.
I'll go get it.
I lived until I was 5 years old, and it's been 13 years since I went home.
It's been 13 years.
It's been a really long time since I wrote a photo book.
I took the same composition when I was little.
It's exactly the same composition.
I also put those photos in my photo book.
That's so interesting.
I went around the places I remember and had a lot of fun.
Wow, that's nice.
Yes, well...
I don't want to talk about it.
Try on a swimsuit.
That's right.
Even if you can only see it here.
I didn't think you would do it, Iku-chan.
I was really surprised.
I was surprised.
But...
It's like...
It's refreshing, beautiful, cute, and lovely.
Oh, did you see?
I saw it! Just a little bit
No, please, all of them.
Please take a look.
I'll take a look.
I'll buy it.
Give me your autograph.
I have two autographs.
Two?
Two autographs?
I have two autographs.
I got it
Oh!
You said it
I'll buy it
The rest is that
Nagisaka station
Hustle bell?
It's a song by Nogizaka.
Your Name is Hope
Did you listen to it?
I didn't listen to it
Everyone doesn't know
Why didn't you tell me?
Captain! Captain!
That's right.
I thought it was okay.
I was scolded for the first time.
This is a lecture room, right?
Please report everything to the captain!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes, thank you.
Finally, it's like a corner.
It's become!
Finally!
As expected, thank you, Iku-chan.
After all, Iku-chan's piano is one of the weapons that represents the group called Nogizaka.
How about you, IKU?
There are a lot of members, of course there are also student members, but probably the most
I think they are members who are trying their best to be on the same level.
I think that's true for the fans as well.
I think everyone knows that.
After all,
Isn't it hard?
Don't you think it's hard?
But surprisingly
I was cornered.
It's better to be cornered.
Let's do this and that in the gap.
I don't know what to say.
I've been thinking that I might be able to come up with a plan, and that it might be the right thing for me.
That's right.
On the contrary, I was told that I was off all day, and I didn't have a school or a job.
It's really...
I become a lazy person.
By the way, wait a minute.
Isn't there such a day?
I don't have much free time in a day.
You don't?
Yeah, I don't.
Yeah.
There are times when I finish school early and then go to school.
I don't really go out to play.
I'm stuck at home working.
Working? What are you doing?
I usually play the piano.
I do my homework and watch TV.
Don't you ever get tired?
I can't move
Mmmmm
There is.
At times like that, I just eat chocolate.
I'm scared.
Intermittent intake.
Then you can do it.
Thank you for watching!
I knew it!
You like to play the piano and sing, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Yeah.
After that, I look at things like that.
I see them singing on stage.
I often go to see them.
I love it.
They must be getting tickets.
What I want to do the most is
It's like a stage.
That's right.
Musical?
Yes, musical.
In the future?
That's what I want to do.
You're also playing a leading role in Japan, aren't you, Ikuta-san?
I'm grateful.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you for watching!
It's a witch's mansion.
Witch's?
But I thought you were really hard-working.
No, no, no.
I was watching you up close.
Really?
Yes!
It's true.
The ribbon knight had a big box, and there was a local park.
There was a lot of pressure.
Hmm...
But...
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you for watching.
For the ribbon, Reika...
It made me feel good to be close to him.
That's right.
But it's not that much pressure.
I mean...
It's fun, so I want to do more and more.
Maybe I was more curious about that.
Oh, so you didn't have a hard time because it was fun.
Ah!
Yes, I do.
I want to express it in a different way, but I can't.
I went to Nogizaka when I was in junior high school, so I spent all my junior high and high school years as a student here, and I didn't have the experience that ordinary people have.
That's right.
So I have to be like that person.
Even if I try to put out the life of that person, I can't put it out to the depths.
I think that's still not enough.
Life experience
That's true.
It's hard to express.
Yes.
From now on...
As Rika Ikuta,
this year
It's not a goal. What do you want to be in the future?
It's the end of my teenage years.
I'll turn 19 soon.
That's fast!
Really?
Scary!
It suddenly became a good voice.
That's right, so now...
I don't want to limit myself to this path, but I want to try various things.
What do you think?
The image of Nogizaka is not so different from the image seen by people.
So that kind of thing...
This year, we did a lot of things.
I hope it changes little by little.
I want more people to think that I'm doing something like this, or that I didn't have this image.
Hmm.
I see.
Your future is bright, so I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Let's do our best together.
Thank you for watching!
Nogizaka 46
Next up is...
Nogizaka Under Live was held for two days in December last year.
This live is performed by members other than the selection of Nogizaka46.
In 2014, it was held at a handshake event.
And then...
The scale is getting bigger and bigger.
Finally, they have arrived at Budokan, which they had been aiming for.
This commemorative live will be reported by...
I'm Reika! I'm Yumi Okatsuki!
Captain Reika Sakurai and Yumi Wakatsuki.
Today, tomorrow, and for the next two days.
Underlove is here.
That's right.
It's done!
It's cold outside, isn't it?
That's a nice follow-up.
Thank you.
You can say that in the dressing room.
The two are a little unreliable, but will they be able to bring out the charm of the members firmly?
Thank you for watching!
The highlight of the 5-day concert is...
All participants will perform one song at a time.
In addition, the members have come up with various ideas for the set list.
Based on that, Tokuhai interviews the members before the concert.
Sakurai-san has been watching a lot of UNDERLIVE.
I go to see it every time.
Underlife is fun, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
This is a catering black pepper yaki.
It's a meal for the other members.
On the first day, Tokuhain Sakurai is the interviewer and Tokuhain Wakatsuki is the cameraman.
Good morning!
Can I ask you a question?
What song did you two choose?
Oh, today!
My song is called KOROGATTA KANE O NARASE
That's right!
I run around a lot and do a lot of things
I want to try that
Isn't it unexpected?
I didn't think I'd do it with a song like that
I think it's very unexpected, but I might want to see you
Really?
It's perfect!
Yeah, so I'm dancing with excitement, so please don't miss it.
Next, let's go to the dining room.
Ta-da!
Yay!
I'm eating rice.
I'm a person who doesn't eat at all when I'm on stage, but I'm really hungry today.
ZEN IN CENTER project, Saito-san is in charge of the sun knock.
It's my first time, so I hope I can get excited.
The song is also an exciting song, so I think it's suitable for the first song.
Ah!
Mi-o-na-tana
Oh!
How is it?
I'm very nervous, but the Budokan is a wonderful place, so I want to do my best so that everyone can have a good live.
It's so cool to be in the middle of the stage.
I can't imagine who would be able to come this far in the first place.
That's right.
This is the goal, isn't it?
Yes, it's true.
It's really amazing.
I'm really curious about what's going on.
I'm curious about what's going on.
After this, I hate you right away.
By the way, who will be the center today?
I will do it today.
I'm the center today because I lied to Tossa that day.
Last year's ARIAKE was the main song.
Our goal is to surpass last year's ARIAKE.
That's good.
Mr. Nagashima is the first member to know about the beginning of Under Live.
The engine of the Cayenne Miner
We keep saying the same thing over and over again.
It's really...
This is the last round of the competition.
Let's do it so that we can show you great things together!
No!
Thank you for watching!
Their dream, the Budokan Live, is about to begin!
In the middle of the game, the all-center game begins.
Everyone, please take a look at the center stage at once!
What are you wearing?
I'm 23 years old.
Did you watch it?
Here...
A certain announcement...
I'm Seira Nagashima
Nogizaka46
I'm going to graduate.
Yes.
I am...
To the next dream
Nagashima Seiru to shite no michi wo
I chose it.
From now on,
Nogizaka46
And...
Please take care of the other members of KAWAIKASHI MIRAI here.
Thank you for your support!
I can't stop looking at it.
I couldn't do it.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I want you to do your best, Nogizaka.
I'll do my best, too.
I want to make a better group.
What else do you want to do?
I agree with you.
I feel refreshed.
I've always wanted to tell everyone.
Under Live, Day 2
Let's go!
See you on the second day!
The second day of UNDERLIVE.
To be honest, I was the most excited at this venue yesterday.
I was confident that I stood out more than anyone else.
It was noisy.
I got a super lesson.
After everyone found it, I was told that it was there, so I would like to enjoy it so much that everyone will find it today.
On the second day, Tokuhain interviews Tokuhain and Tokuhain intervenes as a cameraman.
Nakano-san, are you there?
Here we are!
We're going to perform at the center today.
What song are you going to perform?
I'm going to perform for the first time in a while.
I'm so nervous.
Kiju-san and Kii-chan are here too.
Kii-chan?
They look so similar.
Kii-chan, you performed yesterday, right?
Yes, I finished yesterday.
Kiju-san was so cute.
Kiju-san?
Don't make fun of me.
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you too!
So today you're going to do it?
I'm the center today.
What song are you going to do today?
I'm going to be by your side when you can't do anything.
That's right.
The center of the fan club is special.
I don't know.
You're pretty good at it.
You're like a conductor.
I was doing a part-time job yesterday.
Reika, I think the camera suits you.
That's right.
The staff asked me if I could take it.
This is only three minutes long.
I'm desperate.
Oh!
Kimen-chan, Mikke-!
I couldn't listen to it yesterday.
That's right!
Today, do you have a center?
What is it?
I'm Haru's melody.
We've decided on a lot of MCs as well.
That's right.
Among the members, she has become a big sister, so that's right.
Hime-tan has a good voice, so I love her voice when she was an MC.
Oh, I'm happy. I'm doing my best.
Oh, I'm happy.
On this day, the members who had previously appeared in the Under Live came to support them.
They're having a good time.
Let's listen to the story of the start of the Under Live.
It's a bonus at the beginning.
I did it as a bonus for the handshake party.
After the handshake party, I watched it in Nagoya.
Everyone came to see the movie.
The members were the most excited when the fans were there.
MINAMI said this.
Not yet
When we didn't know each other, we decided to do a vlog together.
But at that time, I was like,
I can't do it.
To be honest.
I was serious about it.
What do you need?
It's been a long time since I came here, and it's been two days.
I can't believe it.
This is what I'm thinking about.
The second day of UnderLive has finally begun!
The two delivery men also hurried to the seats.
I didn't make it to the opening yesterday, so I want to make it to the opening today.
Thank you for watching!
The under members are also on standby!
Please take a look at the next performance!
Thank you so much for finding me.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it a high rating.
This is the end.
Mia-chan...
I did it!
Thank you for watching!
This is the end of our report for the past 10 days.
How was it?
It was a fun live.
We have to do our best.
We can't lose.
We got a lot of power, so let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
That's all for Nagizaka 46 Under Live!
Bye-bye!
And the second member of the lecture room is...
I wonder who will come.
Thank you for watching!
NANCHO
Hello, I'm Nishino.
Welcome!
It's rare to talk one-on-one like this.
No.
Just once,
Yeah.
When I went somewhere,
Airplane
Yes.
There was a seat next to me.
And together...
game
Yes, I did.
I rode it for a long time.
We played the game without sleeping for a long time.
Oh, maybe we did.
I think we did.
We did it.
Yeah.
It was when everyone was sleeping, right?
Even though it was pitch black.
Just the two of us.
I looked at the screen.
There was such a thing.
a ring
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching until the end.
But they talk, don't they?
I don't know.
I will talk about it.
Yes.
Reika is the same age as me.
Amazing.
Lick!
I'm being teased.
I'm saying this as a captain, but...
Nana is one of the members
I think it's the only...
For Raker,
They'll come, right?
It's a bit complicated.
But Reika is...
I'm not mad at you.
It's a little annoying.
I'm not angry.
That's why I'm the one who's happy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What the...
I don't even use my ears.
I can do it.
That's a good thing. I'm happy.
I think she's a good person.
He looked at me and didn't say anything at all.
I'm going to look down at you.
It's that kind of relationship.
First of all, this time it's called Kouhaku Special
How was it?
It's my first time.
Hmm...
It's been a long day.
It's really...
It was very deep.
Yes, it's a bit bumpy.
I knew it.
I thought it was a secret.
Mm-hmm.
But it was really fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, the atmosphere was...
But you know...
Well, it's amazing that I was able to come out.
I mean...
I don't think it makes much sense if it's just once.
Yeah.
When I was told that,
That's what I was told when I was gathered.
This year, Nogizaka Kohaku
It comes out like this.
At that moment,
This is definitely, just once
I thought it would never make any sense.
Wait, that's...
That's what I thought as soon as I heard the announcement.
I'm glad that I'm happy.
It's amazing.
It's kind of...
Now Kouhaku is over
I was happy to be in the group this year, but I want to be a group that can be in the group next year and the year after that.
There are a lot of members who say that in interviews.
As soon as I heard it for the first time,
It's amazing that your thoughts come to mind.
I thought so.
It's so fast.
You've changed a lot since the beginning, haven't you?
I think I have a lot of experiences, especially at the center.
I think they're doing a great job.
Since when did it change? After the center?
I think so.
When I realized it, it was the first time I had one thought in my mind.
I'm going to apply it on the center of my face.
All right.
And then...
After all, it was a hit wish.
Um...
Bungee jumping
I think I did my best
That was pretty...
Hmm.
For me, it's really...
so big
I highly recommend it.
Bungie? Macau's Bungie, right?
It's the highest in the world.
But I recommend it to everyone.
It flies really well.
Because of my anxiety and fear,
I won.
I mean, the result is...
I think I've become more confident about myself.
So after that, it's been a long time.
I was so excited.
Until then...
I was under a lot of pressure.
And then...
Ah, but...
Oh, I got it.
Like, I'll do it.
That's what I thought.
It changed so fast.
......
Thank you.
Hmm.
She's definitely different, but she seems to have a lot of room.
I don't like it.
again and again.
What is it?
the front and the center
Let me do it.
And then...
Well, when I say getting used to it,
I don't know if it's because of the music
I think she's moving on to the next step.
It's not about whether you can be in the center or not.
Right?
What do you personally think?
Gong-gu
What do you think, Nanase?
I want to be like that.
That's what I'm thinking.
Mmmmmmm...
Wow...
But now I'm in a group.
Yeah.
Hmm, but...
Right now, I'm...
Yeah
Oh, wait a minute.
What I want to do is...
Animal work.
I really like the work of animals.
And...
with animals that have something to do with it.
I got a hard job.
There's one thing I wish I could do.
I think so.
I can do it, bang bang
No, no, no
You can do it
That's how I feel.
I don't really say what I like
She's not the type of girl who's all over the place.
I get bored of my own face.
What?
There's that thing
Thank you for watching!
so
Are you bored?
Yes, I am.
And then...
I'm not a bully.
I feel like I'm getting tired of looking at the mirror when I'm doing my make-up.
I'm tired of watching it, so I'll just watch it.
It's not that I don't fully understand, but...
Make-up is also popular, and there are also things that are popular among themselves.
It's not about being particular about it.
I get it, I get it.
That's also...
I have to be aware of it.
I mean,
I was like, this is good enough for today.
It's like...
Let's turn it off.
I was thinking about changing the shape of my eyebrows.
Well, today...
I want to make the middle part thicker.
It's so cool.
It's always like this.
The freshness is amazing.
I've been told that it's important.
It's not always the same.
That's true.
Nagisaka is a girl group.
I've recently been told that it's a good group, but I'm rushing it.
I think she is one of the most important members of the group.
I'll do my best.
From now on,
I want you to get used to it.
Translated by Releska
Bye!
It looks like this.
Is it okay?
I talked to you as usual.
It was fun.
Really?
Is it fun?
Thank you for watching!
Don't give up, 46!