It's small but
Thank you so much!
Let's go home
Hello!
I'm Noyuko.
I'm the manager of Nogizaka46.
I suddenly took it with my cell phone
I was asked to make a video, but
I was wondering what to use, but I didn't know how to use it like this, and I didn't know the meaning of my birthday, so I was told to speak casually today.
I'm not a talent for the time being
This is Nagizaka46
I would like to introduce a video taken by our manager, but I am alone.
Nanaka-san from Senpai also came.
Hello, I'm Nonaka.
Konnichiwa.
Well, today I happened to be
When I went to the office, I learned that there was a narration, and when the scene was over, I was allowed to sit here, but let's leave that aside and watch the behind-the-scenes video of the handshake meeting.
Let's go!
This is what the backstage looks like.
When it comes to Overture, other than the well-known site, Haruto Farm, everyone's tension is maxed out and it's like that.
Minami is pushing Nanami.
That was cute.
Nanami is cute, too.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I took the next one.
For me, for someone else
I'm singing in the back
There are four of us.
Thank you for watching!
It's not about singing and dancing, is it?
Yes, it is.
What are you singing at the end of the song?
The people who wanted to sing at the end of the song.
It's just that the larynx is a little rough.
But it takes time.
Your face is great too!
It's fun.
Hohohohoho!
On the other side
Marika Shiraishi and
Kikimoto
but
This side looks like this, too.
People usually dance when they're in a bad mood, right?
Even if they're not in a good mood.
dance
We are having fun and having fun behind the scenes.
There are a lot of people who like songs that they haven't done before, so everyone does it seriously like this.
That's true.
Seriously.
That's right.
It looks fun.
Oh, it hurts. I ran into the field and was about to do my best.
And then we left.
Have a good trip.
This is how the actual handshake looks like, but who took this? Koi-chan?
No, it's not me.
Who is it?
Hmm?
Uh...
It's here!
The two people who love cameras.
The face of the person
They will come in for sure.
This is the one I took.
This is Chie-chan's birthday.
Who is this?
Chi-chan and Ami.
Yes.
Thank you for watching!
Huh? Isn't Ami here?
The old lady from the summer tour.
It was fun.
This is Nanami-san in the summer
She's practicing for the members
Can I sit here?
Thank you for watching!
I like this a lot.
It's a refreshing dish.
I can feel the summer.
Oh, this is Kawagopi trying to shake hands.
This is from a while ago.
Thank you very much.
A little?
I think so too.
I'm transforming into her.
Cargo P.
I'm transforming into Cargo P.
Konno-san.
Konno-san is leading the way.
Thank you.
You're kidding, right?
Yes, I am.
You can access it from here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time!
Let's eat!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
There was a face-shoot.
What?
Wasn't it a member?
Was it a member?
A member was coming.
Really?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Now it's time for the live performance.
Koi-chan...
Do you have any memories of the concert?
That's a lot.
There might be a lot, but it's a place where all the members have a sense of unity.
It's a good memory every time.
That's right.
Sigh...
Jingu from last year
It's already nostalgic.
I don't think it's been a year yet, but it's nostalgic.
Yes!
I don't know.
Everyone is screaming.
This person is getting closer and closer to the camera.
Hahaha
But it was fun.
It was exciting.
Good luck everyone!
This is from our national tour in 2013, and when I was listening to Kana,
Thank you for watching.
It's like a picture of Marika trying to make a fool out of herself.
That's all for today.
Nanami and Renarin are smart.
That's normal.
It's definitely the first time.
The first time.
Your face is so strong.
So, I'll tell Maya.
I'm trying to answer to Maya.
I'm glad I was able to do it today.
Thank you.
Don't look at me like that.
It's so funny.
This happy look is also nostalgic.
Is this a get-up?
Ah!
This.
It's delicious.
The one where Kazumi got injured and couldn't come out.
The one where Kazumi got injured and couldn't come out of the girls' room.
That's what I was wearing.
This is how we do our concerts.
There's a lot of drama behind it.
There is.
It's so hard.
I put a lot of thought into the stage.
Actually...
I was worried but I couldn't go out
Kazumi-san, seriously...
I wanted to be on stage for a long time.
I was so frustrated.
My hair is...
What?
Sit down.
Thank you for your viewing.
Right?
At times like this,
Translated by Releska
Thank you for watching!
The way she speaks and the way she talks
I don't know what to say.
Mom.
All I can do is stay by her side and encourage her.
Yeah.
The concert tour too.
There are probably only a few times.
The person himself is also very prominent.
It was like that.
It was hard for me too.
I'm happy to be with you.
This is a picture of Hashimoto's rehearsal.
Thank you for watching!
What are the two of them doing behind the scenes?
I don't know what you're doing, but I didn't notice you two.
I don't know if I was beaten by Hashimoto.
Thank you for watching!
The overreaction is amazing.
It's like a major leaguer because he's chewing gum.
Major leaguer?
This is a practice video of the Nogidan.
Can you play 8 beats?
I want to try this angle
Just like that
It didn't change much, but it was the limit of my height.
That's right.
Waki-Ai-Ai
Nogidan's...
I practiced a lot.
is
I was so busy that I couldn't find the time to do it, so everyone was so excited.
But it was so much fun to be able to do it all together.
That's right.
That's why it's like this every time.
lol
Thank you for watching!
From now on, it will be a production series.
Yes, everyone gathers for the release of the CD, so we shoot various things, but we don't remember what we shot.
I have a lot of things to do, and when I realize it, I have a lot of videos and photos that I don't remember taking on my phone.
This is Shiraishi and Takayama practicing Shibuya Blues during the mannequin photoshoot.
Nanonono
Are you going to school?
Thank you for watching until the end.
Unable to move freely, wearing a uniform
Rokokanoro
Shibuya
Yeah!
Thank you!
Can you hear me?
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you for watching!
Yes, this is the back of the shooting, not here, but somewhere else.
Iku-chan holding a knife is scary.
It's dark.
It's beautiful.
It looks good.
You can do it.
I forgot to take off my mask.
Okay, let's go.
It's hot.
I want to live as I am, but I can't do that.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
It's just a normal kiss.
Thank you very much.
In the end, it was dangerous, so I was stopped by Ikoma.
Shut up!
I'm getting used to it.
Minami can do it too.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Let's eat!
There are so many of them.
Now
There's also a cooking event.
They seem to be doing it, so I want them to do their best.
The cat is still a child.
The cat is cute.
This is the food series for Na-chan.
Thank you for watching.
Let's open your mouth a little more.
All right, all right, all right.
It's over.
Then, from there...
I don't understand.
It's silent.
It's quiet, isn't it, Nanase-san?
Thank you for watching.
普段も
That's how I feel about it.
Just like that.
But you eat quite a lot, don't you?
Yes, I do.
This is the sun nook mv
This is Naa-chan, who shows me Tokyo during the shooting.
This is from when I shot the fan MV.
Yes.
It's nostalgic.
6th sheet
It's the 6th one.
What is this? It's a freebie.
Is this a freebie?
It's for the production team.
This
Yeah, well...
MVs, for example...
When I was on a singing program, I always took a choreography video of the members dancing to this song.
制作の方に
I'm doing this work so that people can see it in advance.
That...
That's V, right?
Ahime Kamoa
I know.
This is Kimeka's dance.
I'm exhausted.
Wow, it's so nostalgic.
This is a dance lesson for a music video that I did by accident.
The sound was reversed, so it was a lot of work.
It looks like it's going to be a really tough day.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
The sound is reversed.
I think it's good.
I want everyone to be in the same team.
For some reason, Takayama-san and Shirai-san are in the same team.
Matsumura-san, no, Hashimoto-san
I was walking around like, I don't know, 5th floor?
The last one!
This is the first step.
Hey!
Thank you!
It went well up to ton ton ton.
This is a really cute moment for Minami.
Thank you!
You are so cute.
You do that a lot.
lol
Have you forgotten this song?
No, I haven't.
Thank you very much.
This is also recent.
Sekkachi!
It's a one-piece MV.
That's right.
This is probably a problem with Hei.
You can't decide which is which
I'm sorry.
I hate it.
It's a pancake.
It's been a long time since I've been here, so I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go to Karagishima.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
Do you have any memories with MaiMai?
There seems to be a lot, do you have any?
I have a lot of memories with him.
Recently
Hashimoto, Kawago, Shinuchi,
We celebrated MaiMai's birthday.
You included Koi-chan too?
Thank you for watching.
This is a special video of the single.
It's about overcoming your weaknesses.
T-Money
Akimoto Manatsu
That's right.
But...
I'll think about it.
You're trying to think about it, aren't you?
I'm still thinking about it.
It's like...
Poor thing, she's crying.
Thank you.
while crying
Kiyo-chan is 2 years old.
I can't believe it!
This is what Iku-chan is not good at.
What did I do?
What is it?
Yuri!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is there another one? I can't think of one.
Thank you.
I don't think so.
Then let's open it.
I don't want it to pop out like this.
I don't want to go to the bathroom.
Yes.
Awww!
I can't believe it!
lol
You scream a lot.
It looks fun, but I'm not good at it.
lol
Thank you for watching!
Ah!
I can't believe it!
Thank you for watching until the end.
I don't seem to be very good at it, though.
I really don't like this
Bye!
So, today, Ikuta-san will...
I'm not good at it.
KOKUFU
Itadakimasu
How do I do it?
Anyway, let's have fun!
In order to be able to get along with pigeons,
Today, I'm going to show you
I'm going to learn HATOMAGIC
lol
What are you doing?
AHHHHH
Thank you for watching!
You'll get even worse at it.
Thank you for your viewing.
So,
He gradually became friends with the pigeons, and in the end...
It's delicious.
I'm going to show you today.
What kind of person do you want to get along with?
Well, let's try that.
No way.
It's a theory in the first place, isn't it?
Do you have to get along with someone?
I was surprised.
Done.
For the time being, I will do my best even though I'm not good at it.
Well, I'll do my best for now.
What are you doing?
Thank you for your viewing.
I'll do my best.
I'll take this.
I'll learn magic.
I'll do my best with magic.
Okay, I'll take it.
Just a little bit.
I don't know what you mean by just a little bit.
I don't think so.
It's hard at the end.
I'm sure it's a snake.
Wow!
Let's hide it once.
Let's pretend it didn't happen.
lol
What?
How many times have I said meaningless things?
It's amazing!
It's really big.
It's packed tightly.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you for watching.
What?
Let's go to Hakodate.
It's written on the other side.
Can you see it?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It's convenient.
What are you doing there?
Don't you say you don't bite?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
It's a living thing.
Basically, it doesn't matter.
Basically?
It's very quiet.
Is there something?
If you feel that you have been damaged, you can eat it.
Thank you very much.
Basically, you have to do it gently.
Translated by Releska
Thank you for your viewing.
This is a personal pv of Shiraishi at the time of the 5th one.
mhm
I think it's the back side.
OK, go!
I can't make up
Let's go home.
Is that Takayama?
Takayama.
I can do it except for Takayama.
I used to go to an e-commerce store.
I can't do it.
If you use the features, you can do it.
Oh, someone's here.
Thank you.
something like that
do you do that?
I do
really?
I don't remember
who else?
It's delicious.
The quality of Shiraishi's impersonations is really high.
It's really high.
It's really...
Um...
I'm good at grasping the characteristics.
It's not just an impersonation, but I think she's very smart.
There's a lot.
And this is Ikoma biting a lemon.
Mmm
The reaction is really good, so please check it out.
Let's do it at once.
I'm hungry
3, 2, 1...
Bye!
Thank you for watching!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Ma'am?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know.
IKOMA has always had a good reaction to music.
Sometimes I feel like...
It's a reaction that you can understand, isn't it?
It's really amazing.
Thank you, Sakizu-san!
OK!
This is a real failure!
I'll do it, too.
Thank you very much!
At the right time.
This is the one I took.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm going to put it in your hand.
Everyone is taking pictures of Oni-chan's phone.
Is that so?
I don't like it.
I'm not talking about the doctor, I'm talking about Minami.
Minami is like this.
Thank you.
No matter what I do, I end up in the south.
It goes well with pancakes.
It's amazing.
No matter what you do, you're still Minami.
Thank you very much.
This is the Sato Shigoto series.
First of all, it seems to be a very valuable video.
This is the bus heading to the Kouhaku press conference.
Thank you.
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
He's the only one who's nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous and my chopsticks are stuck
Thank you very much.
How is it?
Is the wind okay?
Thank you very much.
I did it by myself.
See you tomorrow or the day after.
What is this?
Unexpectedly
It's fun!
Everyone
It's not that I'm nervous.
I'm so excited!
Shomei-san!
You're so cute!
Are you nervous?
A little bit.
Yeah
So I'll see you in China
Yeah, that's nice
I think it's a good idea to do it every day.
Thank you so much everyone.
Everyone is shining on me.
It's me.
It's normal.
Are you nervous?
I'm so nervous.
You're not lying, are you?
No, I'm not.
Oh, really?
Really?
Yes
I'm going to eat dinner!
We just got together.
It's Kohaku Mile.
If you're hungry, you have to go to the war.
I have to go to the war.
Thank you very much.
It's already NHK.
There are people outside.
Last year, I was able to participate in Nengan no Kouhaku.
That's great. I'm so moved.
How about you, Koi-chan?
Yes, I am...
After this...
The year before that, I was in charge of AKB48, and I first appeared in Kohaku.
This time, Nogizaka...
I was very happy to be able to come out as 146.
The day of Kouhaku...
All day long, from morning to night, we had no time to rest.
We were able to wrap up 2015 with a good sense of tension and a smile.
And then...
This one was taken by Kikuchi-san in Prague.
It's amazing.
How are you feeling from the second day in Asaichi?
I'm fine.
I put it in the first place.
As expected
Thank you for watching.
I was a little sleepy.
I overslept, but it's cold in the morning.
During the day, it's over 30 degrees, but in the morning, it feels like spring.
We're doing our best!
What time is it today?
Today is...
3, 2, 1
5 o'clock start!
This is the place.
I woke up at 3 o'clock at 10 o'clock.
Oh, it's already night time.
If I stay up late, I won't be able to sleep.
Let's do our best today.
Japan, please wait for us.
Yes.
Na-chan, please do something.
Thank you for watching!
Is it on?
Yes.
I'm waiting for the second day.
I'm doing graphics over there.
Mayan is shooting over there, and I'm alone.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
I'm bored.
There is also
What are you looking at?
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
I'm going home today.
Hmm?
This is...
Kyoto's
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
I'm glad I could come to FURAHA.
Thank you.
I'm wearing a white bra.
It's so cute. It's in the box.
Thank you.
It's a very recent one. I shot it.
The one from 7-Eleven?
Yes, the one from the commercial.
Thank you for watching.
7-Eleven
I'm so excited!
Okay okay
This tree is amazing.
It's hot.
A video?
I'm scared.
From now on...
I'm going to take a picture.
I'm going to say my lines one by one.
I'll finish it in one shot.
I'm going home at 9 o'clock today.
Is this okay?
I'm tired.
This is my ability.
Thank you.
I'm so busy.
Tomorrow is the big day!
This is crazy!
16 days
Thank you very much.
Go for it! Go for it!
I'm rooting for you, Mama!
This is from Teiichi's rehearsal on the day before the actual show.
He pulled Inoue out of the stage and did the commercial shoot here.
This is also a very recent video.
It's the Sayuringo Corps behind the scenes of Nogibingo.
Koi-chan, look at this.
Are you filming while rotating with Matsumura and the others?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
It's just a game.
The captain of the Sayuringo Corps and the vice-captain.
I can't believe it.
Kanji
It's a joke.
Thank you for watching!
Oh, that's right!
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Are you serious?
I also bought a DVD of the song that I had a hard time listening to, so I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I'm scared.
I'm a real Umamiko.
Oh, you said that.
Umamiko, Umamiko, Umamiko.
I don't know what to say.
Is that so?
I think so.
I heard it from a friend.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
Could it be that Kuma and Ichi-san went back to their room?
Yes, they went back to their room.
I don't know how to describe it.
It's the same, isn't it?
Oh, this is what I...
It's a weird face from the day I took it forcibly.
It's almost the same.
It's pretty, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Shin-chan, come here!
This is what Maaya asked me to do
Facial exercise?
It's not good.
I don't know.
He said he wanted to talk to me.
Thank you for watching!
Hold it with your hand like this.
Basically, you can do it on this side.
I don't know what to say.
But Maaya is really...
The mood maker of the group is really kind.
It's a healing Maya.
And this is Karin who can't open the key.
Karin-sama...
I'll do my best a little more.
I think there's a trick to this.
It's a little difficult.
I gave up.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm taking a break now. Who is it?
It's amazing!
I can see it! It's an art!
Who is it?
I'm sorry for waking you up
lol
Let's go!
Good morning!
It's really messy now.
Let's do our best!
Let's go!
SOMBARU
This is also during the break in the middle of the summer.
This is something I'm drawing with my voice out.
Don't you want to eat?
I don't want to eat
Iku-chan is watching.
I don't know.
Thank you very much.
Oh, peace!
Peace!
I won't give it to you.
There's no sound from the sub.
No, no, no.
Soshin!
I feel the same way as Ikusa.
It's really like this in the summer.
From here, we'll look at the parts that we thought we shot well and the parts that we don't know why we shot them.
Moving on. This is a pretty famous scene.
This is a scene of the members of the principal's school watching over the IKOMA that appeared in the AKB's election.
Yes
I think it's my first time to appear with a reaction.
I was nervous on the other side as well.
Right?
I'm scared.
Thank you very much.
Doi-Chu-Yo-I
Final cut shot
40,000
I'm going to throw up.
There is a video of Ikoma.
The sound is
Thank you for watching.
Yes.
That's right.
That's the main thing.
Get out of Akasaka
I'm going to taste it now, but it's delicious.
Yes.
But today...
How is it?
I voted for Estelle.
and Wakatsuki.
I'm going to take a picture.
Today is the second day.
while eating fruits and granola
I thought it was a monitor infection.
I don't know.
Now I can go out.
I was happy.
Like...
Good sense of tension
We went on stage together.
Thank you for watching!
Long time no see.
It was fun.
This is the last one.
There are so many
Thank you for watching!
Can you do it?
I'm grateful for that.
See you at the end
Maybe next time
After the event is over, I get in this car and listen to something.
I might be able to listen to it.
What do you think?
What? But...
No matter what the ranking is, even if it's low, I think it's expensive for us.
I don't know.
Even though it's raining,
My activities in AKB48 are
I can't do it.
Recently, I've been doing a lot of stretching at the principal.
So...
In my opinion,
I will
It's not like NATO.
This is a pre-election story.
In this way, IKOMA...
The members can see how hard they work on their own.
I was watching it.
Well, Nogizaka...
In any of our projects, we use IKOMA together.
We were given a tissue to cheer them on.
All of us.
All of us, all of the members.
I feel like I was supporting IKOMA.
All the fans and all the members together.
I think this is the 14th place.
This is Ikoma after the election.
Yeah, that's true.
Ah...
Ah!
Everyone is crying.
Thank you for watching!
It's like...
I want people to support me
It's so...
This is Nii's.
I'm so happy to be able to do something like this.
Thank you.
There are so many words that support us.
It's very powerful.
I got it.
It's been a long time.
I really did my best today.
I got it.
I can't say everything when I'm speaking, so I regret it a little.
I'm surprised.
So today...
When I get home,
What do I want to do at the end? Just the end.
This is the last question.
Ta-da!
I want to eat rice.
Today...
I think it's something I like.
Yes.
and put it on the principal's fixed camera
For some reason, it contains Matsumura's toothpaste.
I was doing this to the camera all the time.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Did you do it on purpose?
And this is the moment when we get to know Ikoma's surprise announcement.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
This is the end of the video.
I'm out of here.
Who?
Rena is out of here.
I'm out of here.
I don't know what to do.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Okay.
Uchiwa is the only one.
There are a lot of other remover products.
Thank you.
I see.
Okay, let's go.
I'm not in that position, but
From this point of view,
It might make you feel relieved
To be honest, it looked like it was a lot of work.
I don't know what IKONA is thinking right now.
But when I think about my body,
Was it good?
Thank you very much.
Nogizaka
I can concentrate on that.
It might be a good opportunity.
This is Asuka, who was kidnapped for some reason, and this is Koi.
I got it.
What is this?
No!
If you turn it, the
lol
Who's that in the back?
Marika.
Oh, it's Marika.
Thank you.
I can hear Kazumi's voice.
Where is this?
Oh, I see.
Fried chicken with shumai
Are you laughing at me?
Thank you for watching until the end.
It's a bit of a disappointment.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
What are you doing?
She's like a baby.
She laughs a lot.
Let's go.
Good luck.
See you.
Thank you for watching!
This is the most meaningless thing.
This is Miria's part
It's close.
Even with the makeup on, your skin is still so soft and soft.
Yes, my skin is so beautiful.
I'm so jealous.
Ayane-chan
But everyone really likes cameras, right?
It's a service for everyone.
When you turn the camera,
When I look at her phone, she always reacts to whatever it is.
This is the footage of Seira Nagashima's graduation concert.
It's a picture of the members who hang out with the staff during the shoot.
That's it.
There may be people who don't know, but a person named Seira Nagashima is actually about to graduate, so I think it's still a secret, but this weekend, Seira Nagashima's graduation live will be held, so unfortunately everyone is doing the first day of the under-live, so unfortunately you can't go.
There may be people who go to see it, but they can't go out.
Finally, this may be a little too much, but it's a song that everyone sings while drinking.
It's a song that everyone sings while drinking.
That's right.
It's not going any further.
It's a song that everyone sings while drinking.
Every time, every time.
It's a jittery reaction.
This is really recent.
I think it's Guam.
Yes.
I don't know what they're trying to do.
We don't know what's going on.
We're just running.
They look like they're having fun.
What are they doing?
Are you starting to do it?
But this is how it's supposed to be.
It's always like this.
It's not like I have a goal or anything, but I just want to have fun.
That's how I do it.
So...
Bye!
I thought it would be better to run, so I brought you here to run with me.
You're not thinking that way, are you?
Thank you for watching until the end.
What?
What? What? What?
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
It's pretty.
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute.
This is the four-person version of the story.
Nope.
Is the water okay?
Yes
The water is delicious
Thank you very much.
I don't have a specific goal.
That's right.
Bye!
Anyway, it was hot, so I had to bring water from time to time.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
Parasol Nider!
Oh, I didn't expect that.
I came out of the beach.
Wow.
Is it a stolen car?
It's a stolen car.
It's a colorful parasol rider.
I feel like I could fly. But I feel like it's going to rain.
I know, right?
Thank you for watching.
If you go that way, you can't go forward because of the wind.
I'm trying my best, so please cheer me up.
I'm sorry.
Really.
Really?
Yes, really.
That's wonderful.
Keep it up.
It's fun.
It's really firm.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching.
It's about time.
It's the end, but is it really okay?
I don't have any tears or anything, but is it okay?
I wonder if it's okay.
I just want to say this.
I don't want to be rude, but I'm really shy, so if you see me shaking hands, I want you to be quiet.
I'm really sorry.
That's all I ask.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Then I'll say goodbye to this song at the end.
I'm sorry for the autumn and midsummer.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I was worried about not being able to rest.
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye.
See you next time!
Thank you for watching until the end.
It's hot!
If you think so, why don't you hug me?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!