This time, we have invited 12 students
from Nogizaka 3rd grade.
A total of 15 students will have fun
learning English for 60 minutes.
In the self-introduction that will be
held from now on,
you will be told the three English
sentences that you have just learned in
your room.
In addition, you will be asked to ask a
question to get to know the other
person.
Here is the question that can be used
there.
Kubo-san, what does this mean?
What do you do on your day off?
Please answer what you do on your day
off.
For example, if you're going to watch a
movie, Ozono-san.
Ah, that's good, that's good. You don't
have to go.
Sensei, please listen to me until the
end.
Watch.
Movie.
TV.
Ah, watch TV.
Movies are called watch movies.
Actually, movies were a lie.
Please answer without stopping.
From now on, the lyrics of a famous
Japanese song will be announced in
English.
The members will translate the English
lyrics and guess what song it is.
Ms. Ozono, Ms. Nojo, and Ms. Ito got the
correct answer.
The last one is...
Correct!
Nakamura-san, there's only one person
left.
Do you have anything in mind?
A happy song.
That's a good one!
There's no such song.
"Oh, how happy we would be."
"Sekai shiawase no uta."
That's the part you're best at.
Yes.
For Ms Nakamura who still doesn't know
the answer, let's ask Ms Ozono to
translate it into Japanese.
Oh, how happy we would be.
What was that?
You understood it perfectly, didn't you?
But I didn't get it.
You still didn't get it. Are you okay?
I don't know.
What was that reaction?
You sang that far.
Are you ok?
I'm just kidding.
It's ok.
That was perfect.
I'm glad you said that.
I have to say it on TV.
It's hard to be on TV.
It's ok.
Can you sing for her in English?
Sing for her in English.
"Under the big tree"
That's a good one!
You don't know it?
Please sing it in Japanese.
Then maybe she will understand.
One, two, three!
"Under the big tree"
You don't know it?
You really don't know it?
The answer is this!
"Under the big chestnut tree"
The word that we want the 3rd generation
to remember is
"How"
"How to"
What does "How to" mean?
You've heard of it right?
Yes
How much?
Did you just sing?
Yes, I did.
How much?
Isn't it good? Sing that song.
How many, how much, how much do you
want?
Did you learn it at school?
Yes, I did.
How many, how much, how much do you
want?
But since it's "How to" you often say
"How to bon" right?
That's easy.
She's laughing.
It means how to do something.
For example, how to play tennis?
Yes, how to play tennis.
How to dance?
Yes, how to dance.
From now on, Nick will appear and have a
conversation using "how to" and
"something".
Nick asks, "Can you teach me how to do
'something'?"
Nick says, "I'll show you how to do
'something'."
Let's teach Nick the correct way to do
it.
When you teach with gestures, the
expression you use is familiar to the
regular 3 people, right?
What was it?
Like this.
As expected!
Like this, right?
For example, if it's how to eat sushi,
say "like this" and teach.
First up is Ms. Ozono and Ms. Mukai.
Here we go.
How do you do sumo?
Wait a minute. Say this properly.
I'll show you how to sumo.
No, it's not a sumo wrestler.
It's a sumo wrestler.
Is it hand clapping?
Oh, Ozono.
Like.
Why are they silent?
You learned it, right?
Oh, they're pushing each other.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes.
So now you are satisfied.
I'm satisfied.
3 regular members will be the captains,
and the game will be split into 3 teams.
The team that wins the game will receive
a King of Rokkeben, Jojoen Bento as a
reward.
However, the losing team will receive a
severe punishment.
Kubo, I heard from Wada-chan
I was studying for a test and I was
watching Nogieigo
I got a question and I was able to
answer it
What is this? The teacher...
The teacher is Kubo
What did you get?
I got "Like this"
Oh, that's good.
Great!
It's useful for the test, too.
That's right.
From the various things in the gym,
Nick brings what he said in English.
"Lend-a-thing race"
Each team selects one person and plays
against three people at the same time.
The team that brings the right thing
will get 5 points.
This is the third round.
Please bring me something old people
would like.
Bring me something old people would
like.
Please bring me something old people
would like.
Come on.
Something old people would like.
No, no, no, no.
OK?
Calm down.
You see, Onsei-san is running with a
gun.
Armament?
I thought you were going to go over a
high bar.
They might have sold to old people.
That's a difficult...
This is different, right?
This isn't right.
People's favorite things.
Sleeping.
People's favorite things. Sleeping.
Blanket.
Everyday, people's favorite things.
Sleeping.
I see.
That's how you interpret it, right?
Yes.
Okay, O-dono.
What did you think it was?
Light.
Light?
Right?
What's right?
Thank you.
Bring what is related to the right.
It's a matter of principle.
I see. I understand.
And then, Iwamoto.
I heard a beep.
Did you say something you shouldn't have
said?
One more time.
Please bring me something old people
would like.
Do you think this is right?
Gold?
What did the two bring?
Osano didn't change.
She went to the other side.
She didn't change.
She went with this.
I see.
And Iwamoto.
Gold?
This is old, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It was developed a long time ago.
I see.
It's old.
So, say it again, please.
Please bring me something old people
would like.
In other words, bring me something old
people would like.
OK?
So, that's OK?
What about that?
What do you think, Glove?
I don't know Japanese, I'm sorry.
Baseball lover
Japanese
Yeah?
Grandfather
Japanese grandfather
Baseball lover
Oh, Japanese grandfathers love baseball
Love
That's right
Is that true?
Yeah, that's true
You're convinced?
Yeah, I'm convinced
If they like it
Okay, 1 point!
Let's go with 1 point
I don't know.
How do you say "tradition" in English?
Oh, you're not convinced.
Kendo!
She's just saying "kendo" over and over
again.
But the old people like kendo?
Old people like kendo.
Oh, really?
Alright, then maybe let's just give her
one point.
One point.
You get one point.
You already know the answer.
The traditional one is "traditional".
"Kendo is a traditional Japanese sport"
is the correct answer.
Each team has a number from 1 to 5.
If you hit the opponent with a
dodgeball,
you can see the number.
The team with the most correct answers
wins.
The winning team gets 10 points.
I think it's best to guess the first
letter.
That's right.
It's easier to understand if you know
the first letter than the middle of the
word.
So I think it's easier to understand if
you guess the first letter as much as
possible.
This is a hint.
Please do it like that.
What do you think about dodgeball?
Are you good at it?
I'm good at it.
That's good.
How about you, Ozora?
I hate it.
Why do you hate it?
I hate watermelon and dodgeball the most
in the world.
You hate watermelon and dodgeball the
most in the world?
I'm really curious about the watermelon
one, too.
Why do you hate dodgeball?
I've had a lot of questions about
hitting games since I was in elementary
school.
Hitting? The act of hitting a person
with a ball?
If it's a knife, is it a game to kill?
If it's a knife, it's not a game to
kill, right?
It's definitely not.
It's not, right?
That's what I thought when I was in
elementary school.
If the ball is a knife, what are you
going to do?
What is this game?
But today, don't worry.
It's not a knife.
It's a ball today, so don't worry.
NEXT GAME
That's all for today.
Next game is next month, so I'll show
you a little bit.
MES OZONO is finally challenging a
dodgeball that she is not good at.
In addition, the members are really
embarrassed by the obstacle relay.
And...
MES YAMASHITA is crying.
See you next time!
There?
The reason for the shock is...
John Mese
And the second round is Team Nojo vs.
Team Wada
Are you okay, Ozono?
Are you okay?
I'm okay
Actually, on Miss Ozono's last month's
broadcast
I hate watermelon and dodgeball the most
in the world
Why do you hate dodgeball?
I've been wondering if it's a game where
you have to hit the ball
You think it's weird to hit a person
with a ball?
If it's a knife, it's a game where you
have to kill someone
What will happen if she confesses her
fear of dodgeball?
Let's go
Are you okay? Didn't you just say your
hand was messed up?
Iwamoto! You're so aggressive!
Go, Watase!
Someone help Otono!
No one can save the adult.
Now, Wada-chan is...
Miss Maya got number 3.
The problem is her English ability.
Number 3 is coming.
Number 3 is A.
Anything is fine.
I think number 3 is A.
Class.
Oh, that's too bad.
By the way, is Kurasa in third place?
That's right.
Waza-san, that was a nice play.
I see.
Well, you're out.
Well, let's go.
Let's start with the Nojo team!
Are you okay?
What's going on?
This is dodgeball!
It's like this!
It's coming out!
That's right!
I'm going to die!
You're not going to die!
Ozono, you're not going to die!
Are you okay, Ozono?
Ozono, get in the line!
It's like someone with a knife really
appeared!
Look at her reaction.
It's a ball, right?
She said she wouldn't die, but...
She has a family.
She said, "I have a family too."
She said, "Please help me."
I see.
Team Nojo's first hit.
The answer is "Yes, Iwamoto"
What does that have to do with it?
What's with that face?
If you're going to chase me, listen to
me!
What a waste!
It's fine, if you say it right away, you
might get it right.
Oh, 3?
Sorry, not 3.
Nice try.
Team Wada Ball is back.
Alright, Mukai, you can go now.
Mukai, you're amazing!
You've saved a lot of power.
You can do it with feint.
Ah, this is strong!
They hit each other!
Now, let's go with the two of you.
You got 2 and 4.
Megoto, Messato got 2.
Number 4 got 2.
And what will each of them get?
L and C.
Will they get it?
What is it?
No, you can't discuss it.
You can't discuss it.
It's a big deal.
At times like this, Owada-chan won't say
anything.
Let's go with the one that didn't work.
Yes.
It's okay, it's okay.
Black.
K.
And...
B.
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
If you don't get the meaning right, you
won't get the correct answer.
The meaning is...
Black.
Correct!
Yay!
The facial expression team has become
beautiful, right?
Everyone has this kind of expression.
Can you say something like "Damn it"?
It's frustrating.
The last is Team Kawago vs. Team Wada.
Here I go.
Damn it!
There is still a secret weapon, OZONO.
OZONO is very scared because it is a
pass to the ally.
Oh! Yoda is amazing!
Kubo!
Good!
Oh! Tsume!
Oh!
You can get it firmly, Kubo!
OZONO!
It's a pass!
Go!
Oh! Yoda!
Oh!
Yoda!
What's Yoda's number?
It's number 2.
Team Wada gets number 2.
The answer is Miss Kubo.
I got number 2.
Now, H.
Now, Kubo.
Are you okay? Kubo looks like he's going
to collapse.
Are you okay?
It's useless.
Now, Kanbei.
Yes.
It's only Kanbei.
Shoes.
It's the same, right?
Ah, it's really good.
Even with shoes, H will come here.
But, unfortunately, it's not.
Now, it's time for the game to resume.
Well then, Oozora.
Don't do that!
Cameraman, please step back a little.
I'm going to make a place for you to be
spoiled.
You've never done this before, have you?
Hiding behind the cameraman.
You didn't have a cameraman at school,
did you?
Do it properly.
Please.
Well then, let's start.
Let's start with Kawako's team.
Go ahead!
You're throwing it while smiling.
Well then, Yoda.
Go ahead!
Here it comes, Kawako!
Are you okay?
Don't come this way!
I'm going to die!
You're not going to die.
Here it comes, Nakamura!
Are you okay?
It's starting to sound like Panko-san.
If it's like this, just don't dance.
Just don't dance.
Wow, amazing!
Is this how you do it?
No, it's not a bomb, it's a line that's
coming out.
I can't go.
Are you okay?
Nice, isn't Mukai good too?
Nakamura was hit.
Unlike how it looks, Miss Kubo got the
correct answer.
Will she get the correct answer this
time?
This is D.
I don't know this one.
D.
The second one is H.
So it's D.
Let's use the image of the whole body
and try to guess.
I can't think of anything.
I want you to guess this one.
Do your best.
To be continued.
You don't want to fight with everyone,
do you?
I don't know which one to choose.
There's only one word that came out.
It's not a word, but...
"Third"
It's a nice try, but...
It's not in this word.
That's too bad.
Nice try. Very nice try.
It's from now on.
Team Power-Go's attack is back.
Of course, the target is...
Ouch!
Watch out when you run away.
Go!
Here it comes!
What?
How did it go?
You got it!
Umezawa got it!
Team Wada got the 3rd letter. Will it be
the correct answer?
The 4th letter is "L".
How is it?
This is good.
Let's imagine the whole picture.
What is it?
Did you get it?
What is the answer?
Child.
Don't say the meaning yet.
No.1 is C. And No.3 is I.
Child. What does it mean?
Correct!
I wanted someone to get it right.
I thought I was going to die.
So, Team Wada wins!
Team Wada wins!
After the second round, as you can see,
the team spirit has been taken away a
little.
And the final match is the obstacle
relay in English.
The team with the best time wins by
clearing the course with five obstacles
in relay.
However, the button is the A word.
Write the word on the back of the next
runner.
If you can get the right answer, the
next runner will give you another
question, and you'll have to clear the
obstacle course and pass it on to the
next runner.
You get 15 points for first place, 10
points for second place, and 5 points
for third place.
At this point, the possibility of
winning the team farm is gone.
Oh my gosh!
Next up is Team Wada.
I'll challenge you in the order you see
here.
The top batter is Mukai.
So, Niku-san, please!
Let's go!
Everyone is struggling at the beginning.
Great!
I wanted Mukai to run.
When Mukai does something, everyone
laughs.
That's good!
Please write on your back.
One more time?
Yes
A
T
That's correct!
The next keyword is this!
Everyone is having a hard time with this
That's amazing
Are you okay? You're stammering
Did you hit your head?
You hit your head, didn't you?
Are you okay?
Will it come out? Will it come out?
It came out!
Wada-chan
Wada-chan is good, but let's see how
powerful she is.
Yes, OK.
Man!
That's correct!
Now, the next keyword is this.
Yes, OK.
OK.
Now, this is...
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
This really hurts.
Now, jump! Jump straight!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it
hurts!
It's hard to write, isn't it?
Here it is.
Tell me what it says.
One.
That's fast.
Next keyword.
Here it is.
It's not scary this time.
That's good.
That's the best so far.
Let's go.
Omoji! Omoji!
Ok, Y
O, Y
O, O?
O
U
O? What?
O!
Yes! Correct!
Not yet, not yet, not yet
Not yet, not yet
Ok
You can turn around
1, 2, 3, 4
5, 6
Sit!
8, 9, 10
Are you ok?
You are doing great!
Last one!
E
E?
E, A
E, A?
T, F
T, E, A
E, T
E, E
T, F
E, A, T
What is it?
E, A, E
Correct
So, what is the correct answer?
How many seconds was it?
34 seconds!
Amazing!
So, the final result announcement.
First is 3rd place.
Of course...
25 points.
Nojo team!
We did our best.
I thought Nojo was 1st place.
Why did you say that?
So, who is the winning team?
1st place is...
51 points for Team Wada!
Team Wada won by a landslide with "King
of Rokeben" and "Jojoen Mentouga".
And the last team is...
It's a penalty game!
Did you forget?
How was it? What did you dislike the
most?
I didn't like dodgeball.
Really?
I didn't like the game where you have to
hit the ball.
I don't think it's good.
Was it your dream to be a triathlete?
I wasn't good at English.
But it was fun to play while exercising.
I wanted to learn more.
From now on, hit the ball with both
hands.
Next time, hit the ball with your left
hand.
I didn't want to hit the ball.
Next time, we will show you the
unreleased scenes of the special that
the 3rd generation didn't get to do.
The scenes that were cut off from
classes and games are repeated.
The special that the 3rd generation came
to Nogiei after 2 months.
This time, we will show you a lot of
unreleased scenes that were not included
in the special.
First of all, let's start with the self-
introduction in the English of the 3rd
generation, which was broadcast on the
July special.
Introduce your name, birthplace,
nickname to the other person as a pair.
In addition, the rule that you have to
ask one question to know the other
person.
In the July special,
First of all, Miss Maya and Miss Nojo,
rock-paper-scissors in English.
These two did it.
Rock, scissors, scissors, go.
Rock, paper, scissors, go.
Say it again.
Ozora-san didn't say it at all.
One more time.
Rock, paper, scissor, scissor, scissor.
Ozono-san, it's not good to do it later.
Try to say it with rhythm.
Rock, paper, scissor, scissor, scissor.
You can't do rock-paper-scissors.
After rock-paper-scissors, Ms. Ozono
will introduce herself.
My name is Momoko Ozono.
I'm from Kagoshima.
Please call me Momoko.
Momoko. OK.
You haven't asked her yet.
What do you do on a holiday?
I go shopping.
Yes.
Dai-chan, please give her a reaction.
You asked her a question.
Don't ignore her when she answers.
That's right.
Reaction is important.
You go shopping, right?
Yes.
I go shopping.
That's right. I go shopping.
You should have said that.
I go shopping.
"Go shopping" is "I go shopping".
"To" doesn't go in before "shopping", so
be careful.
My name is Minami Umezawa. I'm from...
Please look at the person who is
talking.
I'm from Kanagawa. Please call me
Minami.
Well...
What is your least favorite food?
Can you take a picture of her?
What's your favorite?
Or least favorite?
Don't answer questions with questions.
I'm...
Watermelon.
"I'm Suica"
The teacher has changed a bit.
I've made up my mind.
It's "I'm Suica".
What does "I'm Suica" mean?
It means "I'm Suica".
Do you know how to say "Suica" in
English?
Yes.
Watermelon.
Christy, you're amazing.
"I don't like watermelon."
My least favorite food is watermelon.