Once again for those supporting Keyakizaka46
arigatou gozaimasu
And then for everything so far in this live stream
to those who have been watching
arigatou gozaimasu
arigatou gozaimasu~
Its been so long since we've done a concert
Those who have always been there to support us
its been awhile since you've seen us moving around on stage
with all of us wanting to deliver the power from the messages in our songs
its been awhile since they've let us put on a performance for you
Hopefully you were able to recapture all those feelings again?
And then right here
all of us have a message for all of you
We the members of Keyakizaka46
are closing the curtains on our 5 years of history
And then regarding Keyakizaka46
we will remain positive as we say goodbye
In October...Keyakizaka46 is scheduled
to have a final concert
As Keyakizaka46
that event will mark the end of the group's activities
And then
we will be given a new group name...there will be a rebirth
Of course this decision
is not something all the members can take in and accept so quickly
For us personally we have an incredibly strong emotional attachment to Keyakizaka46
To keep going with these mixed feelings....there is no way we'd be allowed to continue with this group as it is
Me personally and the Keyakizaka46 that I love
I was hoping I'd be able to protect it forever
and I worked to protect it
However
however
in order for this group to become much much stronger
following all the discussions between the staff and the members
The decision was that now is the time to move forward
Its because we are Keyakizaka46
that a lot of our dreams have come true
Including the members not here with us now
our dreams came true together and then
its because you were all there supporting us
you made so many of our dreams come true
The members who gave us strength and all the staff
and then the wonderful songs
and then the truly wonderful creative team
and then
the countless number of fans I've had a chance to meet truly makes me proud
Really up to now
getting to be a part of Keyakizaka46
I grew to love Keyakizaka46
and all the support Keyakizaka46 has given me
I truly want to say....arigatou gozaimashita
arigatou gozaimashita
But along with all the fun memories
to be honest there's been a lot of painful memories
In these 2 years especially
its felt like we've been walking lost in a tunnel with no visible exit
There were so many unpredictable events
and there were days we couldn't do our job the way we had hoped
There's been days where we wondered if we had let everyone down
And then members continued to graduate and withdraw
The group name took on a life of its own
there were days with events so troubling that it made you want to cover your ears from the outside world
But Keyakizaka46
the more I think about how much I loved it
it starts to hurt
more and more I think about what I should have done
It feels like I've become obsessed with thinking about it
Right now
for the group to become strong
the new members that joined...the 2nd members and new 2nd members
and then 1st members....all 28 of us together
From here we must get off to a new start
and again we'll all have to work hard to get back to where a lot of our dreams can come true
And then
in order to become strong in the future..up to this point
the things we've held precious will have to be let go
and in that open space
I truly believe something new and precious can once again fill that void
From this point on our restart begins
I think a treacherous road awaits us
however
with us becoming a colorless group with a clean slate again
together I'd like to fill those colors in
All the experience gained in Keyakizaka46
I'm sure it has made us tougher
because of that we'll believe in our experience
and then
once again
I promise we will become a strong group
with that said
from now on as well
please expect big things from us
In the future....your continued support
dozo yoroshiku onegai itashimasu
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
For our last song
this will be Keyakizaka46's last single
please listen