Thank you for watching.
Good evening, everyone! We are
Keikizaka46!
It's been a while, everyone! Are you
enjoying yourselves?
Today is the 4th...
This is a limited edition of Keyakizaka
46, so I hope we can have a great time
together.
I'm really happy that you came to see
this and made a Keyakizaka card.
Thank you!
I'd like to deliver a special live to
all of you today.
Thank you until the end!
Yes!
Keyakizaka's cards are really cool.
I didn't expect you to make your own
cards.
Keyakizaka's cards are really black.
All the members voted for it and chose
it.
It was really cool.
And when we were shooting it, it was a
dark outfit that matched the color.
It was really cool.
It had a cool image.
I actually made the card...
Made...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I made it.
On the back, there was a logo of
Keyakizaka, and I was really happy about
that.
Yonkado-san, you made a lot of different
versions of commercials.
Hono-chan, do you have any memorable
scenes while shooting a commercial?
When I was shooting with Yumiko Seki, we
were shooting for a school uniform.
There was a scene where the two of us
were laughing together, and Yumiko Seki
said that the white bread in Enoshima
was really delicious.
So we used that scene to make fun of
her.
So I was wondering what she was doing.
I was talking about my mom.
Everyone, please watch it again.
And Lisa, in the commercial, you played
the role of a cameraman, right?
Yes.
Do you actually like cameras?
Yes, when I was thinking about buying a
camera,
I got to play the role of a cameraman in
the commercial.
Did you happen to know about it?
Yes, it was a really fun shoot.
So you don't have a front camera yet?
No, I don't, so I thought I'd ask Shi-
chan to teach me.
I'd like Shi-chan to teach me too.
That'd be fun.
And I'd like to let everyone know again,
but we, Keyakizaka46, will continue to
work as Sakurazaka46 after the last
live.
We're still...
I haven't been able to say it yet.
The intonation is a bit difficult.
I was wondering if it was Sakurazaka46.
It's easier to say than Keyakizaka46.
It's easier to say than Keyakizaka46?
It's easier to say.
I'm glad you said it.
I was wondering if there was still a
key.
I'm glad it's easier to say.
Once again, Mii-chan...
What impression did you get when you
heard "Sakurazaka"?
To be honest, I thought it was a really
beautiful name at first.
It has the same origin as Keyakizaka.
It's not just about strength, it's also
about beauty and strength, so I'm glad
that we were given such a wonderful
name.
I'm glad.
I want to be a group with a good name.
First of all, I want to do my best to
close the barrier of Keyakizaka.
There are only two weeks left until the
last ride.
Two weeks?
Yes.
How do you feel right now, Akane?
We're getting closer to our last
concert,
but we're also getting closer to the end
of our career as Keyakizaka,
and we're also getting closer to the end
of our career as Keyakizaka.
I'm starting to feel that.
We'll continue to do our best.
I want to do my best to do my best in
each work.
I'm glad I could do the last live today.
I'll do my best for the last live, so
please look forward to it.
First of all, I would like to thank
everyone who supports this live today.
I want to make it a memorable live.
Everyone, please enjoy the special live
until the end.
Are you enjoying the live?
I can hear you.
Thank you for joining us.
From now on, Nikisei will be in charge
of MC.
Thank you.
It's started.
It's the first half.
It's so fast.
It's ION CARD's live.
There are a lot of ION CARD commercials.
As I mentioned earlier, we were able to
get a commercial from the 2nd
generation.
Thank you so much!
Yumiko Seki, Hono Tamura, and Hikaru
Morita were participating from the
middle of the story.
Thank you so much!
I saw it!
You saw it, right?
I'm so happy!
By the way, Yumi, what was the story
about?
Do you have any episodes while filming?
It was difficult because I had to act in
a drama.
I was a junior model of HABU, so I had a
lot of scenes with HABU.
I had a lot of fun filming while being
taught a lot.
I feel at ease when I'm with my seniors.
Yumi-chan was cool, wasn't she?
Yeah, she was cool.
I was with Yumi-chan earlier, and we had
a chance to film together.
Yumi-chan was really amazing.
What?
I'm glad to hear that.
As I said before, it was about Shirasu
bread.
But the reason why I thought it was
amazing was that at first,
the two of us were talking about
something that was already decided.
And both of us were like, "Huh?"
We couldn't do it well, so when we were
told to talk about anything,
I was like, "What should I talk about?"
And then Yumi-chan started talking about
Shirasu bread,
and I was like, "That's a relief."
It was delicious.
That's right.
I starred with Sugai-san and Muriya-san.
What about you, Hii-chan?
I starred with Kobayashi-san and Nanami-
Risa-san.
I was really nervous.
That's right.
I don't usually have a chance to act, so
I was really nervous.
But they were both really good.
Even when I was at a loss, they told me
what to do with eye contact.
I was able to do my best because I was
able to feel the support of my seniors.
It's reassuring to have your seniors.
I feel that every day.
I know, I know.
I'm glad it's a commercial.
Please continue to support us.
It's been about 2 years since we joined,
but we're about to close the curtain on
Keyakizaka 46.
How do you feel now, Ten-chan?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The first day and the second day, we're
going to show it on a separate menu, so
the members are different, so I'm really
excited about what it's going to be
like, and the staff are really
passionate about it, and I'm really
looking forward to seeing what the set
will be like.
I'm really excited about this.
No, it's true.
I definitely want you to see it.
Both of them.
Do it like this.
Please look at it like this.
We'll do our best to make Kiyakizaka 46
cool, beautiful, and brave.
We'll do our best to advance to a new
position, so please continue to support
us.
Please enjoy the rest of the
performance.
Good evening, everyone watching the live
broadcast.
From now on, we...
We, SHINNIKISEI, will be the MCs for
today's show.
Thank you for your support.
I'm Endo Hikari.
I'm Onuma Akiho.
I'm Masumoto Kira.
I'm Moriya Rena.
I'm Kosaka Marino.
I'm Oozono Rei.
Thank you for joining the ION CARD.
Thank you very much.
We have an announcement from the ION
CARD.
We, Shinnikisei, will deliver it to you.
Part 1
You can use it as it is.
Yeah!
We
Keyakizaka46 will end their activities
with a live next month, but you can
continue to use the ION card.
The benefits will not change, so please
continue to use the ION card for a long
time.
Thank you for your viewing.
By all means, exchange it as soon as
possible.
The "Ion Card Original Clear File",
which is a replacement product of
"Tokimeki Point", will be finished as
soon as the stock runs out, so please
exchange it as soon as possible.
Yes!
No.3
I'm in the middle of a campaign!
"Ion Card Original Clear File"
In addition, you can also register for
minor points by paying in Japanese.
We are currently in the campaign, so if
you haven't registered yet, please do
so.
Yes!
Please take good care of your ION cards
from now on.
Yes!
Well, we were assigned to Keyakizaka46
in February this year.
We were assigned, but before that...
I'd like to ask everyone what
Keyakizaka46 meant to us.
First, Akipo. What was Keyakizaka46 to
you?
When I listen to Keyakizaka46's songs, I
feel like I've never met them before.
When I was a trainee, I listened to them
over and over again.
I was saved by the lyrics.
Hikarin, do you have a song that you
were saved by the lyrics of this song?
I've always been saved by "Eccentric".
Even if I'm worried about a lot of
things, if I listen to "Eccentric", it's
a song that makes me feel like I can be
myself, so I always listen to it.
I see.
How about you, Kera-chan?
When I met Keyakizaka46,
Keyakizaka46 made me pay attention to
the lyrics of the song.
What made you pay attention to the
lyrics of this song?
"Silent Majority".
When I saw the performance video for the
first time,
I felt that they were appealing to
something.
I searched for lyrics for the first
time, and it was a new encounter that
there are lyrics like this.
It was a new encounter.
Marina, do you pay attention to lyrics?
I always pay attention to lyrics and
listen to them.
Keyaki's lyrics resonate with my heart.
When I'm listening to a song, I always
follow the lyrics with my eyes.
You pay attention to the lyrics of
RIVAN.
How about you, RENA RENA?
What kind of person are you to RENA
RENA?
I was able to join Keyakizaka46, which I
longed for, for a very short time.
For me, Keyakizaka46 is a group that
stimulates the passion in my heart.
How about you, Rei-chan?
For me, Keyakizaka46 is a group that
gave me a story that I didn't have.
Now that I'm in this group, I feel like
I have a sense of accomplishment.
It's a story about how I became a member
of Sakurazaka46, and also how I became a
member of Keyakizaka46.
We've been disbanded for a short time,
but we'll do our best until the last
live, so please support us until the
end.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you for waiting!
Thank you everyone for coming!
I feel nostalgic. I think it was during
our tour last year.
I'm wearing a lot of rare clothes today.
And just now...
As Shinriki-sen told me,
the Keyakizaka46 card will be in use
from now on,
so I'd be happy if you could use it a
lot.
And I'm very grateful.
Even if I become Sakurazaka46,
I'll be in the care of Yoncard-san...
in the care of...
I'm getting used to it today.
I'm good at it.
Thank you so much for taking care of me.
I'm really grateful.
I'll do my best from now on too.
And now, I'll play the songs that were
used a lot in Yonkado-san's commercial.
[Yonkado-san's commercial starts
playing]
Thank you so much for watching until the
end today.
I'll do my best from now on too.
There are two weeks left until the end,
but I want to run through all of them
until the end.
And I'm also working on a 4-card stream,
so please look forward to that as well.
Thank you for today.
That's all.
I'm Keisuke Takahashi.
Thank you very much.