To be honest, at first, I had a strong
feeling that I liked Aikizaka.
I was prepared for it, but I felt that
it was new.
I was able to realize that it was from
scratch.
Since then, everyone has become more and
more like me.
I think I felt a lot of things, and I
also have a lot of regretful feelings.
I feel like I've been reset once again,
or I've been able to feel like I'm going
to do my best again.
I'm glad I made the right choice.
It's been a year, or yesterday and
today.
I'm glad I didn't make a mistake.
It's been a year.
It's been a year, but it's still a year.
It's been about three years.
No, it's not.
On the first day, we're going to perform
"Habugyo" and on the second day, we're
going to perform "Akane and Pei-chan's
Graduation Ceremony".
This time, we're only going to perform
"Over Chair".
The members are going to stand on the
stairs in the shape of a "1".
At the end of "Over Chair", you can see
the members through the LED in front of
you.
It's like a real celebration.
The main story is very gorgeous.
I was very excited about the development
of the explanation of the staging.
I don't think it's been that long since
it changed on the first and second day.
I think we can enjoy each of them on day
1 and day 2.
Thank you for watching!
I lowered it because I couldn't touch
it.
You can't see it, can you?
It's like a stride.
I did it!
I was told that I wouldn't come back
after the live practice, so I started
rehearsing, and a few days later, I
heard that Jamaica was free, and I was
very happy that Mr. Komachi would come
back.
The next person will come back.
I'm going to participate from the bottom
of the water.
Thank you.
Let's check the block above and do it
with the block.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your viewing.
0.1 seconds.
0.1 seconds to the beat.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
[Face-to-face practice]
I think this is a good idea.
(Takahashi's dancing)
OK!
Nice, nice, nice!
That was really cool
It looks like a cherry blossom tree when
all of us gather together.
It looks like a princess.
It's so cute.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Thank you so much.
I got married.
I'm going to have a baby.
You are big.
I got married.
It's my 2nd anniversary, and it's my
first solo concert as SAKURAZAKA.
It's also the last concert of NAKANEN
and FUE-CHAN.
It's a very packed venue.
I want to return to the venue with no
regrets.
I want to make this concert the best
concert I've ever had.
It's not just this concert.
I really don't know how much I can
perform this song with the current
members.
There are a lot of moments when our eyes
meet, so I want to show each song with
Rika and Moriya.
I'm nervous.
I never thought I would be able to do
this again.
I'm happy to sing my favorite song at
the end.
I haven't been here since the first
tour.
So I practiced while watching the VTR of
the dance.
I got a flower.
I think this is the last time we'll be
able to share our feelings with
everyone.
I want to have fun with everyone.
It's a celebration of our first
anniversary.
I want to create a stage for everyone.
I want to share our feelings with
everyone.
That's the main thing.
I want to celebrate it.
It's the last one for me.
I want to show the best of me.
I changed my name at the last live of
Rei-chan and Akane, but I was really
happy to be able to perform my original
song again at the live.
I thought there was nothing more to do,
so I was really happy to be able to do
both songs as an encore.
Good morning.
Good morning. We are SAKURA TOKA 46.
We will do our best to do our best, so
please take care of us.
Please take care of us.
Thank you.
I think I can do it, but I'm one step
behind.
You can do it at a fast pace, but focus
and remember everything.
Yes, thank you.
I'll start from where the music comes
out.
Then I'll teach you the song.
(The dance is really hard)
I heard that I can see a new Rox today
It took a long time.
If you are called, let's go.
Long legs.
It's a style.
Today's bangs look good on you.
I love it.
It looks like a Jamaican beer.
I want to match everything with a
Jamaican beer.
I know.
It looks good on you when you dance.
You're right.
I think it's better to match these three
with a Jamaican beer.
I think so, too.
This is the first time I've seen this
kind of performance.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Let's get started!
Thank you so much for coming to see us!
Thank you so much!
Look at this. Kira ran to make this.
Cute.
I'm exhausted, but I'm going to take it
easy from now on.
I don't know what I'm worried about.
I've been practicing with the set since
the rehearsal, so I have no choice but
to do it.
Yes!
We were able to celebrate one year as
SAKURAZAKA46.
I think this was supported by many
people, especially the fans.
I hope that the fans who came today will
be able to convey their gratitude.
I want to make today a memorable day for
the fans and us.
Let's cheer up and do our best until the
end!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy to be welcomed by all of
you like this.
I'm so happy that I've been able to work
hard with everyone for a year.
I think it's a happy thing.
Thank you for your support this time.
It will be the last live for Akane and
Pei.
I want to do my best to make everyone
smile for two days.
See you.
Let's deliver the best live performance
with gratitude, confidence and pride.
Always be brave and drink like sakura.
Just trust yourself.
Sake! Sake! SAKURAZAKA 46
Cheers!
It's crazy, isn't it?
This is crazy.
This is beautiful.
Kobayashi Yui.
Revival.
I'm Rina Anoue from SAKURAIZAKA46.
I'm Rina Matsuda.
Together, we are Futarina.
OK, perfect.
Today,
Thank you very much for coming to the
SAKURAIZAKA46 1st Year Anniversary Live.
I'm Rina Inoue from SAKURAZAKA46!
I'm Rina Matsuda.
We are Rina and Rina.
I'm going to stand on the back of the
panel.
"Beautiful Nervous" was the first time I
did it in front of the fans, so I danced
while watching the reaction of the fans.
I think I was able to show the best
Nervous I've ever done.
[Music]
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Matsuda encouraged me a lot
There were a lot of eyes in the song and
there were eyes with the audience, so I
had a feeling that it was reaching, and
I think it was fun.
I hope we can enjoy it and convey the
lyrics and the worldview of the song.
In the actual performance, I was able to
enjoy the performance with Inoue and
eyes more than usual.
Inoue's first performance at the Tokyo
Dome
Inoue's second performance at the Tokyo
I was nervous just before I went on
stage.
But as a dance unit, I was able to show
a different side of me from the group.
This is the first time I've done
something like this.
What was it?
"THE DANCE"
Is that so?
It was the first time I did it in my
life.
I just did a free dance.
It was fun.
I've been doing this for a few days.
As I said in the MC,
I can't think of anything but Jamaica
beer.
I watch the video every day.
The three of us were just thinking about
what we could do together.
I'm really happy that Yui-san came back.
I felt that it was a very happy time to
be able to show it to the fans.
It was a very happy time to be able to
show it to the fans.
Thank you very much.
I was able to get a sense of the team
spirit.
I was happy.
I didn't feel nervous or anxious.
Not only me, but everyone was calm and
decided the team.
I felt like I could make it to the first
day.
I felt that Sakurazaka's team spirit
improved.
I can't read it.
It's old.
Thank you.
Rock-paper-scissors.
How many seconds?
10 seconds.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10.
But I'm sure I'll be very lonely at the
end of tomorrow.
I don't know what to do.
I'm lonely.
I wonder if everyone will graduate like
this.
I'm thinking about it.
Rika and Akane's last live performance
together.
I want to do my best to deliver the best
thing I've ever done.
Thank you.
I want to deliver the best thing I've
ever done with a smile.
Where have you been?
I was caught.
It's here, isn't it?
It's Detroit, isn't it?
Why are you so tall?
I'm sorry.
Why did you notice that no one was
coming?
Was it a lie?
Yesterday...
I was so excited and happy that U-PON is
coming back.
I felt like we were going to celebrate
our first anniversary together.
On the second day, Pei and Kana
graduated.
I thought it would be the last time I
could sing with them.
could do it with them.
I was thinking about it, and I felt very
lonely.
I wanted to cry even though it wasn't a
song at all.
Let's do the second half.
It's a surprise.
We gave flowers to two people on the way
here.
I was checking if there was a surprise.
So cute!
I don't know what time it is, but I'm
happy that I can see their beautiful
dresses.
This is the first time I've seen a dress
like this.
I was wondering if it would finally open
at that time.
It's so natural that there are two of
them.
It feels strange.
I'm going to wear it today.
I have a lot of things to do, so I want
to do my best so that I can do them
well.
I will do my best so that I can do my
best for the people around me.
I don't know.
I've been on TV for a long time.
But I feel different.
I feel different.
Thank you.
I'm so hungry.
I was so surprised when I saw the two-
body video of us in the back.
I was about to cry when I saw that.
I changed my mind.
What? It's not true.
It's a video of us in trouble.
When I saw it, I thought I was going to
cry, so I changed my mind.
I can't see the actual performance, so
I'm looking forward to seeing the video
when I get home.
It's the last live performance.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to have fun with everyone.
We're going to dance at the end.
I don't want to do that.
Let's dance in the dressing room.
I don't know what to do.
You can dance in the back.
I don't know what to do at the end.
I don't know what to watch today.
If I watch the past videos...
If you watch too much, it might be a
little dangerous.
Keyakizaka's song is a ban.
I hope I can have a lot of communication
with everyone today,
laugh a lot, and have a fun day.
Thank you very much.
I want to have a live concert with
everyone. Thank you very much.
I want to put all the feelings of 6 and
a half years and do today's live, and I
hope that everyone will be able to have
the best live that will lead to the
second year as Sakurazaka.
Let's all do our best to success with
gratitude!
Ready, set, go!
As always, let's eat and drink!
Like sakura, let's drink and dance!
Just trust yourself!
Sake! Sake! Sakurazaka!
4TG!
Cheers!
Thank you for watching!
I hope this day will be a wonderful day
that will never be forgotten by
everyone.
Thank you for everything.
Let's go!
Come here.
Let's go.
Do they remember?
Do you want to do it?
Let's do it.
I forgot.
Let's have fun.
One, two, three.
Kekyo, Yabashita, Kizuna, Kirakira,
Kirari, Keisuke, Kaho, Onishi.
Bye.
Akane said that she wanted to do "Kizuna
no Enjin" with only Ikisei.
So I did it with Ikisei only.
I remembered the feeling of the engine
at that time,
and the atmosphere of the second engine
that Akane put in.
So I did it with Ikisei only.
There are things that I've never felt
before, so I can't share them with them.
When the number of members decreases,
the number of people I can share with
decreases, so I feel lonely.
I don't know when I'll be able to say
goodbye to the rest of the students.
I want to spend every day enjoying
myself.
We're moving!
We've been waiting for yesterday, so
we're moving today as well!
Every day is peaceful
Look up at the sky that's different from
yesterday
Especially for the chorus,
I think it's the same for the members.
It's a song that anyone can sing.
I'm happy when my eyes meet.
I'm relieved when someone is next to me,
in front of me, or behind me.
♪ Sobina, Sobina, Sobina ♪
♪ The cherry blossoms that are in full
bloom ♪
♪ Sobina, Sobina, Sobina ♪
♪ I'm going to give you a surprise ♪
♪ that you've never seen before ♪
♪ The fire that's been burning ever
since the moon rose ♪
♪ Sobina, Sobina, Sobina ♪
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow, I'll be someone
else ♪
♪ And that's fine ♪
Nagare-dango
I'll do it properly
I think all 14 of us will be able to do
it.
I think we will be able to do it on the
first day.
This is the only time, right?
Yes.
It's really...
It was so fleeting, and it was so much
fun, and it was so sad.
It was the first time I felt that
emotion in front of the ball.
(The sound of the ball bouncing)
She is so beautiful.
She is a princess.
Good morning.
She is so beautiful.
Enjoy it.
She is so cute.
Thank you very much.
Do you have a letter?
No, I don't.
Can I have it?
Of course.
It's the cutest.
It's not a negative graduation.
I'm always thinking about everyone.
I'm grateful to everyone who met me.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God.
Isn't it an audition?
It's definitely an audition.
Let's go as far as we can see.
In a good way, in a bad way.
I'm an honest person.
I'm trying not to cry when I'm sad.
I want to cry for something better.
I'm going to do my best.
I think it's better not to see you in 30
seconds.
I'm going to do my best.
Let's move.
I'm going to take a picture.
Hot and warm.
It was like the sun that shined on
everyone.
I'm the oldest.
I want to be like a kind sister to
everyone.
She, who knows people's most difficult
times,
clings to her members more than anyone.
Softly.
Watanabe Rika was like the blue sky that
enveloped everything, a kind sister to
everyone.
So, with today's live performance, the
members Moriya Akane and Watanabe Rika
have finally graduated.
So cute.
Thank you.
Beautiful.
To be honest, I wanted to see a lot more
wonderful scenery together, and I had a
lot of dreams that I wanted to make come
true.
But I felt that my personality was not
suitable for being an idol, and I
honestly couldn't lie about anything.
If only I had been able to stand up more
and more cleverly.
It's because I'm not strong enough.
I'm sorry that I chose this decision.
But it's not the end.
I've been serious about each and every
job so as not to regret it.
I'm kidding.
In the music video shoot, we all lay
down and looked at the stars,
or danced in the pool with our clothes
on,
or went to various places on the tour
and ate delicious food together.
I can't count them all, but
I remember the days when I did silly
things with the members and laughed.
I can't count them all, but
I remember the days when I did silly
things with the members and laughed.
I think it was really fun.
But it wasn't just fun.
There were times when I wasn't good at
dancing,
and there were times when I couldn't do
what I wanted to do.
There were times when I was sad,
and there were times when I was
frustrated.
Tei-chan...
All of them were fun, but the one I had
the most fun with was when I said, "It's
the dressing room!"
Everyone was laughing their heads off.
It's true that those moments were
important, fun, and irreplaceable.
That's what I thought in the comments.
With Aozora and Marie,
"Footprints That Are Not Here"
Today was really...
I think the lyrics really resonate with
the two of them.
Especially after "Koko ni nai shi"
I want them to walk a very happy path
from now on.
The two of them are singing "Koko ni nai
shi"
That's it!
Today, Mori Akane and Watanabe Rika will
graduate.
I have a lot of memories with them.
I would like to surprise them with
something from the members.
I would like to give it to you in this
size.
Please come over here.
Please line up.
Kei-chan, please stand here.
Please stand diagonally.
Okay, everyone, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm sad that we have to part, but I'm
happy that it was a beautiful and happy
day.
I'm glad that we were able to finish the
show with a happy smile.
I was nervous, but I think it was a day
that I could do my best.
I'm glad that we were able to finish the
show with a happy smile.
I think the number of members will
increase or decrease.
I think the most important thing is to
be able to spend time with them for a
long time.
I get messages from overseas fans saying
that they support me.
I hope I can be the second person who
can spread my message to those people.
I want to do more with SAKURAZAKA46.
I want to be able to deliver my message
to as many people as possible.
I was surprised!
It was the best!