Yua Mikami's cosplay photo shooting
Hello.
I'm Yasuha, the manager of Sakurazaki.
I'm Ai Mochizuki.
Nice to meet you.
I'm going to show you a video of me
sleeping on my manager's phone.
I usually take a look at the members.
This time, I would like to show you the
members.
We always play the video.
Even if there is nothing, we always play
the video.
Please take a look at it.
She is a member of the final of the
HERSHA tour.
Yes.
She is a child, so she will continue to
play the video.
This is a toy I got at a candy store.
It was quite popular and everyone was
playing with it.
Like putting it on the wall.
Let's do it.
Ready, go.
He's dodging a lot.
Is he a detective?
I think so.
I used to have a serious conversation
with the director,
but now I'm playing a mysterious game
where Risa and Karin turn around.
This is the picture of Kobayashi, who
meets the expectations of the youngest
Yamasaki in the music video of "Dead
End".
It's always like this, even in a cool
music video, the back side is like this.
I wonder what it is.
Hinata is playing like this.
It's not hard to win.
Everyone, please.
Everyone, let's go in.
Matsuha is always in service spirit when
she looks at the camera.
Let's go home with me.
She is popular.
But...
Let's go home with me.
I...
Let's go home.
What should I do?
But I like both of them.
So I'm not sure.
It's close.
It's a cozy dressing room in front of a
music show.
Thank you for watching!
It's too light.
It's too easy.
Ten's solo is...
What kind of theme is it?
There's a dance solo part.
I'm sorry.
Ten's dance solo is...
No.
It's a folk music dance.
I'm sorry.
Really?
It's amazing.
It's like turning your head around.
Because it's folk music.
What do you think?
It's good.
Is that all?
You look good in it.
Do I?
Do I look good in it?
You look good in it.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
I think it's good to be live.
Where is Blue One Cafe?
It's over there, isn't it?
Matsuda crushed my solo part.
I felt like I was going to enter the
world.
Matsuda's head was here.
I thought he was going to do it.
After that, he didn't apologize at all.
He was grinning and looking at me.
I thought, "Damn it."
He just apologized.
Matsuda!
Yasuda-san noticed it too.
I'm really sorry.
I made a mistake for the first time.
I'm really sorry about this.
I was thinking about how to tell Yui-
chan I'm sorry in the middle of the
song,
but when I look at Yui-chan's face, I
feel like I'm entering the world.
Of course you will.
That's why I always say, "I'm sorry."
I'm really sorry.
I'm even more angry now.
What are you sorry about?
How beautiful it is when you go like
this.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I did it.
What kind of face was it?
I made a mistake.
I understand.
I can't do it, but I'm trying to do my
best.
I'm really sorry.
I was thinking about how to do it, but I
made a mistake.
I'm really sorry.
I was trying to be sexy like you, but I
was surprised to be back to reality.
I was surprised too.
I was stunned.
I couldn't read myself.
This song is the most difficult song for
the members.
I think this song was performed for the
first time on a singing program.
Everyone is doing the last check-in
before the last TV recording in front of
the mirror.
They are always doing it.
I'm singing.
Drone.
I'm reenacting a music video.
I'm doing a good job.
I saw a splash.
I saw a splash of water.
I think people will get drunk if they
watch this video.
I think so, too.
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Done.
- I taught her. - Did you?
It's good, right?
We're going to have a proper match.
This scene has increased a lot.
We're doing a backslide.
There are more songs that everyone can
dance to.
I think it's good.
This figure behind me is...
It's the master.
The master is...
We're going to win.
It's a little embarrassing to read it
out loud.
I'm honored to be called a master.
Are you serious?
I was surprised.
It's okay, you can continue.
Minami, your hair is too short.
This is when I did the backslide for the
second time in 2002.
Minami is teaching me how to get into
position.
When I was doing the backslide, everyone
was teaching me how to do it.
It was a great experience.
I didn't know this would happen.
Oh, it's the sun.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you so much for coming today.
It's my first solo concert, so I'm very
excited.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for everything you've done for
me.
Let's go!
We're on our way!
OK, thank you!
Pay attention to TAKIMOTO's facial
expression when she sings in front of
the camera.
I hope TEN-TEN watches this video.
This happens every time.
TEN-TEN is trying to do something that
you can't usually see.
Please check it out in the future.
Please subscribe to our channel.
As expected of the master.
The second time, I will do my best in
anything.
I don't think I can do it if I don't
practice.
You're good.
(Playing the saxophone)
(Laughing)
This is the best.
As expected from saxophone player.
It's like a weapon, isn't it?
It's funny.
I often compose with an ocarina.
If you take a picture of this message,
you can listen to various works so far.
There are many songs of the ocarina that
I want you to listen to before going to
bed, so please check them out.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to cry.
I can't cry.
You're cheerful.
Wait, wait.
Watch out!
These two are always cheerful, but...
She's even more serious.
She's so serious about her work.
That's how she is.
Is it too high?
It's a bit high.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Okay, let's do it.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
I'm imitating you.
Imitating me?
No, it's private.
It looks good.
Imitating me?
Imitating you.
I don't look good with twin tails.
Karin is doing something.
I'm imitating her.
I don't care.
Thank you for your viewing.
BUDDIES?
LENA-CHAN
KINKA-SAN
I'm not talking with my throat
This is LENA-GOKKO's
This is the place of "Hashirimou".
I feel that "Renagoko" started from
here.
What is this?
The master is crying.
Can't you sleep?
I can't sleep.
Basically, women can't sleep.
She practices at home all the time.
So, before the performance...
Let me shake your hand.
She shakes my hand.
But she does her best in the
performance.
She is reliable.
Everyone has to fix their makeup.
Thank you.
It's really good.
Have you ever seen Marim crying?
I've never seen it.
Why are you crying so much?
Are you both wearing makeup?
Yes.
Marino, you shouldn't cry.
Marino is cool.
I'm not crying in this situation.
It's a short film.
I took a picture of you two.
Cool.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't want to see you again.
I want to do it, I'm sorry, I want to do
it.
Go for it, Koni-chan.
I'm sorry.
I like you.
Don't look at me like that.
Who do you choose?
I choose you.
I'm in a good mood.
Oh, it's you!
I was surprised.
Say something.
Camera.
How was today?
Well, it was fun.
One more, one more.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Good luck.
Thank you for always.
I love you.
What?
Thank you for always.
It's Ikisei's 10th anniversary.
Happy 10th anniversary.
Ikisei, thank you always.
We celebrate it every time.
Thank you.
There is a cow.
Really?
There is a cow in front of me.
This is the first anniversary of the
Double Keyaki Festival.
That's true.
I'm her little sister now.
She's still doing it.
She's been doing it every show.
It must hurt a lot.
Ten-chan can't fly.
Hang in there, Ten-chan.
It's okay!
Ten can't fly very well.
I'm okay.
What about you, Ten?
We are the best!
That's what I was told.
What is "Ten" in Yamasaki prefecture?
"Ten" in Chonten!
- She did it for me. - I got 20 yen!
- Oh no, I did it on purpose. - You can
only do it on purpose.
- That was Ten-ten! Thank you! - Ten-
chan, you can do it!
Ten-chan, you can do it!
- You can do it if you jump once. - Are
you going to keep jumping?
- Yeah, for about 30 minutes. - You're
noisy.
In the end, the performance was a
success, as expected.
She was doing her best.
On the other side, she was in a hurry.
It's a cute video that everyone is
watching.
It's okay if you're close.
I'm afraid I'm going to jump off.
We've been jumping off all over the
country.
From the tree to the cliff.
On the count of three.
Take a video.
There's a big one.
This is the keyhole of the tour.
Before the show starts, the members have
to be careful.
How was Jamaica Beer today?
It was really cool.
How was the stage after a long time?
How was it?
Were you nervous?
Yes, I was.
I was nervous when I was on TV.
I couldn't speak when I was on TV.
But your performance was so cool.
I was so nervous that I couldn't move at
all.
I liked your entrance scene.
It was so cool.
The angle of your body was so long.
It was so sharp.
Let's go back.
- It's so nostalgic. - It's so nice.
It's nice, isn't it?
- Where should we light the fire? -
Yeah.
We did something like this on a TV show,
didn't we?
- What was it? - Inoue was good at it,
or something like that.
- It's so nice. - I think Hono is better
at it.
I'm not sure about the second one, but I
think it's this one.
I'm scared.
The curry isn't burnt at all, though.
I think it's burnt.
I'm so excited.
At this time, I think everyone was
eating marshmallows after shooting.
It's delicious.
I made it for the production team.
Then I burned two marshmallows.
It's like a child.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much.
If it's not on the top, it won't be
baked.
I have no experience in camping.
It's a good idea to have fun in a place
like this.
Hashimaru Daikushi
Is it delicious?
This is a crepe, and on top of the cafe
latte, there's a lot of stuff.
This is a famous croissant from Fukuoka.
What flavor is it?
Mine is a black honey cream.
Hikaru fits perfectly in this cart.
It looks fun.
I forgot my shoes.
What?
We are wearing the same socks today.
Our fans will be surprised to see us
wearing the same socks.
We really don't wear the same socks.
Can I do this pose?
Yes, you can.
It's good.
It's cute.
Yui-san, Risa-san, Ten-chan.
It looks fun!
I want to climb this.
What's that?
A truck?
A bus?
Let's go.
Combo.
When I collaborated with Skytree at the
time of the release of "BAN",
I went to the observatory to take a
picture of the music video and the
members came to sign it.
I'm glad I stopped here.
This is cool.
The color of this is autumn.
I'm glad I stopped here.
Thank you very much.
I think it was around that time.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
This is the signature of Oze.
Who wrote this?
This is the signature of Saitama Kyoken.
What is that?
This is the signature of the person who
wrote the wish.
What is that?
I will write a wish too.
Did you write a wish?
I wrote a wish.
That's amazing.
Do you know who wrote the wish?
I don't know who wrote it.
I don't know.
There are a lot of people who really
think Ozaki wrote his autograph.
Actually, the members write their
autographs every time.
It's not close.
I'm glad you're Tom.
I bought it.
Thank you.
This is RUN's first experience.
There are so many.
Are you throwing this?
This is the first time to throw a
bowling ball.
This is very heavy.
This is heavy.
Are you throwing this?
This is lighter.
This is dangerous.
This is really heavy.
What are you doing?
I want to take a picture of a princess.
I have a strong desire to be a princess.
This is a finger.
I wanted to see this.
I can't do it.
This is the production of the song
"Microscope" of the first tour.
There is a tricycle race.
Takemoto and Rina.
Is it shining?
I'm going to sneeze.
I think it was Hikaru before I knew it.
Every time I saw you, you were playing a
game.
I don't know what to look forward to.
I'm playing the role of a goalkeeper.
I'm playing with KONO.
It's boring.
Everyone seems to be having fun.
Why are you playing the role of a
goalkeeper?
It's boring.
I'm not bored!
I'm a child.
Akemoto is really weak.
"Out of shape"
"Respect"
Can you translate it for me?
"Bento"
"O bento no soto wa"
"Shape"
"Dakara"
"Yaseru"
"O bento no soto wa yaseru"
"Shape"
"Natsukashi"
It's like a chest hair.
Cute.
I don't call it chest hair.
It's chest hair.
Not chest hair.
I said chest hair.
It's chest hair.
But it's chest meat.
It's chest meat.
It's definitely a cut.
I've never cut my hair like this before.
It's the latest fashion.
I look like a loser.
I'm going to be used for this.
I'm going to be used twice.
Was it good?
I did it.
I said it first.
I said it first, so I hope you'll use
it.
Please be quiet.
I want to run away from here.
I'm being punished by Yumiko.
No, no, no.
Inoue, look at me.
I didn't do anything.
Inoue, help me.
Yumiko.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, calendar shooting.
Everyone is so young.
Hikari has long hair.
I have bangs.
This is the era of Patsun.
Ena has changed a lot.
Is that so?
I think I'm in my first year of high
school this time.
Isn't that the same?
I feel nostalgic about the costume of
BANIBI.
I'm in my first year of high school.
"Yahoo!"
When we were shooting this music video,
the production team prepared a bench
coat for us.
There was only one red bench coat,
and it said "JAPAN" on the back.
We were excited to see who would wear
it.
I remember that.
FUKUOKA is easy to get.
I think FUKUOKA often wore the red bench
coat that was chosen.
I miss it.
Everyone tries to draw YOSHIKO.
YASUHA is in the middle.
I drew YOSHIKO.
MATSU always tells me, but I can't
remember it.
I like this picture.
There are many people who remember this
picture.
If there is a whiteboard, I will draw
it.
All the members try to draw YOSHIKO.
It seems to be easy, but it's
surprisingly difficult.
Is this your first time to see this?
Yes.
This is my first time to see this.
This is my first time to see this three
years ago.
I see.
I'm scared.
What kind of self-introduction do you
do?
Please don't do that.
Thank you very much.
I love to eat.
I love to eat Yakiniku.
I love to eat Shabu-Shabu.
It was cute.
What is your favorite point?
My favorite point is...
It's dangerous.
I want to go home.
It's cute.
It's cute, Karin.
We take a commemorative photo and then
we take a group photo.
This is a thread for "Why do you love
me?"
I always use it.
Koba and Lisa are good at winding.
Oh, really?
I see.
I think it's not a big deal.
Mi-chan was sleeping.
No way!
Mi-chan was sitting behind me.
And she screamed in the car.
I thought she was a ghost, but I heard
Rina.
I definitely heard you.
I heard you from behind.
You were sitting like this.
I heard you from behind, but I heard you
from the front.
I thought you were a driver.
I thought you were a member of the
audition.
I thought you were talking to yourself.
Isn't it crazy?
I was so scared that I couldn't sleep.
I thought it was a woman's voice.
Yes, I thought so, too.
It was tall but a little bit of a man's
voice.
Is it a woman?
It was tall but a little bit of a man's
voice.
I thought it was a woman.
Here is a couple playing with each
other.
What are you doing secretly?
This is dangerous.
Cute.
It's a nice picture.
Hello.
I hope Seina High School will be happy.
Bang!
Karin is back.
This is the first time I've come to
Piha.
It's like a fairy tale.
It's like a phantom.
It's like a father and a son.
It's like a cat, Karin.
I'm back!
It's a cat that's been around for a long
time.
These two get along well.
Minami is in love with a lot of people.
She is very outgoing.
We look alike.
They got along well.
Koma is younger than her.
She is sweeter than Koma.
Koma is sweeter than Kuma.
Thank you for your viewing.
I think this is the coldest place I've
ever been.
It's so cold.
It was really cold on the roof.
Be careful not to close your eyes.
I'm going to die.
Take care of your neck.
Did you close your eyes?
Yes, I did.
Thank you.
She is so cute.
I used to take a lot of photos with her.
It's summer.
She is so cute.
This cat is so cute.
I put out the cat's position.
The wind is blowing.
I will never use this.
Thank you for watching my video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
See you soon.
Akane gave me a handwritten message of
"Hachimaki".
She was very motivated and kept writing
in the dressing room.
Akane Moriya is not a person who gives
up easily.
Thank you very much. I'm so happy.
Oh, not yet.
84.
Wow!
It's a big one.
Let's start.
It's easy.
I got number 8.
I wanted to put this on number 4.
But I got number 9.
Great.
It's amazing.
I got number 8.
Let's do this.
It's shocking.
Congratulation.
It's true.
I can't put my right hand in.
Are you happy? Thank you.
This is big.
This is a little finger.
Bye-bye.
She put her finger on it.
This is a cafe.
This is a little finger.
It's been there for a long time, hasn't
it?
What do you mean?
It's broken.
I can't do it because I'm so good at it.
Wow, with one hand.
What?
Oh?
You're right.
Annoying.
Oh, great.
Yu-chan, you're great.
Annoying.
Let's try to hit it cool.
Miracle?
Wow.
Isn't it cool?
Please watch it.
What?
It's a tumbler.
It's a sniper.
I can't stop laughing.
You're serious, aren't you?
It's fun.
I did it.
This is really fun.
It's over.
Just before the live started in the rain
on this day, I was wondering if I should
be careful, but it started safely, and
then there was a lot of fog on the way,
so I thought it was a little fantastic.
I'm glad there was such a big applause.
It's almost over, but how was it?
It's nice, isn't it? It's very important
to take a look back and take a video,
and I thought it was interesting.
I was able to see the expressions of the
members that I had never seen on stage,
and thank you for watching until the
end.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet again somewhere.
Goodbye.
Thank you for watching.