I was watching a video on a new desktop
Then I just hated it
I was absorbed in everything
And today, I'm scared again
I closed my eyes
And then I started to sleep
Why did I pretend to sleep?
I don't know
Hey!
What do you want to be? What do you want
to be?
When did you change? I can't see it now
While I was playing games
I became an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why is it so sad?
Wait a minute
What happened to me?
So that I can be healthy
I'm the only ideal
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told I can't
I can't be a different person
I can't
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told I can't
I can't
I want to know
Where the standard is
Hey!
The time I've been worried about
I can disappear without doing anything
If I were you
I wouldn't be able to do anything
What are you doing?
I'm the only one playing
Someone tell me
Is it something I can't do if I don't
play?
Suddenly, that one-step
Made the future a new one
If I'm banned, what should I do?
I just didn't know
It's hard to give me a chance
To do it again
If I'm banned, what should I do?
Are you going to show me?
Don't make me do it
Please forgive me
For the mistake I made
Suddenly, that one-step
Made the future a new one
Hey!
The sun is too bright
The sun is burning from the wind
Until the darkness comes
There's still time
No matter how much I'm told
No matter how much I'm banned
Even if I'm told it's no good
I can't give myself that time anymore
No matter how much I'm told
Even if I'm told it's no good
I understand
I won't throw it away
Am I the only one who can't do it?
I want to know where that standard is
No matter what situation I'm in
I will never be banned
Hey!
(Applause)
Good evening, everyone!
We are Sakurazaka46!
(Applause)
Thank you!
Sakurazaka46's
2nd year anniversary live
Thank you!
(Applause)
On December 9th last year, we released
"Nobody's Fault".
Yesterday, I finally turned 1 year old.
2 years? 1 year? I'm sorry.
I'm so happy to be able to share the
same moment with you at the Nippon
Budokan today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for coming.
There's a seat over there, but you can
see us from the back or from the side,
so I hope you can enjoy it.
And again, it's been a year, hasn't it,
Hono-chan?
That's right. It's been a year since the
first single, and we've released three
singles.
I think a lot of things have happened
since then.
All of them are precious memories, and
when I feel anxious, BUDDIES are always
there for me.
I'm so happy to be able to spend time
with you in front of me like this.
Thank you always.
Thank you.
I'd like to express my gratitude to all
of you today.
Let's ask Ten-chan.
Ten-chan, you've changed a lot in a
year.
How was your year?
I've become a high school student.
The environment around me has changed a
lot.
The existence of the members has changed
a lot.
I think Ten-chan is the biggest.
I enjoyed everything with everyone.
I enjoyed the production period with
everyone.
I think it's a good memory.
Cute.
I want to watch Ten-chan's growth with
everyone.
Thank you very much.
Today is the 1st anniversary live,
and there is also a graduation ceremony
for Moriya Akane and Watanabe Rika.
It's very sad that we will be the last
members to stand on this stage today.
How do you feel, Aoi-chan?
Akanen and Pei-chan and I have been
through a lot together,
and we have a lot of gratitude to each
other,
so I want to convey that in this
concert.
Not only in this concert, but I want to
make it a wonderful concert that can be
conveyed in this concert as well.
I'm so happy that I was able to welcome
the last concert of these two with the
BUDDIES,
and I want to spend a time that is
irreplaceable with everyone.
I hope we can spend a time that is
So today, I want to make this a day I'll
never forget with everyone.
Is everyone ready?
You can still do it!
Thank you!
Let's have fun together until the end!
I'm a lover
I'm a lover who loves you
My heart is trembling, nervous, nervous
Deep in my eyes, deep in my eyes
My memories of the past life
Are burning hot like a fire
What more can I do?
This is the first time I've had this
kind of experience
You're the only one in front of me
My heart is throbbing, throbbing
I can't sleep
If my cheeks get hot, I'll probably fall
in love
That's a sign of unrequited love
Yes! A beautiful number
Yes! A mysterious number
I can't move because I'm nervous
I'm too pure to fall in love
A beautiful number
Yes! A meeting is always a coincidence
What should I talk about?
I didn't even forget to get ready
I'm a lover who loves you
My heart is throbbing, throbbing
I can't sleep
Hey, I'm like a girl
I'm shy when I'm shy
I knew I wasn't that kind of person
A place where we can meet
It's too romantic, this epic destiny
Yes! Delusion is panic
Emotions are panic
I want to talk, but I can't
I can't stop thinking
Yes! A single person is panic
My whole body is full of love
My limbs are tied
I feel like I've been thrown into
reality
What happened?
Right now, in front of me
But for some reason, I don't remember
It was a shocking event
Beautiful number
I didn't know the number
I can't move because I'm nervous
I'm too pure to fall in love
Beautiful number
Our meeting is always a coincidence
I didn't even have time to prepare
My voice, my voice, it won't come out
Everything stops
Now, I'm nervous
This is love, nervous
Love is a ticket, nervous
I'll tell you, nervous nervous
I'm nervous now
Suddenly, I'm nervous
I like you, nervous
My heart is trembling, nervous nervous
nervous nervous
I'm nervous now
I'm not the type to fall in love
I don't want you to understand
When did I realize
Being alone is the easiest
My bangs are long
I want to hide my gaze
Go away, go away
I'm not here
Even if you suddenly confess
I can't believe it
I'm covering my face
My big eyes and skin
It's all messed up
I'm nervous, nervous
There's nothing good about loving each
other
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
It doesn't matter
I'm nervous, nervous
What do you feel when you look at each
other?
Tell me your true feelings
I'll tell you later
Ah, falling in love is a pain
I've never seen you like that
One of the many
It's not special
I don't feel anything
I hate being judged
The corner of my chest
I'm looking for someone's shadow
Like a coincidence
I'm being pushed into the corner of the
station
The direction of my eyes
It's all messed up
I can't accept it
I'll remember the scenario
It's calculated, isn't it?
Ah, if I do this, I'll do that
This is how it's going to be
I don't want to fight according to the
scenario
I'd rather do this
I want to believe in myself
Ah, with you who resonates in my heart
I don't want to hurt my instinct
My first love is too cowardly
Even if I don't have a chance
Even if we love each other half-
heartedly
It's not a good thing
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
It doesn't matter
Even if we look at each other half-
heartedly
Hey, what do you feel?
Tell me your true feelings
I'll tell you later
Ah, it's a pain in the ass to be in love
"Budokan"
Budokan members!
Hanshin members!
Let's make a circle with me!
Yeah!
Being able to celebrate with everyone in
a circle
This is love, isn't it?
Yeah!
Let's all be one at the end!
I'm always surprised
I'm always talking to myself
I'm the worst person
Hey, do you understand?
Even if I don't have a chance
I don't want to hurt my instinct
From now on, I definitely don't want to
see you again
No, thank you!
Even so
Ah, it's a pain in the ass to be in love
It's okay if you don't have a chance
Come on, come on
I'll hug you like a star
It's not a big deal
It's a pity
Even if I do the same thing over and
over again
I can't sleep like this
In my heart
If I wasn't there
I'd be sleeping soundly
Even if I don't have friends or parents
I can't see anyone
This is love, isn't it?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
You're in a wide world
A laughable guy that I can't imagine
A pure girl that I can't doubt
I want you to love me
Until now
I've always believed in legends
I'll have hope
I want to shine in front of God
If I were to look around
I'd be swayed by the best love
If I were to be knocked down by the
bottom of hell
If I were to be swallowed up, I'd end up
breaking
I'll wipe my tears
Because I know I can't do it
I have no choice
If you want me
Smile
I'll be able to be myself
I'll go all out
If there's something I want
I can't just
Steal it
I have nothing
I am not embarrassed
That is love, isn't it?
(Music)
Hi, it's been a while. I'm Yui
Kobayashi.
I hope I can get back to the stage
little by little.
I hope I can start my second year with
SAKURAZAKA.
Thank you very much.
So everyone, please continue to support
U-KON!
Thank you!
This time, Jamaica Beer, the unit song,
was performed for the first time at this
concert.
Yui, how did you feel when you performed
it again today?
Well, I was very excited.
It's like an adult-like dance unit.
It was a very fresh feeling.
I think I was able to stand on this
stage and dance.
It was really cool.
All three of you have a good style.
Thank you everyone.
I'd like to ask the two of you.
Karin-chan and Hikari-chan, how was it
to perform for the first time today?
I've been waiting for Kobayashi-san to
come back.
I was thinking that it would be nice if
we could perform Jamaica Beer together
someday,
so I was wondering if Kobayashi-san's
first day of rehearsal would be a real
illusion.
I was looking forward to it, so I was
really happy to be able to perform
"Jamaica Veil" together like this.
I'm glad I didn't say it was an
illusion.
Hikari-chan was also very nervous, but
were you relieved to try it?
Yes, but it was really fun when the song
started on the stage.
I was so happy to see Yui-san in the
middle of the song.
That's great.
I'm looking forward to these three from
now on.
I feel like I've become one of the
members stronger because Yui-pon came
back.
I'd like to enjoy the rest of the live
together.
And I'd like to look back on this year
and ask a few people.
Yui-chan!
This year!
If you were to describe it in one word?
One word?
One word is...
It's similar to number one, so...
It's the axis of a tree.
The axis of a tree!
Sorry, Ue-san, you were just bouncing
around.
But, you know...
So it's a tree?
Listen, listen.
That's nice.
As Sakurazaka, we've made a new start.
So it's the axis of a tree.
And everyone's goal is...
To make a flower bloom, you need an
axis.
No matter how strong the wind blows, I
want to stand strong enough not to fall.
That's a good thing to say.
I knew you'd say that.
As expected.
The nutrients of the tree are you,
BUDDIES.
I'm happy.
So I hope everyone will continue to show
us your love and support.
I'd like to ask one more person.
Lena!
Lena, it's been a year since you've been
on TV a lot.
How do you feel?
It's really nice to be able to meet
BUDDIES all over the country like this.
I also had the opportunity to perform
with LUMMIT.
This year, I felt everyone's warmth and
kindness, and I thought that the group
had grown even a little.
I want to do my best to become a bigger
group in the second year.
Lastly, I'd like to ask Ozeki, who was
looking forward to Yui's return.
I'm really happy that Yui is back and
we're all on stage together.
As I was doing my activities...
I'm sure you all had fun at that time,
too.
I'm sure you all liked that moment.
But those moments never come back the
same way.
It's been two years since then.
I hope we can enjoy every time without
regret.
Thank you.
I want to enjoy it, but it's finally the
second half.
Everyone, get ready to get excited!
Wow!
I wonder if it's true!
Let's get excited for the second half!
[Music]
[Applause]
Don't push me
I'm going to the shopping street in my
hometown
I'll run with all my strength
I know what's in my body
I'm out of breath, I'm out of breath
There's always an end to the world
What should I do from here?
It's pitch black in front of me
I'm out of breath, I'm out of breath
If it's a wall, I can break it
Should I go back to the north road?
When I dream too much
I can't help it even if I'm here
I was wrong
I'm out of breath, I'm out of breath
How can I live in the present that
connects the past and the future?
I don't know what to do
Even if I resist, it's the same result
The more I go around
I become a person in the middle of the
night
Even if I keep hesitating
What should I answer?
I got a call from my parents
That's where I came from
If it's over, if it's over
Where will it start next?
What will happen next?
The future of despair
If it's over, if it's over
Looking for a way out
Is there no continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
I've been waiting until dawn
If it's over, if it's over
Do you want to rewind the bright days
and start over?
Do you want to start over?
No matter where you run
There is no way
Right or left
A wall that blocks
The neon is out
The rusty horse path
It's impossible
I ran, but I'm just tired
A dead end, a dead end
There is an end to the world
What should I do from here?
It's pitch black in front of me
A dead end, a dead end
It's broken from the wall
Should I go back to the way I came from?
When I dream too much
I can't help it even if I'm here
I was wrong
A dead end, a dead end
While hitting the wall in front of me
I'm screaming in my heart
Connecting the past and the future
What should I live for now?
Even if I go back to the way I came from
I realized that I wanted to take a break
Even if I think about it and laugh
I can't help it even if I'm here
I was wrong
A dead end, a dead end
It's broken from the wall in front of me
I'm screaming in my heart
No matter what you say
I don't care at all
Give me back my smile
I can't make happiness
Why didn't I fall in love?
"I love you" is like a cat in a cage
But I found out when I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meeting and loving each other is
impossible
I don't want to be myself, I want to
find my true self
People say, "It's okay to be you"
Or "Show me your smartphone photos"
Or "Just talk about love"
I'm so stupid
I'm so stupid that I'm so stupid
Christmas is coming soon
I don't want to be alone
What should I say for my birthday?
I want to be happy
I'm in love with you
I don't want to be myself
Because I'm having fun
What should I do?
I don't want to be in a love drama
I should have realized it earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so
nervous
People who are lost
Confess your love right away
Look at me closely, like you're feeling
it
Meet each other, hug each other
Let's kiss
Why is happiness so short-lived?
I've never been in love
I've always understood
Because both of us
Say "I love you"
It's like a cat in a cage
But when I fell in love
I understood
What people live for
Meet each other, love each other
It's impossible
I don't want to be myself
I want to be the real me
I don't want to be in a love drama
I should have realized it earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm so excited, I'm so nervous, I'm so
nervous
I want to be in a love drama
I should have realized it earlier
Meet each other, hug each other
Let's kiss
The scent of flowers
The green trees, the sunset
Let's live, let's live, let's live
If I had taken everything away
It would have been too late
It's like I've never been in love
This earth is so peaceful
Let's live
I can't stop here
Let's step forward with our own feet
My heart is looking somewhere far away
Is there really hope?
If I'm with you, I can go
If I'm with you, I can reach
Let's walk, let's walk, let's walk
We are buddies
We are dreaming
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Even if I lose something
Tomorrow will come again
The day will come
The sad rain and wind are darkness
A new day will come
Come on, 3, 2, 1, 9, 10
Yo! Let's start again from here
Yo! Freedom! I'm not waiting for
anything
Yo! We can go anywhere
Yo! Let's throw away despair with tears
Yo! I've been waiting for you
To the future, to the future, to the
future
We are friends
We are feeling
Oh oh oh oh oh...
We are friends
Yo! How are you? I wanted to see you
Yo! Look at this bright blue sky
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We are the same as we were
Yo! The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the leaking
sunlight
Let's go, let's go, let's go
We are friends
We are feeling
We are buddies, like a mother
We are buddies
Thank you for your support this year as
well!
We are standing here because you are
here!
Today is the second year of Sakurazuka
4D6!
We will become a bigger group and do our
best to repay you!
Will you continue to support us?
Thank you!
We are buddies!
Sakurazuka 4D6
This year
The process, the denial, everything
passed by at high speed.
I kept running, but I couldn't see the
future.
Was this choice the right one?
Or was it a mistake?
It's hard to make a 1 from a 0.
I know that.
Master.
The road to enlightenment is obviously
steep.
I wonder if I was really prepared.
I thought it was impossible somewhere.
There's no point in trying to be
rewarded.
I can't do it even if I'm told to do it.
I don't have myself.
The road to enlightenment
But what about it?
We have experienced despair in the
closest place.
I shook my head.
Anxiety became a means of growth.
The ups and downs turned into the power
to move the moon.
If I don't have confidence, I danced
until I collapsed every night.
"Failure is nothing. You just have to
look forward. You just have to use all
your energy to get rid of the noise.
There are things that only we can do."
Be proud.
Focus.
Look forward.
We are already number one.
I will make the precious number one,
which was created like that, bloom for
thousands and tens of thousands of
people.
Yes.
One year.
We are, just like us, beautiful and
strong, Sakurae.
"Sakurae"
The World of the Married
(Music)
I don't want to change this world
I don't want to be deceived
The sky that has been drowned in a white
sea
Swims in front of the galaxy
The window that I closed with the breath
I exhaled
Is clouded
Let's change the time of the heart
Even so, if you want to dream
No! No! No! Don't blame people
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
I'm despairing on my own
Because I don't have a mission, I've
already noticed
No! No! No! Even if you blame someone
One remains, it's a story game
If so, I'd rather choose loneliness
No! No! No! Nobody's fault
(Music)
I can't say that I want to change my way
of living
Before I knew it, I've become an adult
I'm just making excuses
I don't want to cry
No matter how much I regret it, I'll
scream
Even if I don't do something
If I were to be reborn again
No! No! No! Don't say beautiful things
Even if you laugh, even if you laugh,
you won't lose
Even so, believe in the strength to live
No! No! No! Nobody's fault
(Music)
No matter how deep the forest is
Trees are gathering
If the wind blows, you'll understand
Yeah
Light and shadow overlap many times
It'll become a big forest
I won't blame myself
Oh!
No! No! No! Nobody's fault
(Music)
No! No! No! Don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
I'm despairing on my own
I've already noticed that it's natural
No! No! No! Even if you blame someone
There's only one thing left, this story
game
If that's the case, choose loneliness
No! No! No! Nobody's fault
(Music)
A flow ball made of empty
A love I didn't know was being thrown
away
For some reason, my heart was bleeding
I wonder if it's half the fun
What's going on? What's going on?
I'm on the rise
Even if I'm just walking normally
Even if I'm just wearing boots and
leggings
I'm just living
There's still a lot of magic left
Who are you? What are you doing?
That's right, it's me
I'm a fluttering angel
I don't know what it's like, but I'm
hiding my face
It's a pitch party
(It's a pitch party)
I don't want to be a target
I wonder if I'm a good girl
Hey, if I did something like this
Nobody's fault
Let's talk, let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah, I'm not kidding
A flow ball has nothing to do with that
Baby, what did you say?
Say goodbye, next love
I don't want to be alone
It's a pitch party
(It's a pitch party)
You're apologizing
Don't look at me with that face
The one who stood out was you
Come on, let's go
I don't know what to do with you
If I didn't do it
I'm sure it's my turn
It's a pitch party to protect myself
Tomorrow is tomorrow
Endless party with someone else
If I'm caught up in a trial
I'll crush it
High five
I don't want to be a target
Nobody's fault
(It's a pitch party)
Let's believe, let's not believe
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah, I'm not kidding
A flow ball has nothing to do with that
Baby, it's so close, stay away
I didn't feel the pain
Wait a sec
Let me say what I want to say
Yeah, in a certain place
Every time I'm called by a different
team
There's only one rule
I don't know about others
Everyone talked about themselves
Everyone wanted to talk to someone
Is that all?
Yeah
I don't know about tonight
Hide your smile
It's a pitch party
(It's a pitch party)
I don't want to be a target
Am I a good girl?
Hey, if I do this
No one will get out of the house
Let's talk, let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah
A flow ball has nothing to do with that
I'm not looking outside the circle
In the city at the end of the night
I can't hear gunshots
Thank you very much for today
Thank you very much
It's a pitch party
A flow ball has nothing to do with that
I'm not looking outside the circle
In the city at the end of the night
I can't hear gunshots
Thank you very much for today
It's not a negative graduation.
I'm always thinking about everyone.
I'm grateful to everyone who met me.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
I'm Moriya Akami, 17 years old, 3rd year
high school.
I want to be a person who can make many
people smile and be moved.
Even in a bad way, I think I'm an honest
person
I only had ambitions
It was really fun to be able to
challenge
No matter what, I will do my best
I like to mess around, and I love having
fun.
I love variety shows, so sometimes I'm
really glad I got in.
I want to go on location!
In her form, who enjoys everything with
all her might,
everyone received power.
Go home.
I had a lot of things I wanted to cry
about and things I wanted to run away
from.
But now I try not to cry when I'm sad.
I want to cry in a better way.
I'm really glad I've been able to do my
best so far.
There's nothing I can't do.
Even though I'm discouraged, I'm just
going straight.
She stood in front of the members and
kept looking forward.
I don't know if I deserve to exist.
I don't know what I'm doing this for.
The people who supported me were the
fans who came to support me.
Thank you very much.
I really want to do my best.
Let's go!
Moriya Akane was hot and warm.
She was like the sun that shined on
everyone.
Moriya Akane was hot and warm.
She was like the sun that shined on
everyone.
I was the only one who could see her
face.
Thank you for watching.
I'm the oldest, so I want to be like a
kind sister to everyone.
I'm Rika Watanabe. I'm from Ibaraki
Prefecture.
People often say that I'm old-fashioned
and old-fashioned,
but I'm not inferior to anyone in
motivation and guts, so I look forward
to working with you.
Which eye is sexy?
It's not sexy at all.
Rika Watanabe
I can't do it.
The only one with the air of infinity.
I was loved by everyone and always made
people around me smile.
If you do it, you can do it.
Dance, too.
I wasn't very good at it, so I was
worried.
I wanted to repay the fans, so I wanted
to show them that I was doing my best.
I've been practicing more than anyone
else, and I've been practicing without
wasting my time on the Shinkansen.
That's what I've been doing for six
years, so I'm a really hard-working
person.
You're telling me it's okay, aren't you?
When someone seems to be in pain, I see
Pei-chan coming and going secretly, and
I think it's really kind.
She, who knew the hardest part of life,
was closer to the members than anyone
else,
and she smiled at them.
Her kindness
touched many people.
The people of Watanabe were saved.
Watanabe Rika was like the blue sky that
enveloped everything.
She was everyone's kind sister.
"I'm going to cry."
Fei is crying.
What does that mean?
So with today's live performance, the
members Moriya Akane and Watanabe Rika
are finally graduating.
I didn't realize it until the day of the
ceremony.
You two are so beautiful.
Thank you.
So beautiful.
So cool.
It's a great honor to be able to welcome
the end of these two together with you
in such a proper way.
And the two of you wrote a letter to
everyone, didn't you?
Yes, I wrote a letter.
Thank you.
Then I'd like to ask Akane to read the
letter.
Thank you.
To everyone who has supported me so far,
I joined Keyakizaka46 in 2015 and
graduated from Sakurazaka46 in 2021.
I've had a lot of experiences in the
past six years.
If I wasn't here, I would have met a lot
of emotions I didn't know.
It was a happy idol life to be able to
walk through so many life experiences.
Thank you very much.
Of course, it wasn't all good things.
There were times when I had to worry
about things that I couldn't do on my
own.
But at that time, there were a lot of
things that made me stronger because I
had a hard time and such experiences.
So I think that everything that happens
has a meaning and makes people grow.
I'm really grateful for what I have now.
At first, I didn't know what I was, what
kind of person I was,
but thanks to those who supported my
activities, I was able to find a little
bit of my own identity.
There are many things that I have
overcome because everyone who loved
Keyakizaka and Sakurazaka has been
watching over me for a long time.
Thank you so much to all the wonderful
fans.
To be honest, I wanted to see more
wonderful scenery together and I had a
lot of dreams that I wanted to make come
true.
But I felt that my personality was not
suitable for being an idol, and to be
honest, I couldn't lie about anything.
If I had been able to stand up more and
more cleverly, it would have been
possible because of my lack of strength.
I'm sorry that I chose this decision.
But no matter when it's the last time,
I've been serious about each and every
job so as not to regret it.
I can say from the bottom of my heart
that I've done everything I can do now.
So I have no regrets.
On a new path.
I hope we can make our dreams come true
without any rush.
And lastly,
the members who have always been with
us,
sometimes rivals,
who understand each other's feelings,
the only existence,
our beloved members,
who always think about us,
who support us and give us light.
Thank you.
I would like to thank all of my beloved
staff and everyone who has supported me
from the bottom of my heart.
I am where I am now because of you.
Thank you so much for everything you
have done for me.
I will be leaving this place that I
loved so much, but I will always be
connected to you in my heart.
I hope that the day will come when I can
see you all again.
I will do my best.
Please continue to support me.
Moriya Akane
Thank you so much.
Are you ready, Kei-chan?
Yes.
Kei-chan, please.
To everyone who came today, to everyone
who is watching the live stream, thank
you so much.
I'm not good at expressing my feelings
in words, but this is the last time, so
I wrote a letter so that I could convey
my feelings to everyone.
Thank you so much.
To all of you who always support me,
It's been 6 years since I joined
Keyakizaka 46 at the age of 20.
When I first joined, every day was new
to me.
Everything was new and full of things I
didn't know,
but we spent time supporting each other,
and every day went by in a flash.
Keyakizaka 46
In the music video shooting, we all lay
down and looked at the stars,
wore clothes and danced in the pool,
went to various places on the tour,
and ate delicious food together.
I can't count them all,
but I loved the days when I did silly
things with the members and laughed.
Ordinary daily life
I think it was a lot of fun.
But it wasn't just fun.
There were times when I wasn't good at
dancing,
and there were times when I couldn't do
what I wanted to do.
There were a lot of painful,
frustrating, and sad things.
But at that time, I had my beloved
members around me,
my fans who always watch over me warmly,
and the staff who support me a lot.
Thanks to everyone's support, I was able
to do my best.
When I looked at everyone's faces during
today's live performance, a lot of fun
memories came back to me, and I thought
it would be nice if this time could go
on forever.
During these 6 years at Keyakizaka 46
and Sakurazaka 46, I received a lot of
love, made a lot of wonderful memories,
and I think I was able to grow a little.
Even after graduation, I am proud to
have been a member of the group, and I
will continue to move forward firmly and
live as myself.
I hope I can continue to have fun and
relax.
I had a lot of fun with the members of
the group for 6 years.
I'm really glad that I joined Kyokizaka
46 and Sakurazaka 46.
That's what I think from the bottom of
my heart.
Thank you very much to everyone who has
supported me so far.
See you again, BELICA!
Thank you, both of you.
I read your letters and remembered a lot
of things.
I'm really glad that you two are here.
You're such a big presence.
I can't believe you're gone.
I can feel it, but I think it would be
nice if you could tell us some
unforgettable memories or fun things
that we've been doing together for six
and a half years, but how about you,
Akane?
But from the beginning, the music video
shooting was amazing, and Pei-chan also
said in a letter, but the music video
that I was doing with a lot of energy
was
The world view is really amazing, and it
doesn't change even if it becomes a
cherry blossom.
The pursuit of such performances and the
workability were strong from the
beginning, so it's memorable.
Even if I look back now,
I think it's a great memory.
It's an experience that I can't do
easily.
I've been with Akane and Shinmei since
Keyakizaka.
I've been able to overcome various
things with Akane.
But being together, Akane's true
strength,
Shinmei's strength, and Akane's passion.
I'm glad to have met the members, and I
hope they will continue to smile from
now on, including the hard times.
Thank you.
Looking back on the past 6 years, I had
a lot of fun, but the most fun was when
I was talking with everyone in the
dressing room.
Thank you very much.
She hasn't changed since she was a
child, hasn't she?
But Pei-chan has a lot of interesting
things that you can't see on TV.
She was a really kind sister, and I
think she was a mood maker that made
everyone laugh.
There were a lot of fun things, but
since I'm here, I'd like to have another
member come and talk to me.
Hi!
Lisa is here!
Thank you.
I've been listening to their letters
behind the scenes,
and when I look back at their idol life,
there are a lot of moments that make me
think, "It was fun. It was good."
I thought it would be nice if we could
meet, and I thought that we could send
it out without any regrets, so I hope
that we can continue to do our best
looking at such a figure.
It's not goodbye with this, but it's a
long life from now on, so let's meet a
lot from now on.
Thank you for watching!
Well, since these members have gathered,
I'd like you to listen to a song called
"Futari ga Saigo".
Are you ready?
Thank you very much.
Well then, please listen.
With Aozora and Mari,
"Footprints That Are Not Here"
The footprints on the sandy beach
The ripples of tears
I erased everything
But I'm sure I've come this far
I've walked here on my own
Even if I'm forgotten by someone
I won't cry
After I met you and learned about love
I finally understood something important
It's not how I've lived up to this day
Where do I want to go next?
I strongly wish
The footprints that continue to the left
Are the footprints that are not here
The palm of my hand holding up to the
sun
I'm sure I won't get tired of the
footprints in the blue sky
But I'm sure I've come this far
I reached out to the crowd
Someday, yes, someone's fingertips
If I could finally touch them
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
After I said goodbye to you, I lost
everything
The place where the pain I'd been
holding on to
Wasn't it where my heart was crying?
I looked for the past
And the pain I'd been holding on to
became heavier
It was there before
And now it's here
The sand of time is falling on the
ground
I can disappear from here
After I met you and learned about love
I finally understood something important
It's not how I've lived up to this day
I want to go next?
I strongly wish
The footprints that continue to the
future
Are the footprints that are not here
The sand of time is falling on the
ground
I can disappear from here
I'm being honest
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
The first time I came to this city
I was mixed up like a washing machine
The brilliance I saw on TV
Became an immoral emoji
Until I knew your address
While changing several trains
I can only hear the standard
Let's take the wrong train
I pushed it on my own
Long-distance love
I want to see you just once
Because I was on the phone for the first
time in a long time
Because I was always in a seat
I suddenly became curious
The more I have to live far away
Is the dream so important?
Is the blue sky somewhere different?
The door of the apartment I saw in the
photo is open
When I saw you, who seemed to catch a
cold
I couldn't say anything
Tears overflow and I can't stop
In the corner of the scattered room
There are days of your efforts and
battles
If you're scared of the cold
I was always there to pick you up
I was scolded by my voice
The more I have to endure loneliness
Is the dream still the future?
I can't see the blue sky in the window
I brought sunflower seeds
Let's bury it in the soil on the pot
Let the flowers bloom someday
The sun will tell you the position
Don't forget the blue sky
I pushed it on my own
Because I was always in a seat
I suddenly became curious
The more I have to live far away
Is the dream so important?
But I can't see
If the wind blows, I won't kiss you
I reached out to you
I forced a kiss
I really want to go home together
But I definitely want my dream to come
true
I can see the blue sky a little
The blue sky is different somewhere
Translated by Releska
Thank you very much, everyone.
We, Aozora and Mani, were a unit formed
in the Tiaki-Zaka era.
We performed "Ashiata" and "Aozora ga
Chigau" here.
How was it to perform in front of
everyone for the first time in a long
time?
I'll never forget it.
Thank you very much.
It was nostalgic, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Was it fun, Pe-chan?
It was fun.
I was surprised by the video in the
back.
Thank you very much for letting me
perform like this.
Thank you, everyone.
The sun has set.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Since we're here, I'd like to ask the
members to say a few words to the two of
you, starting with Ikisei.
Rina-chan.
Yes.
Please.
As you saw in the letter,
as Keyakizaka Ikisei,
we've been together for six and a half
years.
Really?
We've been through a lot together.
Take your time.
It was my first time, so I didn't know
anything, and there were a lot of hard
things, but when I think back on the
memories with the two of them, I think I
laughed a lot in the dressing room.
Finally, I think it was really good to
be able to have a graduation ceremony
for the two of them at the live show.
I'm really happy to be able to see this
beautiful dress.
I'm really happy to be able to see the
last song of the unit "Aozora" and
"Marie" that I liked the most at
Keyakizaka.
I'm really looking forward to it.
From now on, the two of them are going
to be very...
I've been loved by so many people, so
I'm sure I'll be able to live happily
ever after.
I hope you'll continue to be healthy.
Thank you for the past six and a half
years.
Thank you for such a wonderful message.
Thank you.
Next, Matsuri-chan, please.
I think you both have a wonderful
personality.
Moriya-san, you have your own way of
life.
You have a strong belief.
Well...
I want to be a strong person who has a
strong belief.
Rika-san, you have a pure and pure
heart.
I think that kind of personality is
rare.
I think it's not something that can be
easily done, but when I see the
wonderful side of the two of them, I
often think that I want to be that kind
of person.
After all, I heard that I had been
thinking about graduating for more than
a year or a year, and I think I was very
worried and decided.
I think that kind of personality is
rare.
I want to continue to support the path
that the two of them have decided in
their hearts, so I was very happy to be
able to work with Kei Akizaka 46 for
about three years as Sakurazaka 46, so I
will keep the memories of that time
firmly in my heart and continue to
support them.
I really want to support the two of
them. Thank you very much.
Let's start with Kira-chan.
Well, I received a lot of love from you
two.
I wanted to repay you little by little,
but I didn't have enough time.
Rika-san was really good just by being
by my side.
That alone gave me a lot of warmth.
She listened to my silly stories and
smiled when our eyes met.
I feel like I have a hole in my heart
when I think that I can't live a life
that can be healed by Rika-san.
My actions, my personality...
I loved Rika-san so much that I couldn't
lose to anyone.
Akane-san...
I realized...
I realized that it was natural for me to
be close to you.
I can't imagine spending my days without
you.
I miss you so much that I don't know
what to do.
When I look back at my memories of the
last year,
I'm happy that I can be in your
memories.
I hope you never forget me.
I'm honest, a little clumsy, a tsundere,
I'm not honest, I'm a little clumsy.
I'm clumsy, but Akane-san is cute,
lovely, and a really important person to
me.
It's really lonely to be apart from you
two.
But even if today is the last day of our
break-up,
even if it's a year from now,
it doesn't change the fact that I'm
lonely.
So, rather than the pain of breaking up,
I'd like to express my gratitude for
meeting you.
Thank you.
I'd like to cheer for the future with
all my heart.
You've left a lot of wonderful things in
this group.
I've always loved the two of you with a
smile on your face.
Thank you so much for everything you've
done for me.
Thank you.
As the three members said, these two
left a lot of things for the group.
I think that the experiences they have
overcome will definitely support their
lives in the future.
I want them to be confident and do a lot
of things they want to do in the future.
I want them to have a lot of fun.
I want to tell them how grateful I am.
Thank you.
The two of us will be moving on to a new
path.
Yesterday was the first anniversary of
Sakurazaka46.
To be honest, I didn't know what was
going to happen a year later.
But I'm glad that everyone's smiles have
increased this year.
But we...
But it wasn't just fun. It was also a
year of fighting against reality.
Each member had various conflicts and
anxiety.
But the reason I'm standing here today
is thanks to everyone who supports me
and BUDDIES.
I don't think I made the wrong choice a
year ago.
We have no choice but to believe in the
path in front of us and continue to
walk.
However, as we all work hard together,
the cherry blossoms in this year have
become irreplaceable and important.
I want to give back more and more love
to many people,
and I want to make bigger cherry
blossoms bloom.
Thank you for everything.
We will not forget our humble and kind
bonds, and we will continue to move
forward with the goal of becoming a
group that can bloom proudly and
beautifully.
Please follow us in the future. Thank
you for your support in the second year.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, thank you very much.
I would like to sing one last song with
everyone.
I would be happy if everyone could sing
"Cherry Blossom Pink" in your heart.
Then, let's sing together.
One, two!
"Cherry Blossom Pink Song"!
"Cherry Blossom Pink Song"
I was waiting for the sun to rise
The cherry blossoms in full bloom
Are singing in the gentle wind of winter
What was I waiting for
When I saw your smile?
Even if the people passing by
Forget the flowers of that day
The scenery of the next spring
Will always be remembered by us
Wow Wow Wow
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
The feeling of nostalgia in my heart
It's like I'm going to cry
Cherry blossoms are in full bloom
Wow Wow Wow
Yes, that's it for today
Akane Moriya and Rika Watanabe will
graduate.
I have a lot of memories with them.
I want to say thank you to them.
I would like to give this as a surprise.
Please come over here.
Please line up.
Kei-chan, this way.
Diagonally.
Okay, everyone, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to singing this
song.
Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you for changing my life.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[Yois leaving and leaving]
Thank you so much!
Thank you
Thank you!
- I love you all! Thank you so much! -
[Kizuna AI]
[Mika]
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
I love you forever!
Thank you so much!
[Kizuna AI]
[Mika]
Thank you for cheering me on!
I love you!
I love you too!
Akane, thank you.
Akane will never change.
Thank you.
Thank you for all your love.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you for meeting me.
Akane will never change.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I love you.
Thank you.
Finally, the two of us are starting a
new path.
Please continue to support us.
Thank you.
Translated by Releska