2nd year anniversary!
Start!
Good evening everyone!
We are Sakurazuka46!
Welcome to Sakurazuka46 2nd year
anniversary!
Buddy's thanksgiving!
Welcome!
Amazing!
360 degrees!
Thank you!
We are here with Sakura Tokai's
costumes.
First of all, this is the costume for
Samidare.
It's Samidare.
And that is my Jirenma.
It's my Jirenma.
It's cute, isn't it?
And that is Shakankyori.
Shakankyori.
And that is Masatsukesu.
It's Masatsukesu.
I don't think there are many costumes
like this.
How about you, Rena?
I thought there were so many costumes.
All of them are cute.
They are cute.
They are fashionable and cute.
And this time, we have a long-distance
stage like this.
BUDDIES are here 360 degrees.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
I'm so happy.
And it's Sakurazaka's second birthday,
so Yui-san, how do you feel?
I was able to come to this Budokan on my
first birthday, so I'm really happy to
be surrounded by so many BUDDIES in the
same place for my second anniversary.
How about you, Karin?
I'm so happy to be able to make a lot of
memories with you all in such a
wonderful place like Budokan.
I'd like to spend some precious time
with you all.
Everyone, thank you for your support
until the end!
What is it?
Everyone at SAKURAZAKO, everyone at
BUDDIES, good evening!
Good evening!
Happy 2nd anniversary!
Thank you!
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
Please be honest.
You're Shouji, the narrator of
SAKURAZAKO, right?
Yes, I'm Shouji.
Shouji-san!
Nice to meet you!
He's always sitting there.
I'm Umeka Shoju, and I'm in charge of
the narration for "Sokomagattara
Sakurazaka".
Nice to meet you!
Thank you very much.
From now on, I'll be singing in Ten's
voice.
What a luxury!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's move on to the first corner.
Let's take a look at Sakurazaka's second
year.
Four teams competing against each other.
Sakurazaka46 Second Year Quiz!
Sakurazaka46!
First, please take a look at this VTR.
So, we had a look at the activities of
SAKURAZAKA from last year's 1st
anniversary to the present.
Yamazaki-san, there were a lot of things
going on this year, right?
That's right.
Starting with "SAMIDARE YO", we were
able to release an album,
go on a tour, and perform at the Tokyo
Dome.
I think it was a big year for
SAKURAZAKA.
And the new captain was born.
I hope you can look forward to the new
SAKURAZAKA.
Looking back on the 2nd year of
SAKURAZAKA with the memories of the
members,
The corner "Let's participate in the
quiz" will start from now on.
This time, it's a four-team competition,
Each team is divided into teams
according to the costumes you are
wearing now,
You will have a quiz battle.
In addition, the venue is divided into
four.
As a supporter of each team, I would
like you to support the team.
There is also a quiz to borrow your
strength, so please cooperate for the
members.
Let's introduce the team.
First of all, the Samidareo team.
"Saminareyou" will end from here.
Please take care of us.
Everyone, please take care of us.
Let's do our best.
Moving on, it's time for "Boku no
Jirenba Team"!
Yes, it's time for "Boku no Jirenba
Team"!
All of our supporters are from the
southern side of the Hanamichi...
Zododododododo~
Hey! Don't make fun of me!
Don't make fun of me! Not now!
Not now!
Zodododododo~
And all the way to the western side of
the Hanamichi are the supporters of
"Boku no Jirenba Team"!
They're all in blue!
I'm so happy!
I want them to be in blue!
They're all in blue!
Okay, let's move on to the next one.
Next up is the social distancing team.
Yes, we are the social distancing team.
We are from the north side of Hanamichi
to the west side of Hanamichi.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Let's continue.
Last but not least, Team Masatsu Keisuu!
Yes, we are Team Masatsu Keisuu!
Our supporters are from the north side
of the Hanamichi...
...to the east side of the Hanamichi!
Please take care of us!
It's dyed in color, isn't it?
Team 1, please do your best to support
them!
Please do your best!
Now, let's move on to the quiz.
The team with the least points will have
a punishment game.
What is it?
Please do your best to support your
supporters!
Please do your best!
This is a tongue twister.
The first one is...
Yamasaki-san from Team Samidario!
You knew it, didn't you?
Here is the question!
What was the biggest failure I made at W
Keyaki Festival?
Please go ahead.
I'm from Team Shakankyori.
At Hanamichi...
Wait a minute!
This question...
I thought this question was a failure.
I'm going to show you my big failure.
Don't say it!
It's not the correct answer, but it's
been revealed a lot.
But, yes, it's true.
It was really foggy.
It was foggy.
It was raining.
It's not the correct answer, but it's
not a mistake.
I see.
So, everyone, please look forward to the
correct answer.
What is it?
Next, where is it?
Yes, it's Masatsuke Suu.
When she was playing the doll in the
school uniform,
she forgot to come out,
and came out from the middle.
Ping pong, ping pong!
It's not ping pong, ping pong!
Do it properly!
Can you tell us why that happened?
Well, there's a place where you can
change your clothes.
I sat there, and the previous song was
"Jamaica Beer",
which is my favorite song in Sakurazaka.
Thank you.
I thought it was cool, so I listened to
it.
No, no, no.
Eh? Is it over?
It's not over yet.
I panicked.
Did everyone notice that?
Yes.
That's right, and the song was the first
one.
Really?
Even I panicked.
Hikaru made a mistake.
That's right.
She panicked and made a mistake.
I thought Ten-chan wasn't there.
But she was there.
In time for the song.
This is an incident of the times.
I dashed for the first time this year.
I panicked.
Thank you for the wonderful question.
The team that got the correct answer
will get 10 points.
The next questioner is Saito from the
"Boku no Jirenma" team.
Here is the question.
What do you think is the best thing
about the members this year?
I wonder what it is.
I'm Ryo Samida.
Horizontal row.
That's true.
We did a lot of live shows.
I'm Meguro.
I'm from the Jirenma team.
When I take a picture, the lines are
lined up.
I see.
I'm Suu Masatsuki.
I had a lot of tours, so I changed my
clothes quickly.
It's related to that.
Ah, yes!
The travel time.
We traveled a lot during the tour,
so the way we passed the Shinkansen.
Do you have a hint?
A hint?
I think I know what it is.
It's something you do before a live.
Before a live?
Something you do before a live?
Here it is.
The engine of an engine.
Ah!
But...
What?
I don't know!
I got it!
Yes, it's the Girenma Team.
"Eating rice has become faster."
"Engine."
[Correct!]
Yay!
That was so close!
I got it!
It's correct!
Can you explain a little bit about it?
Yes, I'll explain it first.
"Sakurazaka" is quite a long song.
It's long.
It's long, and there's a little bit of
choreography.
Until the first year, we didn't really
get together,
but I think we've all become perfect
this year.
We can go without hesitation.
That's right.
Can you show us a little bit?
Shall we?
Let's do it again.
Haku-san, please.
Ikeki-san, please.
Let's go, everyone.
Ready, go!
Always beautiful and strong, like a
cherry blossom, just trust yourself!
Sake! Sake! Sakura! Sakura! 46!
Makkai!
That's it.
Is this your first time?
Is this your first time at the store?
It's my first time.
That was the first time I heard that.
Next up is the flag push-up question.
The team that gets the flag at the end
of the flower path will have the right
to push the flag.
The team that gets the flag, please
stand by.
Go!
We'll be waiting for you here, Rin!
Morita, Masatsukesu, Fujiyoshi, Jirenma,
Otoma, Samidare, and Yamasaki.
This question is from Koike-san from the
"Shakankyori" team.
Yes.
After reading the question to Koike-san,
please start running with the signal
"Start".
Now, please read the question.
Yes.
Here's the question.
What was the first thing we did together
before the second tour?
Now, start!
You can do it!
The Jiren team was faster!
It's the Jiren team!
- What is it? - You're discussing it,
right?
You're discussing it, right?
- Huh? - You're serious, right?
Yes! "Voiture"!
- That's correct! - You did it!
- You're fast! - As expected!
- Your speed is different! - Don't rush
it!
"Voiture" and "Voiture"...
So, Koike-san, what does this mean?
Well, up until now, we've been doing the
voice training in separate groups,
but starting with this tour, we've been
doing it as a group.
I think everyone's voice has really come
out.
So, if you don't mind, how would you
like to do it?
Would you like to show us?
Matsuda, Matsuda, Matsuda Rina-chan.
Are you ok?
Let's start with the Achilles tendon.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Don't raise your shoulders.
Bend your stomach.
Don't use your strength.
Next, let's do the "Chu-Daisho".
Breathe out.
Breathe in.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I want to see it.
It's okay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It was precious to see it.
That's right.
Nice.
So cute.
From Shakan Kyori,
Masumoto-san.
From Masatsuki Sue,
Habu-san.
From Okuno Jirema,
Kobayashi-san.
From Tamida Leo,
Matsuda-san.
Good luck!
This person is Tamura-san.
Hi, I'm Tamura.
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
Here's the question.
What is the famous snack in Hiroshima
that was a huge hit during this year's
tour?
Here I go.
Let's start!
Everyone's so fast!
It's a social distance.
Everyone's so fast.
Everyone's so fast!
Are you okay? Please take a deep breath.
Please give us the answer.
Agemomiji!
This is a classic game.
It was delicious.
That's right.
This "Agemomiji" was a huge hit, right?
Yes, it was.
We hadn't been to Hiroshima as a group
yet.
So we received "Agemomiji" there,
and everyone said it was delicious.
I think "Agemomiji" was a huge hit.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Isn't it just fire?
You're kidding, right?
I don't think so, but isn't it mostly
fire?
Yes, it is.
I can't decide.
But everyone ate it, right?
Everyone did.
So it's okay.
Next, it's a question for BUDDIES to
help us.
Please.
BUDDIES Time Shock!
It's cute.
From now on, each team will be asked
three questions in a row.
You have 15 seconds to answer each
question.
If you get the correct answer within 15
seconds, you will get 5 points for each
question.
And this question.
The supporters of each team will answer
this question with a penlight.
Members, please answer with reference to
it.
Whether you believe in Buddies or not,
it's up to you.
That's a good voice.
Thank you very much.
Well then, let's start with Team
Samidareo.
Please.
Buddies, are you ready?
There are options A and B.
If you think it's A, please choose red.
If you think it's B, please choose blue.
Please prepare for the red and blue
penlights.
Please.
That's good.
Well then, here we go.
BUDDIES
Time Shock
Which of the following was used as a
concert hall for the first time in the
Japanese Budokan?
A. BEATLES B. QUEEN
Tell us!
Red!
Ready, set, go!
A!
Wow!
That's amazing!
BUDDIES is strong!
Thank you!
B. Which is the correct order of the
buttons on the phone?
If I don't know, I'm in trouble.
The order of the buttons on the phone.
B?
Isn't it B?
It's B, right?
It's blue.
Let's believe in this.
One, two...
B!
Wow!
That's amazing!
Which is the key chain that Fujiya-shi
is wearing on her pouch?
A. Tomahiri B. Mukade
Do you know the answer?
Which is it?
We know the answer.
I don't know.
Ready?
B!
It's the other way around.
I didn't believe it.
No, no, no.
You got all the questions right.
That's great.
Thank you.
Next up is "My Dilemma Team"!
Let's get started.
"Buddy's Time Shock"!
Which of the two teams scored the first
goal in the Soccer World Cup?
A. Ritsu Doa B. Takumi Asano
I don't know!
Takumi Asano
It's him!
Let's do it one more time.
Ready, set, go!
A!
Which of the following is the correct
name of the radio show that airs every
Sunday?
A. Nichiyoubi no Heso B. Nichiyou no
Heso
We've done it before.
Let's go.
Ready, set, go!
B!
The origin of the name "Sakurasaka 46"
is from the city of Roppongi, which is
it?
A. Minato-ku B. Shibuya-ku
What?
What is it?
I don't know either!
Me neither!
Oh, you're right!
You're right!
What is it?
It could be a lie!
No, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
Here I go!
Ready, set...
A!
That's not it!
What a great teamwork!
You're so smart!
You got all of them right!
Yay!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
You guys are amazing!
Next, we have the "Shakankyori" team.
We'll do our best.
Nice to meet you.
Let's start.
"Buddy's Time Shock".
Which team does the Japanese
representative, Shouhei Ohtani, belong
to?
A. Los Angeles Angels B. Seattle Angels
Wow.
Ready?
A. Los Angeles Angels B. Seattle Angels
Which of the following is correct?
A. Ageo City, Saitama Prefecture
B. Kasukabe City, Saitama Prefecture
Isn't it A?
Isn't it B?
There's a lot of A's.
That's amazing.
One, two...
A!
Thank you.
When Uemura dances, which song will
Tamura and Yamasaki absolutely burst
into laughter?
A. A doll in a school uniform B. A car
on the top of a mountain
Which one?
It's B, isn't it?
It's A, isn't it?
A, A, A, A
Really?
Ready, set, A!
[A]
I want to see it!
You got it all right!
Well done!
Thank you very much!
The third question, what does this mean?
Please show it to us.
Rina-chan.
This is funny.
Can you show it to us first?
Ten-chan is really good at waves.
There's a movement like this.
I thought it was amazing.
In the middle...
It's really funny.
Let's dance together.
Together?
Do you want to do a collaboration?
I've never seen a collaboration like
this.
Good job!
It's like lighting.
Cute!
Thank you.
The last one!
The friction test!
Let's get the friction going!
You're wrong.
Let's get it going!
Sorry, let's get it going.
Let's get it going.
Here we go.
BUDDY'S TIME SHOCK
Which is the raccoon?
What?
This is hard.
It's the blue one!
What?
It's the blue one.
I think I have confidence.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3!
B!
What is the blood type that Sakurazaka
46 has the most?
A. A type. B. O type.
Isn't it A?
A?
There's a lot of red.
Then let's go with A.
1, 2, 3!
A!
Thank you!
"Saminare" is "rain" that falls in June.
Then, which is "rain" that falls
temporarily from autumn to winter?
A. Unpunished rain B. Shigure
Which is it?
Blue!
Really, everyone...
Everyone, don't you think it's blue?
There's a lot of blue, right?
Let's go!
One, two, three...
B!
Correct!
Amazing!
We did it!
Thank you!
You got all of them right!
I'm relieved!
Thank you!
It's been a while!
We did it!
It was difficult, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was quite difficult, wasn't it?
But the BUDDIES really supported us
perfectly.
Thank you very much.
So, Masatsuke Suu's team also got 15
points.
It's all thanks to everyone.
Thank you very much.
Now that the bond has deepened, let's
move on to the next question.
The next question is...
Sakurazaka Super Intro Quiz with
Asabukuro Relay!
For this question, each team will have 3
people participate.
Yes.
3 people, please get ready.
If this "Super Intro" question is
answered,
the flower path will be connected by a
relay in the morning bag.
The last 3 people will go to the
answering machine and press the button.
If you answer correctly, you will get a
point.
It's a super intro, so...
Everyone, please listen carefully.
If you know the answer, you can start.
Let's start.
Please listen carefully.
"Sakurazaka Introdon"
What?
Let's go!
Is my dilemma too early?
My dilemma is too early!
Will everyone be able to catch up?
The first place is my dilemma!
Yes, please take a deep breath and give
us your answer!
I'm going to cry at the top of my lungs.
Go, go, go, go!
Team Samidario!
Jamaica Beer
Incorrect
Team Masatsukesu!
BUDDIES!
Incorrect
What?
Yes, the "Shakankyaru" team!
"Danjetsu"
Wait, what should we do? Should we ask
again?
Should we answer?
Let's ask one more time.
Should we ask one more time?
Then, let's have the fans play the intro
part.
It's just an intro part.
I can't open my morning goggles.
Listen carefully.
"Sakurazaka Introdon"
What?
It's different from what I thought.
Team Samidario?
Did you get it?
No, I didn't.
I don't think so.
Nobody's fault.
Team Masatsuki?
My dilemma!
Team Samidario?
Dead End.
Incorrect!
Team Masatsuki?
What?
I don't get it.
Please tell us the song title.
I don't know.
Can we hear it one more time?
I want to hear it one more time.
How about it?
This is frustrating.
Ah, yes.
This is my dilemma team.
Is that okay?
Yes.
One, two...
Bang!
What?
That was quick.
That was wrong.
Let's hear it one more time.
One more time.
Let's do it one more time.
Please listen carefully.
"Sakurazaka Introdon"
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I got it, I got it.
Okay, let's start over.
Are you okay?
Can I say it?
Can you say it?
I'll say it.
That's what love is.
She's angry.
Everyone, please calm down.
Can you listen to the music?
Yes, I will.
Do you want to take a deep breath?
Are you ready?
I'm sorry.
Are you ready? Please listen carefully.
"Sakurazaka Introdon"
Isn't it different?
The sound has changed.
It has changed.
How is it?
I think some people understand it.
Do you understand it?
Yes.
It's a song.
"Obaachan"?
That's amazing.
Team Samidario.
"Plastic Regret".
That's amazing.
You are correct.
"Regret" is written on the board.
This is...
That's amazing.
It's written by BUDDIES.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
It's written by BUDDIES.
Thank you.
The correct answer is "Plastic Regret".
Let's change it up a bit.
"Balloon Breaking Relay Quiz"!
Each team will have 4 people
participate.
Each team will have to break the
balloons placed on the flower path one
by one.
If all the balloons are broken, the 4th
member will win.
If you get it right, you'll get a point.
All 4 members will have to do it.
"Balloon Breaking Relay Quiz"!
We'll do our best!
We can do it!
Are you ready?
Yes, we're ready.
Okay, then.
You can proceed as soon as you
understand.
Let's go, everyone.
Please listen carefully.
"Sakurazaka Introdon"
Do your best!
Team "Kamidari" is fast.
You can do it!
Team "Boku no Jirenma" is faster.
I could only hear her breathing.
Breathing?
What?
Are you okay?
Yes!
The sound of the bell is ringing,
though.
Ah, yes, is that okay?
Is that okay?
Then, please give us the answer!
If it's "Zutto Haru", then...
Eh?
Yes, please continue!
It's Team Samidare.
Samidareyo?
Team Samidare is strong.
Zono, Zono, Zono.
Zono.
By the way, did the other teams
understand?
We understood!
That's a suspicious expression.
I got it, I got it.
She's angry.
Because there's a lot of Kansai people.
And with that, all the quizzes are over!
In a blink of an eye.
I'd like to announce the results.
Please do.
Please, please.
The results are...
1st place goes to 2 teams.
What?
The number of explosions is...
Team Samidario.
With 35 points.
2 teams win.
Thank you.
It was hot.
It was hot, wasn't it?
Thank you.
I'm happy.
You did it.
Thank you for your hard work.
And the remaining team is...
The social distancing team.
Really?
I'm kind of sad.
She's praying a lot.
25 points.
My dilemma team...
25 points!
It's a tie, so...
We'll do rock, paper, scissors to decide
who goes first.
- Really? - Rock, paper, scissors?
- Rock, paper, scissors! - Rock, paper,
scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors, who's stronger?
Rock-paper-scissors, who's stronger.
Let's choose.
It's important.
Come here and play rock-paper-scissors.
It's decided, isn't it?
Strong! Strong!
I thought I was going to lose.
Good luck, Kira-chan.
Yui-chan, you're strong.
Kira-chan, you can do it.
You can do it.
I'm sorry if I lose.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Do your best!
You can do it, Kira-chan!
Rock-paper-scissors at first.
Rock-paper-scissors at first, Kira-chan.
I'll do it.
Okay, you two, please.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay!
The Boku no Jirenma team has won!
And so, the punishment game is
"Shakankyori"!
Congratulations!
We're back to square one!
"Shakankyori"!
This is a difficult punishment game.
What is it?
It's a cute confession that you don't
usually show.
Please face the camera one by one.
This is embarrassing.
Kira-chan is here!
Then, let's start with Masumoto.
Kira-chan, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Please face the camera.
I'm nervous.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Please go ahead.
I like you, so let's go for a drive.
But I'll be jealous, so please keep your
social distance.
So cute.
Her eyebrows are moving.
It's like a viper.
A viper?
A car.
OK, next.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
I'll do my best.
Manio-sama, are you OK?
Are you ready?
I'll do my best.
Then, please.
I love you forever.
Cute.
Me too.
OK, next.
Next is Koike-san.
It's Mii-san.
She's the master.
It's easy.
She's a professional.
Can you show us an example?
I don't want to.
Well then, please.
Has it already started?
It's embarrassing, so please listen to
it once.
Not yet.
I love you.
She's going to eat it.
She's cute.
It's still in progress.
Okay, lastly, Morita-san.
It's fast.
It's quite fast.
Well then, let's start.
Yes.
"Buddy's Shika Katan"
Kyaaa!
So cute!
Shika-chan Shika Katan!
Katan!
This is it!
So cute!
Nice, nice.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. I was able to fully
enjoy the cute Sakurazaka-chan.
That was Sakurazaka46's Second Year
Quiz!
Thank you!
Next, we have someone who knows a lot
about sakurazakus.
She has something she really wants to
tell everyone.
Let's have her on stage.
It's this person!
Please come in!
Who is it?
Good evening!
Do you know who I am?
This is the part of my head.
Here's the question.
Who do you think I am?
We all know!
Let's go!
One, two...
TAKAHIRO-SENSEI!
We all know!
Yes!
I'm a spider that looks like Takahiro-
sensei.
Today, I came from the world of "Shakan
Kyori".
I'm Masumoto Kira's spider No.2.
Everyone, please watch the music video
of "Shakan Kyori" by the Shakan Kyori
team.
There is a character of this cloud,
isn't there, Masumoto-san?
Yes, there is. But my cloud didn't spill
this much.
Is that so?
Sensei, can you keep going like that
until the end of today?
It's a little hard to see.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm so happy!
We'll be able to film it, so we'll ask
the staff to help us later.
Thank you so much!
Today is a very important stage for
everyone, so I'm here as the character
of Sakurazaka.
Thank you!
And!
Since I'm here today, as a member of
BUDDIES, I want everyone to know more
about the charm of Sakurazaka!
So!
I would like to explain the song of
Sakura Zaka!
Wow!
Let me do it!
I can see it live here!
Can I do it?
I'm happy!
Thank you very much!
What song are you going to sing today?
I did a survey the other day.
What is your favorite song recently?
I will sing "Nakete Kuru" by Jouken
Haisha.
I'm going to cry.
We'll do our best!
Please sit down, everyone.
I'll do my best!
First of all,
to get into the choreography,
you need lyrics.
When you drink coffee,
you need to smell it.
First, you need to enjoy the lyrics.
You need to enjoy the premise.
First of all,
you don't need to care about the past.
I can't help but remember it now.
Looking back on it now, I remember how
fun it was back then.
And to 1B, it's been a while since Asabu
Juuban...
You're kidding, right?
But this song is different!
Akimoto sensei's lyrics, when he first
puts out something concrete,
he puts it out first.
He creates a place or a space and then
deepens it from there.
For example, in NOVA4,
at the beginning, the sky is dirty.
A dirty space in the sky comes out and
you think, "Ah, that's what it's like."
Or in BAN,
it's like you're looking at a
smartphone.
You're holding a smartphone.
But this song is special. Why?
Why?
1A is an abbreviation.
It reminds me of the old days.
When I look back later, I remember that
it was fun at that time.
It's been a long time since Asabuchuban.
The details come later.
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
This is meaningful.
I think you can imagine what this
abbreviation looks like.
This is not just a love song, but a
scene that everyone can imagine when
they see the lyrics of this song.
In other words, I think it contains the
past and the Keyakizaka era that
everyone has.
Is it true?
So let's go into the first chorus.
Let's go to the first chorus.
It's called "On the way to the hill in
the twilight that cries at the
crossroads."
"On the way to the hill in the
twilight."
I dare to put the word "hill" here.
By doing so, it means that it is related
to our story of the hill road.
Do you know what the twilight is?
The twilight represents the condition of
the sun as the sun sets.
In other words, it is now.
However, it means that it is before
twilight.
It means that there is a time now when
the sun was rising in the sky.
In other words, the hill of twilight
means that there is a hill where the sun
is rising, not twilight.
In other words, it means that the past
is said about the hill road.
In other words, this song is not only
about the hill of twilight, but also
about looking at the past.
It's not just about looking back at the
past, but it's about looking at the
past,
immersing in the past, living in the
present, and what to do in the future.
It's a song with such a question mark.
That's how I feel with BADIZ.
That's right, that's right, that's
right.
And since we don't have time, let's look
at the work!
Let's go!
Don! Let's play it!
It's already amazing here!
Two amazing!
First of all, Yuka Sugai is in the
middle.
People who have come to see the live
tour should know this.
Yuka Sugai was not in the middle.
In this work, she was at the end of the
second floor.
However, this time, Yuka Sugai is in the
middle because it is a special feature
at the Tokyo Dome.
The small changes like this are made by
Sakurazaka team.
First of all, this song is said to be a
big story.
At the beginning of the song, there are
members on the first, second, and third
floors of the stage.
I'm surprised at how they can go back to
the center.
Bang!
The first song of the live concert that
comes with a conditional reflection.
What kind of song do they put in?
Yes, they put in a famous song.
They put in "Bang" and "No.4", but they
come back with a conditional reflection.
It makes a lot of sense to put in a
coupling song.
I'm sure the BUDDIES feel that all the
teams have a meaning in this song.
And look at the composition here.
It says "Natsuka".
That's right!
The person who made it for Keyakizaka,
Sakurazaka's team will put it in for the
first time.
Now, let's put in the past here.
I'll check one more later that it will
cry at the end of the condition.
Please!
Fujiyoshi is coming.
Let's see everyone's charm.
Sakurazaka is singing well these days.
Unlike before, the singing is wonderful.
I can hear your voice in the rehearsal.
Yui Kobayashi is deciding.
Fujiyoshi is also deciding well.
Morita, will you decide?
You have a good face.
Saito is deciding in the middle.
Sakurazaka is doing well.
Morita is coming.
Tamura is coming.
No, this is where the BUDDIES from all
over the world have gathered!
This is Moriya and Tamura's wonderful
place!
I was moved here!
Now, where is it? Don Saito Fuyuka-san,
please!
Eh?
Suddenly?
Is it the expression?
Like this?
It's sweet, it's sweet!
It's sweet?
It's sweet!
Inoue, please teach me!
When you go down the stairs, don't look
down.
Look at the audience in front of you and
perform.
98 points!
2 more points!
I looked down, but the way I looked down
was...
Moriya, please teach me.
That's it.
What is it?
The way I looked down was...
That's it.
I'll tell you the correct answer
When you look down, you have to count 1,
2, 3, 4
When you look down, you have to feel the
music
There's a combo called "Tamuramon"
Let's take a look
1, 2, 3, 4
You guys are amazing
That's right
That's right, Sakura Zakao's members are
like that
It's not just that all the members are
able to convey their charms to their
Buddies
However, all the Sakura members are
working hard
Let's move on
I want you to know this
And the chorus
Here
I'm sorry
OK, let's put it here.
Normally, you would cry at the end of a
song like "Tasogare" or "Kanashii Kyoku"
but you would look down like this.
But this time, Sakura Saka is looking up
to hold back her tears.
Here, your new way of expression has
already begun.
Sakura Saka's original power.
OK, let's go.
Now, repeat, repeat, powerfully.
What Takeshi has is the charm of Sakura
Saka that has been new while having the
charm of the past.
And Kobayashi decides firmly.
Boom!
I want everyone to notice this.
The scenery is blurred and tears come.
Love is just a moment.
Sugai's eyes were good here.
And there is no eternal happiness.
Love is just a moment.
Only the first generation is standing
there.
The second generation stands there and
says the message that there is no
eternal happiness as an answer to that.
In other words, we are looking at the
same scenery, but the time we have spent
is different, so the world that the
first generation has and the world that
the second generation feels should be
different.
The members who have two different
worlds are gathered, so there is now,
and I don't know what the future will
be, which is the interesting part of
this Sakurazaka 46.
I'm glad
Yamasaki-Ten has decided!
From here, it's going to be the original
form.
What do you feel?
Do you feel it?
I feel it!
The pose is decided!
It's coming!
Surrounding Yamasaki-Ten, the opposite
Rising-san's movement has entered!
Rising-san made it in the opposite
shape!
And now, the cute, cute, cute Peacock
Taiyaki that I also think is cute!
And now, it's sad to follow the same
course.
This word is important.
There were many new voices and different
voices.
They're doing their best.
But it was impossible.
And now, Yamasaki-Ten is riding the
Piano Rising!
This is amazing!
The flower road in Hiroshima was 40
meters.
But the flower road in Tokyo Dome is 80
meters!
Now, here's the biggest mystery of the
day!
What?
The word "crying" is very important.
So how do you get it?
Conditional reflection is when you
suddenly feel something and remember it.
Do you know the Proust effect, the
Proust phenomenon?
There was a writer named Proust.
In a work called "Seeking the Lost
Time,"
the scent of tea, the scent of tea
soaked in Madelaine's sweets,
brings back childhood memories.
So the song "Conditional Reflection"...
It's best if the members feel something
while performing, or if the BUDDIES are
with us and suddenly see something and
don't know what it is, but feel it.
That hint is in the lyrics, and that's
why we use a song by a person named
Nansuka.
"Oh, it's new now, but I miss
something." I want to grasp the feeling
of "Gyu".
Don't look too much at it.
So here it is!
What was in the 2A part?
We don't have time, so please answer
right away.
Let's go!
Takemoto!
Is it me?
Well...
Is it this one?
Ah, that one!
The chorus here is in the form of a
silent majority.
You're going to shake it off, right?
That's correct.
That's correct!
Thank you.
But that's the front.
There's another one in the back.
Hint formation!
Thank you.
Fujiyoshi Karin, do it!
How many Keyakizaka formations are
there?
Correct!
Look at this and feel the rest.
There are all the formations from 1st to
9th in Keyakizaka.
In this live, we start from 5th.
And at the black sheep,
we say "it was impossible"
and Yamasaki-ten jumps out.
And we reach the same course.
This is ambivalent.
And we turn around at the black sheep.
We say "it was impossible"
and Yamasaki-ten jumps out.
But he jumps out and comes back at the
end.
We see our group from a different
perspective.
The real meaning of this song lies in
how Yamasaki-Ten feels about it.
That's interesting.
And the members will decide how to move
towards this new world.
I'm going to play this until the end.
I'm going to finish talking.
Please listen carefully.
Because I'm going to do this for 1 hour
and 20 minutes.
2 hours?
Yamasaki-Ten will see the reality of
NIMA.
And she'll realize that she can't resist
her feelings.
She'll go with her emotions.
And then, we'll do our best to make the
last move.
This is a strong point that goes from
the past to the future, now, and then to
the future.
That's why we didn't put in a lot of
moves here.
There are parts that we want you to
shake freely in your own memories.
Fujiyoshi Yamagata is good.
And finally, do you know this
composition?
That's right, it's a composition of
who's going to ring the bell.
This is where everyone comes to the
future.
And at the end, they're going to put it
all together.
This is a great place to put it all
together.
Ah, Mori, Arina, they're putting it all
Wow, that's a good face.
At the end, they turn around and it's
over.
Wow, that's a good song.
If it was a group called Keyakizaka
until now,
at the end, everyone turns their backs
and goes into the back world.
But from there, they look forward and
point to the future.
That's the charm of the new SAKURAZAKA.
And I really believe that the future
that we're going to create is the future
of the members and the future of the
BUDDIES here.
So if the BUDDIES think, "This is good,
this is good," the members will be
guided in that direction.
If the members agree with that and say,
"We're going this way," we can change
the whole story.
It's really up to everyone to make a
story.
The past is always there. It doesn't
change now. It's still there today.
But tomorrow, we can change it with
everyone's help.
It's today to do that. It's a gathering
of everyone now to do that.
So now is very important. This moment is
very important.
Thank you for letting me be here today.
Let's support SAKURAZAKA together.
Thank you very much.
It was Mr. Sakairo. Thank you very much.
Cool!
Thank you very much.
It was supposed to be the same as
yesterday, but I thought about it a lot.
I'm going to tell you what I'm doing for
the first time today.
I thought I'd share it with you.
I thought about it and asked for a new
one.
The first song is "Nobody's Fault".
I'm glad.
It's a good song.
Shall we get ready?
Let's go.
Let's sit down.
Today is the release date of "Nobody's
Fault", right?
Two years ago.
That's right.
After two years,
we can hear Takahiro-sensei's direct
explanation here.
I'm so happy!
It's a very precious time.
It's okay to leave it to the teacher
from now on.
That's right!
But we don't have time!
We have to do it well.
I think so.
Yes.
But the first thing I want to tell you
is the lyrics.
We have to read the lyrics.
Yes, "Nobody's fault" is the beginning
of the song.
What kind of group were you before that?
Keyakizaka46.
Yes, it will be a new group,
"Sakurasaka".
I see.
You all thought about what kind of group
it would be, right?
Is it a sparkling group?
Or is it a happy, happy, exciting group?
I thought so.
Great.
I also thought about it.
What kind of pretense should I do?
Should I do this and that?
I thought so.
At the very beginning.
"Let's change this world"
"Don't be so pessimistic"
I'm sorry!
Also, the sky is still dirty in
Shiranuma.
In the chorus, it says "Don't blame
others"
and "Don't blame yourself"
In "Sakurazaka" and "Keyakizaka",
do you know the song "Zenbu Boku no Sei
Da"?
This "Nobody's Fault" says "Don't blame
yourself" to that song.
In other words, the ground is still
connected.
The sky is still dark.
And it doesn't change into something
new.
"You are yourself."
"But it's different."
It's going to change.
What does that mean?
I'm saying, "I've grown up before I knew
it."
That's right.
It's the same, but time is flowing.
What will the grown-up SAKURAZAKA46 show
us?
And believe in the strength to live even
so.
So open up a new path for yourself.
Don't get something new.
Let's make something new in ourselves.
That's what "Nobody's Fault" is about.
It's a very meaningful song.
And I'd like to see it right away.
Don't stop me too much!
Morita is going to make it!
And he made a pose!
I can't hold it!
That was fast!
So the first thing we did was to figure
out how to create a Nobody's Fault-like
world.
And the first thing we did was to figure
out how to emphasize everyone's image.
And the result was this pose.
Can everyone do it?
Yes.
What do you call this person?
Yes!
It's called "the one in the front."
Someone answered.
The "one in the front" is the shape of
the church's pointed roof.
You put all your fingers on it.
It's a pose that people who have faith
in themselves and have power in their
words make.
Judges and leaders often make this pose.
So I brought the strongest pose to
Morita Hikaru at the beginning.
And at the beginning, this is not a
sudden pose.
At the beginning, this is a reverse.
The world of Keyakizaka is so beautiful
that the more you go, the more you get
into yourself.
But from there, you have to turn the
world upside down in your new world,
but you have to go in a different
direction from the ground you are
connected to.
That's the first page of "Sakurasaka".
So I made a picture from the bottom to
the top, which I made at the beginning.
It goes up gradually.
And the shape of this church, the pose
at the beginning, is a church.
In the last song, there is a song about
who rings the bell.
We are looking for a savior of love.
So, by making the shape with this
church,
we think that Morita Hikaru has the
potential to be a savior of love.
In addition, to make it easier to
understand,
what shape does this shape have in
Sakamichi?
That's right! It has a triangle logo on
it, and it's a new shape that symbolizes
everything.
Now, let's continue the story!
Who is it? The director's hole is still
shrouded in mystery!
I'm still a mystery!
And by raising this finger, you can show
this power even more strongly.
And by touching the shoulder, you can
show your femininity.
And at the beginning of the song, you
can show your femininity as much as you
can in front of your face.
And you can show your whole body.
There are many feminine formations.
For example, when you say "Sorawaa", you
have a skirt.
This is a costume, so you don't have a
skirt, but you have a skirt.
That's right.
Do you know that the lyrics "watashi"
came out after "Sakurazaka"?
It's called "Plastic Regret" and
"Hanshin Hangi".
It's "Nasekoi".
The lyrics "watashi" came out.
The words "watashi" came out from
"Keyakizaka 46" which used the word
"boku".
It's a new "boku" that means "woman".
And in this expression, holding a skirt,
"Nnn!"
I've noticed it!
Morita Hikaru's perfect performance!
Have you heard of it?
Have you noticed it?
What was it?
Here's a question for the members.
Please answer what I thought was amazing
about Morita Hikaru.
What was it?
From the beginning of the first verse to
this part,
there was a wonderful performance that
I've never seen before.
What is it?
Inoue answered.
All of them are amazing, but
I can't see it in the video,
but can you see how the shoulders go up?
Is it different?
It's different!
That's close too! 98 points!
Hint! Hint!
Normally, it's once every 3 seconds.
I got it.
You got it?
Who got it?
Yamasaki Ten-san!
Is it "Mabataki"?
Correct!
Everyone, let's watch the performance
together!
Morita Hikaru's "Mabataki" is amazing.
And there's a moment where you have to
blink.
That blink is amazing.
Please pay attention to that Morita
Hikaru.
Don't blink!
Show it with your eyes so that you can
convey the words well.
But you have to blink no matter what.
- Did you notice? - I did!
It's called a "blues" where you can't
see the universe,
and when you touch it, you blink at the
same time.
That's so cool!
This is...
It's embarrassing!
That's amazing!
Morita with the blues is amazing.
And while watching this video,
please look at what my favorite part is.
All the members of Sakurazaka are
amazing.
Now, let's continue to watch the members
of Sakurazaka who have amazing eye-
blinking.
Inoue doesn't blink!
Kobayashi doesn't blink!
Koike doesn't blink!
Yamasaki doesn't blink from a grin!
Sakurai doesn't blink!
Fujifuji doesn't blink!
Saito doesn't blink!
What's going on?
But wait!
Saito doesn't blink!
Let's see if it's a blink of an eye or
not!
This is...
No!
This is an expression!
It's an expression!
I think it's a wink!
Is it a wink?
Yes, it's a wink!
This is a wink!
It's safe!
Let's go!
Now entering the chorus, she's using her
skirt here.
Actually, in the Keyakizaka era,
from "Kootsu", "Kaze ni Fukarete Mo" to
"Kuroi Hitsujima",
she's never worn a skirt before.
That's Keyakizaka.
A new world is being drawn here.
She's deciding the world.
Now, entering the chorus.
Matsuda is making a good face.
She's deciding the position.
The camera is filming from behind.
Her face is coming out of the camera.
She's wrapping her skirt around her body
so that her body line comes out.
That's Sakurazaka's new style.
Finally, the formation.
Here's the quiz!
Sakurazaka46 is trying something new
between the A melody and the chorus.
What is it?
Now, let's ask Fuyuka Saito.
Fuyuka Saito, you blinked just now, but
the most difficult part of yesterday's
performance,
the formation from the beginning to the
end, was the first rehearsal,
and Fuyuka Saito suddenly came up with
the question.
I noticed.
Fuyuka Saito noticed it.
What was your new attempt at "Nobody's
Fault"?
"Nobody's Fault"?
The formation changes in the second and
third lines of the chorus?
Yes, that's right. It's very close.
I'll give you a hint. Do you already
know?
For example, this is a song that
connects with the past, so I'll tell you
this.
10 times in "Kuroi Hitsuji"
15 times in "Ambivalent"
2 times in "Nova 4"
Uemura, everyone, please!
No formation changes.
Correct!
Oh!
That's right.
I wonder if we'll be able to show it
today.
If there is a "Nova Dizz Folt", please
take a look.
Actually, in the Keyakizaka period,
by moving the formation a lot,
I had the weapon to show the work.
However, when I became Sakurasaka, I
could only show the song, the words, and
the expression.
I had a fierce battle.
That song, that work, is "Nova Dizz
Folt".
Please pay attention to it.
Yes!
Here we go.
Matsuda! He's not blinking!
He's still looking at her!
Yes.
Now, each member's face will change.
Koike is here!
Tamura and Hono are here!
Hono and Tamura didn't blink!
Sugai is here! Nice expression!
Now, here we go!
Here we go!
Ah! Osono has a nice face!
I want you to look at the position of
Hikaru Morita, who has been at the front
of the center until now, but in fact,
Hikaru Morita is at the back or in the
middle.
I'm going to show you how to be a new
center here. That's how Sakurazaka 46
is.
Now, how do you decide at the end?
Chorus
I will sing firmly
I'll show you big
I'm making the formation as small as
possible here.
The 360-degree view of the Tokyo Dome is
also the idea of this work.
What happened?
And...
Entering the B-melo.
Do you notice anything?
Let's ask later.
Good expression.
What's going on?
Yes, you noticed!
Now, something is changing here.
What is changing?
How about a new move that can be done in
1-8, which was created in an instant
after Sakurazaka46?
A. You can recover your physical
strength in 8 counts of 1-8.
B. You can turn the position of the
front and back at once in 8 counts.
Who thinks it's A?
Who thinks it's B?
That's right.
Between 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
I learned the technique of swapping the
front and back at once.
It's very difficult, isn't it?
You bump into each other, don't you?
That's right.
This is going to be a specialty.
Let's go!
Morita and Hikaru are going forward.
It's a new way of expression.
Is this a homage to something?
It's a good expression.
The smile of Emperor Yamazaki came out.
The expression of Emperor Yamazaki is
strong.
It's good here.
A good expression came out.
The scream of Emperor Yamazaki.
Fujiyoshi Karin, of course.
But I thought it was amazing here.
Fujiyoshi Karin + Rina Uemura.
Rina Uemura, who came here.
Recently, the expression method is
wonderful.
Please look at Emperor Yamazaki.
Can you see it?
She's closing her eyes and feeling the
song.
Fuemura Rina is evolving!
Cool!
And now,
Morita's Ebi-zori jump!
Ah!
It's dark!
It's here!
It's really high.
Pay attention to this too.
This is called "Monita's Ebi-zori Jump"
The more you do it...
I'll do my best!
Correct!
The more you do it, the higher you get!
Today, we're aiming for the Japanese
flag
I see!
I'm going to break my leg on the ground
Amazing!
Let's go!
Let's decide the order!
The front and the back are switched
They're showing good expressions! Will
they be able to hold on?
They're holding on! Yamasaki-san is
always showing good expressions!
This Tamura is also showing good
expressions!
They're always coming back!
It's hard to find the right timing to
come back!
They're starting to come back!
This is a good expression!
I've been saying "Sugai, Sugai" for a
while now, but
I think this is another wonderful part!
This image!
This is after Sugai-san graduated!
But it's still in the video!
If there's a good expression,
That's how Sakurazaka's management
works!
I think that's a great way to do it.
Let's leave the good ones behind.
Let's leave them behind.
And Morita Hikaru is coming back.
Takemoto is also making a good
expression.
It's hard to look back.
How do you look back?
It's hard to match the timing.
Can you match it?
There are still stairs left here.
Do you climb the stairs here?
It's a good timing.
He was making a good expression.
The smoke that comes out of the
microphone is also a fun part of the
live performance.
I want to see it.
Morita, are you going to blink?
Are you not going to blink? Which one is
it?
He endured it.
OK.
Great.
It's really amazing.
Her eyes are teary, aren't they?
She's really amazing.
I have one last thing to say before we
end.
I've talked to Morita Hikaru about this.
In this triangle, is it right or left?
The meaning is very different between
right and left.
What is the difference?
The first time I made this triangle was
when I became an adult.
In fact, the shape of the eyes in a
certain music video is a homage to that.
Do you know that?
The eyes are drawn on the square of the
Silent Majority.
And now Morita Hikaru has grown up and
is looking down on himself in the past
from a high position.
So it means that I'm going to make a new
world from there again.
In that world, I'm going to make a new
world with my right eye and my left eye.
I said I don't care which one I choose.
Now, what is the meaning of the left eye
that she is making?
This is the last question.
Akiho Onuma, what do you think?
What is it?
The one on the left is...
Love.
Now, Masumoto!
Kumo-san, tell us the answer!
Eh? The future?
The future.
Takemoto, you look like you can do it.
Eh?
If I were you, I'd be like this.
Give me the power of a beautiful girl!
Me? Eh...
I'm forward-looking.
Ah, forward-looking.
Thank you!
No, that's not it.
"Flaming Tamura-sama"
I wonder what it is.
"Tatakai"
It's close, it's close.
Please go ahead, Morita Hikaru-san.
"Saisei"
Correct.
In ancient Egypt,
the right eye shows destruction.
The left eye brings about a new rebirth.
It means "rebuilding".
I heard this.
New Episode Coming Wed. 1700 JST
You can choose "destruction". You can
destroy everything.
But I want to start over.
By the way, there is a word "Aun" in
Japanese.
The left eye means "beginning".
The right eye means "end".
So, Tamura...
Tamura, not Tamura, Morita and Hikaru
chose "rebuild".
I felt the meaning of the new members.
That's why I decided to take care of the
view count when I make a new song.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's right. Each choreography is not
actually given.
It's a world created by the members.
And this time, I'm talking about the
choreography like this, but the
choreography is alive.
Actually, this is just the beginning.
The members will change more and more.
Maybe it's a little different from the
last time I came to the live.
That's why it's interesting.
Even if I talk about it, the members
will definitely grow, so it won't be
there.
This is the beginning.
The members make me wonder how it will
change from there.
The BUDDIES are the ones who make it
together.
That's why the live is interesting.
That's why I want to keep watching.
Let's support each other.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr.Akairo.
We were able to celebrate our 2nd
anniversary thanks to you, Ms. Takahiro.
You've been with us for the past two
years.
We'll continue to make great works with
you.
Thank you, Ms. Takahiro!