Thank you for watching.
Oh, I'm looking back at the old photos.
It's nostalgic.
This is a picture of when we were still
in lessons before our debut.
Zekken is different now.
There were so many of us.
Now there are six of us.
It's nostalgic.
Like this.
It was when we all went to the
waterfall.
It was a hit song of "Kuroi Hitsuji".
It was hard, but it's still in my
memory.
I can only show you this for a moment.
When we were performing at Fuji-Q
Highland,
I woke up early in the morning and took
a picture on the roller coaster.
Everyone was scared.
I looked at the camera and hid my
forehead.
It's so surreal.
But I was able to ride a jet coaster in
Naoki at 7 in the morning.
It was a great awakening.
It was fun.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please check the latest video on my
channel.
Bye bye.
This is the picture after the last live
of Kiyakizaka.
I took a picture with Takahiro-sensei.
I like it very much.
I miss it.
This is a picture of the award ceremony
when I received the Nagane Dresser
Award.
I remember everyone wearing glasses and
giving a speech.
I remember it.
I miss it.
This is a picture of us when we happened
to find ourselves and were happy when we
visited Lawson.
I was happy.
I was happy to collaborate with the shop
that we decorated.
I miss it.
This is with Hono-chan.
This is when we had the ceremony.
This is my favorite photo.
The one that I miss more than I thought.
When we did the music video.
When we all campfired.
This is the photo I took with Kira-chan.
Kira-chan, who is a little older than
me, has a lot of hair on her face, so
I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about Kira-chan's hair.
Kira-chan's hair is not long.
She have a lot of thick hair, so I'm
worried.
Really, I'm worried about her hair.
Please subscribe to my channel and
follow me on Twitter!
When we spent the day together at the
Kiyaki House,
we stayed there for two days.
We cooked and ate together.
We jumped into the pool together.
It's nostalgic. I like this picture.
It's a great memory that we played "Sui-
Chu-Fu-Kyo-Ao" in the pool.
"Sui-Chu-Fu-Kyo-Ao"
I'm so happy.
I've been waiting for a very scary
person.
I'll close the curtain.
I'll never forget.
When I think back,
I wonder if there is an eternity.
I wanted to change someone's life.
And I wanted to be able to change
someone's life.
But the other day...
The other day...
Oh, wait.
It's fine if it's here.
I'll do my best with 1 million
subscribers.
I want to be a necessary existence.
I want people to feel lonely without me.
I've never worked this hard.
I want to be a captain who can be
recognized by everyone.
I will do my best.
Everyone, please support me.
I was worried because it was my first
experience.
I had the image that the captain would
lead the team in the battle.
I thought, "I can't be the captain."
It's a pitiful love.
I think I have a duty to take
responsibility.
I can't say it because I think it's not
the position to say that.
I'm sorry.
I want to change so that I can say that
it is the position.
I want to change, but I can't change.
What gave me confidence was the members
who accepted me as I was.
I'm glad I'm Yuka.
I'm glad Sugaya is the captain.
I'm glad Yuka is here.
I'm glad I'm Yuka.
I didn't think I could go this far
without her.
She's watching me.
I think I've grown up a little.
I think I've gotten used to myself,
which is a little different from before.
I wanted to run away many times.
I felt like I was going to be crushed.
But...
*Hololive, it's no good. The heroine has
left the town.
*Even if the heroine is gone, the one
who is coming back home is not her.
*We are standing here to make you
realize that.
*You're just like them.
*We'll be waiting for you, my heroine.
*My heart is finally at peace.
*I'll be with you all.
*Wherever you are, we're right here.
*Whatever happens, we will always be
with you.
Thank you.
I'm no longer here...
I will be safe
Thank you
As long as you are by my side
I will never be lonely
I'm here
I will always be here
I will never let go
Thank you for watching.
I am proud to be the captain of this
group.
Everyone, thank you for coming to
Sakurazaka46's tour final concert today.
And thank you so much for holding such a
wonderful graduation ceremony.
Thank you so much for making time to
come to the venue during your busy
schedule
and for watching over us during the live
broadcast
I'm so happy to be able to spend this
day with my beloved Team Sakurazaka
at the Tokyo Dome, which was my dream
I'd like to take this opportunity to
look back on the past 7 years
I joined the team in 2015, and in 2016,
I debuted as Kiyakizaka46 in Silent
Majority.
Looking back, my idol life was full of
ups and downs.
I think it was a turning point in my
life to be appointed as a captain.
Thank you.
I was collaborating with my favorite
members.
It was very complicated.
It was very difficult to put together an
unbalanced group.
Sometimes I felt I was not worthy.
But at that time...
There were many members who were in
their teens, so we all worked hard, but
there were days when things didn't go
the way we wanted.
At that time, as the captain, I was
trying to do my best to be the bridge
connecting everyone in the group.
Even so...
It was hard to convey the image of the
group that I love
Even though I was prepared for it, I was
shocked when I was ignored
It was hard to believe in others
I felt it in my heart
I had to lie to myself
It was a time when it was difficult to
laugh from the bottom of my heart
But at that time
It was a real relief that everyone who
supported me was there
I received a lot of messages of support
from all over the world
I was really happy to be able to perform
live and perform on various stages
and to be able to accept and look
forward to my inexperienced self.
I want to become a person who can
respond to those feelings.
I want to become a person who can be
looked forward to.
Thank you for giving me a chance to move
forward.
I am proud of my life that I was able to
sing many famous songs written by
Yasushi Akimoto with my favorite
members.
Of course, I would like to thank all the
people who have supported me in many
ways,
my beloved members,
and my family who have always been by my
side.
I am very grateful that I was able to
run this far thanks to the support of so
many people.
Thank you very much.
Since I became a member of Sakurazaka46,
I've been able to talk about how the
members' smiles have increased a lot.
Thanks to everyone, my heart has become
lighter, and I've been able to laugh a
lot as a member, regardless of my
position.
I've been fighting with everyone who has
been with me for so long, and I've
become a cute junior who adores me as I
am.
It's very sad to say goodbye now.
Thank you very much.
I think Sakura 46, which I love so much,
has grown and become stronger than
before in the past two years thanks to
everyone's support.
And everyone is doing their best to move
forward.
I'm always full of reliable members who
are always doing their best.
I want to convey the charm of SAKURAZAKA
to more and more people from the bottom
of my heart.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind
of girls will come to the group that I'm
so proud of.
I'm looking forward to seeing SAKURAZAKA
from now on.
I would be happy if you could support
us.
And my favorite Keyakizaka46 and my
favorite Sakurazaka46
Each of them has their own charms.
It's not about which one is good or bad.
I would be happy if you could respect
each of them and accept their charms and
love them both.
Thank you.
I will do my best so that I can meet you
again, and I will never forget this
experience.
I want to embrace all the fun and
painful things and move forward.
I look forward to your continued support
for Sakura Asaka 46 and Yuka Sugai.
Thank you very much.
Yuka-san!
I didn't hear you.
You are so beautiful.
Thank you.
Where should I go?
Please stay here.
I'm happy that you like me.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
Thank you.
Actually, I wrote a letter to each of
the members with my feelings for Yuka-
san.
You wrote a letter?
I hope you'll accept it.
Thank you.
I'm about to cry.
From Inoue.
Can I go first?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
First of all, congratulations on your
graduation.
Thank you.
It's my first time meeting you.
I had a lot of anxiety about whether I
would be accepted.
At that time, Mr. Sugai welcomed me with
the best smile.
I was very relieved.
I'm glad.
I was personally depressed when I met
Asaka Sakura.
At that time, Mr. Sugai sent me a
message and said kind words to me.
Thank you very much.
There were a lot of things, but when I
think about it, I was able to receive
the message that I should do my best,
and I was able to do my best positively.
I'm glad.
I'm very, very lonely about Mr. Sugai's
graduation.
But I'm glad that Mr. Sugai's feelings
and words are still with me.
I will always be in this group, and I
will always have your feelings in my
heart, so I think I can do my best to
cherish those feelings in the future.
It's okay.
I want to give a lot of treasures to the
group.
Thank you very much.
I will treasure it forever.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work for about 7
years.
Thank you.
I will support you forever.
You are the best captain in my life.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Can I hold your hand?
Thank you very much!
I'm so happy! Thank you for accepting
me!
I'm so happy!
Thank you
Ah, Hikarin
Yuka-san, congratulations on your
graduation
Thank you
Yuka-san was the first senior that we
met
On the day of the performance, we were
so nervous
But you came to see us
And the first thing you said to us was
"Thank you for coming to Keyakizaka."
"Since I was assigned to Keyakizaka,"
"I felt like my heart was dancing."
"On the other hand,"
"I wonder if there are fans who would be
happy to join me."
"I was worried about that."
"Yuuka-san, in the words of 'Thank
you',"
"replied to me."
"Thank you."
I'm so happy to be able to feel such
warmth from you, Yuka-san.
I thought that I would definitely grow
more in this group and become a
necessary member.
Now, I think that I only have
Sakurazaka, so everything related to her
is important and precious to me.
Thank you, Yuka-san.
This time, I will be a member who can
hold hands with my new friends.
Thank you very much for taking care of
me in Keyakizaka and Sakurazaka.
And I look forward to working with you
forever.
Endo Hikari
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you so much.
I'm watching over you.
Thank you.
I love you.
Yuka-san, congratulations on your
graduation.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for being here today,
leading the group as the captain,
in the midst of such unimaginable
struggles.
Thank you so much.
When we first met, we promised to stand
together at the Tokyo Dome,
and we wanted to perform the opening
song together.
So we decided to perform the opening
Thank you very much for both of your
promises.
Thank you.
Yuka-san, you always support people
around you with a lot of kindness and
love.
You always say to people around you, "I
want to repay you."
I have received so many things from
Yuka-san that I want to repay her.
Thank you for leading me so far.
I would like to do my best in the future
so that I can give my all to the group
"SAKURAZAKA".
Thank you very much.
I love you.
Thank you.
I love you too.
Yuka-san, congratulations on your
graduation.
Thank you.
Yuka-san, I like your smile.
I'm glad.
The moment I met you, you said, "Thank
you for coming to Keyakizaka."
I was saved by the words, "You can stay
here."
For me, Yuka-san is a person who gives
me courage.
She told me that she likes the part of
me that I don't like.
She always watches my performances and
tells me that she likes them.
I've always been worried about my
performance,
but Yuka-san always tells me that she
likes me.
Like magic, Yuka-san always tells me
that I can do it.
She always encourages me to practice
more and improve myself.
I always wanted to follow Yuka-san
forever.
Yuka-san is a person I can't stop here.
Yuka-san, no matter how big a dream you
have, you can definitely make it come
true.
I really think so.
I'm lonely, but I want to send you a lot
of love.
Thank you so much for everything.
I love you forever and ever.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Sugai-san.
Thank you.
Sugai-san is equal to everyone,
and always smiles like the sun,
which was the support of my heart.
He kindly guided us,
who were confused about which way to go,
and I learned the greatness of the
captain.
During this tour,
I was able to see the performance of
"MIC Drop"
During this tour, I was able to see the
performance of "MIC Drop"
I was able to see the performance of
"MIC Drop"
I will continue to support you
I love you
Thank you
Thank you for watching
"Congratulations on your graduation,
Sugai-san."
"I didn't feel it during the rehearsal
yesterday, but I felt it as soon as the
live started."
"I really didn't want you to come
today."
"I didn't want it to start."
"But I'm so happy to see you so
beautiful like this."
"I still remember the first day I met
you."
"I came all the way here just because I
love you."
"I was worried that I might be a burden
to you."
"You listened to my unstoppable self-
introduction with a smile."
"I became an idol because you have
always protected the group."
"Thank you so much for letting me meet
such wonderful members."
"Please continue to be happier than
anyone else with your smile like the
sun."
"Thank you very much."
"I love you."
I'm so happy.
Yui-chan.
To Sugai-san.
You gave us infinite love every day.
You always have to think about the group
and you.
You look at each other deeply and notice
how small the change of feelings.
No matter what.
Thank you for supporting the group for a
long time.
Thank you for protecting us for a long
time.
I met an idol, and now I'm on stage like
this.
My idol life has begun.
Thank you.
I'm really happy that Sugai-san was in
the best group to be the captain.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Please be happy forever.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Yuka-san.
Thank you.
Yuka-san has always been so kind and
cute since the day we met.
As a member of the group, as a person, I
really respect her.
Yuka-san, who is always thinking about
people and the group more than herself,
and Yuka-san, who prioritizes and acts
on behalf of the group.
I wanted to be of help to Yuka-san as
much as possible.
But I couldn't do that, and sometimes I
was worried about her.
However, she was always kind to me, and
I really liked her.
I'll do my best to keep up with her.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'll leave it to you.
Riria and Riria are looking at Riria
with tears in their eyes.
Riria!
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
When I see you, when you just joined the
group,
I remember the first time I saw you in
the lesson room.
At that time, you were very nervous.
But you were smiling and talking to me
with a bright smile.
Thank you.
Since then, I have always been grateful
for everyone's equal and kind treatment.
And as a captain, I think there were a
lot of scenes where I had to speak on
behalf of the group.
I was always full of respect when I saw
you standing in the front and talking.
Thank you so much.
I wish you a lot of happiness after
graduation.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hiro-chan.
Thank you.
Hello.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Sugai-san.
Thank you.
The two and a half years I spent with
Sugai-san went by so quickly.
It wasn't enough.
I still have a lot to tell you, and I
wanted to spoil you a lot.
I wanted you to stay with me for a long,
long time.
But no matter how long I can stay with
you,
I don't think it was enough when I said
goodbye.
I have to tell myself that the goodbye
that will come someday
just came at the right time.
It's so painful and I can't help it.
That's how much you mean to me.
My everyday joy was Sugai-san.
I thought I could meet cute Sugai-san,
so I came here every day excited.
Even when I was about to fall down, I
was able to raise my face to see Sugai-
san.
Thank you for your reason to do your
best.
Thank you for your dreamy every day.
I want you to be the happiest person in
the world.
I really love you.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
I love you.
"To Yukkawa-san, thank you for your hard
work for about 7 years. When I'm with
Yukkawa-san, my heart is at ease and it
warms me up.
When Yukkawa-san told me that she was
going to graduate, it was when we were
eating together.
Since that day, I've been thinking about
Yukkawa-san every day, and there were
days when I was lonely and anxious and
sometimes cried.
That's how important it is for me to be
in a group."
"Honestly, I was very lonely and a
little anxious.
But I learned from Yukkawa-san's back,
who showed me and continued to be strong
while struggling, and I will do my best
to do what I can do."
"I'm really glad Yukkawa-san is the
captain."
"Because Yukkawa-san was the captain,
this group has now."
"I was really happy to be able to work
with Yukkawa-san in this group."
"Congratulations on your graduation. I
love you forever."
"Thank you."
"I'm rooting for you."
"Let's meet anytime."
"Thank you."
Rin-chan!
Congratulations on your graduation,
Sugai-san.
Thank you.
The day has finally come for you to say
this to Sugai-san.
I know you must be feeling really
lonely, but your feelings of gratitude
are much bigger than that.
Sugai-san always takes the lead in the
group,
and even when things get tough, you
always have a kind smile on your face.
I was able to work with peace of mind
because of you.
Thank you for always supporting and
protecting me.
I'm really happy to be able to work with
you as a captain.
Thank you for your hard work for 7
years.
I hope you can continue to spend your
days full of smiles.
I love you forever.
I love you too.
I'm watching you, okay?
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Yuka-san.
Thank you.
When I was a trainee and announced that
I was disbanded,
you welcomed me very warmly.
When I cried at that time,
Yuka-san said, "It's okay to take your
time."
I was very happy to hear that.
I still feel the same way.
I remember it vividly.
Thank you for taking away our anxiety
with the words and voices we were
nervous about.
And I'm so grateful that Yuka-san said
she wanted to stand with us at the Tokyo
Dome.
I'm so grateful that we're able to make
it happen now, and we're doing it in
such a blessed environment.
I love and admire Yuka-san, who is
always beautiful, strong, and has a kind
smile.
I'm really glad that Yuka-san is the
captain of the group.
Thank you so much for supporting the
group for 7 years.
And thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
To Yuka-san, first of all, thank you for
your hard work for the past 7 years.
Thank you.
No matter how hard it is, I want to
follow Yuka-san who is standing with a
strong chest.
There have been many times when I
thought it would be okay if the captain
said it,
but my heart, which was about to break,
was shaken many times by Yuka-san's
words.
I was able to come this far thanks to
Yuka-san's existence.
Thank you so much for making the group
and bringing me to the Tokyo Dome as
Sakurazaka.
Thank you so much for showing me such a
wonderful view.
I think Yuka-san's warm personality is
most evident in her smile.
I hope her life from now on will be
filled with smiles.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
To Yuka, thank you so much for the past
7 years.
And really, really, thank you for
everything.
Even though there are many difficulties
in the job of an idol,
there were many thoughts and worries
that only Yuka could understand in the
position of the group captain.
I'm sorry that I can't help you at all
even though I'm close in age.
Thank you for being the captain all the
time.
I think from the bottom of my heart that
it was really good that Yuka was the
captain of this group.
Yuka has been working hard and showing
me how hard she works,
and I've done my best so far.
When I was having a hard time and I was
about to quit, Yuka always found my good
points and praised me, so I was saved a
lot and I was able to continue so far.
When I joined the 4th single for the
first time, she congratulated me the
most, and I really can't forget the
words she said at that time.
It's really fun to be with Yuka, and I
want to be with her more and more.
I'm really lonely to graduate, but I've
done my best so far.
Please take care of yourself from now
on.
Yuka's smile when she's eating delicious
food is the cutest and I love it.
Don't hold back and eat a lot.
And thank you for bringing us to the
Tokyo Dome again today.
I'll do my best to be a wonderful person
like Yuka.
I'll do my best! Please continue to
support me! I love you!
Thank you! I love you!
Thank you.
Let's go eat again.
Hurry up and fix it.
Thank you.
Yuka.
Thank you for your hard work for 107
years.
Thank you.
I was still a student when I joined the
company,
so I wasn't used to the new environment.
Thank you for your hard work.
She took me to the city of Tokyo for the
first time.
She said, "I'll be your sister."
I was relieved and relieved.
I remember that I felt like I had a
family in the Kanto region.
My sister was a captain and a pillar of
the group.
I'm sure she had a lot of emotions that
I couldn't measure.
No matter what the situation is, she's
so kind and warm.
I really loved Yuka, who wrapped me up.
From now on, as an older sister, but not
as a member.
I'd like to talk to you about a lot of
things at a closer distance.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
Yuka, you've worked hard for 7 years.
Thank you.
It's been 7 years since we met, but
you're still as young as ever.
Your smile is cute.
Thank you.
There are some parts that are missing.
I love such pure Yuka.
As a captain...
You protected the group and listened to
each member's opinion.
I'm sure you've had a lot of hard times,
and I think you've been able to get
stronger because you've been watching it
by your side.
So I want you to keep in touch with me
as a friend, and we can go out for a
meal and talk about things that have
nothing to do with each other.
I hope that will support each other.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you. Let's go eat.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yuka.
Thank you for your hard work for about 7
years.
Thank you.
I'm glad to be here today at the Tokyo
Dome, where Yuka has always wished to
stand again.
There are many days when I can laugh
now, but there are many days when I
can't laugh no matter how hard I try.
No matter what the situation is, Yuka is
trying to protect the members and the
fans.
I clearly remember Yuka lying down while
holding a notebook in one hand.
I'm sorry.
It may be unfair to say this now, but I
think I was able to reduce Yuka's burden
by being closer to her.
I regret what I did in the past.
I do.
Yuka, you always say that you forget
about the past,
but I will never forget what you have
done for me.
Thank you for being our captain.
I love you. Have a good rest.
Thank you.
Thank you for being my strength.
(I like being alone)
(I want to be with you forever, Yuka)
Yuka.
I want to be with you forever...
I want to be with you forever, Shikori.
Thank you for taking care of the time we
spend together.
Yuka is taking a new step.
I was able to create this wonderful
stage to stand on the second stage.
I'm very happy that I was able to see
you off.
The first day we talked was a casual
conversation, but now it's an
irreplaceable memory for each other.
I'm sure there was a moment like that,
so I think there is now.
That moment is the most precious thing
in my life.
It was a chance to make friends.
It's a deep thought.
When I think back,
I was overflowing with memories of Yuka
Sona.
At any moment, without wasting anything,
we face each other with love.
Thanks to Yuka Sona being by my side,
I think that's what Sakurazaka46 is like
right now.
It's not until the day I graduate.
It's finally the day I graduate.
This...
This feeling of love has no end.
It's something that will remain in
everyone's hearts forever.
Please continue to spoil me.
Of course.
Thank you so much for the past 7 years.
Thank you, too.
Please spoil me, too.
I'm always supporting you.
I'm always having fun.
Thank you very much.
You wrote letters to me when you were
busy.
I didn't know that you thought so.
I'm glad that I could be a captain who
can help you.
Thanks to you, I can be here today.
I'm overflowing with gratitude for being
able to stand on such a wonderful stage.
Thank you so much, everyone.
Please continue to support us with your
love.
(Applause)
And the next song will be the last one.
I would be happy if you could listen to
this song for the last time.
This song was written by Yasushi
Akimoto, who is about to graduate
tomorrow.
I'm sad to say goodbye to everyone, but
I'm going to the next stage.
I'd like to sing a song for everyone
here today.
Please listen.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
I'm not sad
Because we'll meet again someday
Until that day
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
Yes, this place is here
A scene where everyone can see
everything
If you want something, you can get
anything
I decided that I wouldn't be able to
forgive myself for being in such an
environment
Where should I put what I have today?
I feel like I can live more freely
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
I hope your heart will remain in one
piece while laughing and waving
I'm sorry, I'm sorry for saying such a
selfish thing
But I'm happy to see you off to become
an adult
I love you!
Ah, the memories are empty
Reflected from the depths of the sea
New dreams are replaced by old dreams
It's reassuring to have friends
Even the timing of walking alone from
here
Even if I can't see the end of the dark
road
My heart rises and believes in the light
of hope
I pray, I pray, I pray for a happy
future
So that I won't regret today's farewell
I'm sure, I'm sure, even if I'm afraid
I'll just go forward with all my might
until that day
Hey, wait for me forever
Hey, I'll never forget you
"Sakurazaka46"
Today, I, Yuuka Suga, will be graduating
from Sakurazaka46.
I received support from so many people,
and I was able to run this far with the
support of my beloved members.
So that I can meet everyone I love, I
want to start a new journey from
tomorrow.
I would be happy if you could wait until
I can meet you again.
And...
Thank you for being with me today.
I've been fighting to protect you.
There were sad things, but it was the
most fun.
Thank you for your support for 7 years.
Thank you for being with me 7 years.
Stay safe.
Next year I will be with you.
I love you.
Thank you for always being by my side.
Sayonara, sayonara, sayonara
There's no need to be sad
Until the day we meet again
See you, see you, see you
With a smile on your face
May your heart's sadness remain
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, for saying such
selfish things
But I'm strong enough to become an adult
Until the day we meet again
Sayonara, sayonara, sayonara
"Sayonara, sayonara, sayonara"
If I'm with these members, I think I can
overcome any difficulties
I think I can move forward on any path
I want to stand on this stage again
I want to hold hands with the members
I want to hold hands with the staff
And I want to hold hands with the
BUDDIES
I want to work together
From now on, SAKURAZAKA46 will continue
to climb the hill
To all the BUDDIES
From now on, we will continue to walk
with SAKURAZAKA46
Please continue to support SAKURAZAKA46
Thank you
That's all
We are SAKURAZAKA46
Thank you very much
Everyone, please take a picture with us
Everyone, please take a lot of pictures
and post them on SNS
Thank you very much
I love you
Everyone, I love you
Thank you very much
I love you