This is a special video of SAKURAZUKI,
the 5th single.
I'm YASUHARA, the manager of SAKURAZUKI.
This time we will release the 2022
version of the treasure video on the
manager's mobile phone.
There are many treasure videos from last
year.
I will release it for a year.
Please take a look.
I always have a rehearsal at this time.
Are you wearing a hat with the merch?
Yes, everyone wears hats with the merch.
Karin doesn't like hats with the merch.
We were at the center stage of the Paris
Thank You Festival,
so we were waiting for the members from
all over the world.
Lower it a bit.
This is the teacher who got the white
paper license.
She is the daughter of the teacher.
She is serious.
It's a rare sound.
It's called "Bloom and Kiss".
This time, there was a master in Akane
no Koji.
So, it's related to Master Habuto.
The death game was interesting.
I see.
After "HARU DATTARA NA"
There was a setlist for the school
uniform dolls
When the members are waiting
It's good to look forward to it
Her reaction is big
It's cute
Which one is good?
I can do it
I can't take it off
I can't move my body
Did I win?
I'm practicing until just before
recording
I won!
Mel is going to be 12 soon
At the age of a dog
A human?
I don't think there are many people who
can count at the age of a human.
Someone said, "My dog is 58 years old."
I don't think so.
Is it not enough?
From behind.
It was my fault.
I didn't ask anyone to do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared of coffee.
I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
This is Utawanguru's dressing room.
Ten's singing starts here.
I'm doing this every time.
Ten is getting better.
It's not that kind of song.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready yet.
You were singing all the time.
Which song is it?
It's so cute.
Do you really think so?
Yes, I do.
Which part of me is cute?
Your headband.
I'm so happy.
What do you do in your free time?
I'm very excited after the live show.
Do you have a dream?
No, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know the rules of this world.
It's Matsuda again.
It's been a long time since I sang this
song, so I'm not good at it.
You are good at it.
I'm not good at it.
I'm good at it.
I have a lot of rice.
It's delicious.
This is the end of Max Live.
I can't rap.
It's delicious.
After this, I'm going to leave it to
everyone.
There are about 7 kinds, but everyone is
eating each one.
Everyone is saying that it is better to
eat this taste.
Hono-chan seems to be in full control
now.
I think it's about the last one.
Everyone is saying that they ate
everything.
Everyone is talking about coming to
Hiroshima next year.
Right, Yumi-chan?
I want to leave it to this year.
This is delicious.
This is fried food.
YUMIKO was eating a lot.
This is chestnut.
ITADAKIMASU.
Which do you want to eat?
Chestnut?
This is sesame.
I want to eat this.
This is cheese.
The cheese was very delicious.
This is a pumpkin.
There are a lot of pumpkins.
I want to drink pumpkin tea.
I think the person who gave this to us
after the live was gone in an instant.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
We should eat this.
We only have this today.
She has a hard time deciding whether to
eat it or not.
She has a fight with the doctor the day
after tomorrow.
Can I eat it?
I made it a half-ball.
I can eat it.
It's a half-ball, so it's allowed.
This is a reward.
I ate this before it started.
It's a bad dream.
I'm going to eat this because it's the
only one.
It's a catering that I'm looking forward
to.
This is delicious.
It's refreshing.
Actually...
What?
Can I expose you?
Stop it.
You've been quiet, but you seem to like
me.
No, I don't.
So...
Kira is touching you.
I've been doing this since this morning.
I was told by a make-up artist.
You like Kira.
A long time ago.
Is that true?
Yes.
You like her, right?
Why?
I get bored easily.
Did you like someone else?
I don't know.
Yes.
What did I do?
You returned to normal.
You were funny this morning.
Me?
You showed me a lot of videos.
I sent you a lot of funny videos.
Thank you.
This is a movie.
Stay here.
This is the image I took at the game
center.
Shimeji!
Enoki!
Don't get in my way.
I won't lose.
I admit it.
I'm fine.
I am a bit nervous.
Oh, is this a rena movement?
This is where you can't say "I love you"
even if you pass each other.
This is the greeting of the rena.
This is the greeting of the kima.
This is the greeting of the koi.
You can't say "I love you."
No need to say "I love you."
I can't do it.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm going to put my hand out.
Hey!
They are laughing.
I will fix it with the power of Renori.
It's a little different, isn't it?
They're not biting each other.
But after the live, they're all like
this.
It's like they're fighting.
Oh, it's right before the live.
It's right before the live.
It's a little different, isn't it?
I heard a loud voice from Sokora-jyu
last year at the Kyogen Boom.
I think it's a super-duper song.
From Sokora-jyu.
Weak.
It was a good smile.
If Sanri was fun, that's fine.
The girls are trying to lure Nome-san.
Pretty girls.
Here comes the girls' piece!
There's a girl's piece waiting for us.
I want to dance with the girl's piece.
We'll dance afterwards.
We'll be shooting downstairs.
We'll dress up and dance together.
I'm not
Oh, you're not?
Oh, good, good, good.
I'm asking the staff to change it.
They are good friends.
The tower in the middle when Risa
graduated from high school was
surprisingly high.
It was like experiencing something I
wouldn't experience in real life.
Thank you.
Lisa and BUDDIES have a different point
of view.
Yui, you can do it!
Her voice is always clear.
It's funny.
She's been saying "You can do it" in a
meaningless place.
Thank you.
It was so much fun.
It's an attraction.
It looks fun.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Branko and Takehashi.
Who is holding this?
Is it for a photo shoot?
Do your best.
She is taking a picture of me from the
other side.
Good luck.
What is this?
This is the first day after the live.
Everyone is fine after the live.
I will get off.
Be careful.
It doesn't matter, as long as it's a big
VTuber.
It's so big!
Thank you, everyone!
I'm trying to get you to use it in a
good way.
This is a blower that cleans the lens of
the camera.
This is a blower that sucks the air out
of the lens of the camera.
It's like a banana.
It's made of a strong material.
It's gentle.
It's amazing.
Mr. Marino.
Marino-sama!
Cute?
Cute!
The size is cute!
Marino!
Too cute!
Cute!
I like it too!
She is so cute!
Like a baby!
The size is cute!
Everyone wants to take a picture like
this.
Cute!
Karin often says "cute, cute"
I want to take a picture.
This is the costume of "Kyo-Wa-O"
Oh, it's a fitting
We did a fitting at the final Tokyo Dome
of last year's tour
to show "Kyo-Wa-O"
Nikkei students adored this costume
This is from Girls' Award.
There was a purikura on the back.
Everyone wanted to take a picture of it.
I was taking a picture of it.
I'm laughing at the processed face.
It's amazing.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to see it.
It's this big.
Isn't that shrimp disgusting?
Lisa said she likes shrimp.
She prepared a lot of shrimp items.
I think the shrimp line and rice were
full of shrimp.
Shrimp is cute.
This is a short cut.
There is a big pillow on this collar, so
everyone is taking pictures.
Cute
How much?
The most in the universe
Cute, cute
Thank you dad and mom
Great
She is a great girl
This is a flower my mom gave me. It
looks like my mom.
It's a good flower.
This is a lipstick my dad gave me.
It's cute. It's perfect.
It's perfect?
I'm so happy to see this face.
I don't like this mouth.
I'm embarrassed when I'm praised.
It's Eri again.
There were a lot of comedy books.
It's so funny.
I'm going to the world soon.
Eri's tire.
How many times did you say you liked it?
I'm Haku. I'm Sugai. I'm Soemura.
All three of us?
What is it?
You don't have a house in mind?
Thank you very much.
9th prize.
Matryoshka.
Thank you very much.
I'll put the hashtag on my Instagram.
I'm sure my turn was really good.
I'm sure my turn!
Because if I don't do it,
You were in a Samidari mood today,
weren't you?
Samidari!
Hurry up and take it off.
On the last day of rehearsal, we do the
usual tape-off.
The staff of the live team put up a
picture of the set in the rehearsal
studio.
At the end, we peel it off.
Ms. Takahiko is also peeling it off.
I'm going to forget the real one.
Is it fun to peel it off?
Yes, it's fun.
Do you like this work?
Yes, I like this work.
I feel a sense of accomplishment that
it's over.
I feel like it's going to be a live
soon.
This is a masterpiece.
My master told me to introduce my
favorite things.
I'm going to introduce "Hakofugu".
This is the T-shirt I was wearing in the
anime.
Wow!
I'm good at this.
I'm going to show you something.
There's a lot of light.
There's nothing.
I thought the same thing.
I'm good at this.
Thank you very much.
I can't go to MII-CHAN's neck.
Why?
I think it will break.
It's not like that.
I was talking about how YUMIKO would
tighten her neck even if it was red.
MII-CHAN's neck is about to break.
This is a silent message.
Karin doesn't do anything.
(Motorcycle)
(Helicopter)
(Mother)
(Motorcycle)
(Helicopter)
(Mother)
Hiroshima Jacket
(Laughter)
Wait a minute. I'm sorry.
Did you turn off the light?
You have to be patient to enjoy it.
If you don't protect it, it will be
gone.
It's a good sound.
Then I'll be back soon.
Everyone, let's get excited!
Hiroshima Shokken!
Actually, I've been thinking a lot about
it.
I've been thinking a lot about it.
I'm doing it with a lot of preparation.
I'm studying the dialects of each place.
I'll do my best as a man.
Thank you very much.
Here you are.
What are you thinking now?
Good girl.
Wow, you look like you have too much
muscle.
It's Masumoto again.
Kira doesn't like to lose.
Uemura is looking around warmly.
I was hit by Senpai.
I fell down by myself.
I was doing push-ups.
I'm not good at it.
One more time.
I'm sure I'll lose.
You're strong.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
I'm going to take a winter scene with my
feet.
But it was really cold.
And on the lake, it's warmer than the
ground.
It's cold.
It was really cold.
I think it's fun.
It's really fun.
The birds are gone.
Only her face is frozen.
Mt.Fuji.
But I don't know if we can see Mt.Fuji.
It's close to Mt.Fuji.
Hii-chan is the most surprised.
Who was standing in the front?
Ten-chan.
Ten-chan was surprised.
Everyone was looking forward to seeing
me.
Thank you for watching.
Is that so?
This is the bottom of Yuuka's graduation
party.
Shuru?
I'm sorry that I made you wait for so
long.
After this year's final, I'm going to
leave the group.
I'm going to make them react.
I'm going to announce my graduation.
Are you kidding me?
I'll do it again.
When I asked Yuka later, she said, "I
was shocked because I didn't have much
reaction, so I got a reaction."
I was happy to be satisfied.
This is the icing at the end.
I'm crying. It hurts so much.
How long does it take to harden?
It's been about 3 minutes.
How long does it take?
10 minutes.
It's getting cold, so it's hard to do it
well.
But it seems to be very easy.
Wow!
Kissy shop!
It's like a fairy tale!
Isn't the color crazy?
The one who said "kiss shop" is this
person.
It's moving!
In the studio.
Wow!
It's amazing!
Let me introduce you, Kei-chan.
Wow!
There is an S-type outside.
This is Kira, who goes to the zoo to let
the animals go.
Kira has a great love for animals.
Kira also has a good relationship with
insects.
This is Double Keyaki Fessy.
Aoi was riding this when I was a ballet
boy.
Thank you for your viewing.
Habu-san is practicing all the time.
She is always studying how to show.
I'm checking the concentration of the
audience.
This is the last live performance of
Keyakizaka.
Hoba is dancing.
Kobayashi-san is very excited.
It looks fun.
This is the back side of the BUDDIES
thanksgiving festival the other day.
Backsliding is a new thing for us.
We learned a lot of new moves.
I was doing that.
I hate it.
I had a second BAX LIVE on New Year's
Day.
I remember everyone dancing at the end
of the year.
I will play 15 songs.
I will play a new song.
I will play "KYUUDOU" and "URAGI" by
HITTIGAN.
Thank you very much.
The fourth single "HITTIGAN" has been
completed.
I was moved when I achieved this.
Did you do this at about 9 o'clock?
I wanted to say that I did it.
Thank you very much.
We were alone.
The manager was posing.
They all remember the choreography very
well.
I think it's amazing.
It's over if you do it a few times.
It ends much faster than I expected.
It's a song that I've already danced to.
At this time, the first-generation
students got along very well.
They seemed to be happy to be able to
come out to Kyushu.
I'm embarrassed to see O-chan lying
down.
It is a reproduction of the original
photo.
It is a photo of the old JK.
I don't take a lot of photos in the
rehearsal.
I took a lot of photos every day.
It's the same.
It's the early days of ZECKY.
It's Shinjuku-bura.
No, it's not.
It's Nova Studio.
It's Shinjuku-bura.
Sorry.
I'm going to cry.
It's broken.
I saw it.
He said he wanted to go on a tour with
me.
And he moved with the members.
I've been looking forward to the
rehearsal.
We are in the middle of shopping.
At that time, the time machine was
displayed on the float.
Ozeki came to see this.
Sendai.
Ozeki is playing the role of a time
machine.
The setting is that everyone is on the
time machine.
Everyone is here.
Mr. Sugai, who passed away the other
day, came to see me.
I'm going to reenact the "Ganbariki
Arch" at the dome.
It's been exactly a month since you
graduated.
Congratulations on your 7th anniversary!
Thank you, everyone!
This is a commemorative photo for
joining the club.
We are so happy that so many cute girls
have joined us.
Thank you.
Last year, after the tour was over,
we did a live stream on TikTok and
SHOWROOM.
We did it from all over the world.
Oh, that's right.
Let's invite her.
It was an after-live project.
This is Morita and Masumoto after the
Aichi performance.
It was her birthday that day.
Hono also participated in the Aichi
performance.
[The sound is recorded in the room.]
Kira is watching.
It's a binoculars.
I bought binoculars myself.
Did you buy them yourself?
Yes, I did.
I used to use cheap binoculars at first.
I changed them to expensive ones.
This is a video of me chasing Yuka.
Yuka noticed me.
She noticed you a little.
She was happy to see me.
Is this in production?
Yes, it is.
I was chasing her during rehearsal.
This is a rehearsal.
Thank you for your viewing.
She didn't want to be noticed, but now
she is.
She is smiling.
Thank you.
- T-shirt? - Yes, T-shirt.
- What is it? - T-shirt.
- Did you buy it for me? - Yes, I did.
Thank you so much. I'm so happy.
So cute!
Handmade T-shirt
This is cute
Thank you
Hira's cat and Tom
I'm Tom
I'm not Yuka
cute
I'm going to make a T-shirt design
I was told that I was praised
To that store person
You are good at design
I was praised
Thank you
I'm glad
You can wear it tomorrow
I can wear it tomorrow
Thank you
I'm glad
That's all
Thank you
Let's take a picture
I prepared a lot, but I gave it to the
surprise person
Thank you
I'm embarrassed
I didn't say anything
Please give me one of these.
Please wear a microphone until that day.
Even if I watch the rehearsal video
alone, I wear a microphone with my left
hand.
Did you forget?
You're talking from a fan's point of
view, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Please don't forget this.
Foundation
What about eyelashes?
They are different.
We have the same eyelashes.
But I think they are different.
Why are they the same?
I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
I saw it, but I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's shining properly.
To make the mosaic easier
Oh, it's true!
Did you say it's leaking?
Oh, I'm glad
Is it leaking?
What did you say?
It's leaking
It's Oceania
I'll do my best
Ta-da
Are you shooting this?
Yes
If you have a camera, you can come
closer and check
I'm stretching my hair
Oh, really?
If you flip the screen of the camera,
you can see what's on the screen, so
everyone checks it.
I'm going to get sick of animals.
Did you eat beef tongue?
I ate it.
It was delicious.
Thank you very much.
I'm playing with a ball made of peeled
tape.
I'm waiting for the ball.
I can throw the ball well.
I'm waiting for the players.
I'm waiting for the ball.
This is FUJISHI.
Risa graduated from high school and
became a single person.
I'm going to say hello to her.
I'm going to knock her down.
I'm glad to meet her.
It's easy.
Even if I'm told to do it once, I'll
skip it.
I see.
I think this was a rock-paper-scissors
game to decide which position to do on
TikTok.
It's a game where you raise your hand.
It's a game to decide who will go first.
This is Okarina, the master.
If you take a message, you can hear
Okarina.
Please take a message of Onomaki.
I was able to see you off for the first
day at the Buddy's Thank You Festival.
Yes, from the stage.
The members were happy.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've seen
you all up close.
How was it?
There were a lot of fun videos like
yesterday.
I want to take a lot of videos and keep
them.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you again someday.