The theme of this tour is different from
the previous ones.
The theme of this tour is the world-wide
concert hall.
Basically, the concert hall is full of
devices.
There are three boxes.
This is the flower road.
Thank you for your viewing.
In the narration before the concert,
not only in Japanese, but also in
English and Chinese,
I thought a lot about the performance
so that people all over the world can
know more about Sakurazakura 46.
It's a new challenge, so I'm excited.
This time, the number of songs has
increased from last year,
and the content is very realistic.
I'm looking forward to it, but I think
it's a challenge.
It's going to be a complicated staging
like LED with the latest technology.
In a good way, I think there is no tour
that is not like an idol.
I think I have to do my best to keep up
with it.
There is also a piano.
I heard that you imitate playing the
piano.
I can't do it because I can't play the
If I imitate playing the piano, I will
do my best.
I think it will be a live performance
that conveys the feeling of "the
sakurazaka".
I was excited even before I heard
"Orientation" today.
I will do my best.
You go down like this, and when you get
there, you pose like this, and when you
say "Naa" you start.
Like this.
I dance in front of a group of six
people.
I practiced a lot at home, but I wanted
to improve my dancing skills, so I asked
a dancer to teach me.
The first song "Jouken Hansha" was just
released recently, and it's my first
time to perform it.
In addition to that, the first song
means that the heat level will be
decided after the live performance.
I want to show the best of me.
The live performance of "Sakurazako" so
far has been exciting in the second
half.
I'm looking forward to the second half.
This time, the first half was really
intense.
There were a lot of dances and songs for
the first time.
It's a lot of work from the beginning.
I think it's quite difficult to keep my
stamina for the second half, but I have
to dance with all my might.
I think this is the last time.
I'll do my best not to get tired.
I want to do my best in the rehearsal.
I want to do my best not to compromise
and not to regret.
I want to do my best in every detail.
Thank you very much.
It's completely different from what I
imagined when I was in the rehearsal
room and when I actually came here.
It's more complicated and difficult than
I thought, so I'm a little nervous.
If I were a fan, I would have come in
and seen this set and this flower path.
It's so cool that I can cry.
It's really amazing.
I want you to see everything.
I made a mistake.
You're amazing, Akari.
I'm looking forward to it.
The staging is not well-made.
It looks like a construction site.
There are a lot of characters.
The way the screen is used is completely
different depending on the song.
I think you can enjoy it just by
watching the staging.
Nacchan, Nacchan, thank you.
Did you understand?
I'm a little scared.
I'm scared of this.
Let's do a dance battle later.
Don't get closer and closer.
Get closer from the top.
It's a small circle.
Ten-chan, are you tired? Do you think
you can dance?
The number of steps has changed a lot.
I think everyone is full.
We'll do our best.
Thank you for your hard work.
We have no choice but to overcome this.
We'll do our best.
When I saw the stage, I was so excited,
but when we were on stage, there were
times when we bumped into each other
more than we thought.
There were a lot of changes, but it
can't be helped.
I know it's what we're going to do, but
what should I do?
I'm nervous.
I don't know if it's going to go well.
I'm really nervous on the first day.
Osaka! I'm always happy to see such a
big reaction, so this is the perfect
place for the first time.
I'm looking forward to it. I'll do my
best.
Thank you.
Please have a vision that you are
successful.
If you do this well, the audience will
be excited.
And we will move on to the next step.
I think the audience will be drawn to
it.
Let's take care of both the image when
you are excited and when you are
successful.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think it will be a tour that will make
Sakurazaka happy.
Safety is important, but let's do our
best to enjoy it.
Let's do it.
Always bravely, like a cherry blossom,
go ahead.
Just trust yourself.
Sake! Sake! Sakurazaka 46!
Cheers!
Sakurazaka 46
As you know.
[NiziU's first performance at the Tokyo
Dome]
I like the way Ten-chan pulls her hair
back.
And her face when she comes back.
She's always smiling.
I think it's really cool.
Thank you very much.
The choreography was unexpected and
intense, so I wanted to express the
emotions of this song and dance
together.
It was my first performance, so I
wondered how the fans would react.
I thought, "Will the fans follow me?"
After the performance, I heard the
applause of the fans.
I think it's thanks to everyone that we
were able to get through the first half
without any problems.
There were 6 of us, but I was happy to
sing the song "Ikisei" at the end.
The costumes were retro, nostalgic, but
colorful.
We had a concept where we could do a
live performance.
Each of us had the image that we wanted
to wear.
When we came here, everyone looked very
happy, so I was very happy.
Everyone, let's go back to that time!
Everyone in Hiroshima, I love you!
Everyone in Miyagi, I love you!
Everyone in Aichi, I'm back!
Everyone in Fukuoka, I love you!
I hope this concert will be a special
day for all of you.
We've been doing this for two days, so I
hope we can deliver a concert that will
remain in your hearts.
I had a feeling that this tour would be
a concert that I had to grow as a group
and as myself.
Through this concert...
I hope that we can grow as a group and
create a new Sakurazaka.
I wanted to meet you last time
Look, the sky is so bright
The world hasn't changed at all
We're still the same as we were then
The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
The light of the sun, the sunlight
Let's live, let's live, let's live
If you take everything away
It's already too late
It's like a yu-yu
But I can't drink it all at once.
This is a tour-like tour.
It was the first time I saw a tour in
this way.
This time, I had a goal for each
performance.
I changed the clothes of this song since
yesterday.
I thought about how to convey it more.
I thought about how to make it more EMC.
Please look forward to it.
I feel like I'm climbing the stairs one
step at a time.
This is...
How can I say?
This is the first time for me to
experience a tour.
I really think so.
We are the one
I'm scared!
You look cute!
Are you having fun?
I wonder if they are aware of it.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
It's not sad
We'll meet again someday, right? Until
that day
Darling, darling, darling
You're the only one for me
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I can't meet you
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
I'm not sad
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm going to be a good person
You're so shy, Hana-chan.
No, I'm not, really.
No, no, no, no, but you're fine.
With me around...
you're going to be fine.
She's crying at the track,
like she's a man.
I'm not a man.
I'm a man too, you see.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I don't know what to say.
Good morning! We are Sakura Toka 46!
Thank you for your cooperation in
setting up the stage and various
preparations.
We will do our best to give you the best
live performance for two days, so thank
you!
This is the only one here.
I remember it.
It was three years ago.
It was in 2019.
I came here again.
Thank you very much.
It's been three years.
When I first stood here, I thought it
was a horizon.
I couldn't see the end.
I think I grew up because I was still
calm when I got on the train.
I got on the train right away. It was my
first tour.
My legs were shaking all the time.
I think I won't be able to move my legs
this year.
I was very slow on the Takushita train,
but I'm a little faster on the real
train.
So, I was shaking a lot when I got on
the train.
There is a gap between the train and the
platform.
It's scary.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
It's a set train.
It was not a set that fits the song, but
a live performance using LED lights and
lasers.
I think it was a live performance where
we could convey the good points of the
song through various performances.
It was a live performance where we could
convey the good points of the song
through various performances.
This is the first time for me to be a
part of Poetry.
Yuka chose me.
I'll do my best to be a good student.
I'll be a good student until the end.
It's Yuka's position, isn't it?
She did it for me.
I have to do my best!
Why?
It's cute.
Cute.
Left, right.
One, two.
Good.
And get off.
Get off.
Dropped.
Ohhhh.
Day's over.
Yeah?
Thank you for watching!
(Singing)
Is this manual?
Yes, it is.
If it is manual, I want to use it.
I changed the magnification of the
binoculars to 10 times.
What?
Can you see it clearly?
(Singing)
We would like to thank many people for
supporting us.
We will do our best to repay you with
the best live performance.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you.
Surprisingly, I was able to calm down.
Three years ago, I was so nervous.
It was like that, but it was a lot
calmer than that time.
I was able to do my best, but I think it
will be completely different when the
audience enters, so I want to do my best
and prepare for various things.
If you don't have confidence, it leads
to tension. I think there is anxiety and
tension.
This is the 12th performance.
This is what I was doing during this
tour.
I feel like I've leveled up.
I feel like I'm getting used to my body.
I think I'm going to have a lot of fun.
I'm nervous, but I think it's connected
to the earthquake in the 12th park.
I'm nervous, but I'll do my best.
The first time I went to the Tokyo Dome,
I was nervous and anxious, so I couldn't
enjoy it much, so I'd like to enjoy the
scenery of the sakurazaka dome this
time.
It starts with a dirt track, doesn't it?
It's number one, and I've been hearing
it all the time.
I was like, "Oh, my God."
It was big.
There are people on the ceiling.
I was wondering if the people in front
of me were enjoying it.
I was doing my best to get there.
Everyone, where are you?
Tiny Machine, let's go!
Everyone, let's make a big wave!
Are you ready?
Here we go!
It's so cute!
It's beautiful!
You can do it!
I just got my birth certificate.
It was so cute.
I'm jealous of the fans who are pointing
their fingers at me.
When I was walking, I felt like I was
winning.
I feel like I'm getting a bit of a kick
out of it.
I'm really happy that I'm able to
perform with such a fun atmosphere.
It's difficult to do a song for the
first time,
and it's also difficult to organize my
mind,
but I was happy to see Shibai-san having
so much fun.
I felt a lot of emotions.
I thought the captain was amazing.
I was glad that this person was in the
captain's group.
At that moment, I felt a lot of
emotions.
There's something I'd like to tell
everyone.
I'm graduating tomorrow,
so I'd like to leave the next captain to
someone.
Matsuri-chan!
Will you be my captain?
Yes!
That's great! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I'm not used to being the captain that
everyone imagines, or the captain that
Yuka-san was able to be.
However, Yuka-san left it to me, and the
members gave me a very warm look and
words.
There may be some people who get caught
up in it,
but I hope I can become a captain who
can lead a group that can be recognized
even a little someday.
I will do my best. Thank you.
On the other hand, I don't know what I'm
feeling.
If I knew what Yuka-san was doing, I
would know what I was doing.
I think I'm more nervous now.
I want to do my best with everyone.
Everyone told me, "Let's do our best
together."
I'm going to rely on everyone and do my
best together.
Right now, I'm...
The first thing I need to do is to think
about how much I can support Matsuda,
who I've been watching from up close.
Of course, not just me, but all the
second-generation students are saying
that.
We're all second-generation students,
and we're going to support you, so it's
okay.
After I said that, I'm going to support
Captain Matsuda with all the second-
generation students who are here now.
I'd like to continue this cheerfulness
as it is, without a hitch.
I'll take a picture with the last
earphone.
I can do it.
I've been performing in the countryside
for 10 shows, so the direction has
changed a bit, but the framework is the
same, so I'd like to do my best to the
end.
But as a tour, the final is the best.
I want to show everything I've done so
far.
I want to be the last one with Yuka.
I want to do my best without any
regrets.
I can hear the sound.
I'm going to check the keyhole.
I'm Asano Hiro from Sakura Takamoto
Studio.
I'm Tsugaru Yuka.
Thank you for watching.
I'm nervous about my speech.
I have to check my speech.
I have a lot to talk about.
I'm nervous.
This is the last one.
I'm nervous in this place.
I'll do my best not to regret it.
This is the Tokyo Dome.
I want you to show off more.
I want you to think that if you do a pop
dance, the audience's heart will dance.
This is the Tokyo Dome.
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry.
I'm glad that I could play with everyone
today.
I'm glad that I could spend my life with
everyone.
I'm glad that I could play with
I'm looking forward to the live show
tomorrow.
I'm glad to see so many people coming to
see us.
I'm glad to be able to perform with
everyone until the end.
I'm glad to be able to perform on stage
with everyone until the end.
I'm so happy to see everyone.
I'm glad to be able to perform on stage
with everyone.
Let's do our best to give back to
everyone who has supported us so far.
Happy New Year!
I'm going to see Yuka-san.
Where is she?
She's over there.
What is she doing?
She's fixing her make-up.
I'm going to fix my make-up, too.
I'm fixing my make-up.
She's fast.
You can do it.
I can do it.
I can't cry.
You can do it.
I can do it.
OK!
I'm not going to cry.
I feel lonely when I can't meet my fans
in any other way.
I really don't have any grudges against
them.
They always do their best.
They are always supportive.
They always look at me.
Even though there are so many members,
they always look at my individuality.
Thank you.
Sugai-san said, "You can go there."
Sugai-san was the reason for me to do my
best.
From now on, I have to get stronger by
myself.
I want to be a person who can be
independent by following Sugai-san.
"I want to be a person who can be
independent by following Sugai-san."
I don't say yes
I don't shake my head
I've been hesitating until the end.
I thought it would be the last live.
That's how I felt at the end.
But the staff said, "If you do this, I'm
sure you'll be happy."
"You're the only one who can release
this song now."
Goodbye.
I'll do my best if I can make him happy.
I'll make the final decision.
I don't want to do this anymore!
I'm not afraid of the dark
I'm not afraid of being hated
I want to rule everything
I'm not afraid of the dark
I don't want to ruin the future
I'm not afraid of being hated
I'm really, really happy to be able to
celebrate this day with my beloved Team
Sakurazaka at the Tokyo Dome, which was
my dream.
I was able to make cute juniors who have
been fighting together with everyone who
I love, and who adore me as I am.
I'm really sad to say goodbye now.
It was really a relief to see everyone
cheering for me.
I was really happy to be able to accept
my inexperienced self and look forward
to it.
It was everyone who always watched over
me who gave me the opportunity to move
forward to become a person who can
respond to such feelings.
Thank you very much.
And I look forward to your support for
Yuka Sugai.
Thank you very much.
Yuka-san!
My heart is filled with your feelings.
I will continue to be there, so I think
I can continue to take care of that
feeling and do my best.
I really didn't want today to come. I
didn't want it to start, but I'm very
happy to see you look beautiful like
this.
My idol life was the best group where
Sugai-san was the captain.
I think I'm really, really happy.
I will do my best to do what I can.
It may be unfair to say now, but I think
I was able to reduce the burden of Yuka.
I have regrets about my past self.
Thank you so much for being our captain.
Thank you. I love you. Take a good rest.
I can only thank him. He supported me so
much that I can't repay him.
He's the one who's been pulling me all
the time, so I want to send him off with
a smile.
Thank you so much for everything you've
done for me.
I want you to keep up the good work.
It was a live performance that showed
that we were all cheering for each
other.
I thought it was very Yuka-like.
If it wasn't for Yuka, I don't think I
could have performed the song like that.
I don't think I could have performed.
I thought it was a stage for Yuka.
Yua Mikami's first performance at the
Tokyo Dome.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
I don't know why I said that.
I think it's a big event for the group
after Yuka's graduation.
But I think this member can overcome any
difficulties and go forward in any way.
Please continue to support SAKURAZUKA48!
Thank you for your support!
Thank you so much!
I'm going to be a fan from now on.
She was the one who supported me when I
was having a hard time, so I'm very
grateful.
I learned a lot from her.
We have to carry on what she taught us.
We can't let her down.
As a member of SAKURAZAKA, I want to aim
higher and become a group that can
express ourselves to the fullest.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
There are a lot of people around me
because you were there.
Thank you very much.
Are you lonely?
Yes, I am.
Did you concentrate?
Yes, I did.
You are so energetic.
I can do it.
You can do it.
That's your soul.
I am energetic, too.
You are energetic, too.
I see.
I thought this concert was a countdown
to my graduation.
That's right.
Today is the last day. I feel like I'm
having a very strange dream.
Everyone looked so bright and
flamboyant. It was sad to leave one by
one. I felt like I didn't want to leave.
Everyone looked at me kindly. It was
very heartwarming.
When I realized that I was going to
leave at the end,
I realized that I love the members so
much and that I'm irreplaceable.
But I'm the captain, so I want to be the
captain until the end.
I want to do my best to be a force, but
I also rely on the members.
I managed to do it until the end.
I think I was able to run as much as
this.
Thanks to everyone, I was able to run.
I didn't think I'd be able to run in the
final point race,
but I'll do my best.
Even if I get a little dirty,
I'll do my best.
It was my motivation to do it.
I was able to run through the time until
the end.
I was able to finish in the midst of so
many people cheering for me.
I don't think there's such a happy
graduation.
I was able to spend a warm day.
I'm really grateful.
It's been 12 days since the end of the
campaign.
I feel a little liberated.
It's a strange feeling.
The cherry blossoms are gone.
It's sad.
Finally, I'm glad I joined the captain's
group.
A lot of people told me that.
I realized that there is a meaning in
continuing.
I'm really grateful.