Thank you for watching.
- What should we talk about? - It says
"curry".
- I ate curry. - What?
- Huh? - Bonus.
Thank you.
I like butter chicken curry.
- Butter chicken curry? - Yeah.
I'm sorry. I was so curious.
- We ate that the other day. - What?
It's a hamburger stuffed with strawberry
cream.
It's not a hamburger.
It's a fruit sandwich.
I'm not going to talk about anything.
I'm going to relax today.
Are you going to relax?
Hans Inter?
Yeah, Hans Inter.
I thought it wasn't enough.
Isn't Hans Inter cute, too?
Is that so? Shall we do it together?
Whichever is fine with me.
Wasn't there a girl with a twin-tailed
hat when you were a student?
I don't think so.
There was.
There was a girl with a half-twin-tailed
hat.
When I was in elementary school, there
was a girl with a half-twin-tailed hat.
I don't know.
Do you want to answer questions today?
Yes.
Let's answer.
Today is your birthday.
Congratulations.
"Tell us your thoughts on the new song."
Well, I was told not to give away any
spoilers today.
But the new song, "Nagaredama"... No,
it's not "Nagaredama."
- "Saminareyo." - "Saminareyo" is
already...
- I'm sorry, but it's been changed. -
Right, right.
- Shall we talk about it? - Shall we?
- I was really into it. - You were?
I was really into it, and it's today.
If you listen to the lyrics carefully,
you'll be able to feel it.
It's a song that's different from what
you said at the beginning and at the
end, isn't it?
The way it ends is also unique.
That song is good. What kind of dance is
it?
I wonder what kind of dance it is.
I'm really looking forward to the music
video.
Please look forward to it.
The song is...
What is it?
- I'm going to be on the other show. -
Oh, you're going to be on that?
- Oh, you're going to be on that? - Yes,
I'll be on that.
- I'm going to be on that, so I'll be
back. - Yeah.
- I'll be back. - Yeah.
- I love you. I've been saying that for
a while now. - Yeah.
- I love you. - Yeah.
"Please make a heart."
Let's do it together.
We'll win if we do it together.
1, 2, 3.
Is that so?
Let's do it.
Hey, you're betraying me.
1, 2, 3.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it.
1, 2, 3.
Chii will do it.
That's not good.
- Let's play a game like this. - Okay.
Let's play a game with everyone.
Let's say a topic, and if everyone
agrees, we win.
- Okay. - Then...
Please give us a topic.
Wow, there's a mirror ball. Thank you.
Let's take a pose where there's a mirror
ball.
It's a bit difficult for the viewers.
I see, so you want to make a pose that
can be expressed in words.
A pose that I want to take in a
glittering studio with a mirror ball.
I see.
That's good.
Everyone, let's say it together.
One, two.
"Nio-dachi"
Is that what you mean?
No, it's not.
The fact that it matches with the
viewers means that it can be expressed
in words.
I see.
Yes!
"Niwadachi" is the correct answer.
"Niwadachi"
Ah, but pointing fingers up...
Is "Niwadachi" there?
Did you not use your hair?
No.
You were so scared that you said "I want
your left hand" but you only have your
right hand.
What should I do, Fan-chan?
A pose when you're angry.
A pose when I'm angry...
That's good.
Nihon-odachi.
That's not it.
You can't do this with words.
You did it.
Ah, I can't forgive you.
I did it because I thought we would
definitely get along.
Everyone is saying "punpun" and "buu".
I like Nihon-odachi too much.
What should we do next?
- "Pose for when you wake up early in
the morning." - When I wake up early in
the morning.
Let's do it together.
- Ready, set, "Niodachi." - That's not
it.
- I'm just saying what I want to say.
I'm sorry. - Really?
- I'm done. - You're a true Kansai
person.
What is it?
You just sucked all the air in here.
- Today's popular phrase is "Niodachi."
- That's fine.
"Niodachi"
- You're breathing in too much air. -
It's because I talk too much.
- "It's not stretching." - That's right.
- Is there anyone who actually stretches
when they wake up? - What do I do?
I heard that if you stretch before you
go to bed, you can stretch your height.
- Is that so? - I heard so.
Someone said, "#Niodachi."
"It makes you look slender."
- Someone said, "You're stupid." -
That's nice.
- It looks good on you. - Do I look
good? - No, it's okay. Thank you.
- I look good in it, don't I? - You do.
- You look good in it, too. - Thank you.
- We're wearing matching ribbons. -
That's right.
- We're wearing matching twintails, too.
- That's right.
- I just saw a rainbow. - I saw it, too.
- It's beautiful. - Let's drink some
water.
I'm free.
What's for dinner?
I ate something like a hot pot.
- Is that so? - Yeah.
- I bought it. - That's nice.
Please tell me.
- I wanted to match the color of your
stomach. - That's a little scary.
- Some people are asking if the clothes
are the same. - It's not the same at
all.
It's definitely not the same.
- I found a really good one. Let's talk
about Hyogo. - Sure.
This is easy. We're from Hyogo.
- Hyogo is... - Do you have any history?
Hyogo is an octopus.
Speaking of Hyogo, it's shaped like an
octopus.
When we were on the same magazine
together,
we were supposed to take a pose in
Czech,
and I did a Hyogo pose.
You were holding it.
Yes, I was holding it for about three
days.
At that time, we...
I was really shy,
so I couldn't speak at all at that time.
I was like, "What is this?"
At that time, Koike-san was kind,
so I was like, "Oh, this is Hyogo's
pose."
She kindly took a Czech with this.
I see.
I thought about it for 3 days.
After 3 days, I thought about it a lot.
I thought it was amazing.
I thought I had to say it quickly.
I was about a distance away from heaven
and earth at that time.
Kira-chan, who did all the heat shot
experiments, was a fish in the past.
I was surprised.
It's a recent habit.
I forgot to read the comments. I'm
sorry.
I'll read them all.
Which planet?
I can't think of it.
Is oxygen enough?
[Reading comments]
I was waiting for you to stop.
Cute.
[Reading comments]
I can't think of anything. I'm an old
lady.
I'll do it faster.
[Reading comments]
Congratulations! You did well in high
school.
High school?
What did you do in high school?
Me?
When you were a student.
I don't think it was a high school
student-like life.
I didn't really participate in club
activities or school trips.
I didn't participate in school trips
either.
You said something!
I didn't say anything. What was the
reason?
I don't want to go.
I don't want to get sunburned.
I really don't want to get sunburned, so
I won't go.
I didn't want to get sunburned.
Is that the reason?
That's right. I really wanted to look
transparent.
I really don't need any color.
And it's getting lighter, isn't it?
Yeah, it's getting lighter.
Someone asked, "What color is your lip?"
What color is my lip? Pink?
Congratulations on winning first place.
That's amazing. I've been studying for
many years.
For various exams.
"Please tell us about the two of you."
Two episodes?
Kira-chan is...
No matter what it is, I don't say "gion"
or "statatata" when I'm running, but I
say "gion" a lot.
Do you call that an episode?
I feel like I'm introducing Masumoto.
When Kira-chan is smiling, she says "Ni-
cha".
When Koike-san is taking a cute picture,
she says "Ni-cha".
That's so funny.
That's right. That's how you can make
Koike-san's natural smile.
I'm doing my best to say it.
"Ni-cha".
That's how you say it.
What's so funny?
See, everyone's saying it.
They're saying, "Do a weird laugh."
Let's do a weird laugh and say, "If we
get it right, we win."
Here we go.
We got it right.
Let's move on to the next one.
We got it right with "Hayo".
"Hagyo".
"I can't stop sneezing".
When you can't stop sneezing, you have
to push the top of your philtrum.
I see.
I think someone is talking about it.
I think so, too.
"It's peaceful."
It is peaceful.
It's been hurting here for a while.
What's wrong?
My hair is being pulled.
Oh, I see.
Your scalp is tired.
Oh, it's cute.
It's cute.
No, no, no.
Are you angry?
Stop it.
Bite it.
Bite it?
Let's bite each other here.
There are people who say, "Please show
me."
It's cute.
I think you can imagine the delay.
Please look it up.
Bob's delay is really cute.
It's a little too late.
It's pretty late.
Babies...
When you tie it in half...
Do you know what I mean?
Let's have Shiro look it up.
Kina-chan is a baby.
Wow!
My eyebrows are transparent.
Koyake-san's hair is brighter, but it's
not transparent.
I'm transparent.
I don't think there's a lot of bangs.
Everyone has thin bangs, right?
But I didn't cut it down too much.
It's still there, but Koike's bangs are
going up.
Her bangs are growing from here to here.
My middle school teacher told me that.
My middle school teacher said, "Koike's
bangs are growing from here to here."
"Kira-chan's eyebrows are connected."
Who said that?
My bangs are quite short, so it looks
like they're connected to my eyebrows.
I see. It's the same length as your
eyebrows.
That's right.
It's been 15 minutes. I'm done with 1/4.
That's fast.
You're good at calculating.
I'm a genius.
"I'm watching from the Philippines."
Thank you.
"Try standing upside down."
I can't.
Is it okay for me to talk so much?
Thank you for 20,000 viewers. I'm glad.
It's Friday, so you've all worked hard
for a week.
Thank you for your hard work. Please
relax here.
"I'm watching from Kyoto." Thank you. I
want to go to Kyoto.
Kyoto.
What should I do? I really can't catch
up with the comments.
I can catch up with you.
If I move my bangs, it will be Kyoto.
Good evening.
It's my first time to go sightseeing.
What should I do?
What?
It's my first time to go sightseeing.
What should I do?
But...
I just want to relax.
That's right.
Please keep that in mind.
I've said this before, but
there are people who add
a topic to their name.
If it's too long,
I can't read it.
When it pops up,
I can't see the name.
The number of characters is decided.
Maybe.
If it's too long, I can't read it.
I'll be like, "Oh, I'm sorry."
It's simple.
Thank you so much for showing me on the
whiteboard.
We can understand each other.
If it's not a hot topic at all, if you
write, "It's not a hot topic." I'll put
it out.
I don't think Kira-chan will be able to
come out infinitely.
That's right. I've been waiting for the
next person to come.
Because the room is not close at all.
Kira-chan's voice is so cute.
I heard it's fun.
I want to participate.
I thought I'd participate in the
members' meet-and-greet.
I've applied before.
I don't think I can.
We have the same time, so I thought I'd
stop it.
I don't think I can.
I've almost reached the end of my
application.
S-san's.
Do you want to do a push-out match?
All right.
Thank you for watching.
I'm aiming for the counter, so you have
to start from there.
What's a counter?
It's like this.
I see.
Do I have to use only my shoulders?
Anything is fine.
Please don't use your legs.
I'm not using my legs.
Here I go. Ready, go.
I'm trying to feel it.
I made a serious face.
I pray that it will not be an error for
a moment.
Did you see that?
Did you see that timing?
Wow, she's covering her stomach.
She's surprisingly strong.
- My legs are numb. - Your legs are
numb.
- Let's sit on the mountain. - That's a
good idea, isn't it?
That's a good idea, isn't it?
This is so relaxing.
I'm going to start the ventilator soon.
- It's half. - Half?
- Half. - Oh, I see.
Let's read the comments as hard as we
can.
"Oyamasuari"? I can't understand what
you're saying.
- "Oyamasuari". - It's "Oyamasu".
- "Oyamasuari". - "Oyamasuari".
It's "Oyamasuari".
"What's your duo name?" Tsukino-chan,
what's your duo name?
I think Kira-chan has a better sense.
It's decided. It might be a bit long.
We'll announce our duo name.
Here we go.
Hyogo sisters, above -i.
Is it that funny? I'm just kidding.
Above -i, above -i.
I'm just kidding.
Was it funny?
It was funny.
Above -i.
I can think of it right away.
Let's add something.
Let's find something in common.
What do we have in common?
What we have in common is...
We have the same taste in food.
No, we don't.
Dogs and cats are different.
I was surprised.
Do you want to break this?
No, stupid.
There are people who are not good at
this, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to hang it here, right?
It's all right here.
Let's go to the comments.
The name of the combination is Nioh.
It's not bad.
This looks funny.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Bye-bye.
I was watching it with you, but I didn't
see it at all.
I didn't see it.
It's embarrassing.
Hyogo 2/3
Hyogo is a three-member girl group.
Oh, is that so?
But that's what I want to be without
anyone, isn't it?
But it's a great sense.
If everyone gets together, Hyogo will be
over.
That's right.
Thank you for watching.
"Do a "Ni-cha-a-zu""
Stop with the "Ni-cha-a-zu"
"I want to see your ponytail"
No, no, no
Then I'll google "ponytail"
"Ni-cha-a-zu" is dangerous
"Ni-cha-a-zu"
"I'm waiting for your dance stream"
Yes!
I told Fuuka-san, Fuuka-san and
Kobayashi-san do a lot of dance streams,
so I said "I want to dance with you"
Oh, really?
By the way, the name of the stream is "I
taught Fu-chan how to dance"
Oh~
I taught her
I told Fuuka-san, "Let's dance together
on LINE yesterday and today"
I hope we can do it soon
Let's do it together
"I taught Mii-chan and Fuuka-chan how to
dance"
I don't remember at all
"Dead End"?
"Dead End"? It was easy for me to
remember the choreography for "Dead
End".
Yeah, but it was fun to dance to.
Even though it's the chorus, I've
already forgotten it.
"Dead End" was really fun.
I've always liked it.
Yeah, dancing to it was really fun.
Hmm...
Ever since the tour,
I was like, "Ah, this is going to be
fun."
I had a lot of fun with the "Nagaredama"
Really?
It looked like fun
Yes, it ended quickly
This is a "Nagaredama" for those who are
in a hurry
Here you go
No, I was in a hurry
I made a mistake
(Singing)
I don't know what I'm doing.
Was it like this? Not sideways, but
definitely downward.
Like this.
I was so nervous.
I think it was when I was a TV music
producer.
Yes.
Kira-chan was doing this right before
that.
I was so nervous.
It was so funny.
I'm glad.
Oh, no.
It was so funny.
Let's do it in this position.
It's going to be an eco seat.
It's going to be a burden.
It's going to be over in 20 minutes.
It's going to be over in 45 minutes.
You can calculate that much today.
It's not going to be over in 45 minutes.
It started at 15 minutes.
It's 15 minutes, so we have about 30
minutes left.
That's right.
Time flies.
We didn't have that much time.
Someone said we didn't have that much
time.
Was it you, Koike?
Yes.
I made a mistake.
I stopped for a moment.
I was like, "What?"
I made a mistake in my line.
When did you two get along?
When was it?
Wasn't it quite a while ago?
I really remember when you taught me the
choreography before the sun rose.
It was when we were filming the music
video.
It was cute.
The manager said, "Let's dance
together."
You did your best.
I couldn't dance at that time.
Really?
I couldn't do big movements like this,
but now I can.
You're really good at it.
I'm really good at it now. I'm confident
in that part.
Kira and Marino are good at it.
I often watch their dance lessons.
Is it here?
It's really good.
If you remember the first movement you
meet, you can apply it and do a
different dance.
That's right.
It's good.
It's a new thing to learn from the
application.
That's right. If you don't have much
experience, you'll have a lot of first-
time movements.
"Please read the comments." I'm sorry.
I'll ask you a question.
Give me a question.
"Lena's episode." I really like Lena.
Everyone's talking about it. Did you
like it too, Fujii-san?
Yeah, I like it a lot.
Oh, that's right.
I like it so much that I want to play a
prank on the girl I like.
That's what's going on with Lena-chan
right now.
Oh, that's true. I feel like I want to
bully her.
Yeah.
"Hey!"
She's cute when she says that.
I see.
Luna-san...
I really like her profile.
It's so pretty that it makes me want to
touch it.
You want to touch it?
Yes. I wonder if it's real. It's as
pretty as it's made.
I wonder if it's pretty.
"Did you go to see the curtains?"
I went to see it.
Me too.
It was cute.
The moment it started, I thought, "She
must have practiced a lot."
Her vocalization was amazing.
It was beautiful.
Her resonance was amazing.
I shouldn't say it, right?
No, you shouldn't.
I'll say it.
Yeah, that's what it was like.
I thought I had to do my best because
Sugaya-san was doing her best in a
different place.
And she was cute.
She was really cute.
She looked like a doll.
She looked like someone from another
world.
I was a little lonely.
That's true.
But it was good.
I got power.
I saw a new Yuka in front of me.
Thank you.
During this time, Yuka also took a step
forward, and we thought we had to do our
best.
I like Karin-chan.
I like Karin-chan and Rena-chan.
Kira-chan is my little sister.
Inoue-san.
Inori is also my little sister.
We're three siblings.
"Please give us a screenshot time."
It's important.
I have to be careful.
It's the size of your feet.
The size of my feet?
Your feet are bigger than I thought.
Let's say it together.
3.5
Plus 1.
It's 4.5.
Isn't 3.5 pretty high?
It's pretty high.
It hurt so much that I had to go through
it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's cute to put it down.
It's cute no matter what you do.
It's easy. It's easy for anyone.
It's all the same.
Wow, wow, wow.
The place I drew today is Hoya's room.
Oh, really?
I got a call from Hoya.
I bought this about two years ago.
I'm sorry.
- It's different, right? - Yeah.
I made a weird face. What should I do?
One more time.
- Please do it. - You don't want to do
it?
"Yui-chan's performance".
Can you blur it?
- Can you see me now? - I can't.
Is this it?
- I don't think I can do this live. - I
can't do it either.
- It's unfair. - I can only do this.
Let me see that.
I'll show you how I move my chin at high
speed.
Wow.
Huh? My eyes are double.
My chin is going to come off.
Someone said, "Have you ever been to
Okayama?"
We haven't actually been there.
I've been there a while ago.
Did I say that again?
Oh, I see.
"Min-chan, you're so excited."
I'm like this when I'm with Kina-chan.
Have you ever been to Okayama?
I've never been there, but I've heard of
Oen.
Oen, Oen, Oenwa.
It means "I won't forgive you."
Wasn't it "Akan"?
I've heard of Oen.
"Have you ever been to Karuizawa?"
Where is Karuizawa?
Karuizawa...
What prefecture?
I think it's a green place.
Doesn't it look like Hokkaido?
Is it a green place?
She said it's a green place.
Nagano prefecture?
She said it's Nagano prefecture.
Wow!
That's true.
I see.
It's a green place.
"How many prefectures have you been to?"
There are a lot of questions like that.
If I say the places I've been to, I
think I can answer all of them.
I've been to Tokyo, Hyogo, Osaka,
Nagoya, Fukuoka, Yokohama.
Is Yokohama a prefecture?
No, no, no.
That prefecture is...
What was it?
Kanagawa, Saitama.
I think it's Kanagawa.
Oh, Kanagawa.
Please subscribe to this channel.
And Chiba, Hokkaido and... I don't know.
The places I've been on tours.
Me too. I haven't been on a lot of trips
other than that.
But Chiba prefecture is...
Chiba prefecture is a little...
Chiba prefecture is a little... It's
been a little bad lately.
Oh, there's that too.
The place where there's the Fuji-Q that
we met.
Fuji... Fuji-Q.
Oh, it's Onuma-san's prefecture.
- Shizuoka? - Shizuoka, Shizuoka.
- I'll ask a question. - A question.
- "You have a bad tongue." - That's
right, I have a bad tongue.
- You take off your braces and put on a
mouthpiece, right? - I've never done
that.
- That's how you lose your tongue. - Oh,
I see.
"Please go out with me."
"I'm Yamanashi." Sorry, I made a
mistake.
"I'm Yamanashi." I learned a lot.
27,000 people are watching.
"I want a girlfriend like this. Tequila-
chan."
I couldn't read it.
This is the best position. It's so easy.
"I followed you." Thank you.
Thank you.
It smells like food.
Really?
Don't you think so?
Maybe it's because it's hot.
What does it smell like?
It smells fragrant.
No.
What?
From the screen?
Is someone eating something tasty?
"Isn't it burning?"
No, that's the worst.
It might be a sweet smell.
I think it's that.
Someone said it's a macaron container.
- Isn't it that? - Macaron?
Let's do that.
It's 15 minutes now.
15 minutes?
- Shall we do something? - I can't
calculate.
25 minutes.
Let's do something. What do you want us
to do?
Together.
I don't want short hair.
I think it suits you.
I have a high rate of short hair.
I don't cut my hair either.
I'm just reducing the amount.
What kind of short hair do you have?
Like this?
I think it's good. I have that image.
In the old days.
Koyuki dances with her hair.
Really?
Do you know?
I don't know.
In front of here.
1st place.
- In English? - Yes, I shake my head a
lot.
- I think I'm good at showing my hair. -
Really?
If your hair is too long, you look like
you can't meet everyone.
- I'm scared of that. - Do I have to
make my hair dance?
I don't know if you're making it dance.
If it's too long, it'll be a little
slower than your head.
- I was thinking that far. - If this is
your head, it'll be like this.
Since I have long hair, it'll look good
on me.
- If it's this long, it'll be the same
length as your head. - I can do a
ponytail.
Karin-chan is dancing with short hair.
- She's beautiful. - People who dance
with short hair are amazing.
I don't have a body yet.
What?
I'm sorry.
- What did you say? - The screen froze
for a moment.
- I think it's over there. - Isn't it
amazing, Kira-chan?
I don't know if it's me, but it's like a
miracle.
Did it stop? Did it stop? I'm sorry.
What's moving? Oh, it's stopped.
It's stopped at a great place.
Is it stopped?
It's completely silent.
Why?
Oh, it's stopped.
It's stopped now.
It's completely silent.
I'm scared.
I can hear you, I can hear you.
"I'm glad, I'm sorry. I'll do something
for you, Ten-chan."
Isn't that amazing, Kira-chan? It's a
miracle.
I really like Ten-san's singing style.
I get it, I get it, I get it.
It's a melody.
That's right, that's right.
I don't know.
I was watching the recording of that
part, and I thought it was really hard
to make a good sound, but Ten-san was
doing his best many times, and he was
getting better and better, and I thought
that there was a way to absorb it and
apply it.
Kira-chan is good.
What?
Kira-chan.
Is it a song?
Yes.
Hey.
I'll do my best.
I like Koyuki-san's song.
It's definitely a lie.
Everyone made fun of me with my lines.
"Datte yaranakattara"?
Okay, I found it.
Koike-san's... Koike-san's "Zangai"
is...
I think it's over there.
"Datte yaranakattara"? Please say it.
I can't read it.
"Are you enjoying the live?"
I really like that.
"Yaranakattara"?
It feels like "Yaranakattara".
I change it every time.
If I talk, I forget to read the
comments.
I can't smile.
I love you.
What do we like about each other?
First of all, I like how you look.
No way!
I like people with bright hair.
I also like people with long hair.
I like all of you, Kira-chan.
Do you want to be me?
Yeah.
I want to be inside your head.
Let's act like we've switched places.
No way.
I don't want to be in the middle.
If you don't do it, you'll be sad.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
You're messing with me. I'm not messing
with you. I don't like that cute voice.
I'm really bad at English.
I'll introduce myself in English for
those who are watching from overseas.
That's love.
I'm not good at "That's love" dance.
Let's do a live.
Are you going to dance?
No, I can't.
How was it?
It was originally both arms, wasn't it?
No, it was one arm.
It was originally both arms.
It suddenly changed to one arm.
It was definitely both arms.
It was both arms.
It was both arms for the first time.
It was definitely both arms.
No.
Before it was released, it changed to
"Freelance".
- Oh, really? - That's right.
I watched a lot of videos of "Freelance"
and practiced a lot, but it's scary!
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
But I was looking for someone from the
members to contact me.
Has anyone seen it?
I'm sure it was a hand from both hands.
- It really looked like it! - No way! I
don't remember at all!
But I'm sorry if I'm wrong at all.
I'm going to call the insurance company.
I was nervous.
I sang the 2nd verse of the A melody.
I'm really good at it.
This?
I sang it like this.
I'm sorry.
I sang Kira-chan's and Sonia-chan's...
I did it many times.
I'm sorry.
It's a very special day.
I bring it here all the time.
It's difficult to cross my legs.
I think I'm doing it while looking at
the number.
It's here.
Thank you for 30,000 people.
I had time before.
It's too Deja Vu.
It's close.
I can't read it.
Isn't my bangs beautiful?
Beautiful.
I can't read it.
I'm sorry.
I like Hansen.
Baseball?
I don't know much about baseball, but I
think it's really amazing.
My dad used to watch it a lot.
I used to think it was really fast.
It's amazing.
I want to watch it too.
It's called Kawaii Medane.
I heard it's called Kawaii Medane.
"Can you dye your hair black?" I can't
dye my hair black.
It looks better when it's black.
That's right.
When it wasn't bright, I dyed it with an
iron.
And then I dyed it black. I thought it
was really cute.
Really?
No matter how many times I dyed it
black, the iron would come off.
It's pretty dark.
Does that mean it's easy to get damaged?
That's right.
Poor thing.
That's why I go to the beauty salon and
say, "I don't need any damaged parts."
I don't need anything like this.
I don't need this.
I don't need any damaged parts.
Then it's shorter than it used to be.
It says it looks good on me.
I think it'll look good on you, too.
It doesn't look good on me. The contrast
doesn't match.
It's like it's going to pop when it's
lit.
It says to use a high-speed iron.
High-speed iron?
I'm fast at ironing.
But you look fast.
It's hot if you do it slowly.
I've smoked before.
You can't.
I was surprised.
I'm scared.
It's going to melt.
It says I like half-body and half-neck.
Half-body and half-neck.
My neck is really good.
How is it? Please try it.
I can't do it without this.
Let's go.
I'm scared.
I'm scared when I look at it with my
right eye.
Let's start from the right or left.
Let's go.
One, two.
You know how Arion moves in the
sunlight?
Yeah.
Oh, Arion moves like this.
Right?
They say they want to see Sonia.
Kira-chan's version of "Hitori no BAKURU
UUUMU NI"
Hitori, what was it? Ah, I couldn't do
it.
I think only Koike-san can do this.
I don't know how to do it, so I'll do it
in your version.
I'll do Koike-san's version first.
She's laughing a lot.
I'll do it with my real voice.
That's how it is. It's not a song like
"Cappy Cappy".
I almost cried so many times.
It's a good song, isn't it?
I almost cried when we did "Anniversary
Live".
I think I made a terrible face when I
remembered that.
But it wasn't on the screen.
That's good.
I forget that I'm being watched.
It's okay.
"Don't cry, it hurts."
"I want to hug you."
You want to hug me?
I want to hug you.
Baby.
Say "Thank you" to the fans.
(Cute Roda)
(Roda and Fukuhara's weird laughter)
(Kotone is laughing so hard that I can't
keep my eyes off it)
(She's too cute!!!)
(Take a look at her face!)
(Thank you for watching!)
(And thank you for watching until the
end!)
This is my pot.
It's cute.
- It's already 4 minutes. - That's fast.
- We only have 10 minutes left.
- Did you enjoy it? - What do you want
me to do?
- I'm sorry, I'm talking to myself. -
You've been working hard for a week,
so I wanted to cheer you up.
You're so nice.
- You're so nice. - I'm nice?
- You invited me yesterday. - It was
sudden. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
- Let's heal together. - I'm relieved.
- What's for dinner? - Let's decide. How
about udon?
- I want to eat curry udon. - Curry
udon? I ate curry today.
You're cheating.
- I'm lonely. - Come here.
- What's wrong? - Come here, Numa-chan.
- We gave Numa-chan a bag. - Yes.
- It's a duck bag. - I'm so happy.
- But it doesn't have a phone in it. -
It doesn't?
- The bag we bought together before... -
Popo-chan.
The bag we bought together didn't have a
wallet in it.
So we gave it to her as a gift.
But it doesn't have a wallet or a phone
in it.
If it's a GU, I'll hide it.
That's a pretty small one.
I forgot to check the size.
There are people who don't have a lot of
luggage.
It's fashionable to have a minimum
number of people using it.
It says, "Don't carry too much."
Of course.
I have a reason to give it as a gift.
I got it, too.
What did you get?
POMU
I really don't want it to shrink. I
don't want it to fade, so I didn't wear
it at all.
I'll give you a present.
I want to leave it as it is. I'm afraid
it's going to shrink.
I should have given you a present for
your appreciation.
Thank you. I wear it once in a while.
It's important to say a word of comfort.
Thank you for your hard work today.
What do you mean by a word of comfort?
Thank you for watching until the end.
"I'm watching this on Niwadachi."
Oh, Niwadachi?
Thank you for your comments.
"Please say something."
Let's read the comments.
Thank you for your comments.
"I want to come and play."
"Akirako is getting married."
"She's getting proposed."
"I've been cooking lately."
What?
"You want to eat my cooking, right?"
I want to eat it.
I made a mistake.
I wanted to feed Onuma-san, so I made it
for him.
I'm glad.
I made him eat as much as he could.
Onuma-san made it for me, so I don't
want to leave it.
He eats a lot.
I forgot to read the comments again.
"It's cute."
"Strawberry?" That's right. I ate 2 cups
of rice and 2 cups of strawberries.
One cup is for one person.
"Are you looking at the letter?" I am.
I read it a lot.
Do you read it before going out?
I read it, but I can't read it in real
time.
I can't read it in real time, but I read
it every 2 or 3 days.
I read it when I get home.
I read it before going out.
I read it every day.
"I finished my part-time job. Good job."
Good job.
I've never had a part-time job before.
I've worked at a cake shop.
"I have to send a letter again."
Please send it.
"What kind of dance shoes are you
wearing?"
Dance shoes?
I usually wear white ones.
White ones.
We look similar, don't we?
But we're definitely different.
"I got a present from Sugaya for two
years."
I got a present from Sugaya for two
years.
I got sneakers for my birthday. That's
the only thing I can't dance to.
Dasu-chan?
Huh?
Dasu?
This way?
Eh? D'Arcy?
No!
I was asking about the brand.
D'Arcy?
That's the one I told you about last
year.
This time it's CHECK?
That's right.
I don't know what brand it is.
But it's really cute.
You can hug it for the first day and put
it on the next day.
That's right.
Mirin, this...
"I'm doing my best to join Sakura Toka."
Please!
I'll be waiting.
I'm looking forward to seeing my
juniors. I don't know when, but I can't
wait to see my juniors.
I'm sure they'll be cute. I love younger
people.
It might be three years from now.
I want about 32.
I'd like to teach a girl who's not good
at dancing.
"I know! You can't do it, can you?"
People who are not good at dancing.
It's hard for people who really can't do
it.
It's a lot of time, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it.
"It's a fun birthday. Can a man go into
the cherry blossoms?"
- Can you? - What?
"Can a man go into the cherry blossoms?"
But you can talk to them.
You can wear a mii-guri.
"How many juniors do you want?" I want a
lot.
- Let's do it at the end. - I don't know
when, though.
It's about the future.
- Someday. - Did you read a lot today?
I'm really sorry I'm an old lady. I
really couldn't read it.
I'm sorry I've been walking around. My
legs hurt.
Thank you for watching a lot.
How many minutes? It's scheduled to be
up to 15 minutes, right?
4 minutes left.
What's upper?
Upper?
- It says "Woof woof". - It's like this,
right?
- It's an upper. - Doesn't it mean that
it's purring?
Ah! I don't get it!
- It's like it's hitting itself. -
"Ioki-chan".
- It's so cute! - It's like Nagisaka-
san's movement.
- It's so cute. - It's so cute.
It's so cute. I like it.
- I like Satsuki-chan and Ogawaya-chan.
- They're all small.
Yeah, they're all cute.
- I want our juniors to be like that. -
"Please do a "goi-goi-su" with the two
of you." What's a "goi-goi-su"?
- What is it? - I don't know.
- Isn't it like, "It's amazing that
you're doing it backwards?" - Is it
that?
- It's like a comedian doing a "goi-goi-
su." - "Goi-su, goi-su."
- I don't know how to do it at all. -
What should I do today?
For those who couldn't read it all, I'm
sorry.
Thank you for all the comments.
For the 35,000 viewers, thank you.
Thank you, Kira-chan, for showing up
today.
Are you okay? I wanted to hear more of
your voice.
No, I usually don't talk like this, so
my throat is tired.
Really?
My throat hurts.
I think the fans want to see your cute
side.
I'll show you my cute side.
Kira-chan's cute side...
You want to see something like this,
right?
You want to see it, right?
"Koike-san's cute hand"
Hey, listen! My pinky and index
finger...
That's onee-san's finger.
Onee-san's finger is really long.
That's what I noticed recently.
That's all.
Yui-chan said that my little finger and
ring finger are long.
Show me your ring finger.
That's all.
Yui-chan is like a baby.
That's 14 minutes.
Is my face okay?
Maybe my fingers are long
Not at all
This is Sonya
Hey, hey, the lighting here is making
our faces look dark
If you do this, our faces will look
really dark
Come watch the stream again sometime
Promise me you'll wear a hood at the end
I won't
That's right
I'll wear a hood
Let's say goodbye
Thank you so much for coming to see us
today
Thank you so much
We were just chit-chatting
But thank you so much for watching
Thank you for your hard work for the
past week
I guess
See you
Please stream again
I will
Please come to see us
Please come
Let's talk
Bye-bye
Thank you so much
Thank you
I'm going to sleep a lot today
How do I turn this off?
Thank you so much for watching
See you again