Everyone, thank you for the encore.
And everyone who came to the venue
yesterday and today.
And everyone who is watching the live
broadcast.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's right.
I've been active for 7 years, and I've
experienced a lot of things.
I've experienced a lot of happy things,
sad things, happy things, and fun
things.
I've had a lot of hard times, and I've
had a lot of hard times.
I had the opportunity to experience it.
There were a lot of times when I wanted
to run away, but at that time, I turned
around again and pushed my back, and the
presence of everyone who came to see me
was really, really big.
It's been about half a year since I
announced my graduation and I've been
trying to have a lot of fun so that I
can be more and more happy with the
members and myself until the graduation
concert.
The more I look back on my memories, the
more I remember the activities I've done
so far.
So I don't want to be apart from them.
That's how much I love the group.
I felt it once again.
Well,
all the first-year students who have
worked so hard with me so far,
and the second-year students who have
grown up so well,
I feel relieved when I see them.
I graduated today because I thought I
could graduate.
I'm really proud to be in a group that I
want to be proud of.
From now on, I'm going to take a new
path.
Even if I take a different path, I feel
like I can proudly say that I was in
Sakurazaka.
For the past 7 years, I've been able to
spend a lot of precious time and moments
with everyone.
I'm really, really happy about that.
I'm filled with gratitude.
Please continue to support Sakurazaka46
and Watanabe Risa.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
Thank you for the encore.
Thank you.
I realized again that I would really
graduate if I saw Lisa's beautiful
sleeping dress.
Now that I've heard Lisa's wonderful
speech, I'd like to hear the impressions
of the other members.
Rina-chan, how was it?
Through today's live performance, I was
able to hear Keyakizaka-san's speech.
In the second single "Sekai ni wa
aishikanai"
Lisa became the front member for the
first time.
When we were shooting the MV,
we were crying like "I can't lip-sync"
I remember that we were all looking at
each other.
Even though there were times like that,
today we were able to work as a center
for several songs.
I thought it was really cool to be able
to start with Lisa's center song and end
with Lisa's center song.
I thought it was amazing that I became a
completely different person from the
first time I met her.
Fuu-chan is full of tears.
I'm not crying.
You're already crying.
Fuu-chan.
Fuu-chan is close to us.
We've done a lot of showrooms together.
I felt like we were spending a lot of
time together.
How do you feel about today?
I decided not to cry on stage.
I'm not going to cry.
I spent time with Lisa.
Fuu-chan.
The 7 years I spent with Ryo were really
fun.
There were only really fun things.
So I'm really full of gratitude.
I thought about it, but I forgot.
That's how I feel.
It's been about 3 weeks since the last
time we met, and she said, "It's only 3
weeks from now, so let's just have fun
and make good memories."
We've never done a showroom together,
but we've done it so many times in the
last few weeks.
It was fun.
I just want Lisa to do a lot of things
she wants to do and have fun.
It was fun, but I had more and more fun
memories in my mind, and I thought, "Oh,
I don't want it to increase any more."
Really, when there are a lot of groups
and things don't go well, I'm always the
axis of the group.
They kept standing up for me and didn't
leave any space for me to do other
activities.
I'm sure, as I said earlier, there were
a lot of members who were saved by the
fact that they kept standing up for me.
That's why I'm really grateful.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
There were a lot of things.
As a first-generation student, I have a
lot of feelings for 7 years.
I have a lot to feel.
Can I ask you something else?
Ose-chan.
Well, thanks to Lisa going to the group,
I've been able to have a lot of fun
every day.
At first, I didn't think we'd get along
this well.
We're like that kind of friends.
I'm very happy that there are more
people I love, and I'm proud of it now.
But really, for the past seven years,
it's been a lot of motivation for me,
and in fact, it's good for my juniors to
take care of me.
I'm very happy that there are more
people I love, and in fact, it's good
for my juniors to take care of me.
I've learned a lot from Lisa, so I want
to continue to remember what I've
learned, and I don't think I've had much
time to myself until now, so from now
on, I'm really going to focus only on
myself.
I want you to do what you like so much
that you can travel the world.
And I look forward to working with you
in the future.
Thank you.
I'd like to ask everyone, but I'd like
to ask Yui for the last question.
No, but I did this performance today,
and until a while ago.
I didn't feel it at all, but when I
heard this speech, I thought that Lisa
would be gone from tomorrow, and it was
really strange, and it was natural that
she was close to me, so I can't believe
it yet.
For me, Lisa has always been close to me
in terms of position, and she's really
close to me.
But since I became Sakurazaka, I've been
supporting her as Shinmei, and I've had
a lot of responsibilities,
so we're kind of... I don't know.
That's right.
I felt a bit of responsibility.
I wonder if there was something that
these two felt about each other.
I wonder if Lisa feels the same way as I
do.
I was on stage thinking that.
I was saved because of Lisa's presence.
I felt the strength of having someone
who feels the same way as me.
I'm so grateful. It's so sad that it's
going to be gone from now on, but I hope
we can continue to do our best in our
respective places.
Let's do our best.
Thank you.
I was looking at her from behind.
It's a little lonely.
But really, Misa has been a big presence
that has led the group since she became
Sakura.
And I myself was really saved.
If Misa doesn't hunt outside anymore,
I'm really lonely.
I'm so lonely that I'll probably go
home.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
That's about it.
We were able to talk about everything.
Lisa was there, and she made us laugh.
She made us laugh, so we were able to do
a lot of things.
It's like, "Don't go."
I think everyone feels the same way.
Thank you to all the PARTY's who
supported us.
I think that's how much I feel for Lisa.
I'm so happy and grateful that we were
able to have a wonderful live
performance that Lisa came up with.
I don't want this time to end, but can I
show you a few more songs?
Thank you.
Well then, let's start with this song!
Ah!
What is this song?
It's been a while!
It's good!
It's really good!
It's like I'm being kissed by someone
somewhere
I don't care about the size of today
I said that, but why can't I calm down?
I'm using my smartphone while the screen
is still on
When did my heart close?
It's full of scars of love
I want to find someone somewhere
I can't accept being forgiven
I won't run in the waves
The water in the sea is already cold
The waves and my feelings
Are still the same as that summer
Let's watch it forever
What is this song?
It's my favorite!
I met you and found love
Finally, I realized something important
I don't know how I've lived all this
time
Where do I want to go next?
What I strongly wish for in the future
Is the footprints that are not here
I brought sunflower seeds
Let's plant them in the soil on the
pillars
Let the flowers bloom someday
I'll tell you where the sun is
Don't forget the blue sky
I've been on the phone for a long time
I've been coughing all the time
I suddenly became worried
The more I have to live far away
Is the dream so important?
But I can't see
I won't kiss you because the wind is
reflected
I made you zero
I forced a kiss
I want you to go home with me
But I want you to make my dream come
true
I saw the blue sky a little
The blue sky is different somewhere
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes
Thank you
I love you
Someone told me something
I can't move from here
Because I love this place
Now I'm standing on my own feet
To the limited land
Many people have come
I tried to fight many times
The boundary line will disappear someday
Even if there is not one thing
I believe in
We will understand each other in the end
The sun is always
I don't choose people who look up at the
sky
Equally love and warmth
It gives me
Even if the heat of sadness is weak
While shining far away
I'm nodding to that prayer
Which one came first
It doesn't start even if you raise your
voice
Recognize each other's place
It's good to face each other
If you can do something somewhere
By coexisting
There is nothing to forget
Where are you two
You can talk to each other
Even if the pronunciation of love is
different
I can be kind
Because we are the same humans
The sun is just shining
I smile at people who look up at the sky
Just existing in this world
I have hope
Even if the long night is dark
The only way to fill the loneliness
Is to live without hesitation
A new wind has blown through and opened
The last thing was gone
Freedom has awoken
The night is about to dawn
Something will change
The beautiful morning glow that gathers
Come on, let's all look up
The sun is always
I don't choose people who look up at
this sky
Equally love and warmth
It gives me
Even if the thick clouds of sadness are
broken
While shining far away
I'm nodding to that prayer
So, in the encore
All the songs of the unit "Aozora" and
"Marie"
Will be played on the medley
And "The Sun Doesn't Choose People Who
Look Up"
We've performed many times.
We've performed "Aozora" and "Marin"
many times.
"Aozora" is different.
We've performed it many times.
It's been years since we performed
"Wareta Sumaho".
We've performed it many times.
We've also proposed "Aomari" medley.
We've performed "Aozora" many times.
We performed all four songs of "Marie"
in a medley form.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you very much.
It's been a while since we've done this,
so I'm happy.
You're happy? Thank you.
I'm happy that you said you wanted to
sing with us.
Thank you.
We sang together at the end, and it
became a good memory.
I won't forget this.
It was fun.
Thank you.
And this is the last one, so I'd like to
hear what the other members think.
Matsuri-chan.
Yes.
What did you think of Captain's Matsuri-
chan today?
That's right. This day came so quickly.
It's so sad that it's almost over.
I said it yesterday, but I think it was
a live performance that was really Lisa-
like.
I personally think that Lisa is a very
cool person with a great heart.
She always has a strong back and pulls
everyone.
I've only seen her strong back, but when
I saw her back, I realized that she was
a really cool person because she worked
so hard and tried so hard where she
couldn't be seen.
I think that's why we, the members, and
the fans love her so much.
Thank you so much for giving us so many
things,
such as fun memories and things that
we've seen and things that Lisa-san has
shown us.
I really want to cherish them in my
heart from now on.
Lisa-san, thank you so much for making
us laugh and giving us so many things.
Thank you.
Thank you so much. I love you.
Lastly, how do you feel today, Lisa?
I feel like this day has finally come.
I'm so happy that I was able to spend my
graduation day with so many people.
This is not a farewell, so let's meet
again somewhere.
I will do my best so that we can meet
again, so let's meet again. Thank you
very much.
So, now that we're done, let's say our
goodbyes.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let's do it again.
Now that we're done, let's say our
goodbyes.
Yes.
Let's do one last song.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Everyone, please play the song.
Everyone, let's play "Towel" one last
time.
"Dangerous Plan"
Everyone, let's spend the last day of
the resort with a smile!
Everyone, can you laugh without regret?
Everyone, make some noise!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
"It's a quiet song"
That's what people say
But you don't understand that kind of
song, do you?
The key is to hide your weakness
What kind of girl am I?
I'm looking forward to it
Everyone, let's spend the last day of
the resort with a smile!
Everyone, can you laugh without regret?
Everyone, make some noise!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Everyone, take this!
"Come on, let's start the challenge!"
Everyone, shoot the missile!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Let's get dirty with our own hands
It's not tomorrow, it's tonight
Let's always be our own selves
The train that took me to my destination
Let's wander around the world
Because there's no tomorrow
I'll draw a new one
If you think about it, it doesn't look
like you
I've always relied on myself
That's right, I want to be like a flower
I'll draw a new one
I don't know where I'm going with my own
hands
But I'll sing a song that no one else
can hear
Then let me dance here
Then I'll sing my own song
I'm not too shy to say I'm a girl
Let's dance and enjoy
Look at me, let's untie the string
I want to be free
I was just a kid
But now I'm an adult
I have the freedom
I'll forget what I've been protecting
If it's summer, let's go to the beach
Let's go to a new place
Let's grow up and have fun
Let's fall in love, fall in love
It's not summer, high-five!
Yeah, high-five!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's have fun
Yeah, yeah!
I realized that I couldn't use it
I didn't have any positive thoughts
Our summer relationship
It's not easy, it's not easy
I don't want to lose to the sun
That's shining in front of me
Let's go to the hot springs
Let's go to the beach
Let's fall in love
Let's leave our school uniforms and love
cards
And change in the bathroom at the
station
It's not summer, high-five!
Yeah, high-five!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's fall in love, fall in love
It's not summer, high-five!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's fall in love
Yes, once again
Thank you for coming to the graduation
concert of Melissa Watanabe
And thank you for streaming
And I hope that you will have a lot of
happiness and smiles in the future
And although Lisa graduates
Mayumi as Sakurazaka46 will continue
I will continue to treasure what Risa
has left for me,
and I will continue to climb higher and
higher, aiming for a higher place.
Please continue to support Risa
Watanabe, Sakurada, and 46.
That's all!
We are 46!
Thank you!
Wow!
Risa, did you have fun?
Thank you!
Yes.
I would like to go to the second floor.
Wow!
Thank you everyone for preparing in such
a short time.
Departure.
Wow!
Thank you!
Hello!
I'm going up.
I can see it clearly until now. Thank
you very much.
Thank you.
Yubihato!
Thank you!
Punch me!
Let's go to the other side!
Thank you!
Punch me!
It's a memorial book! Thank you!
Yubihato!
Thank you!
Heart!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching the live stream!
Let's meet again!
Thank you!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
When did we do this live?
Thank you very much!
I love you, Lisa-san!
Thank you!
I love you!
I was surprised!
Lisa-san!
Yes!
I don't know if you remember, but when I
was full, you asked me, "Are you okay?"
Lisa-san!
Thank you!
I'm not okay!
You don't have to say you're okay!
I'm still doing my best!
Thank you, Lisa-san!
Thank you!
I love you!
Thank you! I love you!
Please make me laugh a lot from now on!
I love you!
Thank you!
I'm happy!
Yay!
Thank you!
I love you!
I hope we can be together!
Let's match!
Thank you!
Thank you for everything!
I love you!
Thank you!
You're so cute!
I've always admired you!
I want to be like you!
I love you!
Thank you!
Thank you for saving my heart over and
over again!
I'll always love you!
Thank you!
There were so many times when I couldn't
be without you!
Thank you so much!
I love you!
Thank you!
You're so cute!
Karin-chan, you're so cute!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Thank you for always looking into my
eyes and listening to me!
I'll always love you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for always messing
around with me and saying a lot of nice
things to me.
I love you.
Thank you.
When I sing the first and second
singles, I sing a lot in the position
next to me.
Thank you for supporting me.
I really love you.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation,
Risa.
I've always admired you. I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Risa.
Den-chan.
Onee-chan.
Don't stop.
Do your best.
You're cute.
I'll do my best, too.
Thank you.
Rina-chan.
Thank you for making me laugh for 7
years.
Thank you.
Will you continue to date me?
I will.
Thank you.
I love you.
I'm very lonely, so let's meet every day
from tomorrow.
I love you.
Let's keep in touch.
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing me tissues no
matter how many times I spilled food or
drinks.
Thank you.
Don't spill it again.
I won't.
I love you.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work for 7
years.
Thank you.
See you.
Was it fun, Risa?
It was fun.
That's good.
Thank you.
Risa-chan.
Thank you for helping me when I was
having a hard time.
And thank you for your many smiles.
Thank you, Hame-chan.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work for 7
years.
From now on, please take care of
yourself and live with a lot of fun and
smiles.
Yes.
Next is Aoi-chan.
Risa, thank you so much.
Thank you for always helping me.
From now on...
From now on, please be happier.
And please be my friend forever.
Of course.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I always miss you.
Please talk to me all the time.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Right?
Have fun.
Thank you so much for supporting me for
7 years.
Thanks to you, I'm here today.
I think I was able to welcome the day.
Thank you very much. I love you all.
Let's meet again. Thank you.
Thank you very much.