"Sakurazaka46"
Nice to meet you, everyone. We are...
Today...
Thank you for coming to Sankisei
Omotenashi-kai.
We will do our best to make you remember
us as much as possible.
Thank you.
Now, I would like to call the person who
will be the host today.
It's Yumeka Shoji.
Nice to meet you.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
I'm Shouju Meka, voice actress, and I'm
in charge of narration in "Sakurazaka".
Today, I'd like to help with the
progression of this stage.
Everyone, please take care of me until
the end.
Thank you.
Thank you, Se-chan.
First of all, congratulations on joining
Sakurazaka46!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
What do you think of this view?
Kojima-san.
Yes, I'm Kojima.
Well, I'm very moved to be here.
We were very nervous backstage,
but the fans welcomed us so warmly,
so I'm having a lot of fun now.
It's warm, isn't it?
I think this is the first time you've
seen such a wonderful view.
How about you, Murai-san?
Yes, I'm Murai Yu. Nice to meet you.
I'm so happy.
It's my first time.
I'm so happy to be able to meet BUDDIES
today.
When I pushed the button earlier, I felt
like I was going to cry.
I look forward to working with you
today.
I'm sure you're all a little nervous.
BUDDIES, including me, are very kind
people.
Right, everyone?
So I hope everyone can relax and run
through with a smile.
Let's all have fun with a smile today!
Yes!
Today, we have prepared a variety of
songs, dances, and various projects to
let everyone know a little bit about the
charm of the 11th generation of 3rd
generation students who have newly
joined SAKURAZAKA46.
I hope you enjoy seeing Ui Ui Shi, which
can only be seen today, until the end.
Before we go to the first project, I'd
like to hear your enthusiasm for today.
First of all, Odakura-san.
I'm Reina Odakura.
Today, for the sake of today, all the
3rd Gen students have worked hard,
so for the 3rd Gen students and BUDDIES,
I want to make it a memorable stage.
I want to get excited. Thank you.
Let's ask one more person.
How about Yamashita-san?
Thank you.
I'm very nervous today, but I've been
practicing a lot with the 11th
generation, so I'll do my best to
entertain everyone today.
Please.
Yes, let's get started.
First of all, it's a 2-minute show of
Sakura Saka46's 3rd generation, which
contains the individuality of 11 people
in 2 minutes.
Here you go.
"Sakura Saka46"
Rika Ishimori
I'm Rika Ishimori from Gunma Prefecture.
Today, I'm going to wear a handmade
apron and make omelette rice.
Let's get started!
First, I'm going to mince the
ingredients.
If you cut it like this,
I like to put sausages in omelette rice,
so I'll cut the sausages too.
Here's what I cut and stir-fried like
this, so I'll use this.
And I'll stir-fry the ingredients and
this rice together.
Thank you.
Wow, it smells good.
I'll fry it with salt, pepper and
ketchup.
Does it smell good?
I'm glad. Thank you.
And here is the fried one, so I'll use
it today.
I'll crack an egg.
Wow!
Thank you.
I couldn't break it with my hands, so I
broke it with both hands.
And here's the mixed one, so I'll use
this one today.
I'll spread the butter.
I'm going to put it in.
Which do you like, soft-boiled eggs or
hard-boiled eggs?
I like soft-boiled eggs.
So I'm going to make soft-boiled eggs
today.
Stir it hard.
It's looking good.
Can you smell it?
Thank you.
I'll serve it like this.
It's done.
I want to be an idol who can make
everyone smile.
I will do my best so that I can become a
better person.
Please enjoy it after this.
It was Rika Ishimori.
I'm Riko Endo, a 17-year-old high school
second-year student from Chiba
Prefecture.
Today, I'm going to perform "Clarinet",
which I've been doing for three years as
a junior high school singer.
Please be healed by my performance.
[Music]
[Applause]
That's all for today.
Everyone, please enjoy it with all your
might.
That's all, I'm Riko Endo.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Reina Odakura, a third year high
school student from Tokyo, and I'm 18
years old.
Today, I would like to introduce two
things I like.
The first is the violin.
Today, I'm going to play a song by
Sakurazaka.
I would like to play only a little.
"Song of the Sea"
Thank you very much.
The second one is golf.
I joined the golf club after I entered
high school.
Today, I wrote my autograph on the ball.
so I'd be happy if you could accept it.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to hit it.
"One more time, please!"
"I'm going to shoot."
"Thank you!"
"Let's have fun today!"
"This has been Reina Otakura!"
"One more time, please!"
"Everyone, good evening!"
"I'm a second year high school student
from Nagano prefecture."
I'm Nagisa Kojima, 17 years old.
I played the piano in the snow in the
VLOG of Hirome's video
Today, I would like to play a song of
Sakurazaka
What song do you think I will play?
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy.
"Sakurazaka"
Thank you very much, everyone.
That was Nakisa Kojima.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Yamaguchi Ken.
I'm Ari Taniguchi. I'm 17 years old and
I'm from Tokyo.
Today, I'm going to play the guitar.
"Can This Pain End?"
Why are we staring at each other here?
You may have thought it was a strange
thing
"Can This Pain End?"
I was played by chance
It's not a reason.
Even though there are many people in the
wide world,
sharing the same time
It's a waste of time to clean it up with
a miracle
Emotions that have lived longer than
fate
Why? Why?
I realized for the first time that I
don't need words
If you start talking about love even a
little
The serious feeling of "I love you"
It's leaking from here
I can't feel each other
rather than the unknown passion running
away
Even if it's objective, it's because I'm
here
Why is what's important important?
No matter how much I think
I love you freely
Thank you very much.
Please continue to entertain us after
this.
That's all. I'm Airi Taniguchi.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, welcome to Omotenashikai.
I'm Yuzuki Nakajima, 20 years old from
Fukuoka prefecture.
Did you see my 3rd generation video?
I told you that I'm not good at sports,
but I used to do cheerleading.
Today, I will cheerlead with my favorite
song
and give you energy.
The road to my dream
Ah, I'm going to fail
I'm still on the way
I'm on my way
I don't have to hurry
I have to be motivated
I'll do what I like
Selfishly
On my way
Let me hear your voice.
Please call my 3rd generation name.
Rinka-chan
Rinko-chan
Reina
Nagisa
Airi
Yuzu
Mio
Itoha
Yuu
Miu-chan
Chi-chan
Thank you very much.
Let's have fun today.
I'm Yuzu.
Hello, everyone.
I'm 16 years old from Fukuoka
prefecture.
I'm Mio.
My hobby is drawing illustrations.
So this time, I'm going to have a
welcome party.
So, I drew the illustrations of the 11
members of the 3rd generation.
I can't draw all of them here, so please
watch this video first.
While I'm playing this video, I'd like
to talk a little bit about the members
of the 3rd generation.
First of all, Rika.
Rika is always fluffy, but she always
cares about the 3rd generation.
The other day, she made us lunch.
Riko is so cute, but she is unexpectedly
unique to the 3rd generation.
Reina said, "I collected empty PET
bottles during the camp and did my best
in the lesson."
Nagi is...
"I was so happy that I only aimed for 4
hours. I did my best to practice the
piano for this welcome party."
"Airi has a very cool expression, but
she is the tallest among the 3rd
generation."
"Yuzu is nervous during the audition,
but I remember being calm all the time."
"Itoha is always laughing at the 3rd
generation."
"Yu is a man with a steel mentality and
excellent motor nerves."
"Yuzu is often cool."
"Yu's smile is also very cute."
"Yu is always sleeping with a stuffed
animal."
"Yu always listens to me when I'm having
a hard time."
"And finally, Mio is..."
"Sakuranbo!"
"I'm the youngest member of Sakurazaka."
"I'll do my best to show you a cool
performance."
"I'm not going to be boring if I just
follow the script."
"So I'm going to add some colors."
Here I go.
I'll do my best to make the group more
exciting with 3rd Gen and 11th Gen.
That's all from Mio Matsuno.
Thank you.
I'm Itoha Mukai, a 16-year-old high
school freshman.
Today, I'm going to show you my special
skills.
I've prepared a lot, so please take a
look at this first.
I'm going to make a beautiful work from
now on.
Please look forward to what I can do.
I'll do my best.
Today, I'm going to show you my skills
that I showed you on VLOG.
Did you watch my VLOG?
Thank you very much.
I usually do animal kirei, but this time
I did sakura kirei.
I prepared a lot for this omotenashikai
with lessons and rehearsals.
I started kirei when I was in junior
high school, and I'm still doing it.
Now, I'd like to do the final touch-up.
Thank you for watching!
I'm SAKURAZUKI.
I'm done.
That's all.
I'm ITOHA MAKAN.
Thank you.
I'm 18-year-old MURANYU from TOKYO.
Today, I'd like to show you my special
skills that I've never shown you before.
I'm going to show you my special skills
that I've never shown you before.
Hirate Msuta
That's all from me.
Thanks for watching this video!
[Music]
Good morning!
I'm Miyu Murayama, 18 years old, from
Tokyo.
I'm Sappariha. Please teach me how to
make delicious rice.
Today, I'm going to show you a special
skill that I've never shown you before.
I'm Mia Murayama.
Please enjoy the rest of the concert.
[Music]
Hello everyone, I'm Shizuki Yamashita,
18 years old from Kyoto.
Today, I would like to show you the
dance I learned in elementary school and
junior high school.
I'm going to write my goals from now on.
[Music]
Yes, today is
I wrote the character "SAKU".
From now on, through the activities of
SAKURAZAKA46,
I will do my best to bloom like this
character.
Everyone, please continue to enjoy the
show.
This was Shizuki Yamashita. Thank you
very much.
Shizuki Yamashita
How was it, everyone?
It was amazing!
It was a very proud performance that I
don't think it was the first time.
Everyone, let's give them a big round of
applause.
How was the dance?
Endo-san, how was it?
I'm not good at dancing.
If you watched the documentary, you
would know.
Did you watch the documentary?
Thank you.
In the documentary, I was crying all the
time.
I think I've been showing my pathetic
appearance all the time.
In this dance track, I grew up a little.
I think I was able to show my cool self.
It was very cool. Thank you very much.
Next, Matono-san.
Yes.
How was it? Dancing and singing.
Yes, I always practiced in front of the
mirror with 11 people.
When I was dancing, the thing in front
of me was different from usual.
I was very anxious.
Through this performance, I was able to
convey something.
I thought, "It's so much fun!" when I
danced for the first time.
Thank you very much.
When I look in the mirror, it's a little
different from when I dance with
everyone.
Your support and your appearance is a
great help, isn't it?
Yes.
It was really wonderful.
Thank you.
The dance was wonderful, but how was the
two-minute show?
It was very exciting, wasn't it?
It was amazing.
The breath with everyone was perfect.
What should I do?
Ishimori-san, who made the omelette rice
for us.
Yes, I'm Rika Ishimori.
How was it?
Did you decide to cook and think about
what to do?
Yes, it was difficult to cook in 2
minutes.
But I like omelette rice, so I made it.
How was it?
Thank you very much.
Ishimori-san, your call was amazing.
I think it was very fun.
Thank you very much.
That's great, everyone.
That's great.
One more person.
Mukai-san, who showed us a wonderful
Kirie.
That was amazing!
Thank you very much.
That's amazing.
Did you also decide to do the 2 Minute
Show,
and when you thought about what to do,
did you decide to do Kirie?
That's right.
Speaking of special skills,
it was Kirie that was praised by
everyone in the 3rd generation,
so I decided to do it.
I see.
How did you decide on the theme?
That's right.
I thought it would be nice to have
something related to sakurazaka because
it's sakurazaka.
There was also the release of
"Sakurazuki".
I was really surprised.
It's really sakurazaka.
I thought it was sakura, but it was the
last sakurazuki.
That was really wonderful. You were able
to think of the composition yourself,
right?
Yes, it's a case of time and place, but
this time I was able to think of it
myself.
Wonderful!
It was really wonderful.
I think it was so wonderful that it
would be nice if we could perform it
again in the future.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
So, after the 2-minute dance show, I
think I was able to convey the charm of
the 3rd generation to everyone.
Buddies, are you having fun?
Let's move on to the next corner.
Next, we will try the 3rd generation's
"Sakurazaka Ai".
If you are a 3rd generation, you should
know this.
Team competition "Sakurazaka 46" quiz!
Please divide into teams.
From now on...
The question is a quiz that anyone can
answer if they love Sakurazaka.
If you know the answer, please press the
button on your hand and answer.
It's a quick press, so I'll give you a
quiz.
If you know the answer, you can press
the button and answer.
Now, I'd like you to introduce your
team.
Let's start with this team.
We are, 1, 2, 3,
KUISHINBOU!
Team KUISHINBOU!
Are you all "Kuishinbou"?
Yes.
When we were in the training camp, we
ate the most delicious food, so we were
named "Kuishinbou".
You were named "Kuishinbou".
Yes.
I see.
Each of us has a team name, so please
look forward to it.
You are "Kuishinbou".
You eat a lot.
Yes.
We all eat a lot.
I see.
Let's start the quiz.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll do our best.
We are Team KUISHINBO.
Next up is this team.
We are...
Shimae!
What do you mean by "Shimai"?
I'm sure some of the people who watched
the documentary will be able to see it.
But I wanted to look like a Shimai
because of my height.
I see. It's cute.
What do you think, Team Shimai?
Cute.
Please do your best on the quiz with
your cuteness!
Yes!
Well then, let's continue.
One, two...
Team!
Thank you very much!
Angel, is that okay?
Angel.
Then I would like to send a big "Sei" to
these three groups of angels.
Team Angel.
Please do your best in the quiz.
Then, the last team, please.
One, two.
Rabbit.
Cat.
Okay.
We've introduced them in a cute way.
Team "Rabbit-Cat"!
Rabbit-Cat-san.
Do you like rabbits and cats?
I thought they looked similar.
You did?
Yes.
Do we look alike?
They said we look alike.
Then, Usagi Neko-chan,
I hope you'll do your best with "Pyon
Pyon" and "Nyan Nyan".
Thank you.
We'd like to send you off with these 4
unique teams.
Everyone, please give us a lot of
support.
Do your best.
We'll do our best.
I think we'll start with the questions.
Are you ready?
Please get ready.
Here we go. The first question of the
Sakurazaka46 quiz.
How many squares does the word "sakura"
in Sakurazaka46 have in total?
That's fast.
21.
That's correct.
The speed of an angel.
That was fast.
That was amazing.
Who are you?
I'm Murayama.
Ah, Murayama-san.
Does that mean you knew the answer?
Yes, I knew.
Amazing.
Did you count it beforehand?
No, I knew something.
You knew something, I see.
Because you're an angel.
Yes.
As expected.
So, the correct answer was the angel
team.
That was fast.
I was a bit surprised.
Let's keep it up.
Yes.
Let's move on to the second question.
When Sakurazako46's name was revealed,
the group's new group name was announced
as a surprise.
What is the name of the group in Tokyo?
Team "Kuishinbo".
What? Tokyo?
Tokyo...
(laughs)
So close!
Oh, there's an angel!
Eh? Shibuya?
I don't know.
Let's say it again.
When Sakurazaka 46 had its opening,
the new group's name was announced as a
surprise.
The guide vision is...
Tokyo's what intersection?
Yes, Kuishinbou.
Shibuya's scramble intersection.
Correct!
It's correct.
I heard a "tot" sound. I'm sorry, I
can't pronounce it.
Speaking of Sakurazaka, it's Shibuya,
isn't it?
It's a little too easy.
The other teams are pushing me, so
please do your best.
I don't think I can do it.
Do your best, do your best.
I'll do my best.
Then, the third question.
The recording of the third single
"Nagaredama".
The unit that sings "On My Way" is
"Futarina".
Here we go!
Rina Inoue and Rina Matsuda!
Correct!
The question is...
The question was, "Who and whose unit
will sing 'Omoibe'?"
That's a great answer.
You said you liked it.
You showed us a wonderful dance just
now.
I thought you'd be able to do it.
We didn't make it.
That was fast.
That's the power of the Kuishinbo.
Eat a lot.
Make sure you do your best.
10,000 yen.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Please do your best.
Everyone, please spend more than 1,000
yen.
Let's move on to the fourth question.
What does Shiro mean to Sakura Saka46?
10,000 yen.
White.
Yes, you got it right!
"Korekara iro wo tsukeru tame ni"
That was close.
The nuance was a bit...
Motokuri Shimbo, your turn.
"Hakumai no shiro"
Good, good.
That was good.
"Hakumai no shiro"
White from deep blue to white.
It's getting more and more like
KUISHINBON.
Oh, it's here! Is it your first time?
It's here.
It's like you haven't been dyed in
anything yet.
Correct!
It's like you haven't been dyed in
anything yet.
It has the meaning of "white".
That's correct!
It was a little big, but I thought it
wouldn't come out.
No, it wasn't.
Koei Shinbo was a bad example.
Nice try.
It was a nice try, wasn't it?
The sisters did a great job.
Yes.
You did it.
Usagi-san, Neko-san, do your best.
I'm sorry.
Let's move on to the 5th question.
Sakurazaka46's first captain was Sugai
Yuka.
Sugai-sama's signature pose, Ganbari
Kiyo.
Wait, Ganbari Kiyo?
Ganbari Kiyo?
Ready, set, go!
Ganbariki!
Yay!
(Applause)
(Laughs)
That was amazing!
The question was, "Please show us the
correct movement of your signature pose,
Ganbariki."
That was perfect.
As expected of you, Ganbariki.
I'm glad I was able to get it right.
I'm glad, too.
I think that Ganbariki has reached you
as well.
Thank you very much.
Moving on to the 6th question.
Sakura Saka 46's 3rd single,
"Nagaredama", who was in charge of the
center position?
It's me! Usagi Nako!
One, two...
Sakura Hono-san!
I'm glad.
It's the first time.
That's good, that's good. It wasn't
broken, was it?
It wasn't broken, it was fine.
That's good, that's good.
I can't help but say this.
Tamura Honno-san.
Since it's the end.
As expected.
I definitely wanted to say this.
When you say "here it is", you say it.
As expected.
There's still more, so I'd like to keep
going.
Next, the 7th question.
Mikisei
Who is the hero that appears in the
American comic books that Ten Yamazaki
likes?
Wow, you have a big appetite.
One, two...
Spi...
Spiderman!
Correct!
Did you get it right away?
Yes, this is it, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
You were having a lot of fun with that,
right?
You're like a soloist.
The foodie.
Please do your best and cheer for the
other 3 teams.
Let's continue.
Question 8.
The first Tokyo Dome performance as
SAKURAZAKA46 was held in November last
year.
The song that was performed in the first
song is...
"TENSHI"
"JOUKEN HANSHA DE NAKETE KURU"
That's right.
This is...
As you can see...
- Yes. - That's right, at the site.
- Yes. - Yes.
What's wrong?
I can't see.
I thought it was fast to press the
button.
It's fast.
Do you always have to press the button?
That's right.
- I have to hold it. - You have to hold
it.
That's great. It's reassuring to have a
quick move.
That made it a little more interesting.
Yes.
Everyone, please pay attention to the
high-speed button and move on to the
next question.
Oh, it's a question.
Here we go.
Next question, question 9.
What is the job of the father of the
second-generation Onuma Akiho-san?
That was quick.
Go ahead.
Ryo-shi.
That is correct.
Correct.
Did you see the quick move again?
It was cool.
Did you see it, everyone?
Amazing.
Thank you.
It's broken.
It's not broken.
Let's move on to the last question.
Please do your best.
Now, the 10th question.
What is the birthdate of the firstborn,
Mizuho Habu?
(Buzzer)
(Laughter)
Oh, it's coming.
The latest news is fast.
Please.
It's July 7th, just like me.
(Buzzer)
(Laughter)
That's right.
Great.
I think KUISHINBOU was a total disaster,
wasn't it?
It was a total disaster, wasn't it?
Even if it's the same birthday, it's
definitely...
Yes, I couldn't lose this one, so I did
my best to not lose to Miyu.
Did you talk to HABU?
No, I haven't done it yet.
Yes, I have.
You're holding a mouse.
You're holding a hub mouse.
Yes, I'm a hub girl.
I'm a hub girl.
You can't lose to her, can you?
I'm a little disappointed, so I'm going
to talk to her next.
Please cheer for me!
Well then, well then, I might not be
able to announce it, but I'd like to
announce the rankings.
The winning team is...
"Kuishinbou"!
It was overwhelming.
That was strong, that was strong.
By the way, 2nd place is TenChi, with 3
points.
3rd and 4th place...
It was Usagi Neko-chan and Shimae-chan
at the same store.
I hope you can deepen your love for
Sakurazaka.
That's all for the Sakurazaka46 Quiz.
Congratulations!
The 3rd generation, please get ready for
the next stage.
Please get ready.
Bye-bye.
They're so cute, aren't they?
Right?
Did you find your favorite 3rd Gen?
You did, didn't you?
Now, everyone is getting ready for the
next event.
In the meantime, I would like to say
hello to the 3rd generation members for
their hospitality this time.
I would like to introduce you to the
questionnaire.
First of all, Rika Ishimori.
I couldn't introduce it in detail, but
the apron I was wearing was handmade.
I've loved sewing since I was a kid.
The present I got from Santa Claus when
I was an elementary school student was a
sewing machine.
That's what it is.
Yes, next up is...
Yes, thank you very much.
It was Ishimori-chan.
Next up is...
Riko Endo.
My appeal point that I couldn't convey
in the two-minute show.
I will heal everyone with a smile.
Next, Reina Odakura.
What kind of idol do you want to be in
the future?
I want to be an idol who can laugh a lot
and cry a lot when I'm happy and sad
with BUDDIES.
Nagisa Kojima
What kind of idol do you want to be in
the future?
I want to be an idol who is loved by
many people for a long time.
Not only cool and cute,
I want to show you the sparkle that only
idols can show.
Taniguchi Airi
Message to BUDDIES
Don't forget your humble feelings
I will do my best to make you think that
this girl is interesting in various
scenes such as dance, singing, and
variety.
I won't let you lose
Thank you from now on
BUDDIES
Okay, it looks like everyone is ready.
Next is a special event where you can
see a very, very precious figure.
Let's go!
3rd generation private fashion show
Located at the heart of downtown Los
Angeles in the heart of the Loop C
Fontana area
Keep an eye out in the future for unique
European podcasts
People even love their archival footage
With lovely PTA moments.
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
(speaking in foreign language)
How was it? Everyone was so cute, wasn't
they?
I think everyone's voices have been
heard.
Now, it's finally time for the first
live performance of the 3rd generation.
It's okay to speak up.
I think everyone's support will help
them.
Thank you.
Let's have fun!