[Music]
[Applause]
There are so many arenas and stands
here.
I'm so happy to be able to sit here.
Thank you so much.
And today, we're doing a live stream,
but it's also being streamed overseas.
Are you guys having fun watching the
live stream?
Yeah!
Thank you!
Ni hao!
I'll do my best to speak English like I
did yesterday, too.
We will do our best!
We'll do our best!
First of all, I have an announcement to
make.
Koike Minami is taking a break from
Sakurazuka 46 activities.
But the members are waiting for Mii-chan
to come back.
I hope the fans will continue to support
her.
Please support Koike Minami.
Thank you.
We started our 3rd anniversary live
today, but first, Hikari! Welcome back!
Welcome back!
Thank you!
I'm back!
Since you're here, could you say a few
words?
Yes.
BUDDIES, it's been a while.
I'm so happy.
Look at this.
They made it purple.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
It's been about 7 months since our last
comeback.
From now on, I'm going to walk my own
path.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
From now on, let's work hard together at
the pace of light.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
We couldn't all stand like this, but one
person, Hikari, came back and stood on
the stage together.
We are also happy.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
This...
This is our 3rd anniversary concert.
And this is our first outdoor concert as
SAKURAZAKA46.
I'm so happy that so many people came to
see us.
I'm so happy that you're watching this.
I'll do my best to forget the coldness
of today.
Thank you.
Karin-chan!
It's already the second day!
Just now, at BUDDIES...
How do you say it?
The audience...
The stand?
They came out.
They're happy.
That's great!
It was really fun.
Thank you.
At first, I thought it was cold, but now
it's hot, and when I go near the fans,
I'm really happy and it was fun.
It's really the best.
We have a flower road today, so we'll do
our best to get closer to you.
And I'd like to talk to Shizuki, who was
looking away from Karin-chan yesterday.
I'm Yamashita Shizuki.
This is the first time for the 3rd
generation to perform outdoors as
SAKURAZAKA46.
I'm so happy right now.
But the wind is blowing this way.
It's really cold right now, so I hope
the audience will stay warm.
We'll do our best to perform today with
a warm heart.
Let's do our best!
It's really like that. It's really
colder than yesterday, but I'd like to
enjoy it with everyone with all my
might, but I'm ready to shout out!
Yeah!
How far can we go?
Let's have fun together!
Yeah!
SAKURAZAKA46 3rd Anniversary Live
We have been waiting for you.
What?
Wow!
What's going on here?
I'm...
Let's go home.
You'll be ok?
I'll be fine!
I'll be there soon!
What you see is completely different
It's okay to cry
I don't ask for understanding anymore
A restricted identity
To the pessimistic adults
Don't push the cheap love
That you call "human"
Shut the f**k up
The local shopping street
If you run through with all your might
What will you understand?
A dead end
Dead end, dead end
There is an end to the world
What will you do from here?
It's pitch black in front of you
Dead end, dead end
You can break it if it's a wall
Will you go back to the way you came
from?
When you dream too much
It can't be helped if you stay here
You're the one who made a mistake
Dead end, dead end
How will you live in the present
That connects the past and the future?
Even if you resist
"What should I do today?"
It's the same result
The more you look around
The more you become a cautious person
Even if you eat
What should you answer?
Your parents still contact you
Where do you live?
If it's the end, if it's the end
Where will you start next?
What will you do from here?
It's the future of despair
If it's the end, if it's the end
Find a way out
Is there no continuation?
The lost present
What should you wait for?
If you wait until dawn
If it's the end, if it's the end
Will you rewind the dazzling days and
start over?
Will you start over?
No matter where you run
There is no way
Right and left are blocked by the wind
Everything is broken
Even the rusty back door
It's impossible
Even if it's the end, even if it's the
end
Dead end, dead end
There is an end to the world
What will you do from here?
It's pitch black in front of you
Dead end, dead end
If you wake up, you can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
When you've gone too far
Even if you stay here, it can't be
helped
I'm the one who made a mistake
Dead end, dead end
While hitting the wall in front of you
Are you screaming in your heart?
How do you live now connecting the past
and the future?
Dead end, dead end
If you wake up, you can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
When you've gone too far
Even if you stay here, it can't be
helped
I'm the one who made a mistake
Dead end, dead end
While hitting the wall in front of you
What does it mean to become an adult?
Even if you hit it seriously, it won't
be understood
I'm the only one left in the crowd
When I say it, everyone speaks
Now I'm listening as if I understand
I can't hold back my emotions like that
If it's self-destruction, I won't be me
this year
Even if you're a fool, even if you just
do that
What are you holding back?
I'm the one who made a mistake
Tell me what you want to say
Even if you just stare at me quietly, I
can't tell you anything
If you're angry, then be angry
I'm the only one left in the crowd
I'm the one who made a mistake
(Rudin)
Being swallowed up by words is
definitely not good for your health
It's*t's* going to go somewhere in your
heart
It's going to make you mad
What you want to say will disappear, it
won't disappear
The clock that's ticking, the clock
doesn't break
Shall I spit out my tears and fix it?
I don't care what you think
I'll make sure that no one can see me
I'll tell people about me
Everyone laughs at my uncool self-
knowledge
Let me like it, see
Ah, see
Don't run away, it's just the beginning
Don't turn your back on me
Don't try to stop me
Don't be timid, see
The light is proof that I'm alive
Don't tie me up, no no no
Pull me closer, be free
Come closer, what will you do?
(Instrumental)
At this rate, it's the end
There's no choice but to collide and
understand each other
It's bad, but I can't let it go
I can't get any hotter
So one, two, three
Yeah, it's like a defeat
Tell me what you want to say
Even if I'm staring at the map
I can't understand anything
Yeah, if you're pissed off, be pissed
off
There's no choice but to be myself
Even if I'm in a bad mood
(Instrumental)
(Applause)
Yeah
(Instrumental)
Even if I'm a little crazy
Even if I notice it, I skip
Even if I forget the memories
Because I've got a new boyfriend
It's kind of fluffy
I'll lose my heart
No matter what you say
I don't care at all
I'll give you a smile back
Happiness is an electric sky
Why didn't you fall in love?
I've always understood
Because I always, always
I love you
It's like a cat with hair
But I found out when I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meet each other, love each other, and
become nothing
I don't want to be myself
I want to find my true self
Say it in front of people
Show me a picture of yesterday
Talk about things like that
I used to curse such a fool
Sometimes I remember that it was fun
I drink together
It's almost Christmas
Valentine's Day, my sweet
What kind of plan is your birthday?
I want to boast about my happiness
Yes, I didn't fall in love
I'm getting excited
Because it's a fun love story
Why don't you watch a drama?
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm nervous, I'm nervous, I'm nervous
People who are lost
Confess right away
Rather than the audience watching
Look at each other, hug each other
Let's kiss
Why does happiness become a lie?
I didn't fall in love
I've been making fun of you all this
time
Because I love you
I'm like a stray cat
But I found out when I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meet each other, love each other, and
become sleepy
I want to find my true self
Not myself
Let's go! That's love!
More!
I'm always surprised
I say selfish things
I'm the worst person
Do you know that?
Even if I don't have much experience
That's how I am
I don't want to see you from now on
No more thank you
But why?
I want to do it
More!
Let's see each other
Let's look into each other's eyes
Your smile
Thickens my instincts
You don't have to leave
Come here
I'll hold you both
I can't leave you alone
So pitiful
If I'm not there, I'll be like a stray
cat
(I don't want to see you)
I'll meet my friends, even if you don't
like me
(Even if you don't like me)
If you like me, you won't be able to run
away
That's what love is
Ladies!
I can still hear your voices!
Let's go!
One, two!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I'm in this cruel world
I can't imagine a bad tomorrow
I want you to give me a pure heart that
I can't doubt
Until now, I've always believed in the
same legend
I have hope
Where should I give up?
If I'm here to stay
Will the last thread of hope disappear?
I want a story that can be creators
But then it'll end
You can't help yourself if you wipe your
tears
(You can't help yourself)
You don't have to care if you don't do
it
(You don't have to care)
I'm not sure why but I want you to tell
me clearly
(Tell me)
I'm doing what I can, I'll do everything
I can
(Woo!)
If there's something you want, just
casually (just casually)
Just like that, just like that, just
like that, just like that
I should just steal it (I should just
steal it)
I don't have to lose anything
(I don't have to lose anything)
I don't have to lose anything, that's
love, right?
(That's love)
If you look at me like that (If you look
at me like that)
I'll pour everything into the water,
right?
Even if I fall into the same hell (even
if I fall into the same hell)
I'll dream for a moment
(Woo!)
It's okay if you don't want to go home,
come here (come here)
I'll take you away with my two hands
(I'll take you away with my two hands)
(Come here)
I'll take you away with my two hands
(I'll take you away with my two hands)
It's not like I can't protect you
anymore, I feel sorry for you (I feel
sorry for you)
No matter how many times I'm told the
same thing
(Woo!)
I can't sleep like this (I can't sleep)
In this chest (in this chest)
If I wasn't here, I'd be like a cat
(like a cat)
Even if my friends and parents are
stupid and oppose me (and oppose me)
If I fall in love with you, I'll fall in
love with you
That's love, right?
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
Buddies, let's get excited with our
voices!
Hold my right hand on a summer shortcut
In the middle of the wind and the sun
(I'm sure it's there)
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
Is that how close we are?
On the way home,
I see your smile with him
For some reason, it's getting sad
I hope tomorrow comes soon
(Woo!)
I can't catch up with you
Every time you walk ahead of me
I'll wait for the chance to talk to you
I want to invite you to the sea
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
Where should I look for a summer
shortcut?
The door to the next season opens
Love is always a pain
Tell me the future map
Hold my right hand on a summer shortcut
In the middle of the wind and the sun
(I'm sure it's there)
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I hope I can invite you someday
I've never been in a hurry
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
Suddenly, today
The distance between our hearts
(Distance)
I have to hurry
It's a season, it's a season, it's an
order
I want to skip it
No matter what I do, no matter how I
cheat
I can't give you to anyone else
(Buddy, let's go!)
How long will the summer shorcut last?
The rain is dangerous in the dark
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
Let's find a place
where we can meet
Even if the winter shorcut is far away
We'll chase after a miracle
In front of the miraculous
If you turn that corner
There is already the entrance to
midsummer
(Buddy, let's go!)
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!)
If I could, I'd love to fall in love
with you, but
Because of my rival, I don't have much
time
Where should I look for the summer
sunset?
The next season will come
Love is always a precious thing
Tell me the future map
I'm looking for the summer sunset with
my right hand
In the middle of the wind and the sun
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
There's still a long way to go
"Summer Sunset"
One, two, three, four!
It doesn't matter who you like
Can you choose the blooming flowers?
I'm not alone, I'm working hard with
everyone
I support you
There are places where the light hits
and places where it doesn't
The beauty of trying to live hard
It's sunset time!
Let's shout as loud as you can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that sweat blooms someday
Let's keep shining
It's sunset time!
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
I can clearly see it from the other side
of the stage
The wind, the sun, and the rain
I want to nurture you
No matter what kind of flower it is
It's all different
Until it blooms
The moon and the sun are different
Don't compare yourself to others
Aren't you yourself?
Someday you'll understand your own pace
Being desperate is important
Living in self-indulgence
Do what you want to do
A life without regrets
It's sunset time!
Let's put our shoulders together and
sing
Let's be friends who don't run away from
anything
Good points and bad points
I want to be friends with you
Go on! Sunset time!
Let's ring the floor and go beyond the
rhythm
Let me hear your message
Let's make the voltage of the audience
the highest
Please remember that there was a member
like that
You're still waiting
Put on the buds you picked
Believe that you can make a big flower
bloom
Until the day you graduate
Let me see everything
It's sunset time!
Let's sing as loud as we can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that sweat blooms someday
Let's keep shining
It's sunset time!
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
From the other side of the stage
I can clearly see
The wind and the sun
I want to raise you
Buddy! Everyone!
Now!
Turn it up!
Louder!
I want to catch up with you on the
ponytail
You can't catch up with me if you're
slow
Is it that I can only look back?
The sound of the buzzing bus
I can't keep up with you at full speed
It's uncool to follow me
I can't breathe anymore
Come on, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly,
fly through the sky
I'm looking for you, you, you, you, you
from here
But still, instead of my eyes
Let's operate at any distance
I want to keep looking at you
Oh, oh, crossing
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Look, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh, oh, I love you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Drum, drum, full throttle
I can't believe there's no one in this
crowd
I'm going to take you to the cherry
blossom field
Like a bird, I look at the sky freely
I'm sure I'm aiming for something I want
I wonder where I am
I wonder if I'm confident
I wonder if your heart
I thought it was the song I wanted the
most
I look up and see you
I'm still in pain
I'm here, but I don't notice
Ah, my existence
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, one-sided love
This is love, love, love, love, love
Look at me
I can't touch you because you're too
precious
I want to know you more
It's the third birthday of Sakurazaka46
Everyone in Sakurazaka
Everyone in BUDDYS
Happy birthday!
I'll keep the precious memories of the
third year in my heart
I want to grow stronger with everyone in
the fourth year
BUDDYS, we're always on your side
Wow wow wow wow
Please notice me
Come on, you in the distance
From here, you, you, you, you
I'm looking for you, wherever you are
Instead of my eyes
Let's manipulate any distance
I want to look at you anytime
Wow wow wow wow
Hey, I found you
Nice to meet you
Wow wow
I love you
Wow wow wow wow
I want to fall in love with you
Sakurazaka46's third year anniversary
live
It's the last day
Did you all enjoy it?
Thank you
Let me hear your voices until the end
Let's get excited
Sakurazaka46's third year anniversary
live
I said that I didn't like it because it
was spread out, but I pushed it with a
slip
I'm a man who doesn't seem to have a
world view
I've been nervous for a long time
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
It's the first time I've ever been a
professional, so I haven't been able to
calm down since morning
Even if I suddenly clean it up, it seems
that someone is there
The reason I'm opening the door a little
is because I don't have a heart
I wanted you to understand
I wish this kind of time would continue
with the laundry you started
I'm wandering around, but I'm happy with
the little things
I want to spend my daily life with you
rather than having a special date
My scattered room becomes more beautiful
than I can see
What should we do next?
It's dyed in twilight from the other
side of the starry sky
When will you come next time?
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I want to boast to everyone
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
I'm happy with the laundry you washed
for me, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough" I'm sorry for being a
little reckless
Even if I want to forget, I can't forget
Many memories
I can't feel such a taste forever
If I spit it out, I'll say it lightly
Even if I think it lightly, the dream
continues forever
It's a painful feeling that I've left
behind
Something overflows from my eyes, regret
The regret that flows and falls in my
cheeks is not tears
Even if I try to endure it, regret
It would be easier if I could hate you,
but it might be boring
The stronger the love, the more we hurt
each other
I don't have a heart that I can't change
We're a perfect match
I can't do this anymore, plastic
I'm not as weak as I thought, plastic
That's why I don't cry, not a single
tear
I'm not as weak as I thought, plastic
Even if I'm embraced so much, I don't
feel weak
The regret that flows and falls in my
cheeks is not tears
Even if I try to endure it, regret
It would be easier if I could hate you,
but it might be boring
I'm not as weak as I thought, plastic
Everyone, are you having fun?
I don't know if it's just my
imagination, but I feel like I'm in the
water.
If you feel sick, please call the staff
around you.
The second day of the 3rd Anniversary
Live has begun!
I'm so happy!
We're so excited that it's not even cold
anymore.
How about you, BUDDIES?
Thank you so much!
We had a lot of exciting songs in the
first half, but the 3rd generation also
sang 2 songs in a row, so I'd like to
listen to the 3rd generation today.
Then, Yu-chan Murai!
Yu-chan!
Anirawa!
Yes, I'm Yu-chan Murai.
Today, for the first time, I was able to
celebrate the birthday of Sakurazaka
with my beloved seniors and many
BUDDIES.
I'm so happy and excited right now.
I've been feeling the sense of unity
between BUDDIES and us through the live
show.
I want to be with BUDDIES forever.
Thank you.
Thank you, YU-CHAN.
I'd like to ask one more question.
YU-ZU, who was in charge of the center
in ANTHEM TIME.
YU-ZU.
This way.
Good answer.
I'm Yuzuki Nakashima, also known as
Yuzu.
How was ANTHEM TIME, everyone?
It was the best!
I love you!
Thank you!
It was really exciting, wasn't it?
It was exciting!
Thank you so much for making it so
exciting.
I'm in charge of the center.
But that aside,
I really love the song "Anthem Time".
I love it.
Because I feel like I'm really connected
to the BUDDIES.
And I'm so happy that I'm connected to
the 3rd Gen.
I think it's really fun to be able to
perform while feeling the 3rd Gen.
The anthem time was so exciting a while
ago, wasn't it?
Everyone, it was fun, wasn't it?
It was really fun, so let's go on to the
next live show and blow away the cold.
Please!
I...
When I was waiting for the drone, I was
listening to Sankisei's singing voice.
I think Sankisei's songs are loved by
1st and 2nd graders, and I think it's
the same for BUDDIES, but I love it!
I'm so jealous!
There are so many good songs, and the
lyrics are really catchy, like Anthem
Time.
So thanks to that, I was able to do my
best with the drone.
That's great!
Thank you!
That was the best!
The 3rd generation is really cute, and
the 1st and 2nd generation are really
happy about it.
But personally, it was the first time I
became an idol and the 3rd generation
joined me.
I was able to become a senpai thanks to
everyone.
So I'm really happy that the 3rd
generation is spoiling me.
The 2nd generation was a little spoiled,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
That's great!
While we're at it, can we learn more
from you, Ikusei-san?
Of course!
Thank you so much!
Come and get it, everyone!
Thank you!
I always get a lot of smiles when I'm
with everyone.
We, Sakurazaka46, will be entering our
4th year.
We would like to continue to give you
live performances that you can look
forward to.
Can you follow us?
Thank you so much!
Let's keep it up!
(Subbed By VocaloidLiveConcert Any
Mistakes, Please Inform Us)
I'm on the phone
Little by little, my focus goes up
Why is it that when I'm with you
I feel so much better?
I didn't think I'd meet you
Now I can see it clearly
Confidence, is it necessary?
Somehow (I feel that way)
I've heard it over and over again
My feelings, hey, really (I wanted to
hear it)
I already know it
I like you with conviction
The croissant, I'll eat it
I'll drop the egg
I won't blame you for how you eat it
I don't care, it doesn't matter
Where is the uncertain thing?
Even if I look for it
When I became an adult
I was able to confirm it
I won't lie about the truth
Let's just live straight
(Instrumental)
It doesn't matter how I look
I just need to know myself
I don't care
You're the only one who knows me
There's no such thing as certainty
Everyone's only reliance is their life
What is certainty?
Is it necessary?
Somehow
(If you just feel that way)
I've heard it over and over again
My feelings
Hey, really
(That's what I'm saying)
I already know it
Wow wow wow wow
(Instrumental)
(Cheering)
I don't care how I look
I just need to know myself
I don't care
You're the only one who knows me
There's no such thing as certainty
Everyone's only reliance is their life
Wow wow wow wow
Throw it at the launch of an adventure
In the middle of the hill of twilight
Why? Why? Why?
Because the horizon and someone's sky
are disappearing
The scenery blurs and tears come
Love is just a moment
There is no eternal happiness
I'm fine as long as I have a day like
this
It was too much on the way, I was
serious
I was clumsy, I couldn't go
Even if I realize it now, even if I
regret it
In the city after that, at the end of
the crossroad
If only I could go to such a place
I can meet you
I can't help but smile when I see you
Going shopping alone, doing whatever I
want, eating raiyaki, riding the same
coaster, it's so painful
A new love, a different love, I've been
waiting for a lot of time, but it was
impossible
I can't help but reflect on the
situation
I can't resist my own feelings
I'm losing by reflecting on the
situation
On the way back home in the twilight
Why? Why? Why?
The horizon and someone's back disappear
The scenery blurs and tears come
Love is just a moment
There's no happiness for anyone
No matter what kind of day it is, I'll
be fine
Translated by Releska
We performed "Hakushintoki Kurowasu-
chan" and "Jouken Hansho" as a group!
How was it, everyone?
Thank you very much!
"Kakushinteki Kurowasu-san" is a song of
the 7th single "Vax Memba", so I think
that a very cute pose has come out, but
did you all understand?
Oh, there may be some people who don't
understand a little, so let's tell them.
This is a Kurowasu-san pose.
Everyone, if you like, please take a
picture of it.
Thank you very much.
Well, now that we've talked about that,
we have an announcement to make.
Can we announce it now?
First, please look at this video.
(Dance)
(Hands)
(Fingers)
Thank you very much.
And so, the Wax Live has been decided!
I didn't think you would react like
that.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad to hear that.
We've done BAX Live twice before.
In the previous BAX Live,
the members who were in the third row of
each song
did the BAX Live.
From this time,
the selection system has been introduced
to SAKURAZAKA46.
So, the members who were chosen by the
BAX members
are here.
We will do our best together.
I would like to talk about my feelings.
When I heard the announcement of the
selection of BAX members,
I was frustrated because I felt that I
was not strong enough.
I was very frustrated.
I was worried about how to tell BUDDIES
and whether it was okay to tell them.
But when I tried to tell them my honest
feelings,
they said, "I'm praying for you."
"I'll follow you from now on."
"I'm always cheering for you."
I received such wonderful words.
I thought, "I can't just sit here and do
nothing. There are so many things I
can't give up."
Thank you very much.
I think there are many things you can't
do unless you're chosen.
But there are things only we can do.
Isn't that one of the things about
BACK'S LIVE?
I think so.
We all have our own thoughts, and we
want to share them with you through our
performances.
We'll do our best.
Please look forward to it.
Let's hear from the other members.
Rika Ishimori.
I'm Rika Ishimori.
This is the first time for the 3rd
generation to be on the show.
How do you feel?
I feel the same way.
I've been watching the past three BACK-
US live streams and so on, and there's a
name for the BACK-US members like this,
but I'm very impressed with the live
performances where each person shines,
and I think that BACK-US members are the
same every time, but I don't think
they're the same every time.
That's why I can do it now.
I think it's one of the charms of BACK-
US live that each member of the single
can do a live performance, so I was very
happy when I heard that I could do a
live performance with these seniors and
these 3rd generation students this time,
and I will do my best so that I can grow
more and so that the BACK-US members can
make SAKURAZAKA46 stronger.
Thank you very much.
I thought I wanted to do my best.
Thank you.
You were watching, weren't you?
Let's deliver Rika's charm firmly.
Thank you very much.
Are you looking forward to BACK-US live?
Next is FUYUKA.
Yes.
I thought you were going to say yes.
I'm really looking forward to being able
to do a backslide for the first time
with the 3rd generation.
But I don't think it's natural to do a
backslide.
I think everyone has their own feelings
when they do a backslide.
That's right.
I think it would be nice if the members
and the fans who support the members
could also digest that feeling and make
it into a live performance.
I've performed two songs so far, and I
think this performance is our best.
That's right. It's a start.
So I think it's zero.
I'd like you to come and see how much
this member has improved since the day
of the live.
I'd like everyone here to come and see.
You've all seen zero, so I'd like you to
come and see how much you've grown from
zero.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
The venue is the first standing seat.
I think that our passionate feelings
will be conveyed to everyone more
deeply,
so I would be happy if everyone could
look forward to it.
As one of the possibilities of
Sakuraizoka,
I want to do my best to grow more and
more in the future.
Please look forward to it.
Yes, the live is still going on, so
everyone, let's enjoy it with all our
might after this!
Subbed By VocaloidLiveConcerts Any
Mistakes, Please Inform Us
In the middle of the night, I'll see you
in a car somewhere
I can hear the door knocking at midnight
Forget about the people around you
Now, let's go to the corner of the world
Let's kiss at the far end of the airport
The orange lights are swaying
Lovers gather at this place
I still can't sleep at the conbinado
Even if the stars disappear before I
know it
A more romantic conbinado of love
The vintage car with the headlights
turned off
We're lining up in the same direction
On a weekend night, I'll run away from
here
I'll meet you on the other side of the
fence
Lighting up each seat
Lovers support each other sweetly
I've come this far
I don't want to be disturbed by anyone
I want to kiss on an unusual day
Dreaming life, quietly
As if I'm breathing
Before I'm noticed
A world that never rests
Shaking Dreaming life, forever
It's okay if it doesn't change
No matter how many times I come here
I can't get bored
Because it's a conbinado
"Conbinado"
Rather than going to a club
I want to go to an old town that looks
like it's going to go crazy
Iron stairs and a tank
Like a projection mapping
I'm going to get into the center of the
movie
Let's kiss
How about a kiss?
Conbinado
The orange light swaying in the distance
Lovers are drawn to each other
They gather
Conbinado
I can't sleep
Even if the night comes and the stars
disappear
More romantic
Love's Conbinado
"Conbinado"
The blue sky with no clouds
Isn't it cruel?
If I'm shown what's perfect
There's no place for escape
Normally happy days
What's the anxiety?
I was able to meet the expectations of
my parents and teachers
But I'm not the kind of person who can
do that
I want to be myself and do what I want
to do
How can I be forgiven?
If that's the case, I'd rather live a
carefree life
Where do the gaps in my heart come from?
I hurt myself before I knew it
I'm lonely, I'm out of breath, I'm out
of breath
Only this is leaking out little by
little
With a quiet power that I don't even
notice
I pull my legs
A faint breeze that only I can feel
Thank you for watching!
I just need to close my eyes
It'll be easier, won't it?
Even though it's not what I wanted to do
I wonder if I have to keep looking
Even if I just pretend to be like that
I'll start to hate myself
Yes, I'm like this
I'm being told that I've changed
I can't be convinced, but
The world still ignores me
If that's the case, then forever
Don't put me in the numbers
Why am I crying, without a sound or a
crack?
I don't feel it because I'm used to
being hurt
What do you want to know?
I say to myself that it's no good
I don't understand the obvious anymore
Every time I breathe, the sound of
escaping
The air of hope that I've been sucking
in
I can't tell anyone
There must be something in my heart
I don't know, but little by little
I feel like I'm drowning in words
If that's the case, then open that hole
wide
Become the wind and get out of this boat
Where do the gaps in my heart blow from?
Until when did I get hurt?
I'm lonely, I sigh, and I'm out of
breath
This is the only thing I'm getting used
to
With a quiet power that I don't even
notice
I pull my feet
A faint wind that only I can feel
I'm lonely, I sigh, and I'm out of
breath
This is the only thing I'm getting used
to
With a quiet power that I don't even
notice
I pull my feet
A faint wind that only I can feel
I'm lonely, I sigh, and I'm out of
breath
I'm falling in love
If I were to put it into words
It may be easy, but I can't say "from my
side"
What I can't say clearly is
The weather and my feelings are the same
I'm sure my mom won't calm down
I'm fine as a friend
That's why inside my heart
I'm sheltered by the rain
I'll wait for the sun to cut through the
clouds here
Come on, everyone!
From far away, love is coming to me
Even if I look up, it doesn't change
I'm expecting a rainbow somewhere
Come on, everyone!
When will the painful days come?
I have an unbreakable umbrella
So I can go see you right now
I believe that there is an eternity
That I can endure at any time
The rain won't stop
Everyone says so
But is that really true?
I'm attracted to you more and more
Will I open this door?
Will I give up?
I ask myself, who has no reason
It's painful, when I think of you
I can't breathe
I hate half-heartedness
But I can't decide either way
I don't care if I get wet
I should jump out of my anxiety
If I had that courage
I'm sure the rain would stop
I can't tell you
Because I'm being chased by the hot
clouds
Wow wow
The rain won't stop
Come on, everyone!
Even if I look up, it doesn't change
I'm expecting a rainbow somewhere
Come on, everyone!
It's painful, when will that day come?
I have an umbrella that I can't spread
So I can go see you right now
I believe that there is an eternity
That I can endure at any time
There's no answer
That's love
I'm still in love with you
Don't break my heart
Wow wow
Everyone knows that there is no eternity
We're getting forgotten
I feel happiness
Even this moment right now
It's a vague memory
You can be a horse for a moment
You can go to the point where you can't
stop
We're a horse that goes round and round
Everything
I'll dance with all my might
Let me see that legend
Even if I don't have any memories
If I'm happy now, that's fine
Don't stop
Wow wow
Believe
In the light
Wow wow
Disappear
Someday you can be a horse
I saw a miracle
I happen to be to that
Sincerity
Believe
I shed beautiful sweat
That's a joke
I'm strong
Faster than anyone
Keep waiting for that future
Don't worry about the people around you
You're on your own way
Everyone is a dreamer
I'll dance with all my heart
Let me witness that legend
Wow wow wow
Everyone, are you having fun?
When I stand here, I can feel everyone's
enthusiasm from all directions, and I'm
very happy.
Thank you very much.
If you get excited and sweat like this,
your body may get cold.
Please enjoy it while keeping warm so as
not to catch a cold.
If you get sick, please go to the
nearest hospital.
Please call us right away.
Thank you very much.
Are all the members "poka poka"?
Yes, we are "poka poka"!
How about you, En-chan?
We are "poka poka"!
Well, it's a little sudden, but I have
something I want to apologize to you
all.
What is it?
It's a little bit like what we talked
about yesterday, but
at BUDDIES,
it's our 2-year-old birthday!
You noticed!
I noticed!
You noticed?
I'm not a mermaid!
I'm so happy to see you so young!
I'm actually 3 years old.
That was the story.
I'm sorry.
I think I was a little nervous.
But I was really wrapped up in
enthusiasm.
There are so many BUDDIES.
There is no such a wonderful space.
It's amazing, really.
I want to burn it in my eyes from corner
to corner today.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's our first time having a stadium
live since we turned 3 years old.
Today is the last day to celebrate.
I'd like to have a call and response
with you.
I'd like to hear your voices.
Are you ready?
Wow!
Let's start with Lena.
You can do it!
It's my first time, so if I say
something, everyone will say, "I love
you."
That's good.
It's easy to understand.
Here we go.
Do you like chocolate?
We love it!
Do you like chocolate caramel?
I'm going to caramelize you all!
I don't know if I'm doing it right, is
it okay to do it like this?
You're doing it right, you're doing it
right.
Now that everyone in the audience has
been caramelized,
I'd like to go to Tsurugi with this
momentum.
Please continue to speak out and liven
up the atmosphere.
[Music]
Don't tell anyone what's important.
The moment you jump out of your heart,
you rot away.
Even if you choose such beautiful words,
they will turn into something sad and
painful.
Everyone believes in love,
but if you fall in love,
it will become a weakness.
That's why I'll throw my heart away.
Yes, I won't fall for anyone.
I don't care if you're an unlovable man.
I'll pretend that I don't care.
I'll pretend that it doesn't matter.
I want to turn around and live my life.
Even if you look at me like that,
I'm not interested.
I still keep resisting.
I don't want to be an adult.
I want to be a fool like this.
I don't want to be anxious.
I want you to notice my true feelings.
[Music]
My heart is always hard,
so I have to wrap it up
so that no one can touch it.
I don't want to be afraid of anyone
around me.
If you're lonely, you can be lonely.
Kindness and love
sometimes become invisible knives.
I don't even know how to be by your
side.
I'm hurting you.
I didn't mean to do that.
Yes, the distance between people
is more difficult than I thought.
If you say it's over,
of course I won't say it.
I've lived my life without emotions.
I'll break more and more.
I'll let you do whatever you want.
I don't want to be bound.
Don't look for the ordinary.
Nothing will change.
Don't look for the loop.
My last wish is a loop.
Let's break it.
[Music]
Oh, so let me dress up.
I don't care if I'm the real me anymore.
I'll pretend I don't care.
I'll pretend I won't lose.
I want to be honest with you.
I don't care if you look at me like
that.
Nothing will change.
I'll keep going.
I don't want to be an adult.
I'm going to be a fool like this.
I don't want to lose.
Really, I'm feeling good.
Notice me.
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
I'm losing it, I'm losing it
Even if I'm just walking normally
I can't stop myself from complaining
I'm just living my life
I'm just a girl, I'm a legit
Who? For what?
I don't know, B2B
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
I'm losing it, I'm losing it I'm losing
it, I'm losing it
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
I don't want to be a target
Because I'm a good girl
Hey, if you do something like this
Everyone, everyone, yeah
I don't want to get involved
(I don't want to get involved)
Let's talk, let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end,
yeah
It's not a joke, it's a flow
It has nothing to do with that
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry
I'm losing it, I'm losing it
I don't want to be a target
I'm just living my life
I'm running away from lies
I'm apologizing to you
Den, den, den
Put that face in your head
The reporter who appeared hit the bag
You who were far away
I'm just a girl, I'm a legit
Because if I didn't do it, I would have
been a good fighter
I don't care about others to protect
myself
Tomorrow is someone else's tomorrow
So let's go to this party
(Let's go to this party)
If the trial of the miracle opens
I'm going to crush it
(I got it)
No one can stop me
I'm a local wrestler
(I'm a local wrestler)
Let's believe, let's believe
If we don't believe in each other, the
world will end
Yeah
It's a flow that came from nowhere
It was said while I didn't know
Tradition, non-stereo
I didn't feel the pain
(I got it)
Wait a sec
I'm not afraid of anything
Yeah
I'm looking forward to the place where I
can walk
A party called life
(A party called life)
With just one rule
I won't say anything
Why is it that everyone only cares about
themselves?
(Only about themselves)
I see, everyone is just talking to
someone
Yeah
I wonder if it's like this
Hiding my face in a beach party
(In a beach party)
But I'm a good girl who doesn't say
anything
Hey
If I do something like this, no one will
say anything
(No one will say anything)
Let's talk to each other, let's look at
each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah
It's a flow that came from nowhere
I'm not looking outside the window
Even in the city at the end of the night
I can't hear the bell
(I can't hear the bell)
Hey!
I was watching a video on my smartphone
until I fell asleep
There's no way I'd be hated for that
I was late for everything
And I fell asleep again today
Hey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
If that's the case, I'm glad I slept
Why am I acting like this?
I can't do it
Hey!
What do I want to be?
What do I want to do?
When will I be able to dream?
I've been playing games all this time
But before I knew it, I was an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why am I so busy?
Wait a minute!
There's so much time left!
So that I can live my life to the
fullest
I'm the only one who's okay
Even if I'm told I'm not allowed to
touch you
There's no way I can be a different
person now
Even if I'm told I'm not allowed to
touch you
I understand
It's just a dream, isn't it?
I want to know the standard
Hey!
The sand of time that was full
Disappears without doing anything
If I'm serious about it
I thought I could do anything
What am I doing here?
I'm the only one who's playing
Someone tell me
It's something I have to change
Suddenly, one step at a time
I was made a part of the future
What should I do if I'm banned?
I just didn't know
Give me a chance to fix it one more time
What should I do if I'm banned?
Are you going to ignore me?
I believed that the only thing I could
do was to say "I'm worried"
God, please forgive my mistake
I can't believe I suddenly made such a
mistake
I'm sorry
(Hey!)
The sun is too bright
to see through the window
But it's not too late
for darkness to come
(Hey!)
Even if they say you're a fan or a
critic
you can't be someone else
It doesn't mean that I can't do it
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I'll do it again
I won't regret it
God, what is it that I can't do?
Where is that standard?
Even if I'm cornered by someone else's
situation
I'll definitely be banned
Translated by Releska
[The day of the final battle]
We are...
Sakurazaka Court System...
It's been a year since I joined as a
member of the team.
We've been working hard to get to where
we've always wanted to be.
And I finally found it.
The most important role for us is to
stand side-by-side on this stage as a
member of Sakurazaka 46.
This is the 3rd anniversary of
Sakurazaka 46.
I will never forget this responsibility.
This is my favorite song.
I will protect sakura trees with all of
my heart.
Please listen to this song,
"Mamoribito".
"Mamoribito"
And the days full of scars
All of it
Let's make a vow on this stage
Yes, it's our turn this time
Until the next day
A young and strong individual comes
No one moves
Hey!
If you look up at the night sky
Countless stars shine
In the darkness
The stars that can't be seen from here
Even though we're trying in the same way
Flowers that bloom and flowers that
don't bloom
Even the unrepayable emotions
God is watching
The most important role is
Yes, to be here
I was born in this world
You know why, right?
Don't move until the next day
Hey!
I'm a guardian
A guardian of the cherry tree
I'm proud to be chosen by that one
person
Now, let's hold hands and make sure
The days we spent here someday
I'm sure you'll remember
Because we were friends
I think I can always smile
Let's make a vow on this stage
Yes, it's our turn this time
Until the next day when a young and
strong individual comes
No one moves
What can we do?
With a pure heart without any desire
Let's just keep thinking about that
"JUMP"
I'm going to jump!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
"I want to do it someday"
Do you have any dreams?
Do you have any reason to live
to do something someday?
The magic of "I want to do this
tomorrow"
is sleeping.
People are all in a hurry
to forget the bad things.
Let me hear the words of "I want to do
it someday."
In a convenience store's microwave
that makes such a night
Warm the bell
What kind of life are you waiting for?
I'm sure you know
that you're giving up before you know
it.
But pretend you don't notice.
Stand over, stand over
If you think you can do it again
Now is the only time
There is no tomorrow
I'm running away
Wake up now
The moment you open the door
you can become a different person.
What's important
is to start over from somewhere.
That's a few seconds before you give up.
Then what am I?
Can I speak softly to someone?
I don't know, I don't know.
I want to be safe
I don't want to be criticized
so I look away.
What should I do?
Warm the environment
Get out of today
No matter what I do, no matter what I
fail
I want to be alone.
Rather than being protected by security
cameras
I just want freedom that no one can see.
I wonder if I can sacrifice something
like that.
It's better to have no secrets.
So don't worry about others.
Break it down
What I've always had until today
I don't care.
Don't be so selfish.
Don't be so cool.
If you wake up, you'll be like a two-
story, three-story building.
Even if you're in a bad mood
There is no tomorrow
It's not that easy.
I think it's a little better.
I want to be positive
towards you.
I'm not as brave as I used to be.
Keep going.
I want to eat now.
Is it too late?
No, no, no
You're like my past
I'll be your future
Love me
A lump of self-hatred
Stand over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's no other way
There's no way
I'm running away
Now, wake up
In the reality reflected in the glass
window
My heart is dark and I can't lose
But the truth is
It's a momentary illusion
I'm worried about the time
What's important is
Where to start over
That's the strength to give up
Translated by Releska
(Chinese)
(Alarm)
(Music)
Last song
(Chinese)
(Music)
Until the wind goes around the world one
more time and comes back there
Will my resolve remain unwavering?
Are you going to get it?
I can't see the answer
Because I am who I am, I can't be myself
I know I have to go right now
But I can't move my legs
Even if it's a trial, I can't leave you
alone
Because my heart is torn apart
The most important thing in life is to
make a choice
Thank you for your viewing!
I realized that I can't help it even if
it's a selfish goodbye
You smiled gently and gave me a white
flag
It's impossible, I can't go anywhere
anymore
I don't care if you say it's useless
It's a sin, if you can choose either one
Let's stay here and regret it
I don't care if you say it's useless
It's a sin, if you can choose either one
Thank you for watching.
There is nothing in this world that can
be cut off
To live is to struggle with blood and
sweat
You can't walk straight without getting
hurt
You know that, right?
While being lost in the many worlds
(Taking many steps)
Someday, I'll find my own way
I'll find it
(Dilemma)
Dilemma
I have to go right now
I know that
Dilemma
But I can't leave you alone
My heart is torn apart
I don't know which way to go
Translated by Releska
"Hai" (Love)
What I feel when I'm lost
When the wind blows
Like the scent of flowers
Later
I'm not as lonely as I thought
Even if I walk alone, don't worry
I may be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path
Even if you're always looking for a
place to stay
You don't have to worry
Because the circuit is moving
Towards the next one
Let's go!
No matter where we go
I'm distracted by the endless scenery
I miss the flowers at my feet
There's someone who's watching over me,
who's so clumsy
Fate isn't something you can make bloom
It's something that only happens on
spring days
I remember it as if it were a miracle
I'm prepared for this season, it's okay
I'm prepared for this peaceful day
Look up at the sky that's different from
yesterday
Life is changing day by day
The atmosphere is changing
I want to be happy now and in the middle
of the future
Let's do it and move forward!
Smile
Wow wow wow wow wow wow
Everyone was afraid
The darkness of loneliness
Actually, even if I'm alone
I can go on forever
(I want to be closer to you)
(I want you to be by my side)
The world is overflowing with someone's
presence
I'm not alone in someone's voice or
someone's warmth
I was told that, until today
Don't think too much
I'm not as lonely as I thought
I was walking alone, but
I might be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
(I want to be closer to you)
(I want you to be by my side)
Wherever it is
Wow wow wow wow wow wow
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Thank you so much for the encore!
Thank you so much!
Well,
the anniversary live is about to end.
Thank you so much!
I'm so lonely.
It was a short time,
two days.
Yesterday,
there was a graduation ceremony
of Mizuho Habu.
I was so happy.
Thank you so much.
Really.
We were supposed to give HUB a surprise.
But we got the opposite surprise
yesterday.
Some of you may not have seen it.
When we were singing "Sakurazaka no
uta",
we were going to send a message to the
audience.
But HUB prepared a bouquet for each
member
and gave us a message.
It was really...
Yesterday and today, I think each of us
is like that, and I think that each of
you who have seen it will be able to
make various memories.
I'd like to ask the members a lot of
questions, but how was Airi today?
Yes, I'm Airi Taniguchi.
The three of us went to see the final
performance of "As You Know" last year.
At that time...
I was really worried that I wouldn't be
able to stand on the stage with my
seniors like this.
I think I've been able to welcome them
for about a year, so I hope I'll be able
to perform with my seniors next year as
well.
I'm going to follow my favorite seniors'
backs,
and I'm going to do my best while
looking for what I can do by myself.
That's great.
Thank you.
We are always stimulated by the 3rd
generation, so we want to do our best to
show our cool back.
Can I ask Hikaru?
Thank you. Did you have fun today?
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
I love live performances, so I'm glad to
meet so many people today.
I'm really happy to be able to celebrate
the 3rd anniversary of SAKURAZAKO46.
But live performances make you feel a
lot of different emotions, don't they?
There are various songs, performances,
and it's fun.
It's very, I don't know, it's very
quiet.
I think each and every one of these
people has their own emotions, their own
daily lives, and their own lives.
That's what I think.
There may be some people who have fun
and sometimes have a hard time in their
daily lives,
but I feel like we have become one by
sharing our feelings here.
I was really happy, and I always think
that I would be very happy if I could be
a place like that for everyone.
We are really encouraged by the fact
that so many people have responded to
the performance, such as the call and
the demo that you just did.
Of course, we will continue to do our
best in the stadium for the fourth year
in a row.
We are very happy to be able to perform
in such a big venue, but we will do our
best in the fourth year in a row to aim
for even greater strength, so please
continue to support us.
Thank you.
Next, Yui-san, can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Well, this year, we've challenged a lot
of things and tried a lot of things.
We were able to do this because of the
BUDDIES.
BUDDIES are really essential to us.
Today, too, we were able to do it behind
the scenes.
It seems that this venue, where BUDDIES
are, surrounds us a lot.
I realized that we received so much
love.
We really love BUDDIES.
We will continue to be BUDDIES.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I think each of the members had a lot of
thoughts for the 3rd anniversary.
I'm really glad that I was able to
celebrate my 3rd anniversary at the
Zozomarin Stadium.
But at the time when it was just opened,
I was really nervous.
I didn't know what kind of group
SAKURAZAKA was,
or what kind of group SAKURAZAKA was.
I didn't even know the members.
But I made a lot of progress.
Even when I was performing, there were
times when I didn't know how to deliver
this song.
Even though I didn't know, I was
wondering what I should do.
I've been working hard on a group called
Sakurazuka 46.
That's why I didn't know how to deliver
this song.
I just wanted to deliver it to the
members here.
I'm really happy that I can see this
view now because of the support of the
members and the staff who are always
there for me.
But if it was last year or this time, I
would have been a little frustrated.
If it was this year's tour, I would have
had a little bit of a gap in my mind.
This year, I released 3 singles, and I
challenged myself to perform overseas
for the first time.
And this year, at the end of the year, I
have a day to celebrate with everyone.
Thank you so much for this year.
This year was really special for me.
I feel like it was a year that was a
little different from the past.
But I was able to feel that way.
As I said earlier, I came here believing
in the members and staff.
But the most important thing is that I
had the support and support of BUDDIES.
I really want to tell you that this is
the present.
We can really do our best because we
have BUDDIES.
I want to tell you a lot.
I want to repay you for all the love
you've given me.
And for the fourth year, I want to go
see a lot of scenery with BUDDIES again.
I feel like BUDDIES and we can do
anything.
And it's the last song in a flash.
And I said a little bit earlier.
However, I would like to sing with
everyone here and everyone who is
watching the live broadcast while
savoring this little time left.
Let's listen to it.
One, two...
Sakura Sakano Da!
Thank you for watching!
I thought ordinary days would be like a
dream
But it wasn't like that
Until the day I couldn't see you
There was a hole in my heart
The real loneliness isn't when there's
no one around
It's when I can't see the people I care
about
I don't know what happened
But I'm sure you can overcome it
Oh, oh, oh, oh
I've never forgotten the day when the
cherry blossoms were in full bloom
Even if spring passes and the flowers
fall
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that I can remember forever
We'll gather on this hill
And talk about you
Then I'll feel like I can see you again
I'm sure there were sad things that you
couldn't tell anyone
I was watching from afar and I was
worried
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to stand up
Oh, oh, oh, oh
The cherry trees in full bloom
Are facing the gentle winter wind
What were you waiting for
On the branches of the willows?
Even if the people passing by
Forget the flowers of that day
We'll remember the scenery of the next
spring
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
In the nostalgia that fills my heart
Like each petal embracing one another
The cherry blossoms will be in full
bloom
Oh, oh, oh, oh
The cherry trees in full bloom
Have never been forgotten
Even if the flowers fall after spring
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that I can remember forever
We'll gather on this hill
If we talk about you
I feel like we can meet again
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much for watching the live
stream!
Wow, the fireworks are beautiful!
I'm so happy to be able to see such
beautiful fireworks with the BUDDIES.
I'm so happy to be able to gather with
so many people in such a cold weather.
I'm so happy to be able to watch the
live stream.
We really love you, BUDDIES!
That's all!
We are Takarazuka 4 Music!
Thank you!
Oh, I'm sorry!
One more time!
Say "I love you" first.
BUDDIES, we love you!
That's all!
We are Takarazuka 4 Music!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Yeah!
Make the next song come out, please!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for everything!
I love you!
Thank you!
Let's be together again!
I love you!
Thank you!
See you!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
(Applause)