AISubs v3.2
Ame Talk Simulation
Today's topic is Ame Talk Simulation!
We would like to experience Ame Talk
So, Sakura Meets and Ame Talk's staffs
are going to do a collaboration
Nice to meet you
The set is also brought from Ame Talk
It's real, isn't it?
Yes, it is
This is crazy
No, it's not crazy at all
The scenery is too Ame Talk
Yes, Kaji-kun is here too
I always watch
So, tonight, Sakura Meets
Meets Ame Talk
I'm a member of Sakura Saka 46
Let's appeal the charm of Sakura Saka 46 to Ms. Otohara
We also have a special guest
I'm sorry to the fans
I don't know much about you
So, if it's just me
I think it's going to be crazy
So, I invited a person
May I?
Please come in
Hello
I'm calling a person.
May I?
Who is it?
Please come in.
Hello.
It's Kucchi.
I'm sorry, Kucchi.
You look like an interesting idol.
Please sit down.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I was recording all day yesterday.
Did you cheat on me?
No, I didn't.
We don't talk except when we're recording.
No, we don't.
Kucchi is on a TV show.
Yes, he is.
We've been doing this show together for a long time.
He's been watching us since our debut.
Do you know these four people?
I don't have a particular image of these four people.
No way.
I think these four people like variety shows and work hard.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm a little nervous.
We're going to have a lot of fun talking today.
Don't do that.
Kucchi and Chabana are a little...
We're going to start from the top.
Are you sure?
Sakurazaka46's basic information.
I'm sorry.
First of all, I'd like you to know what kind of group
Sakurazaka46 is.
I'd like the viewers to know.
Please tell me.
I'm sure the viewers are your fans.
That's why I told you at the beginning.
I don't want you to get angry.
I'm sure you're angry.
It's okay.
Let's start from the top.
I'm going to study.
These are the members of Sakurazaka46.
There are five first-generation students.
We're all second-generation students.
There are 29 students in total.
By the way, do you know any members?
Do you know any members?
Please introduce someone.
Are you here?
Wait a minute. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if you don't know.
I have no choice but to bite here.
How about Yui Kobayashi?
Yui Kobayashi seems to have a name.
Yui Kobayashi has a name.
Isn't it the same?
Yui Kobayashi, what do you think?
I'm sorry.
Yui Kobayashi doesn't seem to have a name.
Yui Kobayashi is mistaken for someone.
I looked it up.
Tamura is a comedian.
Morita Hikaru is a comedian.
What is this?
I said this at the beginning.
I don't know if Tamura is a comedian.
Tamura is a comedian.
I can see that.
However, he was not related to Kobayashi.
It's hard to get the information of such a person.
First of all, I asked Tsuchiya to follow the members and me.
I'm the captain of the group.
My name is Rina Matsuda, a second-generation student.
I'm active in the morning information program.
You are active in the morning information program of AKASAKA.
The four of us, Inoue, Onuma, Takemoto, and Masumoto
are members of SAKURA MEETS.
The center of the latest song is the second- generation
student, Karin Fujiyoshi.
She is the main character of the drama called Azatoku.
It's amazing.
Does Tsuchiya know all the members of the second-
generation students?
I know all the members of the second-generation students.
The third-generation students are new.
I know the names of the members of the third-
generation students.
So if I live at once, I can know where I was born.
Shizuoka, Hyogo, Shizuoka, and Hyogo.
That is normal.
I have a younger brother, an older brother, an older
sister, an older sister, and a younger sister.
Tsuchiya, you're disgusting.
It's hard for me and Saabe.
Every time a new member comes in, I hide my name and
give him a quiz.
How many members are there in Sakura Meets?
We don't have a clear reason yet.
But you think you're strong, don't you?
I have a strong habit.
You have a strong habit.
I'm not good at controlling my strength.
For example, if you throw a ball and catch it, you'll
be able to control your strength.
I can't believe it.
I can't control my strength.
You have a strong habit.
You're the closest to Ken Horiyuchi in our industry.
You get along well with Ken.
Yes.
When I was on a program with Ken Horiyuchi, I was able
to talk to him even when the camera wasn't rolling.
I think we have a lot in common.
It's the first time I've seen you in the world.
I don't think I'm in the human world.
I think you're like my father.
I don't like that kind of father.
Kirako is a person who makes everyone laugh.
There's a chair with a hole in the back.
If you put your face out of the chair and try to
surprise everyone, you'll fall for it.
Adults will think it's a big deal.
You're really like Ken Horiyuchi.
Inori is gentle.
You're gentle.
I can't believe it.
You don't have to say that.
What's your weak point?
I'm not good at all.
Say it.
I'm doing a radio show, but I'm not good at talking.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's important.
The radio show is especially important.
What do you think?
Takemoto comes to me and does a variety show.
I think Takemoto is like Shikiri.
I think he's reading the script.
Is that so?
Is he that kind of person?
Yes.
He's a hard-working person.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
There's a member of this team whose name came up in the
candy talk.
Do you remember?
His name came up in the candy talk.
His name hasn't come up in the candy talk.
His name has come up in the candy talk.
I have a video clip.
Did his name come up in the candy talk?
Next, we will talk about the 7th generation of comedy.
First of all, there is a problem that his partner likes
idols too much.
I like Takemoto Yui.
I found out that he refused to go to a comedy show
because he liked idols too much.
I was told that I missed it because there was a handshake event.
I remembered.
It was before.
Takemoto Yui was lined up at the handshake event.
That's Yui.
That's right.
I'm glad.
Do you know her?
If there is an online handshake event, please come again.
If there is an online handshake event every week,
please come every week.
I'm actually with Takemoto Yui.
Are you calling her?
I'm actually calling her.
I'm trapped in the basement.
Are you trapped?
I'm in a different room.
It's too early for the staff to work in the studio.
You made a promise at the online handshake event last
year or two years ago.
That's right.
You promised to work together someday.
You made a promise to work together someday.
I appeared on AmeTalk several times.
That's right.
Every time I appear on AmeTalk, I announce it to Takemoto Yui.
I announce that I will appear on AmeTalk.
AmeTalk starts at 23.15.
That's right.
There is a message application of SAKURAZAKA.
I received a message from Takemoto Yui at 22.50 on the
day of the broadcast of AmeTalk.
Can I hear the truth?
I remember that.
Please watch it.
I'm watching all the programs you appear on.
Thank you very much.
Can I watch all the programs you appear on?
Can I see all the programs you appear on?
You can't leave that room.
The walls will get closer over time.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
I will invite you again.
I was surprised.
I, Takemoto, have a question for Mr. Hotawara.
What is it?
Please take a look at the photo.
What?
Why?
You are a former student of Kishu.
Yes, I am.
Actually, my grandfather used to be a teacher.
What?
A teacher?
Yes.
Kaji-kun, you are so negative.
Yes, he is a pervert.
I love these two.
They are from Shiga.
They are from Ritto.
Hey, you are too loud.
Ritto?
You are so funny.
I call him Yuichi-kun.
You call him Yuichi-kun?
Yes, all my family members call him that.
Tsuchi, you are so negative.
Of course, I know.
Even you, Tsuchi, know him.
My grandmother and Yuichi's mother are very close.
I often go to Yuichi-kun's parents' house.
You are very close.
You are like a relative.
You are like a relative's brother.
I often go to Yuichi-kun's training room and play with him.
Because he is small.
I often dance with him.
I see.
I can't believe that your voice got higher.
I was surprised.
I went to Dubai with my grandfather.
Did you go to Dubai?
Yes, I went to Dubai.
Did you go to Dubai with your grandfather?
Yes, I did.
My birthday coincided with the race.
So, I celebrated my birthday in Dubai.
How old do you think your birthday is?
Your birthday is 15 years old.
You spent your birthday in Dubai.
Really?
Yes, I did.
Takemoto remembered it.
I did it.
I want to talk about horse racing with you.
There is a horse racing game.
There is a golf game.
There is a baseball game.
I like shrimp Doria.
Shrimp Doria?
Yes.
I found out on the Internet that I like shrimp Doria.
I am a father.
I can prepare shrimp.
I think I will like it.
I don't hate shrimp Doria.
But I never said that I like shrimp Doria.
You said that on the Internet.
I eat shrimp Doria.
Next time, they will show the charm of SAKURAZAKA46.
I will show it.
That's good.
I am strong against pain.
They will talk about the behind-the-scenes of the music video.
They will talk about the funny episodes during rehearsal.
They will try to jump on a rope.
It's a Lodge quiz.
After this, they will play a game with Lodge.
Hello.