Through this training camp, I want you
to get closer to the real members of
SAKURAZAKA 4K6.
I can dance, but my movements are still
small.
If I don't dance more dynamically, I
won't be able to grow on stage.
This pose of SAKURAZAKA 4K6 is really
important.
I definitely don't want you to forget
this.
SAKURAZAKA 4K6
I'm excited when I think I'm going to be
in a place like this, but I'm just happy
to be able to wear it.
Welcome to KURATAKA!
I want to be able to perform better in
the future.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
I'm so excited.
I can't stop laughing.
India is the best!
Thank you so much, I'm so happy!
Thank you!
I don't want to change this world
I'm not going to be buried in this dirt
The window I closed with the breath I
took
Let's change the key to my heart
But if you still want to dream
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
I'm despairing on my own
Because I don't have a point of view
No, no, no, don't blame others
The only thing left is a game
If so, I'd rather choose loneliness
No, no, no, nobody's fault
I can't change how I live
I've grown up before I knew it
I don't want to hear any crying
But I screamed
I don't want to change this world
No, no, no, don't blame others
The only thing left is a game
I can't change how I live
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No matter how hard I try, I can't take a
step forward
Yeah, yeah, it's a game
You'll understand when the wind blows
Yeah, light and shadow overlap again and
again
You'll understand when the time comes
Don't blame others
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
I don't want to hear any crying
But I screamed
No, no, no, don't blame others
The only thing left is a game
I can't change how I live
No, no, no, nobody's fault
I don't want to change this world
No matter how hard I try, I can't take a
step forward
Yeah, yeah, it's a game
You'll understand when the wind blows
Yeah, light and shadow overlap again and
again
You'll understand when the time comes
Don't blame others
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No, no, no, don't blame others
No matter how hard I try, I can't take a
step forward
The only thing left is a game
I can't change how I live
No, no, no, nobody's fault
I don't want to change this world
When the clouds clear up
I'll wait for the sun here
Sunny darling, from far away
My love is overflowing
Even if I look up, it doesn't change
I'm expecting a rainbow somewhere
Sunny darling, it's painful
Someday, when will it come?
I have an unopened umbrella
Right now, for you
No matter what happens, I'll never stop
I believe in eternal love
There's no rain, there's no rain
That's what everyone says
But is that really true?
I'm drawn to you more and more
Right now, for you
No matter what happens, I'll never stop
I have an unopened umbrella
I'm asking myself a question
It's painful, when I think about it
I can't breathe normally
I hate half-heartedness
But I can't decide which is better
I can become my own arm
I should jump out of my anxiety
If I had the courage
I'm sure it would rain
I don't know anything
Even if I'm covered in hot clouds
I can't reach you
Oh, oh, oh
If I had the courage
I'm sure it would rain
My love for you is piling up
Even if I look up, it doesn't change
It scatters somewhere
It's painful, when I think about it
I can't breathe normally
I have an unopened umbrella
Right now, for you
No matter what happens, I'll never stop
I believe that eternity is love
There's no answer
That's love
My love for you is piling up
I can't stop
Good evening, everyone. We are
"Sakurazaka46"
The live part of "Omotenashikai" has
started
The first song we performed was
"Nobody's Fault" which is the debut song
of Sakurazaka46.
Itoha, how did you feel when you
performed it?
Well, since it was the first live
performance, I was really nervous.
How was it, everyone?
I was nervous.
You were nervous, weren't you?
Well, it's really up to me, but...
It was the song I practiced the most
while saying, "I have to do my best!"
I was very happy to be able to perform
it in front of everyone today.
Nobody's Fault's center Yuu also helped
me a lot during the practice, so we
practiced together many times.
The next song we performed was
"Samidareyo".
Miyu, how was it?
My costume came off.
My shoes came off too.
I was dancing while thinking that
everyone was making a good expression.
It was our first time performing in
front of an audience,
so we were a little nervous.
But thanks to everyone's enthusiasm,
we're able to enjoy ourselves and
perform on stage.
I'd like to move on to the second half
of the show.
Are you still excited?
Can you make some more noise?
I will challenge various songs in the
future.
Please continue to enjoy.
"Kimi ni Auritakatta Yo" (I Wanted To
See You)
Yo!
I wanted to see you for a long time.
Look at this clear sky.
Yo!
The world hasn't changed at all.
We are the same as we were back then.
Yo!
The wind of summer, the scent of
flowers.
Yo!
The sunrise that breaks on the day of
prayer.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I stole everything.
It's already passed.
As if nothing had happened.
This earth is a peaceful ABC.
Let's fly.
Yo!
I can't stand still here.
Let's step forward.
Now is the time to move forward.
Yo!
We are looking at something far away.
Is there really hope?
Yo!
If I'm with you, I'm sure I can go.
If I'm with you, I'll get there.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
We are buddies.
We are dreaming.
Even if you lose something,
Tomorrow will come again.
It's sad.
The rain and wind are darkness.
A new day will dawn.
The sunrise that breaks on the day of
prayer.
Yo!
Let's start our journey from here.
We are free.
Because we don't have anything.
Yo!
We can go anywhere.
Let's throw away despair with tears.
Yo!
I've been waiting for you.
Let's go to the future.
We are friends.
We are dreaming.
Yo!
How are you? I wanted to see you.
Look at this blue sky.
Yo!
The world hasn't changed at all.
We are the same as we were then.
Yo!
The seasonal wind, the scent of flowers.
The green trees, the morning sun.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
We are friends.
We are dreaming.
Everyone!
Are you having fun?
Thank you very much.
I can see you all the way up there.
The first song in the second half was
"Buddies".
This song is of course very important to
us,
but it is also a very important song to
Buddy's.
I think we were able to enjoy it
together
because we were able to use the stage
from end to end and get close to
everyone.
Thank you very much.
Then, shall we talk about the MV?
Yes, the MV of "Natsu no Chikamichi".
Shall we talk about the MV of "Natsu no
Chikamichi"?
Everyone, did you watch it?
Thank you very much.
The first thing that impressed me about
the MV was the dance of the two of you,
wasn't it amazing?
Thank you.
It was really cold on the day of the MV
shooting, wasn't it?
It was snowing.
Yes, the scene where we run down the
corridor, the second chorus, it was
snowing and cherry blossoms were
falling.
It was really beautiful.
During the rehearsal of "Omotenashikai",
we received a report that we went to see
it a million times.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Next, Airi.
I'm Airi Taniguchi.
The next song is a very important song
for us, the 3rd generation, and it's
also the first song we've received.
We're going to perform it for the first
time today, so everyone, please get
excited!
I'm nervous, but if I can hear your
voices, I think I'll be able to relax,
so please shout out a lot!
Thank you!
Let's listen to "Natsu no Chikamichi"
"Natsu no Chikamichi"
Hold the summer's shortcut with your
right hand
There is a light in the east and the
west of the wind
Even though it looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wonder if it was good
Your smile on the way home
For some reason, it's getting sad
I hope tomorrow will come soon
I can't catch up with you
I'm walking ahead of me
I'm waiting for a chance to talk
I want to take you to the sea sometimes
Where should I look for the summer's
shortcut?
I can't wait for the next season
Because love is always a hassle
Tell me the future map
Hold the summer's shortcut with your
right hand
There is a light in the east and the
west of the wind
Even though it looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wonder if it was good
I wasn't in a hurry until now
I have to learn how to shoot
I have to hurry the distance of my heart
It's the order of shooting
I want to skip
No matter what I do
I can't hand you over to anyone else
How long will this rainy road last?
The rain won't stop in the dark
Let's find a place where we can meet
under the clouds
Let's go around the road
and chase the miracle
If you turn the corner in front of you
There is already a summer's entrance
If possible, slowly
I want to fall in love with you
Because of my rival, I don't have time
Let's find a summer's shortcut
I want to shoot the next season
Because love is always a hassle
Tell me the future map
Let's go around the road
and chase the miracle
If you turn the corner in front of you
There is already a summer's entrance
Let's go around the road
and chase the miracle
I didn't know what to do, so I just
stood still
I saw everyone getting better and better
I thought I should do my best
When I was told that I was a dancer, not
an idol
I was very frustrated
I couldn't do it at all
The seniors I saw yesterday will go
first, so I have to do my best and catch
up with everyone.
I've been dancing for 6 years, but I
haven't been able to compete at all.
I feel like I'm not conscious enough.
I can't remember my body perfectly.
I'm really proud of myself.
I'm upset.
I think I can support someone.
I hope we can support each other and
achieve our goals.
I practiced with the help of everyone.
I'm glad to feel that we've become
friends.
We've been working together as a team
for the past month.
We've been making a 3rd generation
version.
When someone is practicing, when they
are in pain or sad,
We've been supporting each other.
I'll show you the best performance I can
do now.
Let's go!
I was watching a video on my smartphone
until dawn.
There's no way I can wake up from that.
I was late for everything.
I fell asleep again today.
I went to the bathroom to take a shower.
Then I went to bed.
Why did I pretend to sleep and wake up?
What do you want to do? What do you want
to do?
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I've been playing games all the time.
What happened to you?
Where did you go?
Why are you so busy?
Wait a minute.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I'm the only one who can live my life.
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned,
Even if I'm told I can't do it,
I can't be a different person now.
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned,
Even if I'm told I can't do it,
I understand.
I won't do anything if I'm banned.
God, can't I do anything?
I want to know where the standard is.
The time I was worried about
disappears without doing anything.
If I were you,
I could do anything.
What are you doing here?
Tell me who you're playing with.
It's something I have to change.
Suddenly, I was told
that I was in the wrong place.
What should I do if I'm banned?
I just didn't know.
One more time?
Let's start over.
Give me a chance.
What should I do if I'm banned?
Are you going to abandon me?
I used to believe that
it was for the sake of worry.
God,
please forgive me.
Suddenly, I was told
that I was in the wrong place.
The sun is too bright.
It's leaking from the wind.
Until the darkness comes,
I'll keep running.
Even if I'm banned,
even if I'm noticed,
even if I'm told that I'm useless,
I can't be negative anymore.
Even if I'm banned,
even if I'm noticed,
even if I'm told that I should stop,
I don't regret it
even if I'm told that I'm stupid.
God, can't I do anything?
Do you know where the standard is?
Even if I'm driven into a situation like
this,
I will never be banned.
Thank you!
I'm Rika Hachimori.
It's a miracle that I was able to join a
group that I've liked for 7 years as a
3rd generation student.
Since I was little, I've been alone a
lot.
I was afraid of what people would think
of me.
I was afraid to interact with people.
That's one of the reasons I wanted to
change myself and apply for the
audition.
And...
The performance I just showed you
Among the three amazing students
To be honest, I was very scared to be in
the center
But
I did my best, and at the meet-and-
greet, everyone complimented me, saying
that I did well and that they were
looking forward to it, so I was able to
do my best today.
Thank you very much.
Everyone is so big to me, and I thought
I needed everyone.
I will do my best to contribute to
SAKURADAKA46 from now on.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm Riko Endo.
Before I joined Sakurazaka 46,
I often thought that I could still do it
even if I tried hard.
But after I joined Sakurazaka 46,
I thought that I was doing my best.
Now, as a member of Sakurazaka 46,
and as a member of Sakurazaka 46,
it's really fun to be able to do my
best.
I want to be an idol who can continue to
work hard without forgetting to be
grateful that there is a place to work
hard,
and I want to be an idol who can make
BUDDIES happy that I joined Sakurazaka
someday.
Thank you.
I'm Reina Odakura, a 18-year-old high
school student from Tokyo.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you.
I've been afraid of failing and getting
hurt since I was a kid.
I've been looking at myself from the
moment I took a step.
That's how I feel.
I hated it so much that I couldn't help
it.
But I gave up on Sakura Saka and tried
something completely different from what
I've done so far.
I tried a lot of new things, I failed a
lot, I cried a lot.
Every time I got over it with everyone
in the 3rd generation, I thought, "Am I
growing up?"
I'm happy now.
I don't think life can be without scars.
So, I want to be a person who can sit
next to BUDDIES and have words and
expressions that I can lean on.
I will do my best from now on, so thank
you.
BUDDIES
I'm Nagisa Kojima, a 17-year-old high
school student from Nagano prefecture.
I've always loved idols since I was a
kid.
Last summer, I auditioned for an idol
for the first time.
Then I passed the audition for
"Sakurazaka46".
A lot of things happened to me.
It was a training camp.
I was shooting a music video.
Of course, there were fun things, but
there were a lot more painful,
frustrating, and painful things than
that.
But at that time, I met my ten friends
here.
Since then, I've experienced a lot of
things.
A lot of bonds have been born, and my
favorite words are "friendship" and
"effort".
The feeling of thinking about such
friends is getting stronger and
stronger, and now I'm standing in front
of you.
I had a lot of thoughts about coming
this far, but I'm really happy to be
able to stand in front of you with these
11 people.
From now on, I think there will be more
difficult things, more fun things, and
more fun things than the training camp.
At that time, I want to hold hands with
these 11 people and BUDDIES and do my
best to become an idol a year ahead.
I'll do my best, so please continue to
support me.
That's all from Nagisa Kojima.
I'm Hairi Taniguchi, 17 years old, from
Yamaguchi prefecture.
I've been dreaming of becoming an idol
since I was in kindergarten.
I'm so happy to be on the first step of
my dream of becoming an idol.
The place I've been dreaming of is so
beautiful.
My family, who have been supporting me
for a long time, came to see me today.
I have a younger brother.
My younger brother told me that he would
go to my first live today.
This is my first live performance in my
life.
My family told me that they wanted to go
to Sakurazaka 46.
I really love that kind of family.
And the BUDDIES who are watching me now
are watching me with very warm eyes.
From now on, I'm going to perform in
Sakurazaka 46.
I want to do my best.
And I want to become a person who can
shine more and more.
Please continue to support me.
I'm Izuki Nakashima, 20 years old, from
Fukuoka prefecture.
My dream is to have you cheer for me
from the bottom of my heart.
I love the meet-and-greet I participated
in the other day.
And I love the live performance today.
I'm so happy to be able to meet you.
Thank you.
I hope that only good things will happen
to all the 3rd Gen students and all the
BUDDIES.
But there may be times when that is not
the case.
I want them to remember me and feel
relieved.
I want to be a strong presence for them.
I will continue to cherish my bond with
the 3rd generation and my time with you.
I will do my best to lead a wonderful
life as an idol.
Thank you.
I'm Mio Mato, 16 years old, from Fukuoka
prefecture.
I first met this group when I was in
elementary school.
I still vividly remember the shock I
felt when I watched that performance on
TV when I didn't know what being an idol
was like.
I've always been supportive of many
different people.
I want to be a person who can support
others.
If I didn't have that feeling,
and if I didn't happen to watch the TV
show at that time,
I don't think I would have been able to
stand in front of you now.
And I want to be myself more than ever.
The reason why I can be myself is
because of you who have been supporting
me for only 2 months.
I can only feel this wonderful scenery
today, but I think it will be engraved
in my heart for the rest of my life.
My goal is to cheer someone up.
That's why I joined this group.
I will do my best to become a beautiful
and strong idol like a cherry tree.
And when I'm sad, I'd be happy if you
could look at me and smile.
Thank you very much.
I'm Itoha Mukai, a 16-year-old high
school student from Hiroshima
prefecture.
I'm most happy in my life that I was
able to join my favorite Sakurazuka 46
as a 3rd year student.
My life has changed 180 degrees since I
became a 3rd year student.
And I have changed a lot.
I feel like I have changed a little.
Negative, crybaby,
and clumsy me,
the ten people who warmly embraced me,
and me, who still can't do anything,
my seniors and managers who are kind to
me,
and my BUDDIES who give me a lot of
happiness.
I feel like I was able to like myself a
little bit, which I hated so much.
Right now, I'm just supported by so many
people.
I may not be able to do anything, but
I'm sure I'll bring you a lot of
happiness one day.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Yuu Murai, 18 years old from Tokyo.
I've been thinking about what kind of
idol I want to be,
so I'd like to talk about it.
BUDDIES have their own daily lives,
and today was a happy day,
and it was fun,
but it was a little hard,
and I had a lot of thoughts.
I think there are many days like that,
but I hope I can always be by your side
and share my feelings.
When you suddenly think about me,
I hope you feel better and feel lighter.
I think I'm very, very happy.
I'm still inexperienced, but I hope I
can continue to move forward with
everyone in the 3rd generation,
and with my heart-warming, reliable, and
cool seniors,
and with everyone in the warm and kind
BUDDIES.
I'll do my best from now on.
Thank you for your support.
I'm Miyu Murayama, 18 years old from
Tokyo.
I'm afraid to show my weakness to
others,
but I met 10 people who accepted it.
And I met my favorite seniors in the
world
through BUDDIES.
I was able to join the group that I love
the most in the world and receive a lot
of happiness.
I hope I can join Sakurazaku 46 and make
someone happy.
I will do my best, so please support me.
Thank you very much.
I'm Shizuki Yamashita, 18 years old,
from Kyoto Prefecture.
Thank you for coming to our 3rd
generation's opening ceremony.
I was announced 2 days ago.
To be honest, I was worried if you would
accept me.
I was worried, but...
I'm very happy that you welcomed me
warmly.
I've experienced a lot of emotions since
I joined Asakurazuka46.
There were a lot of fun and hard times,
but...
My most recent feeling is...
I'm glad I was able to meet such a
wonderful 11 people.
Thank you to everyone who has always
supported me.
I was very happy to meet you, and I
think I wouldn't have been able to
experience it if I hadn't joined
Sakurazaka 46.
Thank you so much for making my place.
I will continue to create more and more
wonderful scenery.
I will do my best so that I can see it
with everyone. Thank you.
Well then, this is the last song for
today's "Motenashi-kai".
Please listen to it.
One, two...
"Sakurazaki Aman-tan"!
"Sakurazaki Aman-tan"
I thought ordinary days were normal
But they weren't
I couldn't see you until today
There was a hole in my heart
The real loneliness isn't that there's
no one around
It's that I want to meet someone
important
I don't know if it's love or not
But I'm sure you can overcome it
Oh, oh, oh...
I've never forgotten
The days of cherry blossoms
Even if spring passes and flowers fall
Dreams should bloom here again
So that I can remember forever
Let's gather here
If I can talk about you
I feel like I can meet you again
There were sad things that I couldn't
tell anyone
I made a mistake for the first time
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to tell me
Oh, oh, oh...
The days of cherry blossoms
Facing the wind of spring and winter
I couldn't tell you
What I've been waiting for
People who are too honest
Even if they forget the flowers of that
day
The scenery of the next spring
I was always thinking of you
Oh, oh, oh...
I've never forgotten
The kindness of the wind
Like the petals of a flower
Cherry blossoms will bloom again
Oh, oh, oh...
I've never forgotten
Even if spring passes and flowers fall
Dreams should bloom here again
So that I can remember forever
Let's gather here
If I can talk about you
I feel like I can meet you again
Oh, oh, oh...
"Thank you"
Thank you everyone for today
Did you enjoy the first stage of the 3rd
season?
Thank you
We are really glad to be able to meet
you today
And I'm really happy to be able to share
what we've been practicing with you
Thank you for watching until the end.
Today, we are going to perform...
One, two...
We are Sakurazaka46!
Thank you!
Sakurazaka46!
Did you hear the encore from backstage?
I didn't think I'd get it, so I'm really
happy.
Thank you very much.
I was so moved.
I'm so happy to be able to perform with
so many BUDDIES at such a wonderful
venue for the first time.
Can I sing one more song?
Everyone, can you make the best sound at
the end?
The last song, let's get excited!
"Summer's shortcut"
It won't reach
I travel further than you
So why don't we spend this chance
together?
I want to have a date to go to the sea
Where can I look for "Summer's
shortcut"?
The next season's door will open
Love is always a hassle
So teach me the future map
Take a right on the summer shortcut
Go through the wind and sunlight
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wish I could invite you someday
I've never been in a hurry
I'm suddenly interested in the distance
between my heart
I'll wake up if I don't hurry
It's the order of the seasons
I want to skip
No matter what I do, no matter what I do
I can't hand you over to anyone else
How long will this rainy road last?
The rain won't stop at the bottom of the
darkness
Let's find a place where we can meet
At the edge of the clouds where the
light shines
Even if it's a long, winding road
I want to chase a miracle forever
If you turn the corner in front of you
That's the entrance to midsummer
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
If you can, take your time
I don't want to fall in love with you
Because of my rival, I don't have time
Let's find a place where we can meet
At the edge of the clouds where the
light shines
Love is always a hurry
Tell me the future map
On a summer day, with my right hand
Inside the wind and sunlight
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
That's the entrance to midsummer
Thank you very much for coming to the
3rd season of "Omochinashi-kai"
I will do my best to show you a lot of
wonderful scenery
And as the last "Omochinashi"
I'll be sending you off with all the
members of SANBISEI.
Please enjoy it to the end.
From now on, I'll be SAKURATAKA46.
Thank you for your support for the 3rd
generation.
We are Sakurazaka46.
Thank you for your support for the 3rd
generation.