AISubs v3.4
It's me! It's me!
"Sakura Mitsu" started in late April.
"Kakakakagun" was making delicacies.
This show is about members and comedians of
"Sakurasaka46" collaborating seriously.
"Tanaka", "Taxi", "Yamane"
It's an experimental variety show where we play games together.
Today, we will introduce some memorable first episodes.
We will also show you our collaboration with "fangirls".
We will also talk about our unreleased scenes that were
cut off from "on air".
Sakura Mitsu
If I don't show my emotions with a big explosion, I
don't think it will work.
By the time I finish this scene, I feel like I'm
getting stronger.
Takemoto Yui
Mitsu
fangirls
"Takemoto" will play a new director and "fangirls" will
play a new director.
Takemoto Yui
Takemoto
Can I do this? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You can do whatever you want.
Takemoto Yui
Mitsu
"fangirls" collaboration!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is the meeting okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Sakazaki-san was also on this show?
That's right.
Tanaka-chan, please help me.
It's okay.
Aren't you always helping me?
Please.
But today, it's not me.
The new director, Takemoto, will be directing for the first time.
It's my first time. Thank you for having me.
Thank you for having me.
I'm Tanaka of "ungirls".
You're young!
How old are you?
I don't want you to judge me by my age, so I can't say that.
Huh? Oh, I'm sorry.
Tanaka-chan, you can't say that now!
Huh?!
It's harassment!
Is that so?!
That's right!
Wow, I'm learning a lot!
I'm counting on you!
I'm sorry.
Then, hurry up with the meeting. I'll go see the scene.
Yes, I understand.
Teach him strictly.
Thank you.
Thank you for having me.
Then, this is today's script.
It's a new show called "Because We're Animals".
Yes.
Today, I'd like you, Tanaka-san, to massage an
alligator to make it feel good and make it sleep.
I'd like you to try that kind of project.
First of all, for the opening shooting, I'd like you to
briefly talk about your enthusiasm for today.
Yes.
But, for now, I'd like you to draw it in the script.
Massage an alligator? What kind of person is that?
I'd like you to say something like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then, I'll leave it up to you after this.
While you're moving, I'd like you to say just one word.
Yes.
Anyway, where is Yamane today?
Yama-ne!
I'd like you to say that.
Is it okay for you to say that much?
Yes...
Well...
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Please continue.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Then, you'll finally meet that alligator.
You'll meet a child alligator, right?
Yes, yes.
I'd like you to say "must" to that.
"Must", yes.
Hey, hey, who do you think I am?
There's no word "impossible" in the Tanaka dictionary.
Yodaredara
I'd like you to say it like that.
Is it "must"?
I'd like you to say "must" for now.
I can't say "yodaredara" at such a good timing.
Didn't you always say it like that?
I sometimes say it, but it's not like I'm aiming for it.
I see.
You'll finally meet the alligator you'll be massaging.
While you're looking at the child alligator,
you'll see a big alligator with meat in its back approaching you.
I'd like you to do it like that.
I'll give you an image.
Yes, yes.
No, no.
Massaging such a small alligator?
I'm not scared or anything like that.
No, no!
Hey, hey!
Yodaredara
Oh, no!
My nose is running.
I'm not that creepy!
I'm not doing it like that.
Did I do it too much?
I'm sorry.
It's not like, "Wow!"
By the way, how do you usually do it?
I always say, "What's up with this kid?"
It's like, "Wow, wow, wow!"
I'd like you to raise the tension a little more.
I'll do it for real!
No, no, no.
If you explain it like that...
No, it's not like that!
Takemoto, I'm sorry!
Forgive me for thinking you were a soldier of the Showa era!
No, Tanaka-chan, be careful!
Yes, yes.
I'll do something about it!
I'm sorry for making such a loud noise.
Yes, I'm sorry about that too.
I won't say anything like that outside.
I didn't do anything that horrible!
Please continue.
I'm sorry. Finally, I'll have you massage me.
Yes!
This is also a must for me.
It's a must for you.
Hey, hey, crocodile!
How do you like it?
Huh? It doesn't feel good.
It's just gross!
Hey, you took one crocodile!
Hey!
The crocodile is rampaging!
It just bit my hand!
Hey, my head is coming up!
I'm drooling!
My nose is running!
Hey, crocodile!
Stop it already!
You only care about other people's affairs!
You're the one who's been left behind the most!
What do you mean?
What do you mean "what do you mean"?
There aren't any comments like "the crocodile bit me"
or "the crocodile bit me completely"
because it hurts so much!
I'm sorry.
Usually, when you read a script, you don't have to imitate me.
Your imitation is always gross!
No, it's actually gross!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's gross!
No, no, no.
Tanaka-san!
No, no, no!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'm sorry!
I'm going to report this to the compliance committee!
What?
Didn't you have a lot of lines?
No, I was surprised that there were a lot of them.
I tried to remember them yesterday, but I couldn't.
I was like, "Oh, well."
And then I fell asleep again.
I had to do it over and over again until this morning.
Wow!
To be honest, I wasn't sure if I could do it.
For us, it's a regular show that we've been hoping for
for a long time.
It's our first time having you as a guest.
I know I can't fail here.
The members also said "it's our first time" and put a
lot of pressure on me.
Then it's not "us", right?
No, no, it's not like that.
It's better to call someone who's not in season.
Yamane forgot her lines and barely...
Barely...
Clearly...
She was like...
Reality, right?
There's a reality.
You say it the moment you come out, but you seriously forgot it.
Let's have a meeting and I'll go see you at the scene.
Yes, I understand.
Be strict and teach her.
She forgot this.
I'm sorry.
I barely said it, but she said "be strict", so I was
worried if I was using power harassment.
Well, well, it's the same.
And as a movement of the heart, she said "are you okay,
Takemoto?", but if I touch it, will it be sexual
harassment?
No, no, it's not like that.
She thought about a lot of things.
There were a lot of changes in the direction of production.
I was supposed to hit Takemoto's head in the end of the
script, right?
The staff said...
No, that's what Tanaka-san gets hit with on the internet.
On the internet?
Yes, on the internet.
Then I'll use my shoulder.
She thought about it a lot, right?
Yes, yes.
I'm grateful for her.
She got angry at me from the first meeting and I...
It's not like that.
She said "If you really want to do it, can you do it?"
I said "No, no, put it back."
I'm responsible for everything.
That's right.
Takemoto fans are scary.
No, no, it's warm, it's warm.
"Sakuranizu" airs every Thursday midnight at 1:56 pm.
"Terasa" also delivers past meetings.
Please check it out!