AISubs v3.2
This time, the script for Sakura Meets has arrived.
Thank you.
Yay!
Oh, it's The Mummy.
This program is a collaboration between members of
Sakurazaka46 and an entertainer.
I have to go now!
It's an experimental variety show where they play games together.
What kind of program is it this time?
This time, I'm going to do a demonstration.
A demonstration?
I'm looking forward to it.
Please watch it.
Watch it three times.
Watch it three times?
Yes.
Akiho Onuma
Three
The Mummy
Stop wasting time!
This time, Kanta is going to do a demonstration.
Did you say that to yourself?
Onuma is going to do a demonstration like Sakai.
The point is how to express the suspiciousness with the
voice and actions.
Mr. Onuma.
Yes.
You look like Mr. Sakai.
I look like an old man.
I feel like I can't speak clearly.
I can barely communicate.
Oh, this is...
This is important.
Oh, that's good.
Did you make this by yourself?
I made it, too.
It's so cute.
What is this?
I'll use this.
Let's do it.
Yes.
You have to shout.
Please leave me alone.
Yes.
I want to make you feel like you're talking.
That's amazing.
You're getting out of it little by little.
I'm sorry I'm getting out of it.
After the commercial, the real show starts.
Onuma Akiho
Miitsu
The Mummy
I'll never forgive you.
Stop wasting money!
Pay your bills!
If you don't, go to hell!
Excuse me, what are you doing here?
Are you a volunteer?
No, I just happened to pass by and heard a loud voice.
I was wondering what you were doing.
This is a demonstration.
Demonstration?
We have a lot of things to think about, so we do
demonstrations every day.
I see.
Would you like to join us?
I'm not dissatisfied with the country.
Country?
It has nothing to do with the country.
We are dissatisfied with ourselves.
Dissatisfied with ourselves?
We can't forgive ourselves!
That's why we make ourselves live.
Ourselves?
Stop it!
Pay your bills!
Didn't you pay your bills?
Yes.
We don't pay our bills because we waste money.
We are scum!
Scum! Get out of here!
How can you say that about yourself?
You're doing something amazing.
Are you going to participate in this self-demo?
Self-demo?
No, I'm not going to participate.
I have nothing to do with you.
So you're saying that we don't have to pay the pension?
What?
You're saying that we don't have to worry about the pension?
No, no, no.
You, uncivilized!
I'm not uncivilized! I'm uncivilized!
Don't say that!
You're scary. What's wrong with you?
We have to pay the pension.
Then let's put that feeling in the demo and tell us.
Come on, Seirei.
Hold this.
What is this?
Did you make this yourself?
I made this.
I thought it was super cute, but what is this?
Disgusting!
Did you stick the ribbon with glue?
It's hard to drink.
Okay, I'll use this.
Thank you!
Please don't use it and say it again and again.
Thank you.
What is it?
Let's continue.
Don't waste it!
Pay the pension you have to pay!
If you don't pay, you'll go to hell!
Is there a problem?
You've been saying something, but what is it?
I'm sorry.
I'm on the side that's being demonstrated.
You're on the side that's being demonstrated?
You're a stranger, but you're so annoying!
It's cute.
What is it?
But it's good.
It's a good idea.
Let's keep going.
Let's leave the pension thing aside.
Let's say something that we can't forgive ourselves.
Something serious.
Something serious?
Yes.
You continue.
Okay.
For example, I'm...
Even though I'm going to the pension,
don't take a taxi and go eat grilled meat!
Don't take a taxi and go eat grilled meat!
You continue.
What is it?
You're on the side that's being demonstrated.
I'm sorry.
I'm on the side that's being demonstrated.
It's scary.
What is it?
Can you do it?
It's that, right?
It's serious.
Why are you calling me onee-chan?
Don't put a fork on the sofa!
Your butt is bleeding!
You're putting a fork on the sofa?
I did.
Can you say that your butt is bleeding?
It's the truth!
You're cutting yourself.
Let's calm down.
It would have been nice if it was a spoon, but please
leave it alone.
It's an ad-lib, isn't it?
That's right.
I threw it all over the place.
I was surprised.
We just met a week ago.
I felt a little lucky.
I thought I could say it next time.
I couldn't say a word after receiving it.
The ad-lib is weak.
It would have been nice if it was a spoon, but I couldn't say it.
It would have been nice if it was a spoon, but please
leave it alone.
It was very difficult for me.
I wanted to make my voice like an old man.
Don't waste your time.
You have a good face.
There was a moment when I lost my character.
If I get depressed even for a moment, it's over.
This is a memo.
I'll write it down later.
He took a memo like this.
It's a job that makes you feel better.
It's embarrassing.
You're doing something weird.
It's like impersonating a gorilla.
It's a job that makes you feel better.
How do you do it?
I want to see it.
MAX GORILLA
It's fast.
It's embarrassing.
It's scary.
The owner panicked at the Yamanote Line Game.
It's a game where you have to bring in the guests.
What did The Mummy bring in?
It's a game where you have to bring in the hosts.
What kind of game is it?
You have to bring in the hosts, and then you have to
answer the questions.
You have to answer the questions, and then you have to
jump 10 times to clear the game.
Do we have to jump later?
Yes, that's why the order is important.
The beginning is the hardest part.
Let's do our best to clear the game.
We have to work together.
If you clear the game, you'll get a reward.
This is a cupcake from Elaz.
It's so cute.
It's a delicious cupcake.
Let's do our best to clear the game.
First, they challenge with The Mummy.
The first challenge is the King of Contest or M1 Grand
Prix winner.
Game start!
I have to go in first.
Nakagawa Kei!
Wait a minute.
Hurry up!
I went in!
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
I can't end it here.
I forgot that I have a really bad athleticism.
They change the order of Sakai in the second half and
challenge again in the same state.
Game start!
Laughing rice!
When do I go in?
Go!
Milk Boy!
Hurry up!
Air Stairs!
I went in!
I didn't go in!
Inoue!
You're late!
Was I late?
Hurry up and go in!
They change the order of Sakai in the last half and
challenge again in the same state.
The next challenge is the Egg dish.
Game start!
Boiled egg!
Wait, I'm scared.
I can't do it.
What's going on?
Stop it!
Hurry up and go in!
I didn't go in!
You can't jump from there!
You have to go in and jump!
Go!
You can do it!
Ready, go!
Go!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
I've never done this before!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
Masumoto, who's not good at this, is the first to go in.
It's the fourth time she's done this.
Game, start!
It's okay.
Now!
It's not a game where you say now!
You have to go this far!
Now!
I can't do this!
It was close, though.
For Masumoto, who's in despair,
the game starts when Onuma and Masumoto go in together.
Now! Now! Now!
Answer!
Egg dish!
Omurice!
Shopping!
Scrambled eggs!
What's the answer?
Did you say omelette?
Omelette?
That's it!
I'm so tired that I can't say that it's you guys.
It's time to decide the last one.
Let's decide it!
Oh no!
Let's eat that cake!
I want to eat it!
The next question is the name of the prefecture in Kyushu.
Let's decide it with this.
It's the last one.
Ready, start!
Okinawa?
Kumamoto!
Kagoshima!
Fukuoka!
Oita!
Saga!
Sakai!
Ready, start!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
I got it!
I did it!
I'm so happy!
Are you all right?
I'm so tired.
Me, too.
Thank you for your hard work!
The next episode is a long-distance journey.
Hey, Takahashi!
Don't be so violent!
It's obvious that they are in love.
Ready, start!
They are getting more and more excited.
I'm so happy!
Don't say that!
I'm so scared.
Who are you?