To be honest, I think I'm happy.
I've been working hard as a member of
the Sakurazaka team for a year.
I've always thought this scenery was a
miracle.
Thank you.
When I started as SAKURAZAKA, I had a
lot of anxiety.
I was numb. I thought this live would be
really good.
The basic production is a live
performance that competes with the
number of songs, so there are 35 songs
in total.
How many songs so far?
Until now, there were 16 songs in the
main story, and 2 songs in the encore.
So there are 36 songs in total.
In other words, there are 36 songs in 2
days.
So, in this show, it's a bit of a burden
on everyone.
Only the songs in red letters are
common.
In other words, only 7 songs are common.
Everything else is sunflower seeds.
It's been my ideal for a long time to
change the set list quite a lot in two
days.
I think there are people who come to
listen to one song that changes.
So doing a lot of songs means that
someone's favorite songs are included.
I'm going to go out.
I think it's a lot of pressure for both
the members and the staff, but I'm
happy.
I have a unit song with Fuu-chan and
Yui-kun, and we're talking about how
nice it would be if we could do that.
I think it's the last song when it comes
true, so I'd like to enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
It's been a while. I'm going to do my
best to recover from this live show
little by little.
I'll do my best little by little.
I came back for you.
I'm glad.
I think the fans will be happy, too.
They're waiting for us.
I'm glad.
I'll do my best little by little.
This time, the number of songs is very
large, so the rehearsal period is longer
than usual, and we were able to pass the
first song twice as a whole, so I think
we are able to prepare for a wider venue
than usual.
Please take a picture of me saying, "I'm
peeling it off properly."
First of all, I like the outdoors, so
it's fun to go around in a truck.
But I think the fans are cold.
And it's by the sea.
I cut my finger.
Good morning.
Let me explain.
Basically, all of these are in real
life.
The main stage's wing, Hanamichi,
and the Hanamichi going to the Kamishino
stage
cannot be recorded,
so I will fold it back here.
This white one is the front.
Enter from this arrow.
Is there a place to take a picture?
No, there isn't.
There isn't?
I forgot that I fell down.
That stage.
I was scared.
Haruru, Haruru.
It's written Haruru.
It was a hole.
Did you know that?
It's Haruru no matter how you look at
it.
It's so cute.
I'm sorry. I was worse than you.
I thought you gave up.
I was worse than you.
It's so cute.
Do a drone.
A drone?
Yes.
Because of H.A.B.U., the atmosphere
became brighter and we could laugh
together.
H.A.B.U. was one of the members who
could improve the atmosphere of the
venue.
The reason why H.A.B.U. is so bright is
because of the future activities of
H.A.B.U.
I wish H.A.B.U. was here.
I don't want them to graduate yet, but I
hope we can send them off warmly at the
last ceremony of ZOZO.
Thank you.
It was like a self-sacrifice.
It was three times bigger than I
thought.
It's a big venue, so there's a lot of
movement.
It's not good at all.
I think I'm getting older.
I want to dance properly in the
rehearsal, but my arms don't listen to
me.
I don't know what to do.
I'm surprised.
It's a mass of wild animals.
Check the wild side of me.
Are you a wild person?
Let's see if you are a wild person or
not.
I want you to see this.
Isn't it cute?
U-tan's light make-up.
I like it.
U-tan has a lot of eyelashes.
Yes, I have a lot of eyelashes.
I like it because it makes me look like
an adult.
But I like the gap when I don't have
eyelashes.
It's cute.
What should I do? I'm going to be
popular.
I'm going to make everyone's first voice
come back.
I'm going to be popular.
I'm sorry. I'm popular.
Are you kidding me?
I'm desperate.
I'm so nervous.
I don't know how they are going to
welcome me.
I'm worried if they remember me.
I'm so nervous that I'm looking forward
to it.
I think it's a content that you can
enjoy, so I hope you can have fun not
only with tension, but also with fun.
It's been a while since I've been on the
same stage as HIKARIN, so I'd like to
enjoy it together so that I can help if
HIKARIN is in trouble.
I'm HIKARIN.
Please take care of me and my fans from
now on.
Thank you.
Let's have a good time with HIKARIN.
HIKARIN's debut song.
I've been watching HIKARIN since his
debut.
I felt nostalgic and I thought I had to
see it, so I flew as soon as I heard the
song.
As I was rehearsing with the members, I
got more and more ideas to make it
better.
The number of people who come to see the
concert has been increasing.
The dancers, of course, but also the
members.
They are curious about what the concert
looks like.
So we thought it would be better to make
it better.
We were the ones who were most concerned
about the details.
I think it's a great step forward.
Even though I'm being interviewed now, I
think I'm doing my best because everyone
is with me, so I think I'm doing my best
as a team.
I want you to make the "Buddy's" a
little bigger than the "Yokoye"
The venue is big, so please make it
bigger than the "Yokoye"
I think there are many new songs, but I
want you to focus on the "Buddy's"
I want you to be able to go on stage as
"Sakurasaka"
I want you to remember the "Buddy's"
There are about 90 of them right now,
but they are all 100% in sync, so when
you crouch, you have to pay attention to
the height of your head, put your chin
in a little, and nod your head.
I think there are still 10% of them, so
I'd like you to take a look at those
10%.
It was released in the summer, so it's
good for festivals.
How can I say? I've been starting over.
I've been regretting it recently.
I think what we want to convey and what
the fans think is a little different.
I've been feeling the difference all the
time.
I don't know how we're going to change,
but I want to do my best.
Thank you for your rehearsal.
We will do our best to create a
wonderful concert with everyone's
cooperation.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for today.
The last day of the concert
Do you have any regrets?
No, I don't.
I have no regrets.
Here.
I have no regrets here.
Great!
Wow, the weather is so nice!
If it's like this, I'd be sweating a
lot.
At this temperature.
Isn't the sky crazy?
What is this color?
Wow, I want to throw it to the top.
I have to get my shoulders used to it.
It's amazing.
I heard this is buried.
I can't do that.
As expected.
This is where the trucks walk.
I'm walking, right?
I feel like I can see quite a bit.
Just thinking about this live makes me
cry every day.
I hear a lot of announcements.
For example, "I bought a ticket."
"I have more seats."
Every time I hear that, I'm like, "Oh,
my God."
I'm about to cry.
Personally, I couldn't participate in
Kodoku Tagashi Sen last year.
But since I made my debut, I've been
working hard for the past three years.
Of course, I was upset that I couldn't
participate.
I'll do my best.
But in a way, I really understood that
it was reality, so I think it was good.
I hope that the three years that I have
been working hard will be seen by
BUDDIES as I have grown a little more in
this live.
I think I'm the happiest, so I have to
do my best to make a live performance
that doesn't betray everyone's
expectations.
There is a little pressure.
But it's okay.
The goal is not to cry.
No.
It's absolutely impossible.
KANO-chan's tears are a treasure.
It's a jewel box.
Wow!
Thank you very much!
It's a new day.
Suddenly the temperature is strange.
It's like a cherry blossom field.
I forgot it.
Mori-chan!
Thank you very much.
I have to go now.
Good morning, everyone. My name is
Chiyoko Takahashi.
I would like to do my best in the Tokyo
Olympics.
First of all, I would like to do my best
with everyone.
Thank you very much.
It's my first 90th birthday.
I'm going to rock the venue with my 3rd
generation song.
I can't do this.
Everyone is going to the Olympics.
I can't help it.
I don't think so.
Of course, there is a possibility that
the wind is too strong and it is
dangerous because there is a chance that
there is a chance that the wind is too
strong, but we will do our best with
that possibility.
With the first song "Buddies", I feel
like I'm going to hit it here from the
first song.
"Buddies"
But I'm nervous about the second day.
I'm scared of the second day.
What's different from the second day?
There are two songs of BAX members.
That's a little scary.
And there's a special version.
I'm nervous.
At this scale, how many songs will the
seniors sing?
If I think about how many songs I will
sing...
"Family" is also amazing.
10 years.
20 years.
Yes.
It's really amazing.
I will do my best.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I couldn't make it in time for the
"Canon" part of "Nervous", so I'd be
happy if I could go a little faster.
Thank you very much.
When I was in the 19th place, I didn't
feel like the lighting was hitting me at
all.
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy to hear that.
You are No.19.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
At first, it was a teleportation.
The one on the lifter was a fake.
And before I knew it,
I feel like I'm in the center of the
stage.
It's like a teleportation.
I think the people at the center of the
B-stage will be very surprised.
I'm looking forward to it from now on.
Do you choose your favorite song?
Yes.
If it's a medley,
I hope people who know me from
Keyakizaka will enjoy it.
It's the last one.
I couldn't see the backstage.
We opened the seats over there.
I thought I couldn't see it.
But I can see it.
I can see it from the gap.
We can see it, too.
We can see it a lot.
That means we can see it from the other
side, too.
I can see it more than I thought.
I thought I was happy, too.
I thought I could see everyone more than
I thought.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't sleep.
Because I was so lonely.
I heard that they are getting along with
each other, so I feel lonely when I
think that he won't come to see me
tomorrow.
I think I'm going to cry when I see his
dress.
I heard that they are getting along with
each other, so I feel lonely when I
think that he won't come to see me
tomorrow.
Since that day, I told him that I'm
fine, but I've been crying every day for
a month since that day.
I'm so lonely.
I'm lonely.
So, even if I graduate,
Please meet me.
Please don't act anymore.
Isn't it good as a group, Sanki-chan?
I think so.
"Sukima Kazeyo" and "Kyou ga Tabun
Hatsuhiro" have their own songs, so I'm
worried about that.
But that song is the first and last song
with Habu-chan.
It's really only once.
Yes, I want to put it in there.
"Sukima Kazeyo" and "Kyou ga Tabun
Hatsuhiro" have their own songs, so I'm
worried about that.
Today is the last day of the show.
I'm so glad that we could come this far.
Let's do our best to make everyone look
forward to the 4th anniversary.
Thank you.
So today is really the 3rd anniversary
of Sakura Saka46 and the last live for
Haku-san.
Today is the only day, so everyone who
came and also the latest is today.
Let's do our best to make the best time
with everyone.
Sake! Sake! Sake! Sakura Saka46!
Let's do our best!
I want you to be able to do it.
I'm going.
Let's do our best.
I'm lonely.
At the end.
Let's do our best.
Did you close your eyes?
I closed my eyes.
Do you have a pose like this?
Pose?
Isn't it the feeling at that time?
That's right.
Let's have fun.
It's okay.
Then we will perform soon.
One, two.
The first STUDIO FRIEND is getting
excited.
One, two.
Kaguya Aisei.
Go! Go! Go!
Thank you for watching.
I'll go after the first BGM is over.
Next is the second BGM.
First BGM is "2nd place".
The second BGM is "3rd place".
This is the first time to use this BGM.
"3rd place" is a song that is often used
in the Japanese pop music world.
I want to be a fan of this song.
It was amazing.
It was my first time to see such a cute
person.
I was happy.
I'm happy.
Please follow me.
I'm getting off.
Open the door
Go for it!
I'm so scared
You can do it!
I'm scared
It's too fast, so stop at the last
minute
I'm scared
Stop at the last minute
Okay
You can do it!
- Let's do it here. - Let's do it here.
Run with all your might, don't stop
until you reach the finish line.
Don't stop breathing, don't stop
breathing.
Stand up and run around the world.
- Is there no one else? - There's no one
else.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Here we go!
I decided to do a dance called "Love
you's" for my fans.
"I love you" and "Love it" are written
on "Love you's".
I thought I'd do a rabbit pose.
I'm going to check the camera now.
I always think about the fans who are
always with us, and I wonder if they are
watching us now.
I'm worried about what kind of
atmosphere it will be.
I was conscious of being myself and not
thinking about anything.
Among tens of thousands of people,
There is no moment when it is quiet in a
live performance, is there?
I thought that there is only now when
the scene becomes a space as a real
performance,
I thought that I definitely wanted to
taste this moment,
I was also very "MU".
There is also a "MU" that is a
collaboration of "MUMA" and "MUMA"
And finally, this is the last video of
"MUMA"
The last video of "MUMA" is the last one
of the "MUMA" series
A video of "MUMA" and "MUMA"
and the last video of "MUMA"
If you watch the video, you can see the
last video of "MUMA"
It's very interesting
Please look forward to it
The last "MUMA" video
Take the chair
The last video of "MUMA"
We'll be boarding in 2 minutes.
The reason I decided to graduate is
because I was able to draw my future
My reliable juniors really colored the
group Sakurazaka46
And I was able to show a reliable and
cool performance
I think it's because I was able to show
it to everyone, and also to myself
[Akari]
[Akari] Ak-chan!
[Akari] Ak-chan! [Akari] Good evening!
[Akari] Good evening!
[Akari] Don't be late!
I can only say it in one song, so I was
wondering which song it would be.
I thought it would be the one that
everyone knows, so I betrayed.
I thought this would be my last
graduation concert, so I didn't think
I'd be able to do it again.
I'm grateful to Hobu-chan for giving me
that opportunity.
I can't really hear the fans' voices
when I'm wearing earphones,
but I was really happy to hear the call
when I was on the roof.
Thank you for watching!
I still haven't forgotten the times when
I loved you
(Sakura no hi wo)
(Mangai no sakura no hi wo)
(Ichido datte wasureta koto wa nai)
(Haru ga sugete hana ga chitte mo)
(Yume wa kurikaeshi kokoro ni saku hazu)
Thank you very much for coming today.
From now on, we will have an outdoor
concert.
I'm glad I could give flowers to
everyone.
It's fun, isn't it?
I think it was a really wonderful eight
years.
Today is the most special day for me,
because so many people have been
watching over me from behind the scenes.
I was really happy that so many people
came to see me off.
Thank you for supporting me for 8 years.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy that you put a bridge on my
future.
I have no regrets.
I will continue to move forward in my
own way.
I look forward to your continued support
for Sakura SAKA46 and Habu Mizuho.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for your viewing.
I don't know what to say.
You look like a leopard.
A leopard?
I cut my bangs.
It's so cute.
I'm so happy.
It's been a while since I wore pants.
I'll do my best.
You're watching Habusan today, right?
I'm watching Habusan today.
I'd like to show you properly.
I'll do my best.
I'm not nervous yet.
I don't know.
I was watching the live yesterday.
I don't feel real yet.
I think I'll be nervous when the
audience comes in.
I feel different from the usual live.
It's still fluffy.
I'll cry if I sing like this.
At least "Kosame"
BUDDIES will catch a cold.
Thank you for watching.
The costume I was wearing was brought to
Tokyo by my boss, but thanks to Kabe-
chan who left it for me yesterday, I'm
wearing it now.
Thank you very much.
It was fun yesterday.
It was good. It was a good group and a
good live.
So, first of all, you may be the
strongest.
You may be the strongest.
But you have something even stronger,
right?
What is it? What is the strongest thing?
God.
There is still a world of God left.
That's right.
It may be a little cold and your body
may get stiff, but I hope you can do
your best.
Let's do our best.
1, 2, 3.
We are always beautiful.
Like sakura, like sakura. Just trust
yourself.
Sake! Sake! Sake! SAKURA SAKURA 4D6!
Thank you!
Let's do our best!
Thank you very much.
Fujiyoshi is always worried about not
being able to be nervous.
He says that he is happy when he feels
something new in the live performance.
Being nervous means that he is trying to
overcome a new wall.
I thought he had a good face today.
Let's get excited today!
Let's go!
We have started the 2nd anniversary of
Sakurazuka 46's 3rd year anniversary!
First of all, we have good news for you!
Those members are coming back!
Hikari!
Welcome back!
We want to make more memories with
Hikari!
Welcome back!
This time, I did a performance of the
thread that I was originally doing, but
I went through it at the end.
When I went through it at the end, the
thread was falling, and I thought,
"Wait, whose thread is this?"
Yui-chan is trying to take a lot.
I thought it was Yui-chan's thread.
I'll take it when I get closer.
When I came back, I wanted to give it to
her, but I couldn't reach it.
Matsu reached out her hand from the
aisle.
She gave it to Yu-chan.
I thought that if I fell down, the crab
would come off.
I thought it would be really entangled.
I prayed for a long time and it came
off.
I was thrilled.
I thought this live would go well.
I was watching it up close.
When I saw it, I thought, "Oh, my God,
I'm going to cry."
I thought, "Oh, this live is going to be
great."
Everyone was looking in the same
direction.
I was listening to everyone's voices
through the earphones, and I felt that
our hearts were connected.
I don't want to be compared to others,
so I want to do my best to meet
everyone's expectations.
My coach advised me that it would be
better for me to get closer to them.
So I decided to run as much as I can.
I talked with my coach about how to run
and how to look at them.
I'm going to run!
I'm going to jump!
(Dark, dark, dark, dark, dark)
(Dark, dark, dark, dark)
(Sand over, sand over)
Right before the start of the show, I
was really scared to be in front of the
camera.
I want to create something new somehow,
but I can only do my best, so I don't
know what to do.
I panicked a little before the show
started.
But I'll do my best.
I want to run up the hill with everyone
in the 4th year of SAKURAZAKA46!
We love you, BATIS!
That's all from SAKURAZAKA46!
Thank you very much!
SAKURAZAKA46! Thank you!
Last year, we were like, "Let's do our
best on our own," or "This is our second
year, so let's do our best on our own."
But this year, we were like, "Let's rely
on BUDDYs and work hard together."
We were like, "Let's do our best with
BUDDYs and Sakurazaka."
During the first tour, we played all the
songs that we had released,
and there were only a few songs that we
could perform live.
We didn't have any songs that we didn't
play,
and we had the same set list, and we
changed the order of the songs.
Now we can choose the songs,
and we can do it on a daily basis.
It's very thoughtful.
As SAKURAZAKA,
When I started, I was very anxious.
I was very happy to celebrate the 3rd
anniversary with many fans who support
SAKURAZAKA.
Thank you very much.
To be honest, I'm so happy that so many
people are cheering for us.
Even if Abu-san is gone, I don't feel
anxious.
I have to do my best.
Abu-san is the only one who can't go.
I don't want to make a mistake.
But I want to cherish what Abu-san left
for me.