AISubs v3.2
I want to find the real me, not myself.
In this program, members of SAKURAZAKA46 collaborate
with entertainers.
It's an experimental variety show where they play games together.
This time, it's Mochikomi Gakuya Game Special.
In addition to the game project with the previous
guest, the president of Japan,
Sanaka! Taxi!
the unreleased scenes of ANGIRS and KIN NO KUNI were broadcasted.
In addition, at the end of the program,
a new exciting project was also announced.
First, the Mochikomi Game of the president of Japan.
It's the second lyrics reading quiz.
What does it mean?
I think you've heard the first lyrics.
The second lyrics are not very familiar to everyone.
And it's a reading quiz, so it's a quiz without a melody.
It's difficult.
I'll give you a question and you'll answer it.
I'll give you a reward.
It's a cake from Arno Rael Paris.
Here's the first question.
All my true feelings.
I've heard this before.
I know this.
Melody!
Can you sing a little bit?
It's too difficult.
What is this?
I love you.
I love you? You don't have to say it with all your heart.
Marigold?
Correct!
Great!
It's so difficult.
I'm so happy to be called like this.
I always sing this song in karaoke.
But you'll be killed by Hanzo.
I'll be killed by Hanzo?
The next question.
I love you.
What is this?
I can't live without falling in love.
Yes!
Yui-chan?
Love!
Correct!
Great!
I'm so happy to be called like this.
The next question.
The rain is falling.
The moon is fading.
Who was crying in the shade?
Someone is calling you to comfort you one by one.
When you count the joys, there are many of you.
The one who shined the way home was a hat of memories.
Paprika.
I got a slip of paprika.
Concentrate. It's a service question.
Please concentrate.
The next question.
Come on.
In front of people.
Itchai.
What did you say?
I didn't know that.
Why didn't you come to me?
Correct.
I didn't know at all.
When you kill your emotions with your own song.
I'm a singer.
This is a dead hit.
I'm listening to the song.
I like Eiko Kano very much.
The next question.
I'm a model human being.
I got it.
Wait.
Inori.
Shut up.
Correct.
Great.
Inori won.
The next question.
It's a scene that hasn't been released yet.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
It's a game where Onuma struggled.
There is another rule.
It's a very difficult version.
In my impersonation.
Crab.
I'll add it to the game.
Tanaka is the same.
When you say taxi.
Both of you.
The person who was stabbed.
Tanaka's crab.
Both sides don't do it.
The person who was stabbed.
Crab.
Tanaka.
It's very difficult.
From Onuma.
Tanaka.
Taxi game.
Taxi.
Crab.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
Crab.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
I don't care.
What?
Tanaka.
Taxi.
I don't care.
Tanaka.
Taxi game.
Taxi.
Crab.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
I don't care.
Itsuki Hirohi.
What's that?
I was just looking at her hand.
You shouldn't look at her.
Tanaka. Taxi game.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
I don't care.
Tanaka.
What?
You just did something like Tanaka.
I don't care.
Which game are you playing?
Please do it again.
Okay.
Tanaka. Taxi game.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
Crab.
She's moving.
Ms. Onuma.
You did something like this.
Your right hand reacted.
My reflexes are too weak.
Don't say that.
It's not like that at all.
You just made a mistake.
It's safe.
It's safe?
It's hard.
She started with a flutter.
I think everyone should meditate.
This is the first time I've seen this kind of show.
This kind of show doesn't exist.
Everyone is in a trance.
Tanaka Taxi Game starts from Onuma.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
Yamamoto.
You moved.
My delusion worked.
In a trance?
Stop it.
You made a mistake in your lines.
It's a mess.
Let's do it again.
Tanaka-Taxi game starts from Takemoto.
Tanaka-Taxi.
No way.
Let's remove Onuma-san from this game.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Next is the unreleased scene from Kinokuni.
Will people cry if they see it?
I don't know.
The previous game was called Onigiri-Nator.
We asked Watabe-Onigiri, who doesn't know anything, questions.
The game is to find the right answer.
Masumoto-Version, who doesn't know anything, also
played this game.
Here is the question.
Yes.
I don't know.
I know a little, but I can't feel it.
The four of them will ask questions in order and guess
the answer.
There are two answers.
Will they be able to answer the eight questions?
The point is whether they can ask a good question that
is close to the correct answer.
Inoue-san, please ask the first question.
Will humans be reflected?
As you think.
No.
Will humans be reflected?
Will humans be reflected on the screen?
Yes.
Have you actually seen it?
Kira-chan has seen it.
I think everyone knows it.
Is it a character?
You can also say you don't know.
I don't know.
You don't know if it's a character or not?
You've seen it before, right?
Yes, I have.
You look like you know.
I know how you feel.
The first round is over.
Please give us an answer.
Is it a Disney character?
Do you know the character?
Do you know Eva?
Eva is also a character.
Please give us an answer.
Spiderman.
No.
It's different.
It's obvious.
The second round.
I don't know at all.
Did I ask a bad question?
Is a person actually reflected in the video?
Regardless of whether it is real or not.
If so, there is a person.
There is a person.
A person suddenly appeared.
Is there a love story?
I don't know if there is a love story.
Is the main character a boy?
Yes.
I was surprised by this question.
I was surprised.
Is it a school thing?
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
It's not a school thing.
It's different.
Thinking time starts.
Conan?
Isn't it a character?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Is it a love story?
Is there such a love story?
Please answer.
Conan.
Maru.
Why? Where did it come from?
I don't think she's a character.
She's not a character?
I don't know if she's a human being or a character.
Because her name is in the title.
Wow, I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
Do you want to do it until the morning?
No, I'm having fun.
Team Nato's new project is announced!
I love it!
Actually, I received a message.
I'd like you to see it.
I'm the revolutionary of the music world, FIFTY.
Nice to meet you.
Numa-chan, how are you?
When you're sad, when you're lonely, when you're happy,
you're listening to FIFTY's songs.
I'm really grateful. Thank you.
I heard that Numa-chan is also making an original song.
Your heart is broken by a six-pack.
That's a great blues.
I felt something similar to FIFTY's musical sense.
I have a surprise for Numa-chan.
I, the revolutionary of the music world, FIFTY,
and Numa-chan of SAKURAZAKA46,
will collaborate together.
Thank you.
Will you make a new song together?
I'm going to decide on a lot of things.
My hope is to do a live performance with the audience.
Let's blow up the wind hole in the music world together.
So make sure you make it.
That's all from FIFTY A. Thank you.
I'm Numa-T.
I'm thinking of performing in front of the audience.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'd like to perform with all four of you.
I want to make a song that will make the audience laugh.
I'll definitely cry when I get home.