AISubs v3.2
I received a collaboration contract from Sakura Meets.
Thank you.
Are you A-MASTER?
I'm glad.
A-MASTER?
Are you with Onuma?
I'm not myself. I want to find the real me.
In this program, members of SAKURAZAKA46 collaborate
with entertainers.
It's an experimental variety show where they play games together.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Are you a student or a gangster?
Onuma and I have different characters.
I want to show the two of them.
I'm looking forward to it.
I will do my best to practice.
Onuma and Takemoto.
Meets.
A-MASTER.
The current situation is a school.
Onuma is a troublemaker.
Takemoto plays a role of a gal.
Onuma.
Yes.
It's gross to look at the eyes.
This part is cut off.
What?
I'm not Onuma.
I'm not stupid.
If I'm in a good mood, I'll do this.
Then, I'll turn around and do this.
Can I do Onuma like this?
Either way is fine.
You can do it as a whole.
I'll do it like this.
CM start.
Onuma Akiko and Takemoto Yui.
Mini 2.
A-masso.
What?
What is this?
A dog.
No.
A kogi.
What is this?
A crab.
No.
A Benizuwai crab.
What is this?
A Tibetan fox.
No.
A kogi.
TWICE. No.
Toritsu High School.
Class 2, Class 1.
Classroom.
Why is she so sensitive?
Even though she's so annoying.
Well, this is...
I'm not interested.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Well...
Let's go to the bathroom.
Bang!
Whee!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, well...
I've heard that you've been doing well lately.
I'm Onuma from the dance club.
Hello!
Thank you, God.
Onuma, where are you?
Onuma!
These are the seniors from Class 3.
I'm Onuma.
Oh, Oizuka.
Yes, I'm Onuma.
You look like Nakamura.
Hey!
Hey, you.
Hey, Onuma.
Come here.
I'm not Onuma.
Then who are you?
No, I'm Onuma.
I'm this girl.
I'm not Onuma.
What?
You're not from the dance club?
No, I'm not.
I'm from Taekwondo.
Really?
Yes.
You seem to be in a good mood, even though it's only been a year.
What?
I didn't say anything!
What do you mean you didn't say anything?
Just a bit, just a bit, just a bit.
I hear you and my boyfriend are getting along really well.
You've got it to be on fire!
How's it to get it to be on fire?
For real?
For real, for real?
Here.
Hey, if you're in a good mood, tell me what you're going to do.
If I'm in a good mood...
I'm going to do Namuru!
What do you mean?
Namuru!
Namuru?
Hey, you!
Are you trying to mess it up?
Remember that!
Sorry?
My nose is itchy.
What the hell?
You made a story for us.
Yes, I did.
I wrote it down for today.
I'm so happy.
The sample was so funny.
I was so moved.
But I couldn't do it well.
I was so frustrated.
No, you did it well.
You made me angry.
Really?
I thought you were that kind of person.
You look so angry.
I'm so happy.
Can you hear me?
What the hell is that?
You, Onuma!
Takemoto's movement was good, too.
Onuma!
Where is Onuma?
That's not a good way to say it.
You were so good at showing your weak side.
I thought you were my enemy.
Thank you. I'm so glad.
I'm glad, too.
I'm so glad.
If you had to choose, is there anything you should have
done differently?
Well, this time,
there was a part where I had to rely on my face.
I was a little too cute.
I need to practice my weird face.
Weird face?
I'm weak, after all.
You said that during rehearsal.
Can you stop being so cute?
Onuma is weak against cuteness.
Okay.
Can you be a little less cute?
She's cute.
When you're doing a skit,
is there anything you have to be careful of?
There are lines, but between the lines,
I have to think about whether I should say it lightly
or if I should take time to say it.
It changes as you build up the lines.
I don't really have a fixed style.
I try to make it longer every time.
I try to change the way I say it.
That's what I want to do.
That's amazing.
You've been so cool ever since we met.
Ever since we met?
That was two hours ago.
At the dressing room,
you were like, I'm going to make you my teacher.
What are you talking about? I made a disciple.
You're that good?
I didn't know you had such a cute disciple.
You were so cool.
Who are you?
Where are you coming from?
Kansai dialect tsukkomi gesture game.
Mochikomi Gakuya Game
It's a game that actors play in the dressing room together.
What did Eima-so bring?
It's a tsukkomi gesture game.
I heard that many of you are from Kansai.
I'm from Hyogo.
I'm from Shiga.
I'm from Shizuoka.
Three of you are from Kansai.
So, I came up with a game based on tsukkomi.
First, there is one person who asks a question.
The other five will be the answerers.
The tsukkomi word will be shown only to the person who
asks the question.
You have to show a gesture to get the tsukkomi word.
The answerer will randomly ask a question to the gesture.
The tsukkomi word with the same nuance is correct.
The tsukkomi word is a gesture, but the tsukkomi word
is also correct.
For example?
It's too funny.
That's right.
That's amazing.
This time, the person who was the most surprised will
be punished.
By the way, what are you going to do?
I think there's a lot of confessions to the camera.
This time, I'm going to have you say goodbye to the camera.
I've never seen anything like that.
There's a lot of things I've never seen.
If you can answer six questions in one minute, you'll clear it.
The point is whether you can make gestures that are
easy for the participants to understand.
Let's get started. Game start!
What's that?
Dance!
Calm down.
Who is that?
It looks fun.
Stay still.
I'm hungry.
I can't calm down.
Pass, pass, pass, pass.
I hate my mom.
A jet fighter.
What are you doing?
A strange bird.
Shut up!
Don't cry, don't cry.
A bird?
Don't make a weird voice.
Go over there.
It's midnight.
I'm just being hit.
A bird?
Did you forget your Japanese?
A bullet.
Calm down.
What's that?
That's a bad example.
That was a bad example.
I told them a lot of things.
Where are you going?
You should have passed earlier.
I was too persistent.
Can we do it again?
Game start!
Don't do anything weird!
Black has 200 colors!
Amigata!
It's not black!
I'm stretching!
What's with that face?
I'm 35 years old this year.
Liar!
Say something!
Wear a hat and a pair of pants.
The other way around!
It's cute.
It's too cute.
We did it!
They cleared the game.
But who will be the one to be punished?
Who was the worst?
Kano-san.
No, no.
I was the worst.
I was so mad at her.
She was so mean.
She was hurt.
She didn't say anything.
Kano-san will be the one to be punished.
What?
Why? We cleared the game.
I was so mad at her.
You should have said something in the beginning.
What did I say?
It was pretty fast.
You should have said something to the camera.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Kano-san, it's your turn.
I'm sorry.
It's over.
It's too hard.
I'm sorry. I made a person I like.
It's cool.
As expected of the master.
You have a lot of respect.
Stop it.
You have to lower it.
My face is cracked.
I didn't say that.
Next time, Masumoto Kira meets Lover Girl.
I'm sorry.
The strange clerk's role is just right.
If you don't like it, you can't see it.
TikTok Video Examination is also held.
I think you should quit this system.
Hey.
Seriously.