Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Identity that has been distorted
By ordinary adults
Don't push the cheap love
That you repeat and say
The boy from my hometown
If you run through with all your might
You'll understand something
It's a dead end, a dead end
The world is ending
What should I do from here?
I don't have a choice
It's a dead end, a dead end
If it's no good, I'll laugh
Will I fall down the path I've chosen?
When I've gone too far
It can't be helped if I stay here
I was the one who made a mistake
It's a dead end, a dead end
Connecting the past and the future
How should I live now?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Even if I resist
"What should I do?"
The same result
The more I look around
The more I become a self-centered person
What should I answer
Even if I keep guessing?
Even my parents
Contacted me
And that's where I live
It's a dead end, a dead end
Where will I start from next?
What will happen from here?
The future of despair
It's a dead end, a dead end
Looking for a way out
Is there no continuation?
The present I've lost
What should I wait for?
If I wait until dawn
If it's the end, if it's the end
I'll rewind the dazzling days
And start over
(And start over)
No matter where I run
There's no way
Right or left
It's a dead end
My brain is running out of energy
And I'm confused
I tried to escape, but
I just got tired
It's a dead end, a dead end
Where will I start from next?
What will happen from here?
The future of despair
It's a dead end, a dead end
If it's a wall, I'll break it
The path I've come to
When I've gone too far
Even if I'm here, it can't be helped
I made a mistake
It's a dead end, a dead end
While I'm hitting the wall in front of
me
I'm shouting from the bottom of my heart
The past and the dream are connected
How can I live in the present?
(And start over)
I don't care if I can't do it
But I'm starting to remember
I want to go back to that time
That was fun
I remember
But the order has changed
It hasn't changed
How long have I been walking here?
I want to hold hands with you
I want to kiss you
I want to fight with you
I want to be close to you
I miss you
The condition is reflected
And I'm crying
In the middle of the twilight
Why? Why? Why?
Because someone's life
Will disappear from the sky
The scenery is blurred
And I'm crying
Love is just for a moment
It's not eternal happiness
No matter how many days pass
I'll be fine
I really liked you
I was serious
I was clumsy
I regretted it
I realized it
The rest of the festival
The middle of the festival
If I walk around like this
I think I can meet you
My feet are moving on their own
That's the kind of relationship I want
to have.
I've done my best for the last time in a
long time.
It's painful to be the same as everyone
else.
I've been working hard to make a lot of
new friends and new love, but...
I couldn't do it.
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
I can't resist my feelings
I'm running with the conditions
reflected
On the way back to the twilight
Why? Why? Why?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Because my back is disappearing
The scenery is blurring and I'm crying
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Because my back is disappearing
The scenery is blurring and I'm crying
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
The scenery is blurring and I'm crying
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Love is just a moment
There's no such thing as eternal
happiness
What kind of situation is this?
I can't help it if the conditions are
reflected
Love is just a moment
I'm the only one who can turn off the
power of love
Even if I'm rejected, even if I'm
denied, even if I'm told I'm useless
I can't be a different person now
Even if I'm rejected, even if I'm
denied, even if I'm told I'm useless
I understand, I won't back down
God, what is it? Can't I live?
Where is this standard? I want to know
"Snow"
The sands of time that have been filled
Disappear without knowing anything
If I had that kind of power
I thought I could do anything
What are you doing here?
Someone, please tell me
"I have to change"
I said that I would change
I was made a new person
If I had that kind of power, what should
I do?
I just didn't know
I'll just go again
I'll give you a chance
If I had that kind of power, what should
I do?
Are you going to abandon me?
I used to believe that I could fly
God, please forgive me
I didn't know that I could do such a
thing
"Snow"
The sun that is too bright
Is leaking from the bottom of the wind
Until the darkness comes
We will meet again
Even if I'm told that I'm stupid, that
I'm a coward, that I'm useless
There's no way I can be a different
person
Even if I'm told that I'm stupid, that
I'm a coward, that I'm useless
There's no way I can be a different
person
I can't run away from anything
I want to know what the standard is
Even if I'm driven into a bad situation
I will never give up
"Snow"
I don't want to hurt you more than I
hurt myself
I thought
[Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter]
Thank you for watching!
Cherry blossoms and cherry blossoms are
blown by the wind
and fly up in my heart
If only I could sing a little more
No matter how much I love you, the
season will pass
and the clouds scatter in a blink of an
eye
I loved cherry blossoms on that day
(I love you)
The reason we're talking about our
dreams here
is so that we can say other words
"I love you" is a goal, but I'm the only
one who gets happy
I can't do that
I'm on a trip to Tokyo
Listening to the summer, I want to push
you in the car
Let's take a picture together
I'm sure you'll think that's good
Sweet and sour youth
I wonder what I'm wearing
I'm already tired of being alone
At least when I think of you
Such a beautiful love song
I don't care if I'm alone
I want to praise the me who was sent
from above
So that there is no flower that
continues to bloom forever
If you can't stay like this
I thought about how to make it beautiful
Fly up in the sky
So that you can remember it many times
I want you to fall slowly
So that you don't notice me
I'm going to close my eyes
Your voice
Listen carefully
I tried to leave it as a memory
The waterfall in the dark night sky
Certainly now
I can see the cherry blossoms in full
bloom
I loved the blue flowers
Even if people grow up
Even if dreams and ideals no longer come
to mind
If you can do such a beautiful way of
living
Cherry blossoms dancing in the mist
Blown by the wind
It rises in my heart
At least I want you to be a little
relieved
No matter how much I love you
The season has passed
In a blink of an eye, the rainbow clouds
Cherry blossoms dancing in the mist
Blown by the wind
It rises in my heart
At least I want you to be a little
relieved
No matter how much I love you
The season has passed
In a blink of an eye, the rainbow clouds
Cherry blossoms dancing in the mist
Blown by the wind
It rises in my heart
"Cherry Blossoms"
(chanting in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
(audience cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
There may be people who haven't seen the
music video yet, so I'd like you to
watch the music video with this as a
trigger.
I'm looking forward to our future
performances, and we'd like to continue
to increase this start-over, so I hope
you'll look forward to it again.
I'll do my best from now on!
Thank you!
First of all, we have to change clothes.
How about our costumes?
Isn't it cute?
Let's take a look at it first.
What do you think?
The length of the front and back of the
shirt is different.
It's fashionable.
Four braids are cute, too.
All the shoes are different.
Only the skirt is the same.
What about you, Mayuna?
I'm out.
Actually, I'm opening one.
I'm opening one.
Detailed points.
I want the first button.
May I open it?
It's not the first button.
It's the second button.
It's the first button.
I made a mistake.
I recommend this kind of frilly part.
Do you recommend it?
For FUJIFILM,
I'm looking forward to it, so I'd like
to look for it at the live show.
I'm sorry I can't introduce you, but
please watch the music video.
I'm going to go.
Bye bye.
I'm going home.
See you later.
Thank you for listening to the new song
"HERO".
We're so happy to be able to perform for
the first time in such a crowded venue,
in a place where so many people can see
us.
I'd like to ask the members about their
impressions.
First, Inoue!
Yes!
How was it?
Everyone, how was it?
I'm so happy.
Yes!
I'm sure that the audience here today,
as well as the people watching the live
stream,
as well as the people in Japan, and the
people all over the world, are watching
this.
I'm so glad that I was able to show you
a new version of Sakurazaka here,
and that I was able to show it to
everyone.
I was really nervous.
I was nervous.
At first, when I turned around, everyone
was like, "Woo!"
I was like, "Woo!"
I was like, "Oh!"
That's true.
I was so nervous, but I'm glad I was
able to show it to everyone today.
I want to do my best to perform in
various places in the future.
Thank you very much.
I was a bit nervous today, wasn't I?
Yes, you were.
It was a quick change from Sakurazuki.
I changed into the start-over costume
right away.
When you're changing, you're conscious
of the change.
But the moment it started, I was like,
"Oh!"
That's amazing.
Next, Hikaru, how was it?
Yes.
I have a question for Matsu.
Me too.
So I was fine.
Cute!
I did put on a full MV, but it was my
first time putting on a full
performance, so I was a little worried
that the audience would leave.
But I think we were able to show a new
side of us, so I hope you'll check out
the MV.
In the music video, there was a sparkly
firework that went off.
Did you notice that it was playing
during the live performance just now?
I really like that.
I also really like the MV filming
location.
I thought it was really cool.
There was a lot of footage just now.
I was even more surprised.
It was really fun.
Thank you.
The MV production.
I'm really happy to be able to show the
same thing here.
Next is Fuuka-san.
How was it? Your first show?
Yes, thank you.
Actually, I'm going to say this because
I revealed it today.
What is it?
I think it was in the music video and
now in the show.
Karin-chan is climbing on top of the
members in the first chorus.
I'm under Karin-chan's butt.
That's good.
- That's amazing. - We have a lot of
songs based on her.
Like "Fuurin Shimai", which is based on
Hikaru-chan.
It's a very stable song.
She chose this song as the base.
Everyone is so kind.
The staff and the members worry about me
a lot.
Without the strength of the members...
I can't do it, so it looks like it's on
top of me, and my shoulders are Yui and
Rei-chan, and I'm supported by their
waists, so maybe if I put it on even one
person, the foundation, the foundation,
everyone's foundation, I don't think
everyone will be able to complete it, so
I
I think it's difficult to say where my
members are, but I hope everyone can
think that they are making one.
I've been practicing dozens of times,
where Karin climbs.
Karin-chan was also doing her best.
Oh, I'm back.
- Welcome back. - Thank you for waiting.
We were waiting for you.
Are you okay, Fuuka-san?
Oh, I'm fine.
Fuuka-san, are you okay?
Yes, I'm being supported.
Thank you for always supporting me.
No problem.
Thank you for waiting, everyone.
We're all here again.
Thank you again, Aqours!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
We can spend time together, so I'd like
to play this song with everyone.
Please listen to it.
"Buddy Zone"
I wanted to meet you
I laugh at the sky full of girls
The world hasn't changed at all
We're still the same as we were back
then
The season is the wind, the scent of
flowers
The sun shines on the green trees
Let's go, let's go, let's go
The day I took everything away
It's already passed
(It's already passed)
As if nothing happened
This earth is so peaceful
(Everything is so fine)
I can't stop here
Let's go, let's go, let's go
My heart is looking somewhere far away
Is there really hope?
If I'm with you, I can go
If I'm with you, I can get there
I go, I go, I go
Let's go, let's go, let's go
You're my dream
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Even if you lose something
Tomorrow will come again
Tomorrow will come
That sad wind will stop
A new world will open
Come on, let's go!
Yo! Let's start again from here
Yo! Because humanity has nothing
Yo! We can go anywhere
Yo! Let's throw away despair with tears
Yo! I've been waiting for you
Open it, open it, open it
We are brave
Come with me
Let's go
We are brave
Yo! I've been waiting for you
Yo! Look at the blue sky tonight
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We are the same as we were
Yo! The season's wind, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the burning sun
Let's go
We are brave
Come with me
We are buddies
The tour that started in April will end
today
I was really happy to meet a lot of
Buddies and hear a lot of voices
The reason why we were able to continue
to evolve
It was a tour that made me feel that the
warmth of Buddies was there
We will continue to fight from now on
Buddies are needed on this road
Will you stay with us from now on?
Thank you!
(Buddies, Buddies, Buddies, Buddies,
Buddies)
See you again
We are Buddies
Thank you!
Thank you for the encore!
We performed the new song "Start Over"
Buddies also performed
How was it everyone?
Thank you!
Are you excited to see the live
broadcast?
It's over
Thank you!
The tour will end today
I would like to ask the members how it
was so far
Matsuri-chan, how was it?
Thank you very much
I wanted to do this
I've been doing it for a long time
Thank you
I don't want to do this
Thank you very much
Through this tour
I was able to learn a lot
I feel like I got a lot of things
Because of this tour
I feel like I can do a lot of things
Also, since I became a captain
It was my first tour
Before the rehearsal
I've been nervous
During this tour
I've never been nervous during a tour
I've never been nervous
As for me
I've shown the members a lot of things
that I'm not good at
I've never seen that
So I was a little embarrassed
But I think it was a good experience for
me
From now on
I'm going to have a lot of things to
learn
That's amazing
There's nothing to do
There's nothing?
Thank you
Thank you very much
The members really supported me a lot
They're really good girls
You're a good girl
I'm really grateful
Also, there's something I wanted to say
As another group
There's a lot of things
I want to do this
I think I've seen that I have to do this
I'm really glad I was able to do this
tour
I'm sorry it's a little long
Thank you very much
Thank you
Next, I'd like to ask the 3rd generation
Murai Yu-chan
Yu-chan
How was it so far?
The 3rd generation
This was my first tour
I was really nervous
But the 3rd generation
I want to liven up the tour
I want to connect well with my seniors
I want people to enjoy it 100%
With that in mind, I did my best
I did a performance
Through the tour
I was able to meet a lot of BUDDIES
There are people who are watching this
live
I'm really happy
Everyone, thank you very much
Thank you
Next, Yui-san
How was it?
Well
The tour started in April
11 shows
I rushed
It's amazing
One show at a time
It's been a long time since I heard the
cheers
It's been a long time
I was able to feel the live
This tour
So
What is it?
This moment is not common
I know how grateful I am
I was moved to meet BUDDIES
I felt that
From now on
I want you to be BUDDIES forever
Cute
Really
All of our live
Various
TV and work
I want you to see it all
I'm glad
The power I got
Various places
I want you to come
From now on
Please be BUDDIES
Cute
Thank you
So
Soon
This live tour
The 5th single period
I'm trying to finish
Really
I feel like I've been able to experience
a lot of different feelings myself.
The members, the staff, and of course
the BUDDIES,
you've all supported me a lot.
I'm really happy that I was able to
experience the tour.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much!
It's all thanks to the BUDDIES that we
were able to do this.
I can't forget the scenery I see from
this stage every time.
Every time, I try to burn it in the
rain.
I'm so happy with everyone's
appreciation.
I'm so grateful that I've been hearing
it all the time.
Thank you very much!
Listening to your voice gives me a lot
of power.
I hope you will continue to support
SAKURA ZAKAO.
The next song is the last song.
Thank you very much!
At the end, please turn the penlight
into cherry blossom pink.
I want you to sing with me.
It's blooming, isn't it?
It's blooming! Thank you very much!
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!
It wasn't like it was a given
I couldn't see you until today
There's a hole in my heart
I was able to meet you.
I don't know what happened, but I'm sure
you can get over it.
I've never forgotten the full bloom of
cherry blossoms.
Even if spring passes and flowers fall,
dreams will repeat and bloom here.
So that we can remember forever,
we gather on this hill.
If I can talk about you,
I feel like I can meet you again.
I'm sure there were sad things that you
couldn't tell anyone.
I was worried because I was watching you
from afar.
There's nothing we can do.
I was waiting for you to stand up.
On the day of the full bloom of cherry
blossoms,
I was blown by the gentle winter wind.
What did I keep waiting for
in that picture of the sunset?
Even if people who pass by
forget the flowers of that day,
we'll always remember
the scenery of the next spring.
Wow...
Why do people love us so much?
I miss you so much.
Like the flowers that bloom one by one
in the distance,
cherry blossoms will bloom again.
Wow...
On the day of the full bloom of cherry
blossoms,
I've never forgotten it even once.
Even if it passes and flowers fall,
dreams will repeat and bloom here.
So that we can remember forever,
we gather on this hill.
When I think of you,
I feel like I can fly again.
Wow...
I feel like I'm a star drummer.
I'm so powerful.
I'm so happy to be able to live freely.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Once again, everyone,
thank you for coming to Osaka Park today
and watching the live stream.
Everyone, if you'd like,
after this live show,
please take a picture of the stage,
upload it to your SNS with your
impressions,
and share a lot of memories.
Thank you.
And from now on,
on June 28th,
the 6th single "START OVER" will be
released,
and in July,
the first exhibition "New World" will be
held.
In addition, in November,
the first stadium of "SAKURAZUKA46 3rd
YEAR ANNIVERSARY LIVE"
will be held at Sozomanie Stadium.
This tour will end with everyone who
always supports me,
but I would like to express my gratitude
to all the BUDDIES who always support
me.
I would like to continue to bring
smiles, happiness, and heart-pounding
things.
I will do my best to make the most of
what I have gained through this tour.
Thank you very much for coming to the
"SAKURAZUKA46 3rd YEAR ANNIVERSARY TOUR
OSAKA KOUEN"
and other venues,
and for watching the live show.
That's all.
We are SAKURAZUKA46.
Thank you very much.
See you in Tokyo.
See you again.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.