AISubs v3.2
KONTO COLLABO DAIHON
Hello.
The new KONTO COLLABO DAIHON of Sakura Meets has arrived.
Are you watching?
I'm watching.
Really?
I was doing it alone.
It was cute.
Really.
I was very nervous.
I was playing a game.
With Kaguya-san?
Why are you all staring at me?
I was in a hurry, too.
Kaguya-san was in a hurry, too.
It was really fun.
KONTO COLLABO DAIHON
This program is a collaborative program between members
of Sakurazaka46 and entertainers.
One, two, three.
This person.
It's an experimental variety show where you can play
games together.
I'm nervous because I can't reach it every time.
I'll show you.
Is this okay?
Wait a minute.
Do I have to put the flow in my head?
Because there are three parts.
That's right.
It's long.
It came out.
There is a dance part every time.
It's cool.
It's amazing.
I'm glad.
I'm looking forward to it.
I really like it.
Watch this, too.
I'll watch it.
It's fun.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
After the commercial, rehearsal and performance.
Rina Inoue
Three.
Long coat travel.
I'm not a dog!
This time, KONTO is going to play a role of a baseball player.
Inoue is going to play a manager.
The key point is the locker in the club room.
I want you to take care of me!
Does it hurt?
No, not at all.
It's fine as long as it's fast.
You can close it even if you're talking.
You can put your mouth in here.
That might be the best.
I haven't thought about the ad-lib yet.
You haven't?
The harder it is, the harder it is.
I'm not going to do that.
Inoue Rina.
Three.
Long coat travel.
Start!
Hey, Yuhei.
Why did you skip the club yesterday?
I just went to karaoke.
What?
What's that?
It doesn't change even if I skip it for a day.
It's annoying every day.
What?
Are you serious?
Hey.
Didn't you and I go to Koshien with your golden battery?
Nasu.
It's good, isn't it?
Everyone is cheering for the next ace candidate.
What? What are you talking about?
You don't know how I feel.
wwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww
Did something happen?
It's none of your business.
It's none of my business? Tell me!
Tell me!
The coach told you to stop being a catcher, right?
What do you mean?
He told me to leave the catcher to Saito and find a
good position for you.
Wait a minute.
It's true that Saito's talent as a catcher is outstanding.
But I've been with you since I was in junior high school.
I've been with you since you picked up my ball.
Hey, Takahashi.
Let me go.
I'm going to quit baseball.
I'm going to quit too.
I realized the difference in level in high school.
But you are good enough to go to high school.
Let's aim for the high school championship with Saito
and the golden battery.
You idiot!
Hey!
Saito, Saito, shut up!
Hey, Takahashi-kun!
Saito!
Thank you very much.
Damn it.
You shouldn't have hit me.
What? If you have a problem, come at me.
You coward.
Ouch!
How dare you hit me?
Damn it.
Did you work hard?
Saito is talented, but he works harder than anyone else.
He practices catching every night until late.
Are you working hard?
What do you know?
I'm asking if you worked hard to give up.
Shut up.
You should be serious, too.
I want you to take the ball.
You're right.
Saito may be more talented.
But Takahashi throws better balls when Yuhei is catching.
You guys...
Try again from the beginning.
Go with me.
That's right.
We promised to go to the game.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
I'll practice again. I'll work hard.
I'll be a good catcher for you someday.
Wait for me until then.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sorry. I was confused.
Are you still confused?
I'll practice hard from today.
Takahashi, you're going to lose all your teeth from tomorrow.
What?
Lose all my teeth?
Can I play baseball?
You don't need teeth.
I told you not to show your white teeth.
Am I the one who's making a fuss?
I'll do my best from today.
FUJISAWA No.1, Fight!
That was really good.
The three of us should be on King of Condor.
What?
I think Inoue's first kick was the best.
Hey, Takahashi-kun! Stop being violent!
That was fast!
I was thinking of kicking after the first kick.
But as I was practicing, the kick hit me.
He has a really bad habit of kicking.
I wanted to kick him so bad.
Takahashi-kun, who was really violent,
will have a menu where all of his teeth fall out from tomorrow.
What is that?
A menu where all of his teeth fall out?
That was really good.
I had a dream recently.
I had a dream where all of my teeth fell out.
When I woke up, I was sweating so much.
I couldn't forget that.
That was really good.
If you have any advice, I'd like to use it in the future.
I think the tone was the same for all of them.
For me, I'd go for a small voice and go for a deep voice.
Or I'd go for a big voice.
I'd go for a deep voice and go for a deep voice.
What does that mean?
Everyone is writing it down.
It's a piece of cake.
I'm determined to study.
Don't be afraid of making mistakes.
People say that a lot.
You might be the best at making mistakes.
Really?
Weren't you afraid?
What?
I was really afraid today.
Inori stole my script.
I'm sorry.
I was looking at it the most.
Stop it.
I didn't bring my script.
I thought it was a piece of cake.
3, 2, 1.
I'm sorry.
After the commercial, everyone is excited.
Accommodation Gaming
In the corner where the performers play games of
themselves that make itần they're in the dressing room
The person Long Cord Darby brought with her is
Man, let's have something to pasta with them!
We're going to hand out three pictures of old men.
And we're going to give you a topic.
When I was in junior high school, I was the captain of
the judo club.
That's the topic.
There's no right or wrong answer.
You have to make up a nuance with just this face.
If everyone gets it right, it's clear.
If you get it right, you'll get a reward.
This is from NAMU CAFE HARAJUKU.
It's TUNKARON.
I'm sure it's TUNKARON.
What is the first topic?
I'm addicted to soba noodles.
I bought a tool to make soba noodles at home.
I made it myself once.
I haven't touched it for three years.
Are you addicted to soba noodles?
Yes.
Did you say the face nuance?
If you keep looking at him, you'll be in the back.
Let's do it.
One, two, three.
KUNITO!
Three pairs.
The front and the back are completely different.
I'm addicted to a lot of things.
If you're addicted to one thing, you'll be addicted to
a lot of things.
What is the next topic?
When you catch a cold, you go into the ice bath.
I have my own way to fix it.
I'm sure it's this.
It doesn't matter if it's the front or the back.
One, two, three.
This person!
I'm sure it's this person!
This person can't stand Kourin Pro!
This person can only stand Kourin Pro!
I could see that he was a good listener to his wife.
I thought this person was single.
Numa-chan, if I said this person was single, I wouldn't
have been able to sleep at all.
This person has the most wives.
I'm sure he's married!
They failed two times in a row.
The next topic is from Takemoto.
He's taking a walk.
He finds a white vine.
He makes a can of canned fish for his grandchild.
I see.
I'm sure it's this person.
One, two, three.
This person!
I'm sure it's this person!
Why?
I'm sure this person is the type of person who looks at
the white vine,
glances at it, and presents the song.
That's right.
You're being pulled by the white vine.
This is the last one.
This is the last chance to ask a question.
The topic is from Masumoto.
When I was in junior high school,
I picked up my favorite girl's handkerchief.
I missed the timing to return it.
I still keep it at home.
I'm sure it's this person.
You didn't steal it, did you?
I dropped it, picked it up, and returned it.
I'm sure it's this person.
One, two, three.
This person!
It's totally different!
It's totally different at the end!
This person is the type of person who takes good care of things.
He puts things in a box.
He puts things on a desk.
But this person is shy.
He can't return them.
Like I said before, this person is like a wife.
There's a wife?
Why is there a wife?
It's so frustrating!
I can't do this anymore.
Lastly, I want to say that I'm proud of my beard.
I don't want to hear that!
Oyashi-tori, let's go!
And another game of Long Coat Daddy will be released!
Gold... money?
After this, the live broadcast will start!
And next week, Yui Takemoto meets the president of Japan!
What are you doing?
This isn't a jutsu!