You can't tell anyone what's important
Until you let out your heart, you'll die
No matter how many hateful words you
choose
You can't tell anyone
Even though everyone believes in love
If you fall in love, it will become a
weakness
So I'll throw my heart away
Yes, I don't want to be like anyone else
I'm fine with a man who looks like I can
fall in love
I'll pretend that it doesn't matter
I want to look at you and be serious
Even if you look at me like that
I'm not interested
I still keep resisting
I don't want to be an adult
I want to be a fool like this
I want you to notice my true feelings
("Immortal Heart" Covered by Nihongo)
I bury my beginning heart into my own
shoulders
I try to not let anyone touch me
I don't want to be afraid of the shaking
that turns me
If I'm lonely, I can be lonely
Kindness and love can't be seen
sometimes, but
Nightwing, even the way you look at me
I don't know, I don't know, I'm hurting
you
I didn't mean to do that
Yes, the distance between people is more
difficult than I thought
Rue, if you say goodbye
Rue, I don't feel like I'll fall
Rue, I've come to live without feeling
any emotions
Rue, my lonely heart
Rue, let me do whatever I want
Rue, I don't want to be bound
I can't go back to normal
Nothing will change
Rue, won't you leave me alone
Rue, my last wish
Rue, Rue, let's break up
Rue, let me do whatever I want
Rue, I don't want to be bound
I can't go back to normal
Nothing will change
Rue, won't you leave me alone
Rue, I don't want to be bound
I can't go back to normal
Nothing will change
Rue, I don't want to be bound
Rue, isn't it okay?
Rue, I'll pretend like I don't care
Rue, I want to turn my back and stay
still
Rue, even if you look at me like that
Rue, I'm not interested
Rue, I'm still resisting
Rue, I don't want to grow up
Rue, I want to be a fool like this
Rue, I don't want to do that
Rue, my true feelings
Rue, Rue, notice me
I'm not the type to rush things, I don't
want you to understand
When I realized it, I realized that
being alone was the easiest
The reason why my bangs are long is
because I want to hide my gaze
Go away, go away, I'm not here
Even if you suddenly confess to me, I
can't believe it even for a second
I'm blocking the front of your eyes,
your huge shoulders are in the way
It doesn't matter if we love each other
half-heartedly
It doesn't matter if it's good for
everyone
It doesn't matter if we look at each
other half-heartedly
Tell me your true feelings, the story
will continue
Ah, it's troublesome to fall in love
I've never seen you with those eyes,
those eyes of yours
It's not special, I don't feel anything
I don't like to be judged
The corner of my chest is looking for
someone's shadow
Like a balloon, I'm waiting for you at
the station platform
Even now, I'm afraid
I'm not good at it at all, I don't want
to accept it
I'll remember it like a scenario
It's calculated, isn't it?
Ah, if I do this, if I do that, this is
what happens
It's like a double-edged sword
I don't want to change it like a
scenario
Ah, if I do this, if I do that, this is
what happens
I don't want to change it like a
scenario
Ah, if I do this, if I do that, this is
what happens
I don't want to hurt you anymore
Even if the first love is too cowardly
and the chance is running out
There's nothing good about loving each
other half-heartedly
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
I don't care, but
Even if we stare at each other half-
heartedly
Our eyes will touch
Tell me your true feelings
I'm going to fall in love now
"I'm going to fall in love now"
It's natural to become an adult
Even if we face each other seriously, we
won't be misunderstood
Even if we're far apart, we can still
get along
All the students say that they
understand the value of the future
I can't even control my emotions like
that
If I try to change it myself, I'll lose
myself
Even if we stare at each other half-
heartedly
What are you going to put up with?
Even if we hesitate, we'll lose
Tell me what you want to say
Even if we stare at each other half-
heartedly
We can't say anything
If you're angry, just be angry
I have no choice but to tell you
I'm going to fall in love now
It's definitely not good for your body
to swallow words
I'm going to tell you something in my
heart
I'm going to make you feel warm
The things I want to say will disappear
and it won't be easy
I'm going to stab you, I'm going to stab
you
I'm going to spit on your back and stand
up
I don't care if I'm a genius
No one's watching
I'm going to do my best
Everyone thinks I'm uncool
I'm going to be laughed at for being
ignorant
I'll do what I want
It's scary, I can't run away, but it's
the beginning
I can't look away
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid
Don't be afraid
Look, we're alive
We're a bound society
Let's tear it apart and be free
Come closer, what are you going to do?
I'm going to do my best
I'm going to be laughed at for being
ignorant
I'll do what I want
It's scary, I can't run away, but it's
the beginning
I can't look away
Don't be afraid
Look, we're alive
We're a bound society
Let's tear it apart and be free
Come closer, what are you going to do?
I'm going to be laughed at for being
ignorant
I'll do what I want
It's scary, I can't run away, but it's
the beginning
Sakurazuka46
Good evening, everyone
One, two
We're Sakurazuka46
Welcome to Sakurazuka46 3rd Tour 2023
Welcome
Are you having fun?
People from Osaka
People from Igari
Thank you so much
Today, we're doing a live stream
Are you having fun?
Hello
Good evening
This time, we're doing a live stream
abroad
I'm so happy
Thank you
Are you watching?
Hello
I love you
Thanks to everyone, BUDDIES is spreading
to the world
I'm so happy
I'm more nervous than usual
But we'll do our best to entertain you
Thank you
And as you know
Endo Hikari is not feeling well
So she's taking a break
She's taking a break now
We're waiting for her to come back
She has a place to go
So I hope she can take a rest
I'm so happy that BUDDIES are waiting
for her
Please continue to support Endo Hikari
Thank you
I'm sure there will be a lot of warm
applause
Hikari is so happy
Thank you
I'm so happy
I'm so happy that Hikari can hear this
Thank you
And the music video that was released
the other day
Did you know?
It got 1 million views
Thank you
That's fast
I think it's faster than usual
Thank you so much
I hope you'll continue to watch and
listen to it
Thank you
And yesterday
There was an announcement
Sakurazaka 46's history and the story of
the future
New world will be held
Thank you
For the performance
From the 1st single to the 1st album
With the photos of the artists and the
CD jacket
Perimetron's Osori-san
Is taking care of it
Thank you
I'm so happy
From July 28th
It will be held at the Tokyo Roppongi
Museum
People from Kanto
Or people from Miyazaki
Like me
There are people like that
From July 28th to October 29th
It will be held
If you have a chance
Please come
Thank you
I want to ask the members
Karin-chan from Osaka
Karin-chan
My home
I'm Fujiyoshi Karin
Like this
In Osaka
I'm so happy to be able to perform
In this venue
I want to stand as Sakurazaka
I'm so happy
Thank you
The members from Osaka
I'm so happy
Don't you admire them?
I admire them
In the live
There are a lot of artists
I admire them
I really admire them
Emotions
How about you, Hono-chan?
Until now
We've been touring a lot
Today is the last day
Personally
I don't think it was short
I can feel the tour period
I can feel it
The members too
I think it's because I was able to spend
a lot of time with BUDDIES.
Until yesterday, I thought that this
tour would last a lifetime.
I thought in a good way that there was
an end.
But today is the last day, so I'll do my
best not to regret it.
Thank you.
Today is the final performance, so I'd
like to thank everyone who came today.
And to all of you watching, I hope today
will be a special day.
Let's all have fun today!
Let's have fun!
Are you ready?
More!
Let's have fun until the end!
Everyone, you're doing great!
Let's hear more!
Arena!
Start!
More!
Yeah!
Everyone!
Let's have fun!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
All the time
I'm saying things that I'm so sick of
It's the worst kind of human being
You're the worst person I've ever met
Do you understand?
Even if I don't have much experience
I don't want to meet a guy like that
I definitely don't want to see him again
No, thank you!
But still, your back is cute
The more I want to do it, the more I
want to do it
I want to win!
I can laugh!
Even if I don't have much experience
You don't have to be afraid, come here
I'll hold you in my arms
It's not that cute, I feel sorry for you
No matter how many times I'm told the
same thing
I can't sleep like this, in my heart
It's like a cat that only has eyes
Even if my friends say I'm stupid
If I like you, I can't see you anymore,
that's love
Everyone, let's make some noise!
Let's make this venue one!
Here we go!
One, two!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Thank you!
You're the worst person I've ever met
I can't doubt your pure heart
I want you to give it back, until now
I've always believed in you
Me too, you too, me too
God, where do you want to give up?
It's about time
If I'm here, if we're together
We'll be able to have the best time of
our lives
Even if my friends say I'm stupid
But then I'll end up laughing
I'm the one who made you cry
Even if it's a lie, I can't accept it,
it's a joke
I want you to tell me clearly
I'll crush everything I can
If there's something I want, I can't run
away
I can't say it, I can't say it, I can't
say it
There's nothing I can lose
I'm not afraid, I don't care, that's
love
If I'm here, if we're together
We'll be able to have the best time of
our lives
Even if I fall in the same way
I'll just look at you for a moment
You don't have to change, come here
I'll hold you in my arms
I'm not really pretty, I feel sorry for
you
That's not true, it's the same thing
over and over again
I can't sleep like this, in my heart
If I wasn't here, I'd be like a child
Even if my friends and family say I'm
stupid
If I fall in love, I can't see it,
that's love
Tell me what you wanna do
Give you something to believe in
Tell me if you'd like to stay for the
never-ending game
Even if the future of humanity
Is just a dream
I'll be there for you
It doesn't matter, the end, the end
Your answer is more important than that
Results, results
Will my love disappear?
Will I survive? What's after that?
Yes or no answer, no more waiting up
It doesn't matter what form you're in
Give me a chance
If there's no possibility, it's a dream
Because I think
Once I'm done, I'll go on forever
You know
If it doesn't end, it'll start again
I just have to keep going
Even if it doesn't start, don't let it
end
I believe, I believe
If it doesn't work now, it's fine like
this
The important thing is to continue
Rather than starting, the never-ending
thing is
I believe, I believe
You know what I want from you
If you just let me close the door
Any number, you'll be here
'Til the day it comes your way
I've never thought about
The future of the earth
Sorry, sorry
Just thinking about myself
Is what I do my best
Selfish, selfish
I'm sure you'll be surprised
What's the purpose of this day?
Take it or leave it
Crack something in the air
Just keep loving like this
There is no chance
If you don't notice, you'll be wasted
I won't give up, keep going
Until I become a fossil, I'll keep it up
Hey!
There's no choice but to evolve
depending on the environment
Oh yeah!
With the power to live under tough
conditions
Oh yeah!
Even if you're not loved
Someday, I'm sure
It doesn't matter what form you're in
Give me a chance
If there's no possibility, what can you
do?
I'm thinking of it on my own
Once I'm done
I'll keep going forever
You know
If it doesn't end, it'll start again
Just keep going
Even if it doesn't start, don't end
I believe, I believe
If it doesn't end, it'll start again
Just keep going
Even if it doesn't start, don't end
I believe, I believe
You know why I won't love you
If you just let me go down
Let me know that you'll be here
See you someday and dance your way
You know why I won't love you
If you just let me go down
Let me know that you'll be here
See you someday and dance your way
Just keep going
Even if it doesn't start, don't end
I believe, I believe
If it doesn't start, don't end
"Moon Kiss"
Moon Kiss
Don't look at me with that face
I'm sorry for surprising you
"Moon Kiss"
The moon was beautiful tonight
That's why I miss you so much
I hugged your shoulder
And suddenly stole your lips
It's unforgivable to make excuses
I've been waiting for this moment
I wish I could be honest
But love is a cowardly emotion
It's like a fragile glass
Ah, I kissed you
The wind blew by
And the lights went out
How awkward
We were awkward
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I wish I hadn't done that
I should have just let you go
If I was going to regret it
I could have predicted
What would happen to us
Moon Kiss
What kind of face should I make?
Should I walk out without saying
anything?
I was actually confident
I was always confident
Suddenly I thought of you
You're like a superman
I've thought about it so many times
I'm not good at soft feelings and love
It's painful to imagine
Let's have a moment of silence
You're too good for me
Ah, I love you so much
Is my heart beating so fast?
I'm sure I heard it
I feel like I'm in a hurry
Ah, it's bad
I'm not calm
Let's try to get along
It might be too late now
Can I be your lover?
I have to let you go now
If I wait like this
It'll be the worst day
It's painful to imagine
It's too romantic
I can't think of anything
Is my heart beating so fast?
I'm sure I heard it
I feel like I'm in a hurry
The wind blows
The sun has set
I don't know why
We don't feel good
I was afraid of loneliness
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have left you
The road home
It's a long way
I could predict
It would be like this
I love you
"SAMIDARE SHIKI"
Samidare yo oshiete kure
Kumorisora ni sakendeta
Yamu tsumori ka? Yamanai yo ka?
Saki no koto wa wakaranai mama
Samidare shiki
Suki ni natte ku
"SAMIDARE SHIKI"
Kotoba ni shite shimaeba
Raku kamo shirenai keredo
Jibun no hou kara nante
Zettai ni iidasenai hazu to
Shinai no wa
Tenki mo kimochi mo onaji
Hazanuki dochi tsukazu
Boku wa tomodachi no mama de ii
Dakara kokoro no uchigawa de
Amayadori shite
Kumo no kireba
Taiyou wo koko de matsu
Samidare yo ato kara to kara
Itoshisa ga kobiagete kuru
Miagetatte kawaranai you ni
Dokoka ni michi kitai shite shimau
Samidare yo setsunaku naru
Itsu no hi ka wa itsu kuru nda
Hirogerarenai kasa wo motteru
Imasugu ni arimitsu tame ni
Donna toki mo taeru koto nai eien wo
Ai to shinjiteru
Yamanai ame wa nai
Daremo ga sou iu keredo
Hontou ni sou darou ka
Kimi ni dondo ni hikarete kuru
Ima sono doa wo
Akeru no ka
Akirameru no ka
Mikuji nashi no
Jibun ni torikakete iru
Kurushii yo
Kimi wo omou to
Uppouteki de
Iki mo dekigai
Chupahapa wa
Kirai dakedo
Dochira ka ni
Kimerarenai
Tsure ni natte mo ii
Fuwan no naka
Tokidasu teki ga
Sou iu ki ga
Boku ni attara
Ame datte
Kitto kiru darou
Nani mo sezu ni
Atsui kumo ni
Owarete ichau
Kimi ni
Tsutawaranai
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Osane ni natta
Yamukana
Sabikareyo
Ado kara dou kara
Itoshisa ga
Komiagete kuru
Miagetatte
Kawaranai no ni
Imiji
Kitai shite shimau
Sabikareyo
Setsunaku naru
Kizunohi kara
Itsukunda
Kirogerarenai
Kasou omotteru
Imasugu ni
Ai ni yuku tame ni
Donna toki mo
Taeru koto nai
Eien wo
Ai to
Shinjiteru
Kotae nanka
Teru wake nai
Sore ga koi da
Sabidarashii kimi
Furitsuzuite ru
Suki ni natteku
Hanayo Yamuna
Dareka namae wo yonderu ki ga shita
Moshikashita na shinjitsu
"Suki nanka natte inai yo" tte
Zutto hitei shiteta no ni
Yappari
Yururirurira
Toyokage ga tsutaeru
Hana no kaori
Kisetsu dake janakute
Kotoba ni nante tsudakatta
Kokoro ni soyogu
Itoshisa no
Koi ni
Kizukasareta omoi
Marude
Shiranai uchi ni
Karachi ga nugitaku natte
Natsuyoku
Dareka namae wo yonderu ki ga shita
Boku wa furimukinagara
Machi no sato no naka
Sagasu you ni
Zutto kimi ni natteru no wa
Dreaming girl
Yururirurira
Hontou no jibun wa
Kimi to nanko wakatte inakatta
Aozora no mukou ga
Hareteiru to wa kagiranai
Sore wa
Omochi areru you na
Masaka
Meguri ga koi de
Mata sugu ni aitaku natte
Shimau kurai ni
Boku ga dareka wo ishiki shichau nante
Ichido nante nakatta
Nazeka zenshinkei shuchuu shite
Hitotsu no koe kikoeta
Kitta
Kaze ga fuite
Subete no oto kakikesare
Ah
Sagashiteita
Boku no chikaku no
Sono sonzai wo
Itsumo naratana no
Yume nanoni de
Dareka namae wo yonderu ki ga shita
Boku wa furimukinagara
Machi no zutto no naka
Sagasu you ni
Zutto kimi ni natteru no wa
Boku ga dareka wo ishiki shichau nante
Ichido nante nakatta
Nazeka zenshinkei shuchuu shite
Hitotsu no koe kikoeta
Kimi
Dareka namae wo yonderu ki ga shita
Moshikashitara
Maboroshi
Tsuri nanka
Terinaiyou tte
Zutto shite shiteta no ni
Yappari
Yururirurirai
そんな風に思われてた
過信をしていた生き方が
抜けなかった
だって全身全霊頑張ったのに
自分だけの思い込み
吐き出すその汗も
乱れた息遣いも
脈打つ鼓動も
何も関係ないのさ
その場所に
行かなくちゃ
気づかれない
熱い情熱
どこまでも
行かなくちゃ
気づかれない
熱い情熱
どこまで駆け登れば
青い海は出てくるのか
夢に近づけるんだ
どこまで駆け登れば
僕は鳥になれるんだろう
止められる日が来るまで
走り続けろ
どんな努力してみたって
ちゃんと結果が出ていなくちゃ
意味がないんだ
そんな誰にもわかる大前提を
忘れていたというのか
流したその涙
滲んだ赤い血も
胸の痛みも
何も語らないよ
誰からも
無視されて
終わるさ
勝ちのないもの
いつまで競い合えば
地平線に辿り着けそうか
それが現実になる
いつまで競い合えば
君を友と呼べるんだろう
思うようにはならなくて
悔しかったよ
不便
まさか乾杯するなんて
思ってもなかったよ
だって僕は僕のベスト
出したつもりか
そんなことを言ったって
何も評価されないんだ
せめて
僕は僕のベスト
結局
自分の力が足りない
そういうこと
どこまで駆け登れば
青い海は出てくるのか
夢に近づけるんだ
どこまで駆け登れば
僕は鳥になれるんだろう
止められる日が来るまで
走り続けよう
不便
つかはなそうこの夢
みなさーん!楽しんでますかー?
今回のこのツアーから
みなさんの声が聞けるようになったということで
てんちゃん!
はい!
間違えた
てんちゃんじゃないの?
間違えちゃった
誰?
ひろちゃん!
じゃあ
ごめんね、てんちゃん
全然ありがとー!
ごめんね
ありがとー!
ひろちゃんどうですか?
大阪のみなさんの声は
そうですね、大阪のみなさん声はもちろん
表情が良くって
表情
目元しか見えないから
分からないと思われてるかもしれないけど
結構にこやかにされてるのがすごい伝わってきて
ほんま好きやわーって
思って
せっかく大阪に来たので
みなさんの魔法の言葉を聞きたくって
なに?なに?
私が今からよく分からないことを言って
せーのって言うので
なんでやねーんって言ってます
あーいいねー
いいですか?
もっと
じゃあいきますよー
桜坂のみなさん
大阪46です
せーの
なんでやねーん
さすがーやっぱ本場は違うわー
ひろちゃんもさー
関西出身やんな
なんでそんなに
大阪っぽいやん
エセっぽい?
エセっぽかった今
そんなことないよな
あるっぽい
そうやな
でもなんかちょっとだけ関西に戻ってきたら
関西語意識して
ちょっとカパコトになっちゃう
あー分かる分かる
あるある
ということでもう一人聞いていきたいなと思うんですけど
今度こそピンちゃん
やったー
どうですかー
嬉しい
でもそれがあいなの音の前に
煽りをさせていただくんですけど
大阪のみなさんほんとにいい声出てて
もう一回聞きたいなって思うんですけど
準備いいですか?
いきますよー
私たちって
可愛い
いい
面白い
ダンスうま
いい
みんなのことが
大好き
ありがとうございます
大好きです
どう天ちゃん
これ2回目かな?
今日やるの
嬉しい
やっぱり
何回やっても嬉しい
ありがとう
これからもね
いっぱいいっぱい声出してほしいなと思います
お願いします
なんかこうやって今の
最後の文字を言うっていうのは
桜坂でしかないコール?
の仕方なんじゃないかなって思うので
みなさんもぜひ覚えて書いてほしいですね
思います
はい
こうしてコール&レスポンスが
今回のライブからできるようになったということで
私たち桜坂46は
桜坂46として活動を始めてから
ライブだったり
みなさんと直接会える機会っていうのが
なかなか難しくて
その時期に
やっぱり私たちも
ファンのみなさんが
桜坂46を好きでいてくれる方って
どこにいるんだろうって
一瞬不安になってしまう時もありました
だけど今こうして
私たちの目の前には
大きな愛と大きな声援と
たくさんのキラキラのサイリウムを見せてくださって
本当に嬉しいです
ありがとうございます
どんなに険しい坂道も
挑戦し続けられるのは
バディーズのみなさんが
いつもそばにいてくれるからです
We are not afraid of such a big love of
BUDDIES!
I will do my best to show you everything
I've got!
Can you keep up with me?
Yeah!
Thank you so much!
Let's have a good time in the second
half of the game!
Here comes the third player!
Let's go!
Let's have a good time in the second
half of the game!
How good we were on the way home
Your smile and his smile
I feel sad for some reason
I hope tomorrow will come soon
I can't catch up with you
Every time you walk ahead of me
I'm waiting for a chance
I want to play with you
Summer touch
Where should I put it?
I don't know where the next season will
be
Because love is always valuable
Tell me the future map
Summer touch
Hold your right hand
There must be something in the wind and
sunlight
We used to say the same thing every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wish I could invite you someday
I've never been in a hurry
Suddenly, today
I have to hurry more and more than my
heart
I want to speed up
the order of the seasons
No matter what I do
I don't know where the next season will
be
How long will the strong road continue?
The rain won't stop
The light shines through the clouds
Let's find a place
Even if the strong road is far away
I'll keep chasing the miracle
Hold your right hand
If you turn your face
It's already the beginning of summer
If I can, I want to fall in love with
you slowly
I don't have time for rivals
Summer touch
Where should I look for?
I don't know where the next season will
be
Because love is always valuable
Tell me the future map
Under the summer road
With my right hand
The wind and the sunset
I used to say the same thing every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
It's already the beginning of summer
Summer touch
Where should I look for?
I don't know where the next season will
be
Because love is always valuable
Tell me the future map
Under the summer road
With my right hand
Hello everyone!
Good evening!
We are SAKURATAKA46 3rd generation!
Are you excited?
Yeah!
I'm going to talk about us 3rd
generation
We joined SAKURATAKA46 this year
and had a welcoming party in March
We will also participate in the 3rd tour
from April
We performed in various places with our
seniors
Did you enjoy the party?
Did you come to the 3rd tour?
Yes!
Thank you!
We came up with a catchphrase
Please introduce yourselves
Let's start with Rika
I have a question for you
Which do you like better?
Toro toro or crispy takoyaki?
Toro toro!
I like crispy takoyaki
I'm Rika Ishimori from Toyama
I know it's sudden, but which do you
like better?
Riko toro!
Everyone calls me baby
but I don't approve of that
I'm Riko Endo from Saitama
Nice to meet you
I'm Reina Odakura from Tokyo
I used to do kickboxing
I want to be the number one student in
your heart
I'm Reina Odakura, the power of the 3rd
generation
Nice to meet you
Everyone!
Kodaki!
Thank you!
I'm Nagisa Kojima from Nagano
I'm 17 years old and I'm the talkative
one
I'm Yamaguchi from Fubin
I'm 18 years old and I'm the talkative
one
I'm 18 years old and I'm from Yamaguchi
Nice to meet you.
I'm Izuki Nakashima. I'm 20 years old
and I want to be your girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sakurazaka46's youngest.
I want to be spoiled by everyone.
I'm 16 years old from Fukuoka
prefecture, my name is Mio Otono.
Nice to meet you.
I eat a lot and grow up, so please
praise me.
I'm 17 years old from Hiroshima
prefecture, my name is Itoha Makaya.
Nice to meet you.
I am you, I love you.
My personality is at my pace, I love to
dance.
I'm Yuu Murai, 18 years old, from Tokyo.
I'm Miyu Murayama from Tokyo and I'm 18
years old.
I'm the tallest among the three, so I
think it's easy to find me.
I'll find you a lot, so thank you.
I love to eat. I'm Yamashita Suzuki, 18
years old, from Kyoto, in charge of
ramen Kaedama for the 3rd generation.
That's all for the 11th generation. I'm
going to try a lot of things and grow
more and more.
Buddies, thank you for your support.
This tour was the first time for us, the
3rd generation, to go around with
everyone.
Today is the final, so I think it went
by in a blink of an eye.
Looking back on the previous tours, I
had a lot more time with my seniors,
and I learned a lot of things up close.
Above all, it was so much fun to enjoy
music with Buddy's.
It was so much fun to enjoy music with
Buddy's
When I remember the anxiety I had when I
stood on the stage of Omotenashikai 3
months ago,
I think I was able to grow little by
little by receiving a lot of power from
everyone during this tour.
I will continue to do my best without
forgetting my gratitude.
And today is the final.
I would like to convey my love to
everyone who came to the venue and
everyone who watched the live broadcast.
We are Marie's...
1, 2...
I love you!
And...
1, 2...
I love you!
We will do our best to perform the rest
of the time.
Are you ready?
Not yet.
I'd like to deliver the message to the
seniors backstage.
Let's make some noise!
Are you ready for the second half?
1, 2...
I love you!
[Song title]
I'm alone on the street, I'm being
cornered
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday
There are so many things I want to say
But all I can do is shout
It's a stage without me
So I can sing with all my heart
It's fine if only those who understand
me listen
That's my message
Liar, liar
Don't lie to me
I want you to listen
Liar, liar
Lower your head
Liar, liar, liar
Where is your soul?
Where is your home?
I'll make you look back
From here, lock you, lock you, lock you
It's fine to be alone, so stop your feet
I wanted you to listen
I'll knock on your shut-off brain
And make your voice hoarse
No matter how you fight against others
You'll become a fool
I don't want to change someone's life
I want to sing a passionate song
Loser, loser
Did you give up on your dream?
You've already given up, haven't you?
Loser, loser
Who is pointing the finger at you?
Loser, loser, loser
Life is full of mud
My heart is stained with tears
I can't help but laugh
Even now, I feel it, I feel it, I feel
it
What am I living for?
I just want to know
Who am I here for?
Until I know the answer, oh yeah
Where is your soul?
Where is the ball?
I'll make you swing
From here, lock you, lock you, lock you
The soul will always exist
As long as life goes on
Please, lock you, lock you, lock you
Translated by Releska
Don't try to change this world
The sky that got dirty before I knew it
The window that I closed with my own
breath
Let's change the direction of your heart
Even so, if you still want to dream
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
The reason you're despairing on your own
Is because you don't have a goal, just
realize it
No, no, no, even if you blame someone
There's only one thing left, a mystery
game
If you don't have that, loneliness is
tears
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Translated by Releska
Don't try to change this world
The sky that got dirty before I knew it
I don't want to cry
No matter how much I hate it, I'll
scream
I don't want to fight, that's all
If I can be reborn again
No, no, no, don't say beautiful things
Even if it's like that, even if it's
like that, I won't fall
Even if it's like that, believe in the
strength to live
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No matter how deep the forest is
A single tree is gathered and made
If the wind blows, you'll understand
Yeah, the light and the shadow overlap
again and again
Time will turn to dust
Don't blame yourself
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Hey, don't spit on the ground
Oh!
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
You're despairing on your own
Even if you don't have a point, notice
it
No, no, no, even if it's someone else's
fault
There's only one thing left, a mystery
game
Even if it's like that, even if it's
like that, I won't fall
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Hey, don't spit on the ground
Oh!
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
You're despairing on your own
Even if you don't have a point, notice
it
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Hey, don't spit on the ground
Oh!
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
You're despairing on your own
Even if you don't have a point, notice
it
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Hey, don't spit on the ground
Oh!
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
You're despairing on your own
Translated by Releska
Even if you get a little carried away
If you notice it, you'll skip it
If you remember it, you'll laugh
Because you'll start to have fun
You'll feel uneasy
You'll lose your heart
No matter what you say
I don't care at all
I'll give you a smile
I want to make you happy
Why didn't you fall in love?
What have you been doing all this time?
Because both of them
"I love you"
It's like a cat with three eyes
But I found out when I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meet each other, love each other
I'm not good at it
It's not me
I want to find the real me
I'm not sure if I should show you my
picture or just talk about myself
I'm not sure if I should curse at such a
stupid couple
I'm not sure if I should think it's fun
or not
I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem
It's almost Christmas
Valentine's Day is coming
What's the plan for my birthday?
I want to boast about my happiness
Yes, I was afraid of falling in love
I'm not sure if I should think it's fun
or not
Because I'm not sure if I should make it
a problem or not
I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem or not
I should have noticed it earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited
People who are lost
Confess right away
Like the audience watching by your side
Look at each other, hug each other
Let's make a wish
(I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem or not)
I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem or not
I was afraid of falling in love
I was always nervous
Because I love you more than anything
I'm like a cat with a stick
But I realized it after I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meet each other, love each other
I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem or not
(I'm not sure if I should make it a
problem or not)
[Megurine Luka - "Toranai Ai"]
♪ Who is it coming from?
♪ I was eating while I didn't know
♪ Where is your confidence?
♪ For some reason, my heart was joking
♪ Hey, counting two, three, tap
♪ A cool one-boxer
♪ Half of the stars
♪ Is it a good idea?
♪ How is it? I'm confused
♪ I'm having a hard time
♪ I'm on the rise
♪ I'm not crying
♪ I'm just being normal
♪ I don't care what happens in the world
♪ I just want to be the best
♪ I'm just a girl
♪ Who is it coming from?
♪ I don't know
♪ Beats me
♪ Everyone, everyone, let's enjoy
♪ Tonight, let's have a party
♪ Let's have a party
♪ I don't want to be a target
♪ Because I'm a good girl
♪ Hey, if we do this
♪ Everyone, everyone, yeah
♪ Can't be entangled
♪ Let's understand each other
♪ Let's look at each other
♪ If there's no love
♪ The world will end, yeah
♪ I'm not kidding
♪ I'm not a fool
♪ I don't care what happens in the world
♪ Take it one, two, three, four
♪ I don't want to be a target
♪ Because I'm a good girl
♪ I don't care what happens in the world
♪ I'm on the rise
♪ I'm not crying
♪ I'm just being normal
♪ I don't know
♪ Beats me
♪ Everyone, everyone, let's enjoy
♪ Tonight, let's have a party
♪ Let's have a party
♪ I don't know
♪ Beats me
♪ Everyone, everyone, yeah
♪ Why?
♪ Why do we care?
♪ Tomorrow we'll cadaver
♪ And enjoy the party
♪ Enjoy the party
♪ If we can get down to business
♪ Do we need to worry
♪ Oh no
♪ If you're desperate
♪ We won't stop
♪ Cheer up
Let's believe, let's believe, if we
don't believe in each other, the world
will end
Yeah!
Where did this flower bud come from?
I don't know, it was just love
Ready, set, go!
I didn't feel any pain
Let's believe, let's believe, if we
don't believe in each other, the world
will end
Yeah!
Where did this flower bud come from?
I don't know, it was just love
Ready, set, go!
I didn't feel any pain
I only thought about myself
(I only thought about myself)
I see, everyone, you were the only one
who could talk to someone
Yeah!
I don't know, it was just love
Let's put a smile on our faces
(Let's put a smile on our faces)
I won't say anything to anyone
I'll be a good girl
Yeah!
I didn't feel any pain
I only thought about myself
(I only thought about myself)
I see, everyone, you were the only one
who could talk to someone
Yeah!
I don't know, it was just love
Ready, set, go!
I didn't feel any pain
(I didn't feel any pain)