AISubs v3.2
I'm going to do it!
Good morning!
I brought the script!
For me?
Yes
Eh?
It's going to come out?
That's right!
2 days later?
Wait!
Really? I'm happy!
Yay!
I'm always in your care.
I'm in your care.
I'm at ease.
That's right.
I'm a hard worker.
In this program, the members of Sakurasaka46
collaborate with the entertainers.
It's wonderful!
It's an experimental variety show.
I'm happy!
Are you okay?
Why me?
I'm happy!
Rochi-san,
Other than the 4 members of Sakuramitsu,
She's the most impressive member of Sakurasaka46.
I'm happy!
I'm so happy!
It's a commercial!
I'm in the middle of an investment!
This time, Kanto will be playing the role of an investor.
Onuma and Yamasaki will be playing the roles of the
boss and the lunch girl, O-El.
They will be investing after being influenced by Nakaoka.
I don't know how to say it,
but when you say,
don't try to take it.
I really want to see it.
Really?
Yes.
Say,
Don't try to take it.
Say it.
Tulips.
Tulips!
After the rehearsal, they go to the dressing room.
It's fun.
Sakuramichi is fun.
It's good.
Regular.
Is it good?
Actually, there is a trick for this Kanto and Yamasaki.
In order to convey the content, they go to the Onuma Studio.
At the end, Ten-chan says,
Tulips.
And you say,
I got it right.
But in reality,
it's not a tulip.
What do you write?
I write sakura.
Ten-chan thinks it's a tulip,
but it's not a tulip.
I see.
The flower is a flower,
but it's not a different flower.
I want you to guide Sakura with those hints.
You can't say sakura.
You can't.
Onuma Akiho and Yamasaki Ten
Three.
Lodge.
The show begins.
Thank you for your hard work this time.
Thank you.
Thanks to the two of you, the project was a great success.
That's not true.
It's thanks to you.
No, no, no.
I'm counting on you from now on.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll follow you forever.
I'm glad you said that.
I'll do my best to be like you.
No way.
Thank you.
You can eat anything.
You're Nakaoka from Skeleton, right?
Yes, I am.
What?
Who?
Do you know him?
He's famous on SNS as a psychic who can do magic.
A psychic who can do magic?
Yes.
He's a hard worker.
What do you mean by a hard worker?
I've never heard of a psychic who's a hard worker.
I've never heard of it.
Then I'll do it for you, Toshi.
Now?
Can you do it now?
I'll do it.
I'd like to see it.
I'm looking forward to it.
With this magic.
With magic?
Draw something on the cross.
Do I have to guess this?
Yes, you have to guess it.
Anything is fine?
Anything is fine.
Wow.
Toshi?
Can Toshi do it?
If you work hard, you can do it.
Is this okay?
Yes.
I drew it.
Is it okay?
Yes.
This is Toshi.
Toshi?
I'll do it.
Really?
What?
What's this?
She's trying so hard!
How can she do this?
Good luck!
Thank you!
She's saying thank you!
I've never heard of this type of person!
Look at me!
Don't talk!
How can you talk like this?
She's trying so hard!
Don't talk like that!
I've never seen this type of person!
She's trying so hard!
I'll move a little bit.
Is that a slouch?
I don't know if that's a slouch!
Can you see me?
I think I can see you!
What's your name?
Hoshi-chan?
Hoshi!
I can see you!
She's the type of person who can invest a lot of money!
That's amazing!
What's that?
That's my line.
That's amazing!
You can do it if you try hard?
Do you have any tips?
I'm trying so hard!
I think you're more talented.
Really?
Can I do it?
Yes, you can!
You have to try hard!
I'll try my best!
You can do it if you try hard.
Everyone doesn't try hard.
I'll try my best.
Please invest a lot of money!
I'll do it!
I'm sure you can do it!
You're trying, but...
Can you do it?
You can do it!
You can't do it, right?
You can't just hit it like that.
Can I cheat?
What do you mean, cheat?
What's wrong with you?
What's cheating?
What do you mean, cheat?
Is this cheating?
It's not cheating.
You can see it with this.
It's okay.
I think I can see it.
You can see it? Really?
Really?
You're trying really hard, but...
The sun?
I can see the sun!
Skeleton!
I don't want to do that either.
Good, good.
If you work hard, you can see the sun!
Okada-senpai, I'm going to quit my job.
Why?
I'm going to eat the sun.
You can?
Didn't you say you were going to work hard for the company?
No, no, no.
Should I try it too?
You're going to do it?
I don't think it's possible.
I think she has more talent.
You think so?
Really?
I think you should try it.
You're going to do it?
Okada-senpai, I'm going to eat the sun too.
What do you mean?
I'm going to quit my job.
You haven't done it yet.
You wanted to quit your job.
You haven't done it yet, but you don't know.
Can you draw something for me?
You can?
Yes.
What is it?
I'm going to work hard.
Good.
You're going to work hard?
Good, good.
I'm going to work hard.
Please draw something for me.
You're good.
This.
I see.
This?
Yes.
Is it okay?
You have to work really hard.
It's okay.
You're really going for it.
Can you see it?
More, more.
You can't see it, can you?
One more time?
One more time is fine.
Just keep going.
What are you doing with your hands?
You can't do it without your hands, can you?
You're doing your best.
I want to cheat, too!
Cheating?
Do you want to cheat a little?
Just a little.
That's not cheating!
On the contrary, it's getting thicker.
It's harder to see, isn't it?
Let's try harder.
That's cheating.
I can't see it!
You can't see it.
That's right.
It's pretty thick, so you can't see it.
It's impossible, isn't it?
I can see it!
You can see it!
You can see it, can't you?
It's a tulip!
Tulip?
No, it's not.
What?
It's not a tulip.
No, it's not.
You can't see it.
You can't see it at all.
It's not a tulip at all.
You can't see it.
Look again.
It's not a tulip.
You can't see it.
You have to work harder.
Tell me what it is.
It may look like a tulip, but it's a little different
from a tulip.
What is it?
Tanpopo.
No, it's not.
What are you talking about?
It's not.
You can't see it at all.
Look at it together and work together.
Teach her what you can see.
I'll teach you if I can see it.
Do it together.
One, two, three.
Teach her.
What color is it?
It's a little light pink.
It's pink.
Can you see it?
It's a cherry blossom.
It's correct.
You can see it.
Let's do it together.
Skate.
Ten-chan, it's your first time, isn't it?
It's my first time.
I had a surprise.
That's right.
Ten-chan said it was a tulip during practice.
I had a surprise.
It's not a tulip.
I didn't make a mistake.
I think you'll get it right.
What did you think when you were told it was a tulip?
I thought it was a tulip.
Are you sure?
I think it's over.
Tulip.
You'll get it right.
It's not a tulip.
I got it right.
I knew I was being fooled.
When I saw the VTR, I felt sorry for Ten-san.
I was thinking about it all the time.
The four of us were rehearsing.
I didn't know it was a tulip.
I read it alone and explained it to you.
I'll do this at Ten-chan's place.
I'm not going to be there.
I said I'd draw a cherry blossom.
You said it was wonderful.
It's not a tulip.
What are you going to draw?
I'll draw a cherry blossom.
It's wonderful.
I didn't want to be pulled by you.
I thought I'd surprise you.
I thought about it for a moment.
But I couldn't convey it.
Why?
Stop it in the middle.
The script says it's a tulip.
You're lying.
We're not the type to write a script.
I'm going to tell you what to do.
I don't usually have a script.
That's why I drew it.
You did what I told you to do.
I thought it was amazing.
I hope you can give me some advice.
If you're going to do a skit,
You can do it as you want.
You can do it again.
It's easier to do it if you do it freely.
You can do it.
Do you think you can do it?
I don't think Nakaoka-san shook her hand.
I was wondering if you thought so.
I didn't shake her hand.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You changed your mind in an instant.
Nakaoka-san, did you shake your hand like that?
No, I was wondering if you thought so.
No, it's because you're laughing.
My head is all messed up.
Nakaoka Shinobu-san's first time hearing it.
Know-it-all Lodge Quiz
Yamasaki also participated in the game.
It will be released later.
Next time, Masumoto Kira meets Kaeru-tei.
Challenge a passionate radio listener.
In addition, in the drawing quiz, the answer is repeated.
No, it's not.