The summer road, I live and hold it
In the wind and the sun, I'm sure I'll
be able to see it
Even though it was a daily routine
It's too late for the sunset to set
Was it okay to be friends like that?
On the way home
That guy and your smile
For some reason, it became painful
I hope tomorrow will come soon
I can't catch up with you
Every time we walk ahead of me
I'm waiting for a chance to talk
I want to invite you to my arms
Where should I look for the summer
sunset?
The door to the next season opens
Love is always precious
Tell me the future map
Hold the summer sunset in your right
hand
In the wind and sunlight
I saw the city at night
Even though it was a daily routine
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wish I could do that someday
Until now, I haven't been in a hurry
Suddenly, I'm curious
I have to hurry the distance of my heart
It's in order, but
I want to skip
No matter what I do, no matter how I
cheat
I can't hand you over to anyone else
How long will the road to the next
season continue?
The rain won't stop at the bottom of the
darkness
Let's find a place where we can meet
At the edge of the clouds where the
light shines
Even if it's a long way on a winter
night
I'll always chase a miracle
If you turn that corner in front of you
That's already the entrance to the
midsummer
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I want to fall in love with you slowly
if I can
But I don't have time because of my
rival
Where should I look for the summer
sunset?
I'm curious about the next season
Because love is always precious
Tell me the map of the future
Hold the summer sunset in your right
hand
In the middle of the wind and the sun
I saw the same thing every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
That's already the entrance to the
midsummer
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
"Summer Sunset"
It's the best time!
Who likes it?
It doesn't matter
Flowers blooming
What to choose
I'm not alone again
Everyone is doing their best
I support the flowers
There are places where the sun shines
There are places where it doesn't shine
I try to live as hard as I can
The beauty
It's the best time!
Let's sing as much as we can
So that the feelings I have for you will
last forever
Until the end of the sky opens again
someday
Let's keep shining
It's the best time!
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
From the other side of the stage
I can clearly see
The wind and the sound of the sun
I want to raise you
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
No matter how many flowers
They all bloom
Until they bloom
The feelings are different
Don't compare me to others
Aren't you yourself?
Someday you'll understand
What's important is persistence
What you can do without hesitation
Do what you want to do
A life without regrets
Go ahead and dive
Let's put our shoulders together and
start
Let's be friends who won't run away from
anything
Good things and bad things
Let's show them all
I want to be your friend
Go ahead and dive
Let's play a song with the rhythm
Let me hear your message
The stage above
Let's have the best time
I don't need that
Leave it in my memory
It's only for the two of us
You put your eyes on it
Believe that you can make a big flower
bloom
Someday you'll graduate
Until that day comes
Let me see everything
It's the same time
Let's play as much as we can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that day comes
Until the flowers bloom
Let's keep shining
It's the same time
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
You can see it clearly from the stage
The wind, the sun, and the rain
I want to raise you
Good evening, Various
We are Sakuranaga 46
The last performance of the new album
has started
Are you excited?
Some of you are here for the live
performance
Can you see us?
We are all here
We are all Various
Let's have a great time
Thank you
The new album is performed by
Nogizaka 46 5th generation
and Hinatazaka 46 4th generation
We are Sakurazaka 46 3rd generation
Sakamichi 3rd group
We are performing in Milano
Today is the last day of the live
performance
We are sad
We would like to hear your enthusiasm
Yu, please
I'm Murayu
Today is the last day
I'm the only one in the 3rd generation
I've come this far
I'm so happy that I've been able to run
through it so far, and that's why I want
the last performance to show all the
power that the 3rd generation has now,
so I want everyone to accept it with all
their might.
Everyone, please watch it with all your
might!
Thank you very much.
I'd like to ask another person.
Yes, I'm Suzuki Yamashita.
Yes, it's already the 10th performance,
so I'm feeling a little lonely.
As Yuu said, we've been practicing a lot
during this period, and we've been
working hard to deliver a wonderful live
performance to BUDDIES, so we might not
be able to see this live performance in
the future.
I hope BUDDIES will feel the same way,
and we'll do our best, so BUDDIES,
please give us your support!
Are you ready?
More! More!
Thank you.
Today is the last day of the 3rd
SAKURAZAKA HOTEI SHINKUZU.
Are you ready to follow us?
Please shout more!
Thank you.
The live has just begun.
Please enjoy it to the end!
"SAKURAZAKA HOTEI"
"MICRO SCOPE"
"SAMIDARE"
and communicate with each other.
Today, we were able to hold the last
performance.
It's a little sad, but it's the last
time for the five of us.
I'd like to hear from everyone.
First of all,
Reina, please.
I'm Reina.
When I thought about what I was able to
absorb the most
when I ran through the ten performances
with everyone,
I thought about each and every one of
us.
For each of the songs, one person must
have this kind of feeling.
"Is it like this? Is it like this?"
While searching for it, I'm conscious of
making more and more good things.
I think that what I was able to share
with everyone was a treasure in this
Shinzan Mono.
Thank you.
As Yuna-chan said, this time we were
able to do a lot of songs with just the
three of us,
and that was also a very first
experience.
We made each song while facing each
other.
Then, I would like to hear the story of
the other person.
Yuzuki.
Yes, please.
I'm Yuzu.
Yes, I am...
This Shinzan Mono is...
Sakura.
I think it was a time when I became even
more fond of the group "Atataka46".
I thought so while facing various songs.
The best friends of the 3rd generation
always help me, and when I'm in trouble,
they reach out to me.
I felt and loved everyone more and more
as if they were warm friends.
And my seniors came to see me and told
me, "This song is like this."
When I heard it, they told me, and I
thought that they were doing it in a
really warm environment.
And above all, the BUDDIES came to see
me like this, and they gave me a
penlight, and I thought that they were
watching over me on the other side of
the screen today.
I'm really happy that everyone's
presence is our support and that we can
make a live performance with everyone
like this.
Thank you, everyone.
I want to make more noise with everyone,
so let's do "Call & Response" together!
Thank you very much.
Nagi-chan, please.
I'm Nagisa Kojima, the captain of the
3rd generation.
Are you ready?
First of all, I'd like to do the usual
thing.
Are you ready?
Let's do it!
Everyone!
Go Nagi!
Wait, I don't want anyone to fly.
Thank you very much.
I have something I want to do today.
Yuzu did the "Call & Response" at the
"Omotenashi-kai".
I want to see it again.
Yuzu, can you do it for me?
I'd love to do it.
If you haven't been to the "Omotenashi-
kai", don't worry.
It's very easy.
Follow my "Rika-chan".
Everyone, please do "Rika-chan".
Rika-chan, Rika-chan, Riko-chan, Riko-
chan.
Please do it for 11 people.
Yeah!
Can I do it?
Let's do it!
Rika-chan!
Riko-chan!
Ena!
Nagisa!
Airi!
Yuzu!
Nao!
Itoha!
Yuu!
Niu!
Shi-chan!
Thank you very much.
Let's continue to make a lot of noise
and get excited!
Yeah!
"Omotenashi-kai"
"Otomenashi-kai"
Thank you!
Super considerable numbers of votes!
That's right!
Even though I feel good.
Can't help.
That's right!
I even wonder what you'll think.
Even though I feel good.
Think about it a bit.
Think a bit.
I want to meet you, I want to meet you
The window I went to die in is clouded
I wish for the opening of my heart
But even so, if I want to dream
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
I'm despairing on my own
Because I don't know, I've already
realized
No, no, no, even if I blame someone
There's only one thing left, this story
game
If that's the case, I'd rather choose
loneliness
No, no, no, nobody's fault
I want to change my way of living
But there's no way I can, so I run away
Before I knew it, I've become an adult
I'm fed up with excuses
I don't want to hear you cry
No matter how much I complain, no matter
how much I scream
I don't want to do it, I don't want to
do it
If that's the case, I'll be reborn again
No, no, no, don't say beautiful things
Even if I laugh, even if I laugh, I
won't fall
Even so, I'll live, I'll believe in my
strength
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No matter how deep the forest is
A single tree gathers and lives
I wonder if you'll understand when the
wind blows
Light and shadow overlap many times
Time will turn into a forest
Don't blame yourself
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Don't hold grudges
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
It's not natural to blame yourself
But you should know
No, no, no, even if it's someone else's
fault
There's only one thing left to say
If that's the case, I'd rather cry alone
No, no, no, nobody's fault
"Spring Day"
Even if I cry a little, I'll live
Even if I cry a little, I'll remember
I think I'm laughing
It's the first time I've had a boyfriend
I'm starting to feel a little fluffy
My heart is going to disappear
I don't care what people say
I'm smiling
Happiness is an enemy
Why didn't I fall in love?
I've never felt that way
Because I've always said "I love you"
I'm a cat with a cat's tail
But I've come to understand after
falling in love
What do people live for?
We met, we loved, we became friends
I want to find a true story that's not
mine
I say it in person
I show my school photos
I talk about love
I want to be a fool like that
I think about it and fall in love
It's almost Christmas
Valentine's Day
How do you feel about your birthday?
Happiness is an enemy
Yes, I've never fallen in love
I'm in the middle of getting excited
Because I've never felt this way
I don't care what people say
I want to find a true story that's not
mine
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm excited, I'm nervous, I'm nervous
People who are lost
Confess your love right away
Hug each other, hug each other
Let's kiss
Happiness is an enemy
Yes, I've never fallen in love
I'm in the middle of getting excited
Because I've never felt this way
I don't care what people say
I want to find a true story that's not
mine
What do people live for?
We met, we loved, we became friends
I want to find a true story that's not
mine
I'm not the type to rush things
I don't want you to understand
When I realized it, it's been a long
time since I've had the easiest time
I want to hide my gaze with my long
bangs
Go away, go away, I'm not here
Even if I'm suddenly confessed to, I
can't believe it even for a second
I'm covering my eyes
My big shoulders are in the way
There's nothing good about loving each
other with all your might
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
It doesn't matter
Even if we stare at each other with all
our might
What will you tell me?
Please tell me how you really feel
That's all I want
Ah, falling in love is a pain in the ass
I've never seen anyone like you
You're not special, I don't feel
anything
I don't like being judged
The corner of my heart is looking for
someone's shadow
Like the rain that suddenly came
I'm waiting for you at the corner of the
station
I can't accept the excuse that I'm going
home
You're calculating what you'll remember
in the scenario, aren't you?
If you do this and that, you'll be in
trouble
I don't want to go against the scenario,
so I'll do this and that
I want to believe in the content of my
own mind
Now, with my heart, I'll make a
resounding "Alarm Call"
"Alarm Call"
I don't want to hurt my instinct
My first love is too cowardly
Even if I get a chance to run away
It's not good to love each other half-
heartedly
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
I don't care
Even if we stare at each other half-
heartedly
Hey, what will you tell me?
Tell me your true feelings, Joven
I'll do it from now on
Ah, it's troublesome to love half-
heartedly
Hey, what will you tell me?
Yes, the live performance is now in the
middle of the show. Are you excited?
This time, it's a solo live performance
for the 3rd generation, so the 3rd
generation will play the songs that the
seniors usually play.
I think it's a live performance without
seniors.
I was very nervous and anxious since the
opening, but I got a chance to do it
only for the 3rd generation, so I think
I can only do it for the 3rd generation.
I want to do it in a way that I can't
express.
We've been practicing a lot, and we're
doing our best, but what do you think,
everyone?
I'd like to hear what everyone has to
say.
Airi-san.
Yes, I'm Taniguchi Airi.
That's right.
It's been a long time since we performed
at Shinzamon.
I was wondering what we were doing a
year ago, and when I looked it up, we
were just practicing the full size of
the band.
At that time, it was hard to arrange
even one song, and I was trying to stand
up.
Itoha is a newcomer, so I've been able
to do a lot of senior songs and 3rd
generation songs, and I think I've grown
and powered up, so I'd like to do my
best to power up more and more in the
future.
How about Itoha?
Well...
I came to Shin-Zamon's old park today.
We watched all the videos of the old
park.
We talked about the members every time.
I thought it would be better to do this.
When I look at the old park,
I think that the good points of each
member have grown a lot.
Above all, the whole 3rd generation?
Thank you very much.
I think that the things that are
conveyed in the performance are getting
bigger and bigger, so I hope that we
will do our best from now on and show
various performances and various 3rd
generation.
Thank you, Itoha.
In January, there will be a backslide.
Thank you very much.
There are members who will participate
in the 3rd generation.
I'm sure you'll be able to do various
positions in the backslide.
I'll do my best to live up to your
expectations.
Please look forward to it.
so please wait for us.
Thank you.
The last performance of Shinjambo.
I'll run through until I run out of
strength.
Thank you for watching!
I want you
Why do I long for someone on a cloudy
night?
The ceiling of the room that turned off
the light
Listen to the voice of my heart
I can't sleep even if I think about this
and that
What should I close my eyes and dream
about?
I think that silence is a kind of
violence
Don't hurt me anymore
The infinite depth that I thought I knew
Like being sucked into the darkness
Everything becomes nothing
The light was denied
By my side
If someone, if you, if you came to me
I'm not afraid
"Sleep"
Has the city already fallen asleep?
Or is it already dead?
With the noise from the world
Everyone will be lonely
In this world, there is someone other
than me
Because I'm noisy
I'm relieved by the presence of people
I'm not alone, I want to believe so
Nothing has happened
I feel like the hands of fate are
spinning around
Like sinking into the bed
My body is cold
My lips are dry
The infinite depth
There is a sound called "silence"
I certainly heard it
The words I said end
"Silence"
Do you love silence by abandoning your
desire to talk?
It's natural to imagine
Even if you say it's a delusion
I can't answer the correct answer
It's useless, but I'll wear it over my
head
I won't get any more love
Until dawn
Don't blink, be quiet
I want to shout from myself
It's okay to cry, my voice is sad
I want to let you know that I'm here
I can't be noticed if I keep quiet
I can forget even if I love
I want you to stop ignoring me
With a loud voice
Just waiting is suffocating
I can't think of anything
What are you going to take from me?
The silence that makes me stop thinking
is
"Voyeurism"
Is it fun? Is it interesting?
Did you get a good idea?
I'm thinking about it
I'm just walking normally
I'm just living normally
I'm just a girl
Who?
For what?
Hey, it's me
Are you interested in me?
A little more
I won't let you do that
Hey, if you are going to do this
If you say it to me, it's useless
Let's talk, let's watch each other
The world will end
It's not a joke, my dear
That's not what it's about
The weather is bad, it's a bad night
The only good thing here is that guy
The world is in chaos, the world is in
chaos
The only one who can stop it is me
I'm sure I'm the only one who can stop
it
Because if I don't do it, I'm sure I'll
lose
I'm sure I'm the only one who can stop
it
Tomorrow is another tomorrow
So let's party, so let's party
If a miracle happens
It's all the same
I'm sure I'm the only one who can stop
it
Let's believe, let's believe, let's
believe
The world will end
Yeah!
The world is in chaos, the world is in
chaos
The only one who can stop it is me
The world is in chaos, the world is in
chaos
The only one who can stop it is me
I'm sure I'm the only one who can stop
it
Because if I don't do it, I'm sure I'll
lose
I'm sure I'm the only one who can stop
it
Tomorrow is another tomorrow
So let's party, so let's party
If a miracle happens
It's all the same
The sky is tiny
Everyone is selfish
Everyone
I thought I was talking to someone
I always thought so
Yeah
I don't know anymore
A familiar smile
I'm so annoyed
But from now on
I'm going to try my best
If you do this, no one will be able to
get out of this house
Let's meet inside, let's look at each
other
If there is no love, the world will end
Yeah!
If you don't close the door,
no one will be able to see you
Even at the end of the weekend night,
you can't hear the bell
Yeah!
I was looking somewhere else in the
corner of the room
That's not the only reason
I was late for everything
I took a walk again today
I'm glad the sky ended with the voice of
the wind
Why did I pretend to be a devil?
Hey!
What, what, what, what are you doing?
I haven't seen you for a long time
While playing games all the time
I became an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why are you so busy?
Wait a minute
But you did that to me!
Where is that?
Bang-san, but Kichi-san
Even if I was told that I couldn't
If you go again, you can't get closer to
me
Bang-san, but Kichi-san
Even if you told me to stop
Understood
I wonder if I'm a fool
God, what is it that I can't do?
I wonder where the standard is
Hey!
If you hide your worries
Even if you do nothing, they will
disappear
If I were you
I would be able to do anything
What are you doing here?
What are you playing with?
Someone please tell me
It's something that has to change
Suddenly, one step further
The future has been disqualified
What should I do if I'm banned?
I just didn't know
One more time, one more time
Give me a chance to start over
What should I do if I'm banned?
Am I going to live?
I was young, I was worried
That's why I believed in my dreams
God, please forgive me
To suddenly make such a declaration
Hey!
The sun is too bright
The wind is blowing
Until the darkness comes
There's still time
Even if I'm banned
I'm being told that I can't
Even now
It's not like I can become a different
person
Even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told that I can't
I understand
I won't hesitate
I won't back down
God, what is it?
Can't I do it?
I wonder if that's the standard
Even if I'm forced into this situation
I'm definitely going to be banned
Hey!
Thank you!
Translated by Releska
(applause)
Senpai-gata...
The beautiful history of SAKURAZAKA46,
which you have built for us.
Now, it's our turn.
What can I do for myself?
What can we 3rd generation students do?
We keep thinking about it
We 3rd generation students
At this important place
We have to be serious
With our seniors
I love you, BUDDIES!
I will protect this cherry tree.
I swear it here.
I love you, BUDDIES!
I can see a single firefly
that is slowly spreading out.
The wind is shaking the buds.
I've been longing for this since a long
time ago.
To live with determination.
Even if I'm struck by a violent storm,
I'll put my roots in the soil.
I'll wait for this place in the future.
The nameless one who has been waiting
for us.
That dream starts from here.
The responsibility is very heavy.
I received it in my arms now.
That beautiful history,
those days full of scars,
everything.
Let's make a vow on this stage.
Yes, this time it's our turn.
Until the day when our young and strong
construction
becomes a moon,
no one will move their heart.
If you look up at the night sky,
many stars are shining.
In the darkness,
you can't see the stars from here.
Hey, you guys.
Even though we're working hard in the
same way,
why are the flowers that bloom and the
flowers that don't bloom
not rewarded?
God is watching.
The most important role is
to put yourself in this place.
You know the reason why you were born in
this world, right?
You won't move until the next wave.
The most important role is
to put yourself in this place.
You know the reason why you were born in
this world, right?
You won't move until the next wave.
You know the reason why you were born in
this world, right?
You won't move until the next wave.
You know the reason why you were born in
this world, right?
You won't move until the next wave.
You know the reason why you were born in
this world, right?
I don't even have the courage to look at
it
What can I do with a pure heart?
I'll just keep thinking about that
Thank you very much
Did you enjoy Sakurazaka 46's new song?
This new song has been going on since
November
But today is the last day
It's finally the last day
I'd like to talk about how I feel a
little.
[Q. How do you feel about your first
live performance as a 3rd generation
member?]
When I first heard that I would be able
to perform as a 3rd generation member,
to be honest, I didn't know if I would
be able to fill this huge venue with my
abilities,
or if I would be able to fill this huge
venue with my connections,
so I was really looking forward to it.
I was worried and worried about whether
I would be able to leave the venue to
Sakura Takahashi 46,
but once I decided to do it, I was able
to see the last day of my life.
That's what I'm thinking right now.
We, Sankisei, have decided that if one
of us gets hurt, we will help each
other.
The goal we set together is "Everyday
Smile".
We have set a big goal of smiling every
day and having fun.
Every time I perform a song like this, I
think of Sankisei.
There were so many moments when our eyes
met.
I thought, "Oh, this is the end of this
live."
I thought, "Is this the last song to
perform?"
I was overflowing with tears.
But in the end, we were able to finish
with a smile.
It's all thanks to the BUDDIES who are
here now.
It's all thanks to the staff who
supported us like this.
And again, I feel that it's all thanks
to my beloved friends.
Thank you for watching until the end
today.
I hope you will continue to support us.
This has been SAKURA TAKA HONTEI 6th
SANCHEI.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you!
SAKURA TAKA HONTEI
(chanting in foreign language)
(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
(chanting in foreign language)
Everything is over
We are one being
We are three being
(chanting in foreign language)
We are three
(dramatic music)
(chanting in foreign language)
We are the BEAST
I'm really happy to hear everyone's
voices today.
Finally, today is the last performance
of "Shinzan Mono".
It's a little sad to end like this, but
I'm really happy to be able to have a
fun live with everyone like this.
Thank you everyone for getting excited
today.
Thank you.
I would like to ask other members for
their impressions of today's live.
Mio!
Yes.
How was it?
It's a little sad to end like this, but
I'm really happy to be able to have a
fun live with everyone like this.
At first, I didn't know what a 3rd
generation live was like when I heard
"Shinza Mono",
but I'm so happy to be able to perform
live like this and paint colors like a
3rd generation.
Also, I feel more confident than I was
before "Shinza Mono" started,
so I hope I can continue to perform with
everyone in the 3rd generation,
but I don't know why I didn't say it at
the end.
I made a huge mistake.
That happened.
But it was cool.
But...
It was good.
It was cool.
Well...
That's life.
It was cool. Thank you.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
At first, I didn't know, but I think I
was able to show my personality little
by little as I did it.
And I wonder if I'll ask one more
person.
Riko-chan!
Yes, I'm Riko Enno.
Shinzanmono, it's over.
I'm so sad.
I feel like all three of us are
connected by a real bond in Shinzanmono.
I had a lot of fun in Shinzanmono.
When the lights were still dark, we
looked at each other and laughed.
When we played Obachan, we patted each
other on the back.
When I look at her, I think, "She's so
lovely."
I'm so happy when I think about it.
I realized that I really like the 3rd
generation, but I really like the 3rd
generation, but I would like to do my
best to grow as a member of Sakurazaka
in the future, so please continue to
support us in the future as well.
Thank you.
This Shinsaimono period is also the bond
between us.
We don't talk, but we communicate with
each other.
We feel like we really understand each
other.
I hope I can use this opportunity to put
my heart into one song.
Can I sing the last song?
We're lonely too, but we'd like to move
on to the last song.
Everyone, please dye this venue cherry-
blossom-colored.
One heart, cherry-blossom-colored.
What did you say?
That's right.
Let's sing the last song with our eyes
together.
Please listen.
"Sakurasaka no Uta"
There was a hole in my heart.
The real loneliness is not that no one
is here.
I want to meet someone important.
I don't know what happened.
I'm sure you can get over it.
Wow, wow, wow.
I've never forgotten the two cherry
blossoms.
Even if the flowers fall in the
distance,
Dreams should bloom here over and over
again.
So that I can remember you.
We'll get together on this hill.
If I can talk about you,
I feel like I can meet you again.
There must have been something sad that
no one could say.
I was worried about you.
There's nothing we can do.
I was waiting for you to stand up.
Wow, wow, wow.
Cherry blossoms in full bloom.
The wind blows in the summer and winter.
What did you keep waiting for?
Even if the people passing by
forget the flowers of that day,
The scenery of the next spring.
We've been thinking about it all the
time.
Wow, wow, wow.
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
My heart trembles with nostalgia.
Like a single tear wipes my shoulder,
Cherry blossoms will be in full bloom.
Wow, wow, wow.
Cherry blossoms in full bloom.
Even if you forget it once,
Dreams should bloom here over and over
again.
So that I can remember you.
We'll get together on this hill.
If I can talk about you,
I feel like I can meet you again.
Wow, wow, wow.
(applause)
Thank you very much for coming to
Shinzan Mono today, watching the live
viewing, and watching the live stream.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I was able to see a lot of your smiles
and hear your voices.
I was really happy to hear a lot of your
voices.
I think it's a natural happiness to be
able to stand on stage with all 11
members of the 3rd generation and to be
able to see everyone.
That's why I want to cherish this
happiness and continue to convey my
gratitude to everyone.
I will continue to work hard with my
seniors to make Takurazaka 46 the best
group ever.
Please continue to support Takurazaka
46.
Thank you for 10 new songs.
That's all. We are Takurazaka 46.
Thank you.
I can see the tent up there.
I can see it. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for the live broadcast.
Takurazaka 46!
(chanting in foreign language)
Sakurada-san! Sakurada-san!
(Cheering and applause)
Hitoha!
(Speaking in Japanese)
I don't care if I throw it away
It's just a black stone
Spread over the asphalt
I don't have a life that I've lost
I only have a part of it
What I got is a bright reality
I'm covered in lies
Don't pick up the pieces
If you're going to talk about it, talk
about the future
It's a useless epilogue
It's too bad for a princess
Let's get it and make sure
If it's not there, it can't be helped
It's not anyone's fault
I can't afford to look back
Rebellion and regret
It's too much
Don't talk about what you can say now
Take it to the bottom of the hill
If you put it into words, it's cheap
The truth that's on sale
If you're going to talk about your past,
your self-righteousness
It's a useless epilogue
Inside my heart
There's a glass bottle
I'm going to fill it up
I'm protecting it carefully so that it
won't break
I don't have a life that I've lost
I only have a part of it
What I got is a bright reality
The level of decoration
Don't talk about what you can say now
Take it to the bottom of the hill
If you put it into words, it's cheap
The truth that's on sale
If you're going to talk about your past,
your self-righteousness
It's a useless epilogue
Thank you very much.
Everyone, once again, today
Thank you for coming to our
"Shinzanmono" and watching the live
broadcast.
This "Shinzanmono" is a live show with
only three people.
It's a big chance for us to grow up, and
a big chance to get along with everyone,
so I've been doing it so far.
On the other hand, I don't say much
pressure, but there's a lot of pressure.
But even among them, we all worked
together and helped each other a lot to
get here.
The reason why we were able to perform
at all the concerts was...
...it's because of you, the BUDDIES,
that we were able to run this far.
It's because of you that we were able to
come this far with a smile on our faces.
It's sad that the concerts are coming to
an end, but...
...with all the love you've given us...
...we'll continue to perform with our
seniors.
We'd like to deliver a lot of exciting
things to everyone.
We look forward to your continued
support for Sakurazaka46.
Thank you for your support for the 10
new songs.
This has been Sakura Tokoho T-630. Thank
you very much.
Thank you for your support for the 10
new songs.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
See you again.
Thank you.