Summer's shortcut, hold it in your right
hand
In the wind and sunlight
I'm sure it's there
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
Were you that close on your way home?
That guy and your smile
For some reason, it makes me sad
I hope tomorrow comes soon
I can't keep up with you
You're walking ahead of me
I'm waiting for a chance to talk to you
I want to invite you to the sea
Where should I look for a summer
shortcut?
The door to the next season opens
Love is always a hassle
Tell me the future map
I'm looking for a summer shortcut
I'm sure it's there
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wish I could invite you someday
I've never been so impatient
Suddenly today
The distance between our hearts
I have to hurry
It's an instant shoot
It's my turn
I want to skip it
No matter what I do
I can't give you to anyone else
How long will this rainy night last?
The rain never stops
Let's find a place where we can meet
In the clouds where the light shines
Even if it's a long way around
I'm always chasing a miracle
If you turn the corner in front of you
That's the entrance to the midsummer
If possible, slowly
I want to fall in love with you
I don't have time because of my rivals
Where should I look for a summer
shortcut?
The door to the next season opens
Love is always a hassle
Tell me the future map
Summer shortcut
Hold your right hand
In the wind and sunlight
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
That's the entrance to the midsummer
Midsummer
It doesn't matter who you like
Can you choose the blooming flowers?
Everyone is doing their best, not just
one
I support the blooming flowers
There are places where the light shines
There are also places where it doesn't
shine
The beauty of trying to live hard
Let's start as loud as we can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that sweat blooms someday
Let's keep shining
Let's make one heart
That's all it takes to be brave
I can see it clearly from the other side
of the stage
In the wind, the sun, and the rain
I want to raise you
Midsummer
No matter what kind of flower it is
It's different, right?
It's different from the moon until it
wakes up
Don't compare yourself to others
Aren't you yourself?
Someday you'll understand your own pace
What's important is determination
To live with a pure heart
Do what you want to do
A life without regrets
Go out and dance
Let's sing with our shoulders together
Let's be friends who won't run away from
anything
Good points and bad points
Let's expose them all
I want to be your friend
Let's ring the floor and get the rhythm
Let your message resonate
Let's make the voltage of the venue the
highest
I want to be a member like that
Please leave it in my memory
You still have a long way to go
Look out and plant a bud
Believe that you can make a big flower
bloom
Until the day you graduate
Let me see everything
Let's sing as loud as we can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that sweat blooms someday
Let's keep shining
It's Ansem Time
Let's raise our hearts one by one
That's all it takes to be brave
From the other side of the stage
You can clearly see
The wind and the sun
I want to raise you
Good evening, everyone!
We are Sakurazaka46!
The 7th performance of "Shinzanmono" has
started!
Are you enjoying it?
Yeah!
Thank you!
"Shinzanmono" was performed by
Nogizaka46 5th generation,
Hinatazaka46 4th generation,
and Sakurazaka46 3rd generation
Three groups from Sakamichi
will perform at the Miranoda
There are various collaborations
throughout Tokyo Kabukicho Tower
I hope everyone will enjoy this new
album in various ways.
Thank you everyone.
Thank you.
And today
Everyone, are you having fun?
We're having fun!
Today, we're going to have fun with all
the BUDDIES watching the live stream.
Everyone, let's have fun!
I think it's time to hear from the other
members.
First of all...
Miyu, how are you?
I'm Miyu Murayama.
While we were taking a break, we took a
picture with the flag at the entrance.
How was it?
Did you take a picture?
Of course!
If you don't have it, you can take it
instead.
It's cold, so you can buy oden and warm
it up.
Let's have fun today.
Let's have fun.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to hear from the other person.
Airi, how are you?
I'm Airi Taniguchi.
Everyone, have you noticed anything
different about me?
I don't understand.
The correct answer is a little different
from the usual bangs.
Cute!
This is what Rika said last night.
"Airi, this definitely suits you."
I'm so excited because all the 3rd
graders complimented me on my bangs.
Cute!
Rika's bangs are so cute.
I have a lot of bangs today.
I hope we can have fun together with the
BUDDIES here and the BUDDIES who are
watching the live stream.
Thank you very much.
As Airi said, there are a lot of BUDDIES
watching the live stream and the live
viewing.
We are very happy.
Are you ready to liven up the venue?
Let's liven up the venue.
The live has just begun, so please enjoy
it to the end!
I thought that no one would be
interested in me
That's why I was happy that you noticed
my short hair
I can't see what love is
But I feel it when I know it
Thank you!
When it's too late, I'll just...
...smell you a little later
I'm not as lonely as I thought
Even if I walk alone, I'm far away
I might be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
I was looking for a place with a lot of
people
But there aren't many people today
Because the sun is moving
Let's walk on a different path
Let's go!
No matter where we go
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
I'm distracted by the scenery around me
I miss the flowers by my feet
There's someone watching me
Who's so clumsy
It's not something you can find forever
It's something you can only find on that
day
I'm sure that after a while
I'll remember that season
I was stronger than I thought
It's OK
I was more relaxed than I thought
Look up at the sky that's different from
yesterday
LUTZ
Let's move forward
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Everyone was afraid
of the darkness of loneliness
Even though I could live forever alone
(Really, really, really)
I wanted you to be by my side
The world is like a labyrinth
Overflowing with loneliness
I'm not alone in this forest
where someone else or someone else is
I'll be saved until the end
Don't think too much
It's not as lonely as I thought
Just walk alone
It may be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
(Really, really, really)
No matter where we are
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hey, hey, hey, Buddies!
Can you hear me?
Yeah!
I can't hear you!
First of all, everyone in the first row,
can you hear me?
Yeah!
You didn't lose in the second row, did
you?
Yeah!
Can you go to the third row?
You didn't lose in the third row, did
you?
Yeah!
Thank you!
Let's keep it up!
That's love!
You're always saying selfish things that
make me feel like I'm going to lose my
mind.
You're the worst person.
Do you understand?
Even if my experience is not enough,
I don't want to see you anymore.
No, thank you!
But for some reason,
I can't get out of the back.
Even though I won the lottery,
You don't have to change.
Come on!
I'll hold you in my arms.
I can't leave you alone.
I feel sorry for you.
No matter how many times I'm told the
same thing that I can't say,
I'm a man.
In this chest.
If I wasn't there,
I'd be like a cat.
Even if my friends and parents are
stupid,
I can't see it when I like it.
That's love.
LOVE
Ready!
Love! Love! Love! Love!
LOVE
You're the worst person in the world.
I can't imagine.
I can't doubt tomorrow.
I want you to love me.
I've always believed in legends.
I don't have any hope.
God, where do you want to give up?
That's it.
If I miss it here,
I'll cut off the best thread in the
world.
I'll be knocked down by the magic of
hell.
But then it's over.
I don't want to cry, so I'll do it
myself.
I don't care if it's a lie.
I want you to whisper to me.
I'll do everything I can.
If there's something you want, just take
it.
I don't want to lose anything.
I'll never regret it.
That's love.
LOVE
Love! Love! Love! Love!
If I miss it here,
I'll cut off the best thread in the
world.
I'll be knocked down by the magic of
hell.
I'll dream for a moment.
You don't have to regret it. Come on.
I'll hold you in my arms.
I can't leave you alone. I feel sorry
for you.
No matter how many times I'm told the
same thing,
I'm a man. I'm sleepy.
If I wasn't here, I'd be like a
abandoned cat.
Even if my friends and I know it's
stupid,
I can't help but notice it. That's love.
LOVE
Love! Love! Love! Love!
Love!
Love! Love! Love!
On a Sunday afternoon when the sky was
clear,
I got a message saying, "I'm going to
hang out."
I said I didn't want to because I was
upset,
but I pushed you to the ground.
I don't have a sense of responsibility.
I'm a man, too.
Yes, I've been nervous for a while now.
The laundry you wanted.
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed.
"That's enough."
I'm sorry I said that out of the blue.
It's the first time I've ever had a
meteor shower.
That's why I haven't been able to calm
down since this morning.
Even if I suddenly clean up,
there seems to be someone there.
I'm opening the door a little bit.
I don't have a heart.
I know. I wanted it.
I'm a novice.
The laundry you started to fold.
I hope this time will continue.
I was wandering around,
but I was happy
as I was.
Rather than having a special date,
I want to spend my daily life with you.
My scattered room
becomes beautiful so that I can see it.
What should we do next?
From the other side of Momoshizawa,
I'm dyed in twilight.
When will you come this time?
Because it's cool.
The laundry you started to fold.
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed.
"That's enough."
I said that out of the blue.
I want to brag to everyone.
I'm a novice.
The laundry you started to fold.
I'm happy as I was.
I want to spend my daily life with you.
My scattered room becomes beautiful so
that I can see it.
[music]
[applause]
I was absolutely sure that it was fate
That I only met you in that crowd
I don't want to go out to Shibuya
I changed my schedule that day and went
alone
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
When I was about to go home after
getting off the train
I climbed the stairs and met your eyes
For some reason, we laughed
Why are we here?
We were surprised by each other
Even if we calculate the probability of
coincidence
There is no answer
Even if we meet, there are things we
can't meet
Even so, there is a mysterious power
I'm attracted to it
I'm noticed by that secret
Oh oh oh oh oh oh
If we walk to the station
If someone sees us
I'll be misunderstood
I suddenly thought
I want to be ridiculed
The fact that we met here
There must be a meaning
Coincidence always
Tells me the answer to something
I thought
There are so many things I can't say
But today is different
I'm not alone
Courage comes from somewhere
Anyway, we are like this
You can go out with me
I know it's a joke
But what is it?
I saw you nodding
Is that serious?
I want to meet you by chance
Why are you here?
We were surprised by each other
Even if we calculate the probability of
coincidence
There is no answer
Even if we meet, there are things we
can't meet
Even so, somehow
I'm attracted to it
I'm noticed by that secret
"Blue Moon Kiss"
Blue Moon Kiss
Don't look at me with that face
I'm sorry for surprising you
The moon was beautiful tonight
That's why I'm very lonely
I hug your shoulder
Our lips suddenly met
It's painful to make excuses
I've been aiming for this moment
To be honest, I'm glad
But love is a cowardly emotion
Like a fragile glass
I kissed you
The wind blew through
I was jealous
How awkward
It's awkward
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I shouldn't have done it
If I regret it
I should have sent it as it was
The road is long
What will happen?
I could predict
Blue Moon Kiss
What should I do with that face?
Should I walk out without saying
anything?
Actually, I was half confident
I've been planning all this time
It suddenly occurred to me
It's a good idea
I've thought about it so many times
A soft feeling and warmth
Love is a selfish imagination
What a painful moment
I love you so much
This heartbeat in my chest
Is it something to be so excited about?
I'm sure I heard it
Feeling impatient
How awkward
Even if I try to act calm
It's too late now
Can I be your lover?
I have to say something now
If I stay silent like this
It will be the worst day
I want to joke
It's too romantic
I can't think of anything
Blue Moon
This heartbeat in my chest
Is it something to be so excited about?
I'm sure I heard it
Feeling impatient
When the wind blows
And the sun sets
How awkward
This awkward feeling
I was afraid of this atmosphere
What should I do?
If I'm going to regret it
I should have left it as it was
The road home is a long way
I could predict this would happen
Blue Moon
I've never loved anyone this much
That's how I feel
I don't want to hurt you
More than I want to hurt myself
I've been cornered
While waiting for the last bus
That timing
I wonder how many times
It's been a long time since we felt this
way
We were facing each other
There's no meaning in "what if"
Ah, until the graduation ceremony
What will change from that day?
Just changing places
Just making more new friends
Leaving behind something precious
I'm called an adult
I think of you
The cherry blossoms face the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least for a little while
Hey, hey, hey, hey
La la la
No matter how much I love you
The seasons pass
And the sun sets
That day, the cherry blossoms
La la la
What I'm dreaming of right now
Is that "what if"
I feel like I'm going to spit it out
A ball of love and hate
If you throw it away, you'll feel better
I can't do that
I'm going to Tokyo
I'm determined
I want to hear your voice and push your
back
I'll always be waiting for you
I'm sure you'll think it was a good
idea.
Sweet and sour youth
I wonder what you're trying to look cool
about.
I'm surprised I'm the only one.
At least that's what I thought when I
remembered you.
Such a beautiful love
Is it okay to be alone?
I want to praise you for the sound you
sent me
If I can't be like this so that the
flowers that will continue to bloom will
not wither
I thought about how to make it beautiful
Soaring in the sky, so that I can
remember it many times
I want to protect it, so I'll slowly
fall
So that you won't notice me softly
I dropped my umbrella
I tried to put my ears to your voice
And leave it in my memories
At the end of the dark night sky, I can
still see the cherry blossoms in full
bloom
That flower is the person I loved so
much
Even if I grow up and my dreams and
ideals don't turn out the way I want
them to
If only I could have such a beautiful
way of living
The cherry blossoms that think of you,
blown by the wind, soar up in my heart
At least for a little while now, stay
with me
No matter how much I love you, the
seasons will pass
In a blink of an eye, the cherry
blossoms will fall
Thank you very much.
Everyone, the live will continue, but
are you having fun?
Thank you very much.
While taking a break, everyone in the
audience, everyone watching the live
viewing, everyone watching the live
viewing,
while taking a break, please have fun.
Today is the 7th performance of
Sakurazaka46's 3rd Gen's Shindanmono
performance.
The 3rd Gen's live was an event in the
summer,
and when I joined, I also experienced a
live viewing.
Is there anyone here who wants to see a
live viewing?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for those who have a welcome
towel.
For those who watched the welcome
meeting,
so that they can surpass us further,
and for those who are watching the 3rd
Gen's live for the first time today,
including everyone at the live viewing
venue,
so that they can think that
Sakurazaka46's 3rd Gen is so amazing,
we will do our best to perform today, so
please enjoy it until the end.
Thank you very much.
Then I will listen to the story from
here.
First of all, Riko-chan, please.
Yes, I'm Endo Riko.
Thank you.
This performance is after yesterday's
two performances and today's lunch,
so I think there are many people who are
worried that they are tired,
but don't worry.
I ate a lot of cod roe today, so I'm
full of energy.
It's cod roe.
Only cod roe.
I'm sorry.
It's like this.
However, I want to continue to have a
lot of fun with everyone.
Let's do our best together.
Thank you.
Then I will listen to another person's
story.
Yuzu, please.
Yes, I'm Yuzu, in charge of coolness.
I'm really happy every day at Shizuoka,
and there's something I'm really happy
about.
I'm really happy to be able to perform
Anthem Time here.
Anthem Time is a song with the lyrics
"all the 3rd Gen and Buddies".
As the lyrics say, we are here because
we have Buddies.
I feel like I have to do this song where
everyone is.
I'm really happy to be able to perform
for the first time live like this.
I was happy.
Thank you, everyone.
Everyone was flying around at Anthem
Time.
Is that so?
It was a song that I enjoyed with the
audience.
Anthem Time was really...
Everyone's voices came out a lot.
The lights were shaking a lot.
The excitement was amazing.
Let's keep up the excitement with the
rest of the songs.
Thank you.
Reina, please give us a call and
response.
Yes, I'm Reina Odakura.
Everyone, are you ready to make a voice?
Today, I'm going to play with you.
What is it?
I'm going to say, "Up!"
Everyone, please shout "Up!"
If you don't usually say it, please say
it.
Just for today.
Here we go.
Up!
You can't go up yet.
Louder!
Up!
Thank you.
Now that everyone's throats are open,
let's make a lot of noise and get
excited!
Up!
Thank you!
I want to show off a little.
There were a lot of difficult moves for
the senior dancers.
We practiced for a long time, but we
were still nervous.
No matter how much we practiced, we were
still nervous.
I think the senior dancers are amazing.
At the same time, I want to do my best
for the junior dancers.
I'd like to talk to you today.
First of all, I'd like to talk about the
two songs so far.
Mio-chan, who was in charge of the
center of the song.
I was in charge of the center of "Omotta
Yoribu Sabishikunai" and "Nazeku
Shitekonakattan Darou".
"Omotta Yoribu Sabishikunai" had a hard
time with the rap part.
Every time the concert was over, I was
asked, "Can you do a little more?"
It was very difficult for me to figure
out how to do it in my own way.
And the reason why I didn't have a voice
was because of my body and my intention.
We practiced a lot, but this time it
went well.
Thank you very much.
And my way of running is really strange.
I did my best, but was it cool?
How was it, everyone?
Was today's run cool?
It was cool.
Ito's practice didn't go well at all.
It was hard at first, wasn't it?
It was hard.
We practiced so many times.
I was teaching Mio how to run in a small
lesson room.
It was cool!
I gave up running like this.
Like a feather.
I asked the dancer to fly.
I talked to the dancer.
That was good.
Thank you.
How about you, Yuu, who taught Niho how
to run?
This was my first time to be the center
of BLOOM! KISS.
Thank you.
The most difficult part of BLOOM! KISS
was...
This is a part of the lines, and this
part is really hard, so I consulted with
the 3rd generation members about how to
do it, and Airi's lines were so cute and
good, so I was taught. Thank you, Airi.
It was amazing.
Really? How was the lines today?
It was so cute.
Thank you for the many cute lines.
We'll do our best to show you our
various expressions!
We'll do our best!
Now, it's time for the last performance.
We, Sakurazaka46, will be performing
this song.
Please accept the feelings I have for
the dead.
I hate the time when it's too quiet
I can't even breathe
On a starry night
Why do people fall in love?
The ceiling of the room that turned off
the light
I can hear the voice of my heart
I can't sleep even if I think about it
What should I close my eyes and dream?
I think silence is a kind of violence
Don't hurt me anymore
A deep and infinite space
It's all impossible to be sucked into
the darkness
If you look at the light by my side
If someone, if you, if you could see it
I'm not afraid
Did the city sleep again?
Or did it die already?
The noise from the world disappears
Who will be lonely?
In this world, there is someone other
than me
Because it's noisy, I'm relieved by the
presence of people
I want to believe that I'm not alone
Nothing is happening
I feel like the hands of the clock are
spinning around
My body is sinking into the bed
My lips are so dry
I can't speak
There is a sound called silence
I certainly heard it
The words I was about to say are over
I want to sleep, I want to give up, but
I can't love silence
It's natural to imagine everyday life
Even if I'm told it's a delusion
I can't answer the correct answer
I'll put a blanket over my head
I won't be loved
Until the dawn
Don't blink
I'm jealous
I want to shout from myself
I don't care if I cry, I'll shout
I want to let you know that I'm here
If I shut up, you won't notice
Even if I love you, I can forget
I want you to stop ignoring me with a
loud voice
Just waiting is suffocating
I'll do my best no matter what
What are you going to take from me?
Silence is violence
Let's get excited
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I don't need time
What I see is different
I don't care if I cry
I don't ask for understanding
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I don't care if I cry, I'll shout
I want to let you know that I'm here
If I shut up, you won't notice
Even if I love you, I can forget
I want you to stop ignoring me with a
loud voice
Just waiting is suffocating
I'll do my best no matter what
Alice, let's go!
A dead end
There's an end to the world
What are you going to do from here?
It's still dark
A dead end
I'm scared when I wake up
Will I go back to the way I came?
I can't help it even if I'm here
I'm the one who made a mistake
A dead end
Let's connect the past and the future
How can I live now?
I don't care if I cry
I don't ask for understanding
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I don't care if I cry, I'll shout
I want to let you know that I'm here
If I shut up, you won't notice
Even if I love you, I can forget
What should I answer?
I got in touch with my parents and moved
on
If it's over, if it's over
Where will it start next?
What will happen in the future of
despair?
If it's over, if it's over
I'll find a way out
Is there a continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
It's still bright until dawn
If it's over, if it's over
Is there a continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
It's still bright until dawn
Where should I run to?
There's no way
Even if it's a lonely and boring street
Even if there's no possibility
I'm just tired
If it's over, if it's over
There's an end to the world
What should I do from here?
It's still bright until dawn
If it's over, if it's over
Is there a continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
It's still bright until dawn
If it's over, if it's over
Is there a continuation?
Translated by Releska
I was looking at you with a smile
There's no way I can give up
I was late for everything
I was late again today
You looked me in the eye
I'm glad I slept
I yawned
And my eyes grew
What do I want to be? What do I want to
do?
I haven't had a dream in a long time
While I was playing games
I became an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why am I so busy?
Wait a minute
What did you do?
So that the power of life can be cut off
I'm the only one who's okay
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told I can't
There's no way I can be a different me
now
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I won't regret it
God, what's wrong with me?
I want to know what the standard is
The sky of the past
Disappears without doing anything
If I were you
I'd be able to do anything
What are you doing here?
I'm the only one who's playing
Someone tell me
Suddenly, one step away
I was made closer to the future
If I'm banned, what should I do?
I just didn't know
Give me another chance to start over
If I'm banned, what should I do?
Are you going to let me go?
I believed it was for the sake of my
youth and worries
God, please forgive us
I can't believe I'm suddenly banned
The sun is too bright
It's leaking from the window
Until the darkness comes
I'll still make it
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told to stop
I can't be a different person now
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I won't regret it
God, what's wrong with me?
Where is that standard?
Even if I'm driven into a situation I
don't want to know
Will I definitely be banned?
Thank you very much
The beautiful history of Sakurazaka 46
that our seniors have built
It's our turn this time
What can I do for myself?
What can we, short-term students, do?
That's what I want to say
Keep this in mind, all eleven of us, and
keep your eyes open.
I want to protect this tree of cherry
blossoms with my beloved seniors and
beloved buddies.
I swear it here.
I'll protect it with my life.
It's my life.
The wind is swaying the spill
I've longed for it since then
To live with a will
Even if I'm struck by a violent storm
I'll put my roots in the ground
The ancestors waited for this place
They waited for us
The nameless one, that dream
Begins from here
The responsibility is very heavy
Now I've received it in my arms
The beautiful history
And the days full of scars
All of it
Let's swear on this ground
Yes, this time it's our turn
A young and strong old man
Until the next day
No one moves from here
If you look up at the night sky
Many stars are shining
In the darkness
The stars that can't be seen from here
Even though I'm trying to do the same
The flowers that bloom and the flowers
that don't bloom
Even the unrepayable guts
God is watching
The most important role
Yes, I'm standing here
I was born into this world
I know the meaning and the reason
I won't move until the next day
I'm a guardian
A guardian of the cherry tree
I was chosen by that person
I'm proud of it
Let's hold hands and make sure
The days I spent here
I'm sure I'll remember it someday
Because my friends were there
I was always able to smile
I think
Let's swear on this ground
Yes, this time it's our turn
A young and strong old man
Until the next day
No one moves from here
What can I do?
With a pure heart
Let's just keep thinking about that
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to see us today.
Did you enjoy the performance of "Kokura
Takaojin Shinsetsu Kouen"?
Thank you.
The show is over, but the next one is
still going on.
I hope you'll enjoy it with us, the
third generation.
Thank you for today.
That's all.
This has been the third generation of
Sakura Nakaho Nijishin.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.
(applause)
(chanting in foreign language)
(singing in foreign language)
(speaking in foreign language)
(applause)
There's a part where we have to decide
on a pose.
Yeah, there is.
In that part, we have to decide on a
theme for every 10 songs.
I see.
Rika, Airi, and I were posing like this.
Today's theme is "Ninja".
I wanted to do it.
I was doing this.
What did Rika do?
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to ask one more question.
Nagi, how was it?
Hi, I'm Nagisa Kojima.
Thank you.
I was happy today.
There were two things that made me
happy.
First of all, I was very happy to show
BUDDIES and the audience that we have
been practicing hard.
And the other thing is that BUDDIES
wrote in the sketchbook.
"Mamoribito" got 1 million views!
Wow!
There are a few people who wrote it.
There was a stream like this.
On the day of the stream,
as a commemoration,
we got 1 million views.
I'm so happy to be able to do this with
you guys.
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you for your support!
I'm so happy!
Thanks to you guys, we're able to do our
daily activities.
Thank you so much.
It's about time for us to go to the last
song.
Yay!
It's really lonely, isn't it?
It's really lonely.
But we're going to the last song, so
everyone...
I'm a pervert.
Please make the cherry blossoms pink.
You over there, please do it too.
Thank you very much.
I think it's time for the last song.
I hope we can continue to deliver the
full bloom of cherry blossoms to
everyone.
Please listen to it.
One, two, three.
"Sakura Saka no Uta"
The real loneliness is not that there's
no one
It's that I can't see my loved ones
I don't know what happened
But I'm sure you can get over it
Oh, oh, oh
I've never forgotten the full bloom of
cherry blossoms
Even if spring passes and the flowers
fall
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that I can remember forever
We gather on this hill
If we talk about you
I feel like I can meet you again
There were sad things that I couldn't
tell anyone
And I was worried
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to stand up
Oh, oh, oh
On the day of the full bloom of cherry
blossoms
In the wind of summer, autumn, and
winter
What was I waiting for
In the branches of the pine forest?
Even if people pass by
And forget the flowers of that day
The scenery of the next spring
We will always remember
Oh, oh, oh
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
In the nostalgia that overflows
Like the petals of each flower
Cherry blossoms will be full bloom
Oh, oh, oh
On the day of the full bloom of cherry
blossoms
Even if spring passes and the flowers
fall
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that I can remember forever
We gather on this hill
If we talk about you
I feel like I can meet you again
Oh, oh, oh
"Cherry Blossom"
Thank you very much!
I'm gonna cry...
Translated by Releska