Thank you for coming to Sakurazuka46's
Sakurazuka46 LIVE ION CARD WITH YOU
Vol.2.
I'm Yumiko Seki from Sakurazuka46.
I'm Ten Jumasaki.
Before I start, I would like to ask
everyone for a favor.
The camera in the venue, the video
camera.
Please refrain from using recording
devices such as video cameras with
recording functions.
Also, please refrain from using mobile
phones in the audience.
Please set your mobile phone to "manner
mode" and make sure that there is no
sound.
Recording and recording actions using
photo shooting, video cameras, etc. in
the audience will be prohibited at all.
Appearance in the venue is prohibited.
Please go to a specific place such as
the dining room.
Do not run away from your seat.
Throwing things to the stage is very
dangerous, and it will be a nuisance to
other customers, so please do not do it.
Also, please hold a towel, sketchbook,
fan, etc. at chest height.
There is a camera for video recording
and photo shooting.
Please be aware that your appearance may
be reflected in the video.
At the end of the show, there is a
possibility that the emergency light,
the guidance light will be turned off or
turned off.
Please notify us of the exit near you in
advance.
And as I told you in advance,
We will support you voluntarily by
requiring you to wear a mask from the
park.
The restrictions on loud voices such as
answering, completing, etc. have been
lifted.
I would be happy if you could send us
power with your warm support.
We will be back soon.
Everyone, call out!
Let's go!
[Music]
[Applause]
It's our era.
We will be in charge of MCing the
popular series of ION CARD, which has
had a lot of members as MCs.
It's about time for us to get our own
unit, isn't it?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
We don't have much time, so let's
welcome our first guests!
Come on in!
Welcome!
Our first guests are these people!
Please have a seat.
Excuse us.
Matsuda-san, we might become your
rivals.
We'll do our best not to lose.
It's a big mystery.
You're strong.
Now, Onoma-san, please explain the
rules.
I'll explain the rules of Kira Kira
Akiho.
On the screen, there is a test.
Let's talk about it with everyone
according to the theme.
It's the first real event, so let's talk
about it with everyone according to one
theme.
Yes, let's go right away.
Are you ready, everyone?
Roulette!
Start!
Stop!
That's good!
We do this kind of thing often, don't
we?
It's not that we do it often, but we do
it a lot.
Kira-chan takes us there.
That's right.
I see.
Well, well, well.
Do you have meals with the members?
We do.
Ten-san?
Yes.
That's Seki-san.
No, it's Ten-san.
Ten-san has a good style.
Ten-san.
No, it's Seki-san.
I'm curious.
Do you have any episodes, Seki-san?
Well, it's winter, so I often make hot
pot.
I have a chance to be a member of the
group, but I'm not sure if I'm doing it
right.
I have a chance to be a member of the
group, but I'm not sure if I'm doing it
right.
There's a lot of it.
And when Takemoto Yui is in the hot pot
team, she buys a lot of maitake
mushrooms.
Maitake mushrooms?
They're healthy.
Yui-chan likes maitake mushrooms the
most in the mushroom world.
Really?
I was wondering if there was anyone
else.
Maitake mushrooms are number one in the
mushroom world.
In the mushroom world...
Is there anyone who likes maitake
mushrooms the most?
Really?
That's amazing.
Yeah.
I didn't want anyone else to feel the
same way.
I didn't know there were so many people.
That's great.
Rena-san seems to like maitake mushrooms
too.
Really?
She seems to like maitake mushrooms.
What was the episode with the members?
We went to eat oden with Matsunari-nan
and Inori-chan.
It was so delicious.
It was really good.
It was just the three of us, but we
ordered a lot.
It wasn't a lot of food.
Endo-san!
Endo-san, you went to eat omurice with
me, right?
Omurice!
At that time, we went to Okinawa.
Who paid for the omurice?
Kira-sama.
She took me to eat the omurice.
But she didn't pay for it.
That's strange.
Well, well, well.
It's okay if you pay for it every time.
Thank you very much.
Morita-san, your name was called.
I'm going to eat with the members.
- Do you go? - Yes, I do.
I often go with Ten-chan.
We eat together, but we also go out
together.
Oh, you're close friends.
We often go to eat sushi together.
That's nice.
We eat sushi, and then have a bite.
It's wonderful.
That's cute.
That's a tradition.
Morita-san, you're wonderful.
Thank you.
That's cute.
That's wonderful.
That's all.
Everyone, it's fun, isn't it?
We often go to eat together.
Let's do it again.
That's all for the good stories.
It's sudden, but let's play a game.
A game?
Lisa-san and Habu-san also had a game.
That's right.
So we want to try it too.
What kind of game is it?
Here it is.
Masumoto.
Masumoto?
Isn't it just Hira-chan's song?
That's what you think, right?
But the person who made me feel the most
comfortable is...
We have luxury goods prepared for you.
We'll do our best.
The rule is that within 60 seconds,
you have to dance to the rhythm like in
the Yamanote Line game.
The person who compliments me in order
and makes me feel good wins.
It's a simple game.
Of course, Onuma-san, the MC, will also
participate.
There are a lot of good points.
I'll do my best.
Are you ready?
Let's start the music!
I'll go first.
Here I go.
You have thin legs.
Cute.
You have smooth hair.
Thank you.
You have a great voice.
You're funny.
Thank you.
You have beautiful hands.
I like your hair too.
Thank you.
Endo-san, let's do it one more time.
One more time?
One more time.
You have a fast head spin.
Thank you.
You're funny.
You're tall.
Thank you.
You have the perfect height for talking.
Your eyebrows move a lot.
Thank you.
You look good in any uniform.
You have a cute forehead.
Thank you.
You look good in braids.
How was it?
It was good.
You did a lot of things.
Thank you.
What made me the happiest was...
What?
Matsuda-san's eyebrows moved a lot.
That's right.
It moved a lot.
I said that because I thought I wouldn't
be chosen.
But you often brag about your eyebrows.
Matsuda-san's eyebrows move a lot.
I'm the youngest, Yoko.
I see.
People say I'm not amazing, but I'm
actually pretty amazing.
You're right.
You can see a lot of me today.
- Show us. - Look.
I'm sparkling.
Amazing.
Everything.
I'm going to show you everything.
Amazing.
I'm going to show you my face.
Let's have Takemoto-san move her face as
well.
Really?
I've never done that before.
I didn't get to hear the episode, so
I'll do it.
You can do it with your face, not the
episode.
Go for it.
Akari-chan.
So cute.
I won't let you talk.
I want you to show off.
Go eat with your senpai.
We made a song called "Cinderella Dance"
It's my song!
Yes, it's a song made by Onuma-san
We went to eat with Yui-san and Fuuka-
san
Really?
Yes
I'm so happy
We invited them to the party
The two senpais treated us to a meal
It was the best.
It's all thanks to me.
It's true. It's not thanks to Nemu-san.
It's true.
Let's go together.
It was so quick.
The first guest is over.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Take care.
See you.
Good luck.
Me too.
The next guests are first-year students.
Welcome.
Come in.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Please sit.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm a senior so I'm not shy.
I'm going to go all out.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please take care.
Seniors.
Did you follow the rules?
Yes.
You are good.
You are good, right?
Let's start with the roulette.
Roulette, start!
What is it?
Start!
It's a story about going out.
Going out.
I want to hear it.
Everyone has something in common.
That's true.
I want to hear it.
Let's have FUYUKA talk about it.
Last year, the five of us went to a
dreamland.
We've been there, but...
We've been there, right?
It's our first time, right?
It's our first time.
Could it be that you made a key chain
for us?
We bought it as a souvenir.
It's cute.
It has our names on it, and we even
prepared one for Sugai-san.
That's right.
During the tour.
We've been there during the tour.
That's right.
I had a job in Igawa.
I was busy.
Before I graduated.
Rumor has it that you had a conversation
in the bullet train.
Scary.
After that,
the next day's departure,
I heard that you left without going out.
Is that true?
I was so excited that I couldn't sleep.
Everyone was like that.
But it was raining a little.
It was a little rainy.
When we were on stage, we were like,
"Oh, it's Samidare!"
We were like, "Oh, it's Samidare!"
We were so excited!
That's amazing!
Also, these two over here...
I'm not very good at screaming, but I
did my best to sing "Time Machine".
I wasn't scared at all.
Koike-san and I went to the amusement
park together.
I've been to the Dreamland, but Koike-
san was really scared all the time.
Once, I was riding a motorcycle with a
bag.
The bag came out of nowhere.
When we were holding on to the bag,
Koyuki-san was laughing so hard.
It seems like you can overcome your fear
of heights by breathing.
Yeah, if you say "Zeha, Zeha" while
breathing,
it's like "Zeha, Zeha."
I want us to go with you.
Let's go together.
I'll take you.
All of us, all the members.
I want to go.
I want to go with Otoma-san.
I've been on a roller coaster before,
and this person is terrible.
I'm on a roller coaster with a mask on.
The mask is fluttering, isn't it funny?
So I said, "Look, look!" because I was
having so much fun.
But she didn't look at me.
I was really scared.
It was a scary roller coaster famous in
Japan.
I can't look at the person next to me.
Kira-chan kept saying, "Ohno-san, look,
look!"
Kira-chan is very relaxed.
In the end, she didn't look at me, so I
got on it again.
Yes, I saw the next one.
I want to go again.
Fuyuka-san, do you have any other great
episode?
Great episode?
This member?
Not this member?
Not at all.
But, that's right.
Just now,
Yui-chan...
Yui-chan often goes out.
She often goes out.
She doesn't go out.
She goes to her house.
She is close to her.
And we stayed the night.
That's nice.
I don't wake up in the morning at all.
That's cute.
I really don't wake up.
Do you sleep together?
Yes, we sleep in the same bed.
Is the video okay?
It's okay.
We didn't have a bed last night.
The room was warm, so it was okay.
That's all.
When you go out with the members, do you
get caught?
No, we don't.
You don't get caught?
But when the five of us went to the
dream country, we got caught.
Habu-chan didn't change her clothes.
Mii-chan hid her hair, but we got
caught.
But it was fun.
I notice Uemura-san right away when I
see her outside.
She's like a fairy.
Her feet are floating about 2mm, so it's
easy to notice her.
"Did you go out to eat the other day?"
Not the other day, but about 2 years
ago.
2 years ago?
- We ate udon together, right? - Yes, we
did.
- That's how it was. - We got along
well.
- We got along well. - We're close,
right, Kizuna?
- Yes. - We'll continue to watch over
you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Yes. - Koike-san, you seem to like
food and go out a lot.
- That's right. That was last year's
D.League? - Yes.
- D.League. - After the dance battle,
- Akiho-chan, Fu-chan, and I went
together. - I see.
- We ate together. - What did you eat?
- Yakiniku. - That's nice.
- How many people? - 6 people.
- Our seniors treated us to it. - It was
really good.
What is it?
It's a good story.
I've heard a lot of stories about going
out with senpais.
Senpais really treat me a lot.
I will continue to receive them.
Thank you.
Kobayashi-san, do you have any special
episodes?
Going out...
But it ended quite early in the morning
at the end of the shooting.
It was around that time.
We went to eat Okinawan noodles together
at a restaurant.
I saw it on your Instagram story.
Thank you.
We went to eat Okinawan noodles.
You two are so close.
We got to know each other unexpectedly.
It was nice to hear from everyone.
Let's play the game again.
Yay!
The next game is this
I'm scared
What is it?
Eh?
I'm fine
The rules are the same as before.
Did you hear it in the back?
You have to get on the rhythm and say it
in order.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Have you found a lot of good points?
Let's go.
Should I answer too?
If you can.
Let's go.
Music start.
Let's start with Rio-chan.
Let's start with Uemura-san.
Your response is bigger than anyone
else.
Your reaction is cute.
You are kind.
You are hard-working.
You are full of energy.
You have small hands.
You are good at dancing.
Your ponytail looks good on you.
Thank you, I'll do my best!
I can pilot a ship!
I'm a mirror!
You must be feeling great!
I'm feeling great!
Who made you the happiest?
Everyone made me happy, but...
Minami Koike's...
What was it again?
Everyone said I was cute, so I was
really happy.
You're cute.
I'd be happy if you said that.
It's cute.
Everyone is cute.
Everyone is happy.
I'm happy.
It's good.
When I heard your voice, I was like,
"Yay! Yay!"
I was like, "This is it! This is it!"
That's right.
Thank you, everyone, for coming today.
Thank you.
It was cute.
It was cute, wasn't it?
Yes.
We have another guest.
They are here.
Welcome.
Hello.
It's so close.
Please have a seat.
How do you feel about being our host?
It's surprising that we can do this.
It's surprising.
The Jamaica Building unit is in danger.
What?
It's dangerous.
We'll dance.
We heard the explanation of the game.
Yes.
Let's get started.
I'll do it.
Let's start the roulette.
What is it?
Stop.
I'm curious.
It's a word from the staff.
I'm curious about Inoue.
Thank you for everything.
- It's so nice. - Yes, yes.
- On top of the sand. - Yes.
Inori looks like she's having fun, so
let's hear it at the end.
- Eh? - Eh?
- I can't hear it. - I can't hear it.
- Can you see it? - Then...
- I'll leave it to the MC. - Let's go
with the 3rd one.
- The 3rd one? Okay. - Then...
- The 1st one is... - You're laughing.
Oh, right. You're going to decide.
The 1st one is... Marino!
- She's surprised. - Marino.
- My staff members are all kind. -
That's true.
Even the members.
- I'm curious about that. - Is it okay?
- I found a cute smartphone case on the
internet a while ago. - That's crazy.
- Yes. - That's crazy.
I was happy to buy it, and I put it on
as soon as it arrived and went to work.
Then, Kira-chan said, "Why did you buy
this?"
- Did she say that? - Yes.
I was shocked, and I haven't put on a
smartphone case since then.
- What? - What?
- I bought it. - I bought it.
- What did you say about that? - I'm
sorry.
No, no.
But you said, "Pick up my forehead."
- You said, "Pick up my forehead." -
That's a charming point.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Listen, Anastomophobius was very
charming.
- He was very charming, but... - Really?
There was a picture of a princess, but
it had terrible quality.
- What? I've seen it. - I wonder if it's
that kind of picture.
- A watercolor painting? - It was like a
painting.
- Ah, I've seen it. - I've heard of it.
- It's a painting. - I want to see it.
- Sorry. - It's fine.
I didn't know it was a painting, I
thought it was a bad picture quality.
Sorry, sorry.
Let's move on.
Who is it?
Karin-chan.
I want to hear it.
I...
What is it?
When I was at Lisa's graduation concert,
I arranged my hair in a rare way.
That's good, that's good.
Half-up or something.
When I was walking down the hallway,
I passed by a hair stylist and asked her
to change my hairstyle.
It's rare to be asked to do that.
I asked her to do that three times.
In the end, my hairstyle was the same as
always.
I just wanted to do it to her liking.
That's how it is.
I really like the arrangement, so I'd
like you to do it more often.
I want to see the dango.
I'll do it someday.
Everyone is happy.
It's rare to see it today.
That's true.
It's rare.
It's cute.
I'll pay attention to that.
What should we do next?
Ten-chan!
For me,
I'd like to do something
for Karin-san
who's sitting next to me.
What is it?
"I get tired when I'm in the tent."
What does that mean?
- That's terrible. - It's a close-knit
story.
That's terrible.
I was just told that I was annoying.
Annoying.
It's my fault.
I was stuck to Fujiyoshi-san's arm.
I was like, "Fujiyoshi-san!"
I was told that I was annoying.
It's true that your mouth was a little
bad.
My mouth?
But I was happy about that.
What?
Ten-san, aren't you happy too?
Not at all.
I see.
That's terrible.
You like it so much that you get tired.
That's right.
Next is...
It's about time for Itome-san.
Inari-chan, you should go last.
What?
I don't care.
You love it so much.
You should go last.
I see. Thank you.
Hono-chan.
Yes.
The MC made a script for this talk part.
Ah, I remember.
Yes, yes, yes.
And the two of them were asked, "How was
the MC?"
And it said, "Tamura was better than
me."
It did say that.
"Better than me."
Yes, yes.
It hadn't even started yet,
so I thought they'd already decided that
the two of them were better.
It was a bit of a shock.
I see.
Thank you.
Were you nervous?
Next is Rei-chan.
I want to hear.
Thank you.
It's the same as Karin-chan, it's about
hairstyles.
I did a half-up hairstyle for the first
time in a Samidareon MV.
I remember.
At that time, Morita's Hikau-chan
praised me a lot,
so I thought I'd give it a try in a live
performance.
I did a half-up hairstyle during a
rehearsal for Lisa's graduation concert.
But I didn't know what to do.
When I got my hair done the same way as
today,
my manager told me that I should change
my hairstyle.
Someone found out.
I found out.
I thought it was a bit weird when we
were doing the actual performance.
It was a shock.
It was a shock when I thought about it.
In the end, it was a hair style that the
audience liked.
Both were cute.
Thank you.
It was a perfect episode for the theme.
Let's go to the last one.
Inori-chan.
Me?
Yes.
Don't give me such a big hurdle.
There's a manager from Kansai.
I'm from Hyogo prefecture.
The members often say, "I know Inoue is
from Kansai."
They say that.
To be honest, it's a variety show.
Really?
The members say it, but it's a variety
show.
It's a variety show, but when I talked
to the manager from Kansai,
he said, "Oh, Inoue, you're in Kansai,
aren't you?"
He's teasing you.
He said it with a smile.
I was like, "Really?"
I was like, "That's not true. I didn't
throw it away at all."
I didn't throw it away, did I?
What do you think?
Why?
I can't take it back.
Okay, then.
It's sudden, but...
It's time for another game!
This time...
The next game is this.
What is it?
"One word with us"
What does that mean?
There will be a picture of you, so
please say something funny about it.
What is this?
A big cut?
Yes, a big cut.
I'll praise you both.
One by one, one by one.
Is everyone okay?
Please.
Let's do it.
Let's start with Inoue-san.
Why me?
Please do something funny.
It's important to be funny, so let's
start with Inoue-san.
I understand. I'll do my best.
Let's go.
Go ahead.
What is this picture?
Wait a minute.
It's difficult.
Hello? Hello? Rei-chan? Rei-chan?
Would you like to go to Masumoto
Amusement Park?
That's really funny.
Next, Rei-chan.
Wow, what is this picture?
Is there something?
I can't fly.
That's cute.
Next, Kosaka Morino.
Sugai-san, I became a horse.
That's amazing.
That's good.
Next, Tamura-san.
Tamura-san, please.
Netsunetsu?
Natsunetsu? Netsunetsu?
I don't know.
Next, Kichiyasu-san, please.
What happened?
That's creepy.
I...
I broke my leg.
So cute.
You're so young.
Ten-san, go ahead.
What are you doing?
Karin, look this way.
What is this game?
It was fun.
I want to do it again.
It's time to say goodbye to Kira Kira
Kyoho.
That was fast.
Everyone, please come in.
How was Kira Kira Kyoho?
How was it?
Was it fun?
Thank you very much.
It was close.
It's sudden, but we have good news for
everyone here.
Matsuri-chan, please tell us.
Please tell us.
What is it?
Everyone.
From now on, it's time for the surprise
lottery.
This time, it's only for those who come
to this venue.
There are various lottery boxes in here.
We will give a wonderful present to the
100 people who are here.
The first one is...
Acrylic stickers with our autographs.
That's nice.
Each member drew 5 stickers.
There are 95 people.
It will take a long time to draw 95
people.
The members drew it in advance.
Thank you.
I drew it properly.
I drew it.
After the event is over, we will show
you the tickets on the monitor.
Please make sure to check it out!
Thank you!
And the next present is...
Ta-da!
I want it!
We're going to give out autographed
notebooks to 5 people!
5 people!
We're going to have the members draw it
now!
First, Yui!
Who is it?
Please pray for me.
Everyone, please pray for me.
The standing number is 1254.
1254!
Yes.
Was it there?
Yes, it was.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
We will give it to you later, so please
look forward to it.
Next, Habu-san, please.
Thank you!
Who is it?
It's...
Mikaeseki's...
A1.
Number 41!
Who is it?
Congratulations!
We will give it to you later.
Next, Hono-chan.
Hono-chan, please.
Please.
Who will you choose, Hono-chan?
Who will you choose?
Who wants it?
You want it, don't you?
Number 1004.
Congratulations!
We will give it to you later.
You were happy.
Next, Karin-chan.
Karin-chan, please.
You want it, don't you?
Number 73.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Karin-chan!
Lastly, Hikaru-chan.
Hikaru-chan, please.
It's a little expensive.
Let's go.
Mikaeseki's...
G-class...
Number 5.
Mikaeseki's G-class Number 5.
Congratulations!
The acrylic stand will be announced at
the end.
You still have a chance.
Please look forward to it.
I'd be happy if you could wait for it.
Let me explain again.
On this monitor, you can see the sales
number on the ticket you have.
Please check the number of your seat on
the second floor.
When you leave the exit, please call the
person on the left.
That's all for the surprise lottery!
The live is finally starting!
I'll sing my new song "Numa Song" until
I'm ready.
This is Numa-chan!
Here you go.
"Numa Song"
I'm always shopping
Cashless, wow
How about being cool?
I'm always shopping
Cashless, wow
How about being cool?
How about shopping with your own card?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Wow, wow, wow
Hey, look at me
Tell me
Screaming in the cloudy sky
Are you going to stop?
Won't you stop?
You don't know what's going to happen
next
I'm getting used to it
I'm falling in love
If I put it into words
It might be easy
But I can't say it from my side
What I want to make clear is
The weather and my feelings are the same
I don't care about the wind
I'm fine as a friend
Inside my heart
I'm sheltered by the rain
The sun is waiting for me
In the clouds
Hey, look at me
From far away
My love is overflowing
Even if I look up
It doesn't change
I'm looking forward to a rainbow
somewhere
Hey, look at me
It's painful
Someday
When will it come?
I have an umbrella that I can't spread
So I can go see you right now
No matter what happens
I'll never wither
I believe in eternity
It won't stop, there's no rain
That's what everyone says
Is that really true?
I'm getting more and more attracted to
you
Should I wait for this door now?
Or should I give up?
I'm asking myself
Without any reason
It's painful
When I think of you
I can't move
I can't breathe
I hate halfway
But I can't decide which way to go
I don't care if I get soaked
I should jump out of my anxiety
If I had the courage
I'm sure it would rain
Without doing anything
I'm being chased by the thick clouds
I can't tell you
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
It's raining
Will it stop?
Sunny darling
From the window
Love is pouring out
Even if I look up
It doesn't change
I'm expecting a rainbow somewhere
Sunny darling
It's painful
When will summer come?
I can't spread it
I have an umbrella
So I can go see you right now
I believe that there is an eternity
That I can endure at any time
There's no answer
That's love
I'm being chased by the thick clouds
I'm falling in love with the thick
clouds
Let's stop the rain
Because, because, because it's painful
My voice, my voice, my voice won't come
out
I'm staring at you
All the time stops
I'm like a
Hey!
Suddenly, you're
The moon is
Hey!
The name of my feelings
I'm like a
Hey!
The name of my feelings
My heart is trembling
Love & Summer
In the back of your gaze
The memories of the past life
I was surprised as if I was thinking
What should I do more?
This is the first time I've had this
experience
Before my eyes
You're the only one I want
My heart is beating fast
If my cheeks are red, I'll probably fall
in love
It's a sign of unrequited love
Yes!
A beautiful number
Even if it's a white horse
I can't move because I'm nervous
The smell of love is too pure
A beautiful number
Yes!
The encounter is always a coincidence
What should I talk about?
I didn't even have a place to prepare
I'm nervous
Hey!
I'm sorry
I'm nervous
Hey!
Love is a test
I'm nervous
Hey!
I'll tell you
I'm nervous
Hey!
Like a girl
I was nervous
I was embarrassed to look down
I knew it wasn't that kind of type
Why?
I realized I wasn't myself
The place where the leaves shine
It's too romantic
I've already thought about the future
Yes!
The fantasy is a party
The emotion is a party
Yes!
I want to talk, but I can't
My head won't stop
The pain is a party
Yes!
My whole body is filled with love
My hands and feet are tied
I feel like I've been thrown into
reality
What happened?
Before I saw you
But for some reason I don't remember
It was a shocking event
Like we were tied up
Beautiful number
Number
Yes!
Before I knew it
Number
I'm nervous and I can't move
I'm too pure to fall in love
Beautiful number
Number
Yes!
Meeting is always a coincidence
What should I talk about?
I didn't even have a place to prepare
Because
It's painful
My voice, my voice, my voice won't come
out
I'm staring at you
All time
Stops
Before I knew it
Number
Yes!
I'm sorry
Number
Yes!
I'm in love
Number
Yes!
I'll tell you
Number
I'm nervous now
Yes!
Suddenly you
I like you
My feelings
Yes!
My heart is trembling
Number
No.1
No.2
No.3
No.4
No.5
No.6
No.7
No.8
No.9
No.10
No.11
No.12
No.13
No.14
No.15
No.16
No.17
No.18
No.19
No.20
No.21
No.22
No.23
I told you I didn't want to
You pushed me with a tulip
You're like a robot
I'm a man, too
Yeah, I've been nervous for a while
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed
I don't want that anymore
I'm sorry for being a little reckless
It's my first time
You're coming
So I haven't been able to calm down
since morning
Even if I clean up all of a sudden
It's like there's someone else
I'm opening the door a little
I wanted you to know that it's not a
joke
I'm serious
The laundry you started to fold
I hope this time will continue
I'm wandering around
But it's a mess
Somehow I was happy
Rather than having a special date
I want to spend my daily life with you
My room that was open
It's getting cleaner
What should we do next?
From beyond the stardust
It's dyed in twilight
When will you come next time?
Because it's beautiful
Thank you for watching!
[Sakurazaka 46's 4th Live Concert]
Everyone, once again, good evening!
One, two...
We are Sakurazaka 46!
Welcome to our 4th Live!
It's started! I'm so happy!
Once again, thank you for coming today,
and thank you to everyone who's watching
the live!
Thank you!
We're watching.
We're watching!
This time, it's Ion Card with You Vol.
2,
and we're really grateful to Ion Card.
I personally use Ion Card's Sakurazaka
card a lot in my daily life.
When I use it in the store,
people always say, "Oh, it's really
cute!"
It's a card I'm proud of.
And this time,
"EON CARD WITH YOU Vol.2"
Actually, when I was in Keyakizaka 46,
I was able to hold this live.
At that time, it was only a live without
an audience.
This time, I was able to hear the
audience, the live, and everyone's
voices.
Thank you.
At that time, I was wondering when I
would be able to hear everyone's voices.
I've been doing this for a long time,
but I'm finally able to listen to it,
and I really feel that it will be
delivered so directly.
Let's enjoy it after this!
From here, Yui-chan, please!
So, once again, this time...
Thank you to everyone who came to the
venue, and thank you to everyone who
watched the live stream.
Yes, I'm sure you all had a live
performance today.
I thought it was going to be a good
start, but I was surprised to see Akiho
Kirakira.
It was really fun, but how was it for
the two MCs?
Akira-chan, how was it?
That's right.
I was so nervous that I just said it out
loud.
But when I looked at the fans, they
reacted to it.
They were like, "Oh!"
I was like, "Your voices are so
reassuring."
I'm really looking forward to the
future.
The future?
The future of everyone's live.
Everyone's future.
I'm looking forward to it.
As expected of Kira-chan, it was fun.
Thank you very much.
As expected.
Applause!
Ms. Akiho, how was it today?
Well, I was really nervous, but I saw
Kira-chan next to me, and the fans said,
"Akipo!" or "Kira-chan!"
We worked together and did our best.
That's great.
After all, the two of you are always
together, and you often talk to each
other in the dressing room, right?
That's right.
I thought you two were MCs with that
atmosphere.
The atmosphere has changed, hasn't it?
The atmosphere has changed, yes.
The atmosphere of Kira-Kira today has
changed, hasn't it?
And speaking of Akio-chan, the new song
"Numa Song"
Everyone, how was it? Akio-chan's new
song
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It was amazing
Really, we also
Just before the actual performance
I saw it for the first time two days
ago, and it was so amazing that everyone
was saying "kyaa kyaa".
It was engraved in my head.
It's a melody that stays in my head. How
was it? How long did it take to make it?
But that was two days ago.
Two days ago?
I was told to make it.
I made it in the middle of the day.
That's right.
I made it in the middle of the day while
I was taking a break.
But I told ION CARD that everyone loves
SAKURAZAKA.
So I thought I'd make it to convey my
love.
I put my heart into it.
It was really good.
Akio-chan really put all of her feelings
of gratitude towards Rion Card-san from
when she was a member of Keyakizaka.
It's amazing. I didn't think I'd be able
to see her new work at the venue.
I was really happy.
With that said, we're still going to
continue with the live.
Everyone, are you ready to shout?
Yes!
Wow!
Can you go even further?
Yes!
Okay, let's continue to have fun after
this!
I don't know what's going to happen next
Isn't it fine if it's extra now?
Even if I think about this and that
I just get more tired
Take it easy
I don't want to resist
Don't worry about it
Be swept away by your own emotions
I'm on my way
The road to my dream
Should I go my own way?
Should I just fail?
I'm still on the way
I'm on my way
I don't have to rush
I have to be motivated
I'll do what I like
Selfishly
On my way
Let's walk straight
With my own feet
Let's do what we want to do
Even if someone points fingers at me
And laughs at me
My heart is calm
If I'm having fun, it doesn't matter how
people look at me
Some days I'll be...
A star
If you get tired, you can throw it away
I'll sing my favorite song and give you
a kiss
Where are you now?
Even if you're a little bit tired
somewhere
That's fine
Where are you now?
You can't be bound by anyone
If you go far away, you won't get lost
Be happy and free
Goodbye, adults
Goodbye, don't worry
Goodbye, I want you to love me
You'll arrive before sunset, right?
No matter how far you walk
It's my life
I'm on my way
The road to my dream
Let's go there, let's go there
Let's just worry
I'm still on the way
I'm on my way
You don't have to hurry
You have to be motivated
Do what you like
Don't be selfish
On my way
Let's walk straight
Straight on my own feet
Let's do what we want to do
I don't like Jamaica's beer
I just happened to find it in the fridge
He put it in on his own
The expiration date is over
I've got all my memories
I finally got it
I've become beautiful
I can't even throw it away
If it's a love that's going to last
I can't fall in love from the beginning
I can't be a single
I'm still on my way
In the past,
What are we supposed to talk about?
The reason I left you in that chair
Is because I wanted you to be able to
walk on your own
Don't be selfish
You've probably noticed instinctively
Love is just a comic in a boat
Either way, my heart can't burn out
I can't tell you how kind you are
It's a convenient lie
It's a woman who can't be distinguished
Oh, that's enough to make me cry
I'm not going to leave you
I'm not good at forgetting
Rather than remembering
What should I do from now on?
If you talk to me nicely
I want you to give me some advice
From this room of 1LDK
He's gone
After all, it looks wide
The existence that was easy
The future is big
I want to be spoiled
Let's drink Jamaican beer
Let's drink
If it's a love that's going to exist
I won't fall in love from the beginning
There's no way I can be selfish
It's a regret
If it's now, I might still make it
If I say something
What will happen to the two of us?
How was it, everyone?
It's been a while since I've personally
performed "On My Way"
Thank you
Actually, it's been a year since the
first anniversary
That's right
We were so happy
We kept saying we wanted to do it
We finally did it
I was so nervous
I was a little nervous
But we did our best
I'm glad we were able to perform
I'm really glad
The shouts were like "Ah, ah"
That's right
When we performed, we didn't have a
voice
I was wondering what it would be like
Everyone was really good
"Ah, ah"
It was really good
I was really happy
But when I said "Yes" to my face, it was
like "Ah"
I was really happy
And here
This is ION CARD WITH YOU Vol.2
I think there were a lot of ION CARD CM
members
Is there anyone here who has any
memories of ION CARD?
In ION CARD, we shot key visuals on the
roof
We ran in the sea
We went to Kamakura
We also ran with Yumiko
That's right
We had a lot of experiences
When we shot at ION MALL
Karin-chan
She put on a hairpin and challenged
herself
That's right
It was really funny
I still remember
Karin-chan was in a hurry
During the make-up
The hairpin you often see
Normally, when you take it off
It's not like you can't see it.
I want to see the video.
I was like, "Oh, it's on!"
Everyone forgot about it.
It's a memory.
That's what happened.
Do you have any questions?
Yes.
Personally, thank you very much.
I have a lot of memories.
I'm not used to it.
We went to the local UNIVERSITY and
filmed there.
We filmed that day before it opened.
We started filming around midnight.
After that, we had another shoot.
We had free time.
We could rest or play at UNIVERSITY.
But we were so sleepy.
That's all.
It was so fun to play with everyone.
But we were so sleepy.
It was dangerous.
That's how much fun it was.
I want to come again. I'm jealous.
I wanted to see it too.
Oh, it's from Jamaica.
Welcome back.
Jamaica was so cool.
Ten-chan, you love it too, right?
It was the best.
It was so cool.
It's been a while since I saw Jamaica.
It's the first time I've seen it live.
I think so.
It's the first time I've seen it at such
a close distance.
I'm jealous.
Ten-chan was dancing in the back all the
time.
I'm jealous.
Let's do it again.
I don't know if we can do it together.
It's a bomb.
I want to do it.
I don't know, though.
And now, everyone, it's finally time for
the second half!
Are you ready to have some fun?
Let's have some fun in the second half!
Why are you doing this?
Because you don't have a point.
But you've already noticed.
No, no, no.
Even if it's someone else's fault,
There's only one thing left to do.
It's a story game.
That's the right answer.
If you choose loneliness,
No, no, no.
Nobody's fault.
Trying to change the way you live
There's no way you can do it.
The reason you run away
Before you know it, you've become an
adult.
You're always making excuses.
You want to cry, don't you?
No matter how much you hate it, you
can't scream.
Is that the only thing you can't change?
If you change again,
No, no, no.
Don't say things like that.
Even if you wash it, even if you wash
it, it won't fall.
Even so, breathe.
Believe in your strength.
No, no, no.
Nobody's fault.
No matter how deep the forest is,
A single tree gathers.
You'll know when the wind blows.
Light and shadow overlap again and
again.
It's going to be a big forest.
Don't blame yourself.
No, no, no.
Nobody's fault.
Don't hold a grudge.
No, no, no.
Don't blame others.
You, reflected in the mirror, have
changed.
You're despairing on your own.
Even if you don't have a point, notice
it.
No, no, no.
Even if it's someone else's fault,
There's only one thing left.
A history game.
If that's the case,
You'll reach it someday.
No, no, no.
Nobody's fault.
Don't blame others.
You, reflected in the mirror, have
changed.
You're despairing on your own.
Even if you don't have a point, notice
it.
No, no, no.
Don't blame others.
You, reflected in the mirror, have
changed.
You're despairing on your own.
Yeah.
Oh.
Even if you change a little,
Even if you notice and skip,
Even if you remember and laugh,
Because,
Even if you make a mistake for the first
time,
Even if you forget the past,
Even if you lose your heart,
No matter what you say,
I don't care at all.
I'll give it back to you with a smile.
I can't be happy.
Why?
I've never been in love.
Until now,
I've been crying all the time.
Because,
Every time,
"I love you."
It's like a cat with a collar.
But,
I found out when I fell in love.
What do people live for?
Meet each other, love each other.
It's impossible.
I don't want to be myself.
I want to find the real me.
I say it in front of people.
I show my phone picture.
I talk in the car.
I curse such a fool.
But I remember that it's fun.
I do the same thing.
Christmas is coming soon.
Valentine's Day is coming.
What's your birthday?
Happiness is the most important thing.
Yes,
I was afraid of falling in love.
I don't want to be myself.
Because,
Love story at this age.
It's not love like a drama.
I should have noticed it earlier.
Love should be the main character.
I'm excited.
I'm nervous.
People who are lost.
Confess your love right away.
Like the audience watching you.
Meet each other, love each other.
Let's kiss.
I want to find happiness.
Why?
I was afraid of falling in love.
I've been afraid of it all this time.
Because,
Love story at this age.
It's not love like a drama.
I should have noticed it earlier.
Love should be the main character.
I'm excited.
I'm nervous.
Why do people live?
Meet each other, love each other.
I'm not myself.
I want to find the real me.
"Love Story at This Age"
A pitch-black one-off
Half-funny
I'm a heavy guitarist
What do you think?
What should I do?
I'm on the rise
It's not easy
Even if I'm just walking normally
I can't stop my breath
Even if I'm just listening quietly
I'm still a child
Who?
For what?
I don't know
Beats me
I'm on the rise
Tonight, I'll hide my face with my head
Rich Party
I won't be a shadow
I'll be a good girl
Hey, if I do this
No one will leave the house
Let's talk
Let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
It's not a joke
It's just a flow
It has nothing to do with that
Baby, what did you say?
I'm in trouble
I'm the only man here
He's the one who did it
I'm checking every hour
You're lying, right?
I'm sorry
I'm apologizing to you
Hey, hey, hey
Put me in that box
Hey, the one who left was a bag
The one who was here a while ago
You're lying, right?
Why didn't you stop?
It's a draw
I don't care if it's to protect myself
Tomorrow is tomorrow
With someone else
Endless Party
If a miraculous trial opens
I'll crush it
Ayay
It's a draw
You're the only one I can't stop
Let's believe
Let's trust each other
If we don't trust each other, the world
will end
Yeah
Where did the ball come from?
I threw it while I didn't know
Rare Edition
Cross Day, Babe
I didn't feel the pain
Waiter Stick
Let me say what I want to say
Yeah
In a place where I can walk
Everytime, I'm searching
You're a party, party
(You're a party, party)
With just one rule
I won't say anything about others
Everyone, everyone
Only about themselves
It's a draw
(It's a draw)
That's right, it's a draw
That's right, everyone
Is it really just you who talked to
someone else?
Yeah
Tonight, I'll hide my face that I don't
know
It's a party
(It's a party)
I won't be a target
I'll be a good girl
Hey
If I do something like this
No one, no one
Can get out of the game
(Can't get out of the game)
Let's talk to each other
Let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah
A flowing ball that can't fly
It's not outside the window
Even in the city at the end of the night
I can't hear the bell
(It's a draw)
(everyone, everyone)
(everyone)
(Aoi-chan, Hikaru-chan)
(Min-chan, Kise-chan, Shima, Kira-chan)
(Kira-chan, Kira-chan, Kira-chan)
Everyone, are you having fun?
Yeah
Wow, I can feel everyone's enthusiasm
from the audience.
Thank you so much!
Now, I'd like to hear Yonkard-san's
stories.
Yui-san, do you have any?
Thankfully, Yonkard-san's commercials
are available from the beginning to the
end.
Even after the show started, we were
able to watch the commercials from the
beginning to the end.
At first, it was like a story.
There were a lot of things that
overlapped with us.
While we were worried, we supported each
other and looked forward.
When the second generation came in, we
were able to do our part.
There were a lot of things like that.
We've been through a lot with Yonkard-
san.
I think it's a commercial where you can
really feel what it's like to be an
idol.
There were a lot of things that really
fit that time.
When I was watching it, I felt that
Kamakura was very natural.
We were able to see the other members.
And Hikaru-chan, how was it?
Hikaru-chan, from the start...
Yes, after I joined, I was Yui-san's
junior.
There was a CM that left a great
impression on me.
It was a tie-up between "Kimi to Boku to
Sentakumono" and "Skip Shite Yume Haato
Suru".
Do you know CM?
Do you know?
The set is all pink
Until now it was black
At first it was cool
Yes
But I was able to do it in a pink
outfit, so I remember it a lot.
Also, did you know about "Nanto"?
What is it?
"Nanto" is a commercial that Tamura
Hono-san was born in.
You've done it many times, haven't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
It was full of "Nan to"s, so it was fun
to shoot, and I have a lot of memories,
but the next song will be the last.
Thank you.
It's been a while since I've performed
that song, which was also used in the
commercial for Ion Card.
Please listen to it.
I'm not bored.
I realized for the first time that I
don't need words.
If I start to talk about love even a
little bit,
the serious feelings of "I love you"
will leak from my heart.
I don't want to feel each other anymore
so that the unknown passion will run
away.
I don't want to be objective anymore.
What is important to me?
No matter how many times I think about
it, I can't figure it out.
I love you without any reason.
Even if one of us disappears from sight
here,
I can imagine what kind of action it
will take.
I wonder how many hours I'll be waiting
for you on the street.
I'll be back for sure.
There's no other place like this in the
world.
We're crushing the miracle we've been
looking for.
We'll never let go of our eternal love.
The secret truth.
A dangerous relationship.
It's a waste of time.
Even if I want to put something in my
mouth,
I can't figure it out.
Rather than trying to tell someone
something,
it's better to stay silent.
There's a shining star in the universe
in the night sky.
I want you to call that light.
Even if you approach me passionately,
I don't know what to do.
You don't have to let go.
Until the day you understand me.
Even if you don't speak,
I can feel it all.
Words get in the way.
At the end of a conversation,
lovers always just look at each other.
Silence is beautiful.
In a world where sound has disappeared,
the pulse of love continues to beat.
My heart beats.
I'm sure I'll sing.
If you start talking about love,
the serious feeling of "I love you"
will leak from your heart.
So that the unknown passion will run
away,
the flow will be different.
It's because you become objective and
look at things.
Why is what's important important?
No matter how much I think about it,
I love you for no reason.
Thank you for coming today.
And thank you for watching the live
broadcast.
Today, I received the power from
everyone directly.
I will continue to aim for that power in
my heart.
That's all.
We are SAKURAZUKO 4D6.
Thank you very much.
KOTIJI! KOTIJI! KOTIJI!
SAKURAZAKA! KOTIJI! SAKURAZAKA! KOTIJI!
SAKURAZAKA! KOTIJI!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming.
It's been a while since I've heard
"Sakurazaka" for the first time.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've been
able to hear everyone's voices in
person, and I was really happy.
It's been a long time since I've felt
like, "Oh, this is a live performance."
I was really happy.
That's right, it's been a while, so
thank you very much.
How was it for you, Rena-chan?
Today, I really...
Thank you very much.
It was my first time to sing in a group
for the first time in a long time, so I
was really happy.
My heart was pounding.
I'm glad.
I was happy. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
She is the center of the 5th single
"Sakurazuki".
I'd like to hear what you think about
being the center of the 5th single
"Sakurazuki".
It was my first time at the center, so I
was really nervous.
But the BUDDIES, the staff, and the
members,
I can feel that they are supporting me
every day.
Thank you so much.
"Sakurazuki" is a song about a breakup.
I'm sure you've all heard it.
It's about how sad it is and how the
protagonist feels.
So, everyone...
I would like you to listen to this song
thinking of your loved ones.
Thank you.
So, the next song is the last one.
Please listen to it.
"Sakurazuki"
I've never liked anyone this much
before.
That's how I feel.
I don't want to hurt you more than I
want to hurt myself.
I've been thinking about it.
While waiting for the last place,
I wonder how many times that timing has
happened.
I haven't felt lonely for a long time.
Even though we were facing each other.
If anything, it doesn't mean anything.
Ah, how many days until graduation?
What will change from that day?
Just because the place I'm going to is
changing,
Just because I have more new friends,
I'm still left with something important.
I'm still being called an adult.
The cherry blossoms that think of you
are blown by the wind.
They flutter up in my heart.
At least stay a little longer.
No matter how beautiful it is,
the season will pass.
In a blink of an eye, everything will
fall apart.
That day was the cherry blossom season.
Tu ru ru tu ru, tu ru ru ru, tu ru ru ru
ru.
The reason I'm talking about my dreams
here
is because I feel like I'm going to say
other words.
I want to be a ball.
I want to be the only one who can be
comfortable.
I can't do that.
I want to go to Tokyo.
I want to push your back.
I always think of you.
I'm glad I met you.
Sweet and sour youth.
What am I trying to look cool about?
I'm tired of being alone.
At least that's what I thought of you.
It was such a beautiful love.
It's okay to be weak alone.
I want to praise you for what you've
given me.
I wish there were no flowers that keep
blooming forever.
If I can't stay like this,
how can I make it beautiful?
That's what I thought.
Fly up in the sky.
So that I can remember it over and over
again.
I want to protect you.
Go down slowly.
So that you don't notice me softly.
I close my eyelids.
I'm going to cross your bottom.
I'm going to pierce your ears.
I tried to leave it in my memory.
Beyond the dark night sky.
I can still see the cherry blossoms in
full bloom.
I loved that flower.
It's a person.
I want to be an adult and have dreams
and ideals.
Even if I can't do what I want to do.
If only I could make such a beautiful
scatter.
The cherry blossoms that think of you.
I'm blown by the wind.
I'm flying up in my heart.
At least, I want you to welcome me a
little.
No matter how much I like you.
The season has passed.
It's going to fall in a blink of an eye.
Don't cry.
Cherry blossoms.
Thank you all so much for coming to the
venue today,
And thank you for watching the live
stream.
I was really happy to hear everyone's
voices, and I was really empowered.
And SAKURAZAKA46 has decided to tour in
spring.
I will continue to work hard to level up
and continue to grow until the day we
meet again.
Please continue to support SAKURAZAKA46.
This was SAKURAZAKA46.
Thank you very much.