AISubs v3.2
This is the script for Sakuramiizu's collaboration skit.
Oh, it's Lover Girl.
This program is a collaborative skit between the
members of Sakurazaka46 and the entertainer.
It's an experimental variety show that challenges
various projects.
I'm going to talk a lot this time, so I'm going to do
my best to memorize it.
Kira Matsumoto
Lover Girl
This time, Kanta is going to challenge a mobile phone shop.
He's good at responding to customers who come to repair
their phones.
Matsumoto is going to play a new employee.
Pay attention to how he treats customers seriously.
It's my first time doing it alone, so I'm nervous.
I'm not trying to get out of the way, but I'm trying to
be nice to customers.
Connect it to the smartphone episode talk.
This is the ad-lib part.
It says two episodes.
I prepared a short one and a long one.
That's amazing.
First, a long one.
If it goes well, the shop will come out.
If it doesn't go well, I'll do it again.
I'll do my best to get you out.
The ad-lib part starts now.
Kira Matsumoto
Lover Girl
I'll be in charge of the customer service from today,
so do your best.
Yes, I'm nervous, but I'll do my best.
Then I'll work behind the scenes, so if you have
anything, call me directly in a loud voice, or use that
line to call me in a loud voice.
Yes, I understand.
Welcome. How about the latest smartphone?
Today, all colors are sold out.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
I dropped my smartphone and the screen was cracked.
Are you the woman who called me at noon?
No, I'm not.
I think you can tell by my appearance.
What's the matter today?
Are you going to say it again?
I dropped my smartphone and the screen was cracked.
So I was wondering if I could fix it or exchange it.
I see. You want to fix it and then exchange it for a new one.
No, I didn't say that.
It's a double-dealing.
Either way is fine.
I see.
Then, please come here.
What's the matter today?
Are you going to say it again?
It's the third time.
You wrote something, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I dropped my smartphone and the screen was cracked.
No, I didn't say that.
If the screen was cracked, I would go to the hospital.
The screen was cracked.
Oh, the screen.
Then I'll borrow your smartphone.
It's not a screen car.
I'll unlock it.
Oh, it's moving.
How did you unlock it?
I don't think you can see my face.
I'm a master key.
I can unlock any smartphone.
I'm a master face.
Can you do that?
If I practice, anyone can do it.
No, anyone can do it.
I'll check the lens.
Is it a camera?
Why are you taking a selfie?
The lens is broken.
But I'm cute in the picture.
How long does it take to repair it?
I don't know.
Can I call the person in charge?
Excuse me! Please help me!
Your voice is too loud!
You'll break her ears!
Ouch!
You're breaking her ears!
Did something happen?
She wants to know how long it'll take to fix it.
It'll take about 10 days to fix it.
That's a long time.
Don't worry.
If it's only 10 days, no one will contact us.
That's rude.
Who would come if it's only 10 days?
That's right.
It looks like you have a lot of friends who can get
coupons on LINE.
That's rude.
I do, but...
It's okay. Let's change the model.
Do you have a model you want?
I'd like this one.
The same as this one?
How about this one?
Then, this one.
That's not good.
I want a new one. It's broken.
Okay.
I'll go check the inventory.
While you wait, let's talk about your phone.
I don't need it.
I understand.
Why do you take it?
It's okay. I'll wait quietly.
When I was on the phone with my friend the other day,
I had 1% battery left.
I wanted to charge it until the battery ran out.
But the remaining 1% was too long.
I thought the battery would run out, so I turned it off.
What are you doing?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's connected perfectly.
How is it?
It's amazing.
I'm so excited.
It was fun.
I was surprised.
Are you transferring the data?
Yes, please.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Thank you for waiting.
Wow!
Did you transfer the data?
Yes, I did.
Here, the fee is 90,000 yen.
Would you like to pay it 24 times?
Oh, no problem.
If you do so, the monthly payment will be 2,160,000 yen.
That's expensive.
What's going on?
Hey, I have to split it.
Split?
Yes, I have to split it 24 times.
Can I split it?
Of course.
I'm sorry. I'm a newbie.
That's terrible.
Then, I'll split this smartphone 24 times.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
That's not what I meant. Stop it!
It was very easy to split.
When I saw the script, I thought it was perfect.
Wow!
She's the usual Kira-chan.
That's right.
She's a little crazy.
Her face was split into pieces.
I didn't say that.
That's terrible.
If her face was split, I would go to the hospital.
I'm sorry!
Please support me!
She has a loud voice.
I practiced it once.
I told her to do it a little more.
She fixed it in one go.
I think it's a great ability.
And the ad-lib was really good.
Really?
I was preparing for the ad-lib.
It was funny.
So, I felt like I didn't have enough ad-lib.
I felt like I was in trouble.
The remaining 1% ad-lib was too long.
So, I turned off the power on my own.
What are you doing?
What?
Is there anything you're careful about when you do the ad-lib?
I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm trying to make it easier for them to say.
That's what I'm thinking.
It's real, isn't it?
It's a real conversation.
You don't have much time.
Do you sometimes bite?
Do you sometimes lick?
It's important to keep saying,
I didn't bite.
It's important.
Don't bite.
I'll write it down.
That's right.
If it's not funny, there's no on-air.
Tick-tock Doma Championship
Let's take a TikTok video!
You're Suzuki, right?
Yes, I am.
Who are you?
I'm just good at guessing things like that.
That's amazing.
Speaking of today's guest, Lover Girl,
this short story is very popular on TikTok.
The four members will take on three short stories
and try to film them.
The best one will get a reward.
The first topic is recording.
What will the four of them do?
Takemoto-san, if you're ready,
please start filming.
Thank you.
I'm ready, so just press the button.
Is that okay?
Thank you.
Why do I have to film?
It's like you're being judged by the teacher.
Thank you very much.
Didn't you film me earlier?
No, I'm recording.
I'm scared!
I'll never be asked to record again.
That was very clear.
Please give me the lipstick.
It's hard to apply.
Wow!
That's all for the first topic video.
So, we have an announcement for the four of you.
There is a video that is not on-air.
Among the four, the one that wasn't the most
interesting is the one that is on-air.
Which one is not on-air?
Takemoto-san.
Wait a minute, Ia-chan.
I think we should really stop with this system.
I'm shocked.
I'm the one who made a comment on the video.
The tension of the comment was really good.
So, it's all thanks to Takemoto-san.
No, no, no.
I'm teaching him.
If this video is on-air, it's going to be a mess.
The second topic is the dressing room.
What is being on-air?
May I come in?
Yes.
Good morning.
I'm Takemoto Yui from Sakurazaka46.
Nice to meet you.
This is a gift for you.
Would you like to eat this?
This is a snack.
Thank you.
Please eat it.
Nice to meet you.
Santa style.
That's good.
Good morning.
You're wearing it.
Thank you.
If you don't mind, I'd like to give you this.
It's my belly button.
That's funny.
You're wearing it.
Long time no see.
Welcome.
Come in.
Sit down.
I'm not going to sit down.
There's a lot of stuff here.
So who's the loser?
It's Onuma-san.
Takemoto-san and Santa-san.
But it was good.
Do you usually think of Santa-san's settings?
I don't think so.
Isn't it pretty amazing?
No, it was amazing.
The last topic is the TV station.
Who will be on air?
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm Inoe Rina from Sakura Meets.
I can't let you pass.
I'm Inoe Rina from Seed&Flower.
Can you give me a catchphrase?
Catchphrase?
Yes.
I'm Inoe Rina, the miracle woman that Hyogo gave birth to.
Inoue-san, that's not it.
I'm Inoe Rina, who has more neck bones than anyone else.
I can't let you pass.
Catchphrase?
Inoue Appa.
I'm Inoe Rina.
Yes, that's it.
Why are you passing it?
I'm passing it with a catchphrase.
Nuhina Kurumi-san, the life of corn.
She's coming.
Thank you for your hard work.
How many floors is it?
It's the third floor.
Have you ever been on an elevator three times?
Isn't it the floor where you get off?
That's amazing.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I dropped my striped handkerchief.
I dropped it.
I'm glad.
I took it.
Thank you very much.
Take a picture and bring it to me.
The last topic.
The loser is...
Inoue-san.
Why?
Ms. Omishi, what do you think of today's overall ranking?
Everyone has a chance.
Who was the best person today?
Takeboto-san.
There was a good one.
There was a bad one.
But I felt that I could make the most interesting one.
I'm glad.
Takeboto wrote the sweets as a reward.
But...
The loser will be punished by Masumoto.
This time, I'm going to get a wrist bandage.
I don't want it.
I'm going to get a bandage on my chin.
Three times.
But this is also from among the four of us.
Takeboto wrote the sweets as a reward.
That's not true.
Who will be punished?
Inoue-san.
Why?
Just before the game started,
Takemoto got a reward,
but Takemoto also has a chance to get a penalty.
He said something mean, so I put it on him.
Thank you very much.
Penalty push-ups 3 times, please.
1, 2, 3.
It's all on you.
No, it's not. Look at me.
Look at me carefully.
It's not on you now.
It's on you.
Next time, Onuma Akiho meets The Mummy.
In Onawa-Yamanote Line Game, Masumoto's lack of
exercise is discovered.
And Sakura Meets Official TikTok will be introduced.
In addition to the video that was aired today,
the three works that were rejected will be released
after the air.
In addition, we will also post collaboration videos on
the program and Lover Girl's account, so please check
them out.
Excuse me. Please cheer for us.
It's all on you.