AISubs v3.2
Next is the script for the collaboration with Sakura Meets.
This is the first time I've received a script from a member.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yamasaki Ten-chan, a member of Sakura Meets.
I'm Yamasaki Ten-chan.
I didn't expect to receive a script from a member.
I'm the president of Japan.
It's amazing.
I'm glad you came.
Don't shoot me with one hand.
We're doing it together.
This program is a collaborative program between the
members of Sakura Saka 4D6 and the comedian.
I'm going to hide my memories.
It is an experimental variety show where you can play
games together.
I've seen the script.
The amount of lines is really a lot.
I'll read this tomorrow.
I can't believe it.
Let me read it, too.
I haven't read it yet.
It's really amazing.
It's rare.
I haven't read it yet.
Can you watch it on air?
I'll watch it.
You're reading it.
It's amazing, but I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good luck.
I got the script from the members.
Look forward to the next time.
I'll do my best.
Don't shoot me with one hand.
We're doing it together.
After the commercial, the rehearsal and the actual performance.
Takemoto Yui
The president of Japan
Self PR
First, please.
This time, he's going to try the situation of the final
interview for his job.
The point is the strange appeal of the interviewee.
Takemoto is going to try the same job as Ketsu.
Will he be able to show the tension and strange appeal
of the final interview?
It's okay if we do it together.
Don't you need to be a little relaxed?
I'll look at you and say,
You're a bad guy.
I think this is going to be hard.
It's perfect for me.
I'm in my fourth year of college, and I'm in the middle of it.
The role and the content were perfect.
I was so happy.
It's your first year.
It's the age when you can get into it.
It's the most realistic time.
I think it's about me.
Can I read it a little?
I've been interested in environmental protection since
I was in high school.
I'm actively participating in the clean-up activities
in the area.
I was involved.
I don't know if the president of Japan knows me.
It's a perfect line.
I don't have to do it now.
It's a little unusual.
Thank you.
Yui Takemoto
Three
President of Japan
Start of the show
Come in.
Excuse me.
I'm Daichi Nishihara from Yoshimoto University. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yui Takemoto from Sakurazaka University. Nice to meet you.
I'm Tsuji from HR. Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
This is the last interview.
How do you feel? Are you nervous?
Yes. To be honest, I'm nervous, but I've come this far,
so I want to appeal to myself.
I'm nervous too, but I have no regrets no matter what
the result of this interview is. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I think you did the first and second interviews, but
let's start with self-promotion. Mr. Nishihara, please.
I started playing soccer from the third year of
elementary school to the time I graduated from high
school.
There, I learned about teamwork and the relationship
between the top players, and I also came up with ideas
to win the game.
Mayonnaise is made at your company, right?
Yes.
I think there is a way to squeeze out the mayonnaise.
Yes, there is.
Yes, there is. That's how I squeezed out the ideas.
I see.
Also, at the university's school festival, I was
elected as the executive director.
However, the management of the first school festival
was not easy at all, and I had a hard time securing
personnel, collaborating with the university side, and
squeezing out the budget.
Mayonnaise produced by Onsha.
You have it, right?
Yes.
I think that mayonnaise also has to be squeezed out.
When you use it, use it, and when there is only a
little left at the end,
I think that you have to squeeze it out.
I have it.
You have it, right?
Yes.
That's right.
That's how much I squeezed out the budget.
I see. Thank you.
Also, last year, I experienced an overseas study
abroad, and I was able to squeeze out my new potential.
Squeezing out means using the mayonnaise produced by
Onsha, use it, use it, and at the end,
Did you get this one?
What?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze it out.
Thank you.
Next, Ms. Takemoto, please.
I have been interested in environmental protection
since I was a high school student, and I am actively
participating in the cleaning activities in the area.
However, at that time, I was not good at getting
involved with people, and I was hesitating to
participate all the time, but I wanted to change
myself.
That's how I got the courage to participate.
Mayonnaise produced by Onsha.
You have it, right?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze that
mayonnaise out.
Use it, use it, and when there is only a little left...
You too?
What does this mean?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze it out.
Yes, there are.
That's how I got the courage to squeeze it out.
I see.
I have been working part-time as a teacher since I
entered university.
I teach students the importance of squeezing out
answers without throwing out difficult questions.
Mayonnaise produced by Onsha.
You have it, right?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze that
mayonnaise out.
Use it, use it, and when there is only a little left...
What does this mean?
You too?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze it out.
What does this mean?
Yes, there are.
That's how I got the courage to squeeze it out.
What does this mean?
Recently, I have been interested in anti-aging.
I try to eat a balanced diet.
I jog every morning to squeeze out sweat.
Squeeze out means making mayonnaise until the end.
What is this?
Is this popular?
What does this mean?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze it out.
That's how I got the courage to squeeze out sweat.
Thank you.
Did you both do this?
From the first interview?
With this one?
If you say one, I think you can count mayonnaise as one or two.
Use it, use it, and at the end...
Don't use one.
You are doing it together.
What does this mean?
What is this?
You look like you are dreaming.
You are too desperate.
You won't do it until you stand up, right?
You are hurting your hand.
Are you okay?
I think there are times when you have to squeeze out sweat.
You are out of breath.
Are you okay?
I understand.
Please tell us your strengths.
Let's start with Nishihara-san.
My strength is that I don't give up until the end.
That's why.
You decided to go with this today.
No matter how hard the practice is, I squeeze out my voice.
Squeezing out means using mayonnaise until the end.
You are being filmed.
Are you okay?
You look really bad.
What is this?
Takemoto-san, please.
My strength is that I am cooperative.
I have been cooperating with my friends.
I have been cooperating with people of different age groups.
That's your strength.
Why do you say that?
I squeeze out my experience.
I squeeze out my mayonnaise until the end.
What is this?
You are being filmed.
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
This is the last interview.
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
This is not a jutsu.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
It's too easy for both of you to get caught, isn't it?
It's like...
Defense.
You're not good at defense.
That's enough.
Sit down.
Excuse me.
What's wrong with you guys?
Seriously.
What's going on?
I'll ask you one last time.
I ask you every year.
Please imagine.
There is a fried potato in front of you.
What do you eat it with?
Yes, Ms. Nishihara, please.
Yes.
Mayonnaise.
Thank you.
Ms. Takemoto, please.
Tonkatsu sauce.
Why?
Was it next to the tonkatsu?
It was perfect.
Really?
I'm glad.
There was an ad-lib at the end, wasn't there?
Yes.
Other than that, it was perfect.
That's true.
It was great.
Especially in the second half.
Yes.
I'll look at it from the front.
You were so confident.
I'll definitely take it back.
It wasn't just an ad-lib, was it?
No, it wasn't.
It was like, I'm going to lose.
I was being pushed.
I was going to stop you a little later, but I saw it.
Really?
I'm going to win.
What are you doing?
You took it too easily, didn't you?
It's like a defense.
You're both weak at defense.
I could see the back of the story.
It looks like the first meeting in the interview, but
it's actually a long-standing rival.
I could even see the background.
It's like, actually, somewhere.
It says the last mayonnaise battle.
Mayonnaise battle.
I could see that it wasn't the first time they met.
You were faking it, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
I thought you were a professional.
Do you have any improvements or advice?
I'm sorry to say this, but I laughed at the last tonkatsu sauce.
I'm sorry, too.
We laughed together.
That's right.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
Takemoto, please.
It's tonkatsu sauce.
Why?
You laughed at the end.
I was so happy.
I laughed at the beginning.
I'm really happy at the end.
I wanted to say it with my face.
I want to say it in front of people.
Tanaka.
Taxi.
You're in my way.
And the unreleased games that couldn't be broadcast.
And the new project has been announced.
What are you doing?