AISubs v3.2
This program is brought to you by SAKURAMINTSU.
I received a collaboration book with SAKURAMINTSU.
Thank you very much.
This is a limited edition.
In this program, members of SAKURAZAKA46 collaborate
with entertainers.
This is an experimental variety show where they play
games together.
This time, Kira-chan has no lines at all.
Again?
This is the first time I've done a content without lines.
I have to convey everything with my movements.
I think it's important to do it in an exaggerated way.
I will do my best.
Good luck.
This is a commercial, so it's a rehearsal and a live performance.
Oh My Aya's Oh My Girl.
This time, Kanta is going to challenge a radio broadcast.
Masumoto is acting as a passionate fan like Nakano.
The movement and facial expression without lines are
very important.
From the moment I came.
Passionate feeling.
How much do you like it?
Look at it and recognize it.
Can you show it?
Murazaka 46. Start. Over.
I said, Yeah!
I also played the air guitar.
I was excited.
I use T-shirts in various contents.
I found a new T-shirt when I went to Harajuku with my wife.
This is...
I thought this would look good on me.
Really?
I decided to look at Masumoto's photos.
Kira Masumoto.
T-shirt.
Kaerutei.
Start.
Hello, everyone. I'm Ohmae Aya from Ohmae Aya, and I'm
broadcasting on FM 806 at 3 p.m. on Thursday, July 6th.
I'm Ohmae Aya, a radio personality. Today is the first
public live broadcast in commemoration of the 1st
anniversary of the start of the broadcast.
Thank you all for coming. Thank you. Some people are
sending me a wonderful message.
Thank you very much. Is it a handwritten message?
Congratulations to cute Aya-chan. Oh, you're sending me
a handwritten message again.
It's big. Thank you very much. It took a long time,
didn't it? I'm so happy.
The kids are coming to play, too. Thank you. Have fun
on your way home.
Now, let's get to the corner. Aoya's big incident. Oh my god.
I, Ohmae Aya, don't think about this corner. I'm sorry
for the incident that I said, Oh my god.
We're sending you an original sticker for those who were hired.
This is the sticker. This is the sticker. Oh, there are
already people who have it.
Thank you very much. I have a lot of them. Thank you very much.
Now, here's the first message.
Mr. Iguana. I went to a popular beauty salon in
preparation for the public live broadcast.
When I asked him to make it light and summer-like, the
side room was gone. No matter how much I drink, it's
too light.
I'm afraid I'm going to fly into the sky.
I'm afraid I'm going to fly. This is...
Oh my god.
I think that hairstyle really suits you.
Next letter.
Radio name Aya-chan Daisuki Kenta-kun.
I'm a first year elementary school student.
The other day, I was going to help my mom, so I washed
the dishes and broke them.
But my mom laughed and forgave me.
I want to do my best next time.
This is...
Oh my god.
You're so cute.
Next is the last letter.
Radio name Mitsuboshi Hamburger-san.
The other day, when I was on the train, I changed my
sweat, so when I wiped my sweat with a handkerchief,
I saw a cold gaze.
What I had in my hand was not a handkerchief, but my
father's trunks.
This is...
Oh my god.
This is embarrassing.
Was it the same design as my father's handkerchief?
This is Mitsuboshi Hamburger-san.
Congratulations.
This is the 10th time you've been hired.
You've been hired 10 times.
I'm going to make a live call and thank you in person.
Hello.
Hello?
I'm the father of Mitsuboshi Hamburger.
Oh, it's you, father!
Yes, she was so excited to go to Aya-chan's house that
she forgot her cell phone.
Oh, is that so?
And then she called Aya-chan.
She loves Aya-chan so much that she's waiting for her cell phone.
Oh, is that so, father? I'm so happy.
Then, father, can you say, Oh my god?
Here we go.
One, two...
Oh my god!
Thank you very much.
You were a very energetic father.
Please don't be too disappointed, Mitsuboshi Hamburger.
I'd like you to listen to a song here.
Today, I'd like to answer a request song from
Mitsuboshi Hamburger.
Please listen to this and get excited.
Sakurazaka46, start over.
Mitsuboshi Hamburger
It's certain that you know
You're just giving up before you know
So I wanted to tell you
Please, wait a little longer
Want me clap, and you're not gonna move
Talk to who?
Then our bonds will disappear
The song you just heard was Sakurazaka46's Start Over.
How was the first public live broadcast?
I'm looking forward to the day I can meet you again.
This is Aya Ohmai. See you next week.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'm not supposed to talk to you.
This story is just a story that I want to enjoy on the stage.
It's a story that I want to laugh when I want to laugh.
I laughed with Masumoto-san's movement.
Thank you very much.
It was perfect.
I'm glad.
What's wrong with me?
I was really scared.
What happened?
I don't think it's meaningful.
I was surprised.
It's like listening to music.
It's meaningless.
I suddenly lost my emotions.
What's wrong with me?
Your facial expressions are perfect.
Do you usually practice by looking in the mirror?
I take a lot of videos.
It's amazing.
I do research on my face.
But there are some characters that I can't do.
What do you mean?
I can't do it at all.
I can't do it.
I want to see it.
I'm in trouble if I sleep in the store.
Can you wake me up?
I want to sleep in the store.
You are like an old man who scolds his grandchild.
I see.
After the commercial, there are a lot of questions in
the drawing quiz.
Bringing in the dressing room game!
It's a game where comedians play in the dressing room together.
What did Kaeru-tei bring in?
Drawing quiz, What are you doing?
My partner Nakano-kun is good at drawing.
This is the only drawing he is good at.
There are a lot more.
He is the only one who is good at drawing.
There is a topic.
For example, like a dog that is relaxing,
there is a topic that is divided into movement and living things.
The questioner draws a picture of the topic, and the
five people who answer it look at the picture and guess
the topic.
If you can answer 6 questions in 3 minutes, you will
get a delicious cream puff as a reward.
Game start!
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
There is no time.
What is it?
Dance?
Macho?
Dancing gorilla?
Correct!
Dancing gorilla!
It's a good pace.
Do your best!
Oh no!
What is it?
Is it a kappa?
It's like a punishment game in the stomach of a kappa.
What is that arrow?
This is it.
A kappa is doing push-ups.
Please do your best.
I have to get it back.
I see.
It's fast.
What is it?
Hurry up!
Do your best!
There is a lot of time left.
A bear?
What is it?
A bear is riding a bicycle.
Is it a scooter?
Correct!
It's a bear riding a bicycle.
Do your best!
What is it?
Is it a monkey?
Is it a koala?
It's a monkey.
What is it?
Is it a surprise monkey?
I don't know the character.
It's like this.
What does it say?
It's a chimpanzee.
It's a teacher.
What does it say?
It's a job.
It's a hot spring.
It's a drunk person.
There is no time left.
Do your best!
What is it?
It's a horse.
It's crying.
It's a horse crying.
Is it a horse being arrested?
No.
Is it a ribbon?
It's moving.
No.
What is it?
It's a horse.
Is it a horse?
It's a horse crying.
What is it?
It's a horse and a human.
Is it a centaur?
It's a centaur crying.
Is it a centaur crying?
Is it moving?
It's a centaur proposing.
It's a centaur with its hands entangled.
Is it a centaur with its fingers injured?
It's a ribbon.
Something is coming out.
It's a cell phone.
Is it a cell phone?
It's being arrested.
Something is coming out.
What is it?
Its arm is being tied.
It's a pin.
I want to turn it around.
What is it?
It's a horse touching a remote control.
It has a lot of arms.
Is it a game?
It's a game.
What is it?
It's a centaur with a stomachache.
It's difficult.
It's a stomachache.
I didn't draw it.
I'm sorry.
Since it's a big deal,
Nakano drew a centaur with a stomachache.
It's amazing.
This is it, Yui-chan.
I want a T-shirt with a centaur hiding in it.
It's an Ametalk simulation.
Next time, it's Sakuramitsu's secret Ametalk.
I'm a member of Sakurazaka46.
We present Sakurazaka46 with all our might.
I'm the type to express a lot in a live performance.
That's cool.
Really?
And there's a special guest.
She's challenging herself to a long jump.
And Terasa is doing a limited edition of the original content.
It's a gold bell.