Waku! Waku! Waku! Waku! Waku! Waku!
Oh, Oh...
Waku!
♪ "Kimi no Koi" by Hatsune Miku ♪ "Kimi
no Koi" by Hatsune Miku
♪ The whole image was blurred
♪ Little by little
♪ Why is it that when I'm with you
♪ It's so much easier
♪ I didn't think about love
♪ Now I can see it clearly
♪ Is it necessary to have confidence?
♪ I've heard it over and over
♪ That it's just a vague thing
♪ Hey, really
♪ I already know
♪ Confidently
♪ I love you
♪ "Kimi no Koi" by Hatsune Miku
♪ "Snow Man" by Hatsune Miku
We've been sweating a lot since the
beginning.
It's fun, it's fun, it can't be helped!
I'm so happy!
Today, we have a live broadcast.
Everyone watching the live broadcast,
are you having fun?
Are you having fun?
Today is the last day of the 9th Single
FACTS LIVE.
I hope everyone at the venue and those
who are watching the stream
can enjoy it to the end!
Everyone, let's enjoy it to the end!
Let's enjoy it!
Thank you very much.
I've already performed 3 songs in the
opening,
and I think everyone was a little
surprised.
"Sonia" and...
It's been a while, but Miihi was able to
perform at the center!
I'm happy.
Miihi, how was it?
Yes, well...
"Sonia" was...
It's been about 2 years since my last
performance,
and I've been hearing a lot about
"Sonia" from everyone,
so I'm really happy to be able to do it
here,
and I'm also really happy to be able to
do it with these members.
The members have always said that they
want to do it together,
so I'm really happy to be able to do it
again like this.
I'm so happy!
We really didn't think that Mii-san
would be able to be in the center with
Sonia, so we were really happy.
I'm glad.
And...
We've had this backslide for three days,
and today is the third day.
There's something I've kept a secret
until today.
What is it?
I think I'll tell everyone about it.
Really?
What is it?
In the opening, I sang "Kakushinteki
Croissant"
and I played the piano there.
Oh?
The piano was played by Nagi-chan!
Thank you!
It was in the middle of a busy schedule,
but thank you so much for playing for
us.
You're welcome.
I really love Rika's songs.
It's been a while since I played the
piano in front of Buddy's.
So I was really nervous.
But when I was practicing, I was
thinking about Rika every day.
I wanted to make Rika the brightest and
brightest on stage.
I was really happy to be able to deliver
Rika's beautiful singing voice to
Buddy's with my piano.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you so much!
When I heard Nagi-chan's piano, I
thought, "Oh, Nagi-chan is playing this
for me."
But when I sang, I was so moved that I
couldn't help it.
I've always wanted to say that, so I'm
glad I could say it here today.
I was really happy to be able to tell
you about the first release and get
excited with you from the opening like
this, but I would like to get excited
with you after this, but are you ready
to enjoy it after this?
Let's get excited together after this!
[Music]
[Applause]
That's right.
Oh-oh-oh-oh
I'm afraid of changing lanes
Even the traffic lights are flashing
The night I rang the crash
My heart was being tested
Ah, I don't want to be swayed by your
whims
It's my decision whether to go straight
or turn
No matter how much the seductive
taillights glare
I just want to go at my own pace
I know who's holding the steering wheel
I'm afraid of changing lanes
I'm lost
I have to keep a distance between us
My heart is being pushed
Even if we're a little apart
Jealousy is just right
If our destination is the same
I don't have to get so close
I won't lose sight of you
Oh-oh-oh-oh
What's the basis of this self-assertive
lifestyle?
By stepping on the accelerator
I'm going to break the mountain
Ah, I'm going to destroy the graveyard
And stop the car
I can't keep chasing love anymore
If I keep chasing it
I'll end up not being myself
I'll try to warn you by passing the
light
I can't see the scenery in the distance
I just want you to look at me as you
like
If I keep a distance between us
Other cars will break in
It's not my intention
That's what love is
Yes, it's all about timing
Even if I can understand your feelings
I'll follow you, so it's up to you
How many times do I have to step on the
brakes
For my feelings to reach you?
But I wonder if you'll notice something
No matter how far apart we are
I can't help but cry
In the end, I'll just keep running
Until I realize that we're not meant to
be
If I can't keep a distance between us
My heart will stop beating
Even if we're a little apart
Jealousy is just right
If we're together at the destination
I don't have to get that close
I won't lose sight of you
That's how I felt
I couldn't live the way I wanted to
I tried my best
But my own feelings
The sweat I spit out
And the disordered breathing
And the beating of my heart
It doesn't matter
If I don't go to that place
I won't be able to realize
My passionate passion
How far can I run?
Will I be able to see the blue sea?
Will I be able to get closer to my
dream?
How far can I run?
Will I be able to become a bird?
Until the day I can admit it
I'll keep running
What kind of effort did I make?
If I don't get good results
It's no use
Even though I know it's important to
everyone
Did I forget?
The tears I shed
And the blurred red blood
And the pain in my chest
I won't tell anyone
I'll be ignored by everyone
And it'll be the end
If I compete with the worthless
Will I be able to reach the horizon?
Will that become the reality?
If I compete with the worthless
Will I be able to call you my friend?
I won't be like that
I was frustrated
I never thought I'd give up
Because I'm going to do my best
Even if I say that
I won't be evaluated
In the end, I don't have enough strength
That's how it is
How far can I run?
Will I be able to see the blue sea?
Will I be able to get closer to my
dream?
How far can I run?
Will I be able to become a bird?
Until the day I can be recognized
I'll keep running
"Basketball"
Even if I get caught up in the game
Even if I realize that I'm playing
basketball
Even if I think about it and laugh
Even if I make a mistake for the first
time
Even if my tears start to fall
I'll be in trouble
No matter what you say
I don't care at all
I'll give you a smile
I can't be happy
Why didn't I fall in love?
I've been making a fool of myself
Because I'm always
I love you
I'm a spoiled cat
But I found out when I fell in love
What do people live for?
Meeting each other, loving each other
It's impossible
It's not me
I want to find the real me
People say it in front of me
Showing me a picture on my phone
Chatting in the park
That's right
I thought I was stupid
I thought it was fun
But I was wrong
I'm sorry, Christmas
Valentine's Day
How do you feel?
Happiness is the best
That's right
I fell in love
I can't see the words
I wrote on my shoulder
Because
I don't know what this is
It's like a love story drama
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
My heart is pounding
I'm nervous
People who are lost
Confess your love right away
The audience watching you
Meeting each other, loving each other
Let's kiss
Happiness is the best
That's right
I fell in love
I can't see the words
I wrote on my shoulder
Because
I don't know what this is
It's like a love story drama
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
My heart is pounding
I'm nervous
I fell in love
I can't see the words
I wrote on my shoulder
Because
I don't know what this is
It's like a love story drama
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
[Music]
[Applause]
I feel like I'm going to cry, but I'm
sure everyone is already excited.
I'm sure there are some of you out there
who are sweating like crazy right now,
aren't there?
Thank you very much.
It's hot, so don't forget to hydrate
yourself and enjoy the concert!
The concert has started, so I'd like to
hear what you have to say.
Well then, Fuyuka-san!
I'm Fuyuka Saito.
Personally, during the MC earlier, Rika-
chan was talking about Nagi's piano.
I think Rika-chan's singing was really,
really wonderful.
Everyone, please give Rika-chan a round
of applause!
Both of you are the best!
It was perfect.
It's Rika-chan's song, but as we
rehearsed it more and more,
even though you were good from the
beginning,
you improved more and more.
I could really feel Rika-chan's effort.
Rika-chan's singing voice was so good.
Takemoto and I started dancing.
We were dancing together.
Contemporary.
Can I say contemporary?
Rina was in the video.
I want to see that.
Rika-chan's singing voice was so good.
Takemoto and I started dancing.
That was the story.
Thank you.
Thank you for the best opening.
I'm glad you danced like that.
I danced like crazy.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'd like you to watch the video later.
I didn't expect you to dance to my song.
I'm a little surprised.
I didn't expect to sing alone.
But when I thought about what I could
do, I thought I had to do my best to do
what I was given, so I did my best to
sing today.
It was cool.
Thank you.
It's me, but I want to make this concert
a fun concert, so I'd like to warm up
everyone's throats to have fun here.
Everyone, can you speak up?
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it, so I'd like
to leave it to someone else to lead from
here today.
Please.
Today...
Itoh-chan, please!
I've been asking for a lot of things for
the past three days.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
At the end, Itoha...
Wait a minute.
At the end, Itoha will say "Let's have
fun" and everyone will say "Ei! Ei! Oh!"
I'm going to ask a lot of questions from
the beginning, but I'd be happy if you
could answer in the loudest voice.
Here we go.
Who was looking forward to DOCKS LIVE?
Yeah!
Who had breakfast today?
Who had lunch?
Yeah!
Let's have fun!
Let's get excited after that!
DOCKS LIVE
At the Coin Land Reservation March
I was often pushed into a corner
The usual me-chan
Was a bit of a troublemaker
While I was looking at my smartphone
I was also standing in a line
Saying such a thing
Is so cool
In this world
In the end, it's like this
Somehow
Timing
It's not fair
One by one, you're all out
I'm just tired of living
Just look at me
Thank you for watching!
I'll just wait for you by your side
I've been waiting for my girlfriend to
call me
But why is it that this time I'm going
to be told by my grandma?
I've been here all this time
I've been here since a few hours ago
I'm going to live my life
In life, it's not like everyone will be
on your side
It's not like everyone will be on your
side
You're reading too much into it
Yeah, it's full of walls around you
Throw away the things you don't need
I don't want to hear it
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
Thank you for watching!
I don't have the kindness to wipe away
my tears
Even if I blow away the white clouds, I
don't remember crying
Woah, woah, woah, woah
In such a small space
The selfish ones are acting freely
What's still wet isn't just mine
Should I stop for today?
I'm not in a hurry
Look at me, I'm not dirty
I don't hate choices
[Music]
1,2,3
Don't touch mine
What are you laughing at?
I don't want to know
The things you have to laugh at are
different
Even if you put a lot on your back
It won't be as beautiful as you think
1,2,3
Your heart is dirty
If you use it more
You can be kind
A pure white thing
Isn't it asymmetrical?
It's too late
If you aim ahead
It's no good to get involved
Even such a lecture
I just want you
Just wait by my side
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't like Jamaica's beer
I just happened to have it in the fridge
If he does it on his own
The expiration date is still on
Memories are all garbage
I'm sure it's finally beautiful
Big tears
I can't even throw it away by myself
Ah, if it's a growing love
I don't want to fall in love from the
beginning
There's no way I can be a reliable
sponsor
If you look at it, it's still in time
Which comment is it?
What's going to happen?
[Music]
The reason I left the chair I used to
like
I left it alone so I could take it
Don't continue with your new girlfriend
I'm sure you've noticed instinctively
Love is garbage anyway
I can't think of one
My heart is in a hurry
I don't know what to do
Desperate lies
I'm a woman who can't distinguish
Ah, if it's a growing love
I don't want to fall in love from the
beginning
I'm not good at forgetting
Rather than remembering
What should I do from now on?
If you talk to me
Can you give me some advice?
[Music]
From this room of bad decay
Even if he's gone
It still looks wide
The existence that was lost is big
I want to be spoiled
La la la la la
La la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la
[Music]
Let's drink Jamaica beer
Let's drink
Ah, if it's a growing love
I don't want to fall in love from the
beginning
I'm not good at forgetting
Rather than remembering
I may still make it now
If you say something
I wonder what will happen to us
[Music]
[Applause]
Suddenly you're gone
I'm standing in the classroom
The back door of the classroom
Boldly, I go out
I couldn't see the teacher
Or did you give up?
I want to run away right now
But I didn't have the courage to do so
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on my ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
I didn't want to hear anything
I wonder if there's something I don't
want to hear
It's troublesome to grow up
Mixing various things
It's difficult to live like myself
[Music]
I wonder what I should say
I'm looking at you
I don't want to get in your way
Shall we quietly get close to each
other?
It doesn't matter if it's empty
Freedom is a piece of cake
Soon the noise around me will disappear
The wind passed by and I heard a voice
It doesn't seem to be possible
But it's okay
Then you turned to me
You smiled and said, "Did you hear
that?"
I was drowned
I lied to you
Of course, I'm upset
If I become a fool
I'll block your ears
Don't give me anything I don't want
You're crouching
I can't stay like this forever
Youth is always
Without realizing it
The wind passes by
But still
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on your ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
What did you hear?
It's not just a picture
I don't want to hear
There must be something
Becoming an adult
It's troublesome
There are many kinds of adults
Living like myself
It's difficult
The wind passes by
But still
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on your ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
What did you hear?
It's not just a picture
I don't want to hear
There must be something
Becoming an adult
It's difficult
The wind passes by
But still
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on your ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
What did you hear?
It's not just a picture
I don't want to hear
There must be something
Becoming an adult
It's difficult
The wind passes by
But still
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on your ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
What did you hear?
It's not just a picture
I don't want to hear
There must be something
Becoming an adult
It's difficult
The wind passes by
But still
The blue sky is a dazzling rooftop
You put your hand on your ear like this
As I approached
You opened your fingers
What did you hear?
It's not just a picture
I don't want to hear
There must be something
Becoming an adult
Under the armor
I had a weak heart
I thought I was a titan
I fought until now
But I can't help it, I'm crying
I was broken
Even so, we
Stand up again and again
In the world, there is only one
Who can endure weakness
There is only one person I love
Let me cry
With your hands
Hold me tight
I want to be spoiled like a mother
Somehow I'm tired
I just want you to wipe away my tears
Hold me tight
I don't need anything
For a while
Hold me tight
Warmth
I wanted to love you
The bullet of words
In the flying battleship
Flowing the red blood
Even if I fall to the ground
The faint pride
I didn't throw it away
If I can't move
I want to fall one step forward
At such a time
I suddenly thought of
That scenery of my hometown
Stay with me
Hold my hand
Tell me you're here
Such a pathetic
Useless figure
You're the only one
I can show you
The truth disappears through the tears
Translated by Releska
Please leave it to me
Please stay by my side
I don't have any regrets
I want to be spoiled like a mother
Somehow I'm tired
I just want you to wipe away my tears
Hold me tight
I don't need anything
Warmth
Hold me tight
I wanted to love you
I don't have any regrets
My body that was with you
It's getting dark
In my eyes
The most important thing in the world
Is reflected
With your hands
Hold me tight
I want to be spoiled like a mother
Somehow I'm tired
I just want you to wipe away
My tears
Hold me tight
I don't need anything
Warmth
Hold me tight
I wanted to love you
"I want to be spoiled like a mother"
The blue sky that is not one
Isn't it cruel?
If you show me something perfect
There's no place to run
Always happy days
What are you worried about?
It's enough for parents and teachers
I answered the question
But I'm not the kind of person who can
do that
I want to do what I like more
How can you forgive me?
If that's the case
I just need to be brave
A gap in my chest
Where is it coming from?
I hurt myself before I knew it
I was lonely, I was discouraged
Only the truth that came out of my mouth
Is breaking down little by little
I don't notice
With a quiet force
Pulling the bridge
A faint wind that only I can feel
When I keep looking at something
dazzling
I feel dizzy
I just need to close my eyes for a
moment
It will be easier
It's not a big deal
I wonder if I have to look at it
Even if I just pretend to be like that
I hate myself
Yes, I'm like this
I'm told that I'm different
I can't be convinced
The world still ignores me
If that's the case, never
Don't put me in the number
A gap in my chest
Why am I crying without a sound?
I hurt myself before I knew it
I don't feel
If I say I want to do something
I say I can't
I don't understand the obvious
Oh oh oh oh oh
Every time I breathe
The sound of escaping
Oh oh oh oh oh
I've been holding back
The air of hope sucked in
I can't tell anyone
I'm sure there's something in my heart
Little by little without knowing
I feel like I'm drowning in words
If that's the case, open that hole wide
Become the wind in my chest and get out
A gap in my chest
Why am I crying without a sound?
I hurt myself before I knew it
I don't understand the obvious
Oh oh oh oh oh
I've been holding back
The air of hope sucked in
I can't tell anyone
I'm sure there's something in my chest
I'm lonely and I'm out of breath
Only the truth that came out of my mouth
It's leaking little by little
Oh oh oh oh oh
The live is still going on
Are you all having fun?
Thank you
This time it's the 9th single "Back
Flive"
It was held in May
It's a different member and a different
set list, but I'd like to hear from you
about the actual performance and the
rehearsal.
Lena-chan!
This time, I performed "Don't Cut In
Line" at VAXLIVE.
There was one thing that I struggled
with.
Sakura Takahashi is quite... What was
this again?
Headset?
Headset! I think I perform with a
headset a lot.
It was the first time I used a hand mic
while dancing and singing.
It was the first time I did it while
holding a mic.
I was very nervous and I held the mic on
the right side only once during the
rehearsal.
After that, I couldn't understand
anything.
I was like, "Why is my right hand
covered?"
I had a hard time.
But today, I held the mic with my left
hand.
I was able to sing without leaving my
mouth.
I'm glad.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you.
It's refreshing to have a microphone in
Sakurazaka, isn't it?
The five of us here are members of Don't
Cut the Line.
It was difficult.
I practiced at home with a tube of face
wash.
You saw the picture, didn't you?
Onuma-san was practicing with a shocking
thing.
What is it?
My remote control.
Isn't it normal?
If you hold it too hard, the TV will
turn on.
I can't look forward to it.
What did you practice with, Marino-san?
I practiced with my hands.
I see.
You can do it with your hands.
I want to hold it with my hands.
I see.
There was a microphone exchange.
Can I buy it?
I don't think so.
I didn't have it.
Oh, really?
I'm grateful.
Then it's a very grateful song.
How about Marino, who was practicing
with her hands?
Thank you very much.
I'm glad that you are very excited
today, but today is the last day and
there is also a live broadcast, so I
have a little wet hair.
How about everyone?
Actually, this is a request from our
member, Miu Murayama.
Miu-chan, the day before yesterday and
the day before yesterday, she came to
see our live.
She sent a voice message to all of us
and gave us her thoughts.
Among them, she said, "I want to see
Twintail."
That's right.
I thought I had to answer my juniors'
requests, so I answered them.
Yeah, her hair...
Riko-chan's hair is very mature, isn't
it?
This is the hairstyle I did on the first
day.
Everyone told me it was cool.
It was a social distance, but I made it
a cool hairstyle to fit the social
distance.
It's cool.
As Riko-chan just said, the backslide is
the distance between the cars.
The distance between the cars is the
first song in Backslide, and the
beautiful bus is also a performance in
Backslide for the first time in a long
time.
There are many wonderful songs in
Sakurazaka, and I think that Backslide
is an opportunity for everyone to get to
know them.
We will continue to play various songs,
so please pay attention to it until the
end and enjoy it!
Thank you!
It's about time for us to get closer to
everyone.
Everyone, do you want to get closer to
us?
We also want to get closer to everyone!
Let's have fun this morning!
Your smile
For some reason, it makes me sad
I hope tomorrow will come soon
I can't catch up with you
The two of us walking ahead of me
The chance to talk
I'm waiting for you
I want to count you on my right hand
Where should I look for a summer
shortcut?
I'm thirsty for the next season
Because love is always in a hurry
Tell me the map of the future
Hold the summer shortcut in your right
hand
Inside the wind and sunlight
It looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
I wish I could invite you someday
Until now, I haven't been in a hurry
Suddenly, today
I have to hurry the distance of my heart
It's the order of the shooting
I want to skip
No matter what I do, even if I cheat
I can't hand you over to someone else
How long will the rainy night continue?
The rain won't stop at the darkness
Let's find a place where we can meet
Outside the clouds
Even if it's a long way around
Always chasing a miracle
If you turn the corner in front of you
That's already the entrance to the
midsummer
If possible, I want to fall in love with
you slowly
Because of my rival, I don't have time
Where should I look for the summer
shortcut?
The next season is just around the
corner
Because love is always in a hurry
Tell me the map of the future
Find the summer shortcut with your right
hand
Outside the wind and sunlight
Even though it looked the same every day
It's too late for the sunset to set
That's already the entrance to the
midsummer
Midsummer
The next song is "Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-
Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ki-Night"
"Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ko-Ki-Night"
I thought it was the beginning
Everyone has already found out
I'll hand over the meaningless things to
the other side
The parking lot is still full
I can hear it from somewhere
The door at midnight
Forget about the people around you
Now, let's kiss only in the corner of
the world
Far away from here
The orange light is shaking
The lovers gather in this place
I still can't sleep here
Soon the night will come
Even if the stars disappear
More romantic
A combination of love
The vintage car turned off the
headlights
Line up many times in the same direction
The night of the weekend is full of lies
The face of love, the near future on the
other side
The lovers whisper sweetly
With their own thoughts
How far will it come?
Without being disturbed by anyone
In everyday life
I want to kiss
Dreaming night
Quietly
As if breathing
Before you notice
A world that never fades
Shaking
Dreaming night
Forever
It's okay if it doesn't change
No matter how many times you come here
It's not boring
Because it's a combination
Rather than going to a club like that
It's like going crazy
The underground is small
The stairs and the tank are full of heat
Like a projection mapping
Smiling
With a deep breath
Kiss only in the corner of the world
Let's kiss
How about a kiss?
Here
In the distance
The orange light is swaying
Lovers are drawn
They gather
Even now
Here
I can't sleep
Soon the night will dawn
Even if the unknown stars disappear
Let's go back
To the combination of love
"MAX LIVE"
Be here
I'm stuck in the asphalt
When I'm barefoot
A clear expression
Smiling
The night is coming
The time has come
Farewell to him now
Where I met him in the past
It doesn't make sense
I'm stuck
I can't stand it
I'm afraid
If you're going to have a new love
On the magic song
Someday I'll be swept away
If I chase you
Any man
Just a scratch
It's over
You're especially dangerous
Disappearing without noticing
I can't sleep
Soon the night will dawn
Even if the unknown stars disappear
Let's go back
To the combination of love
"MAX LIVE"
I want to do it
I want to make it work
I can't decide
Are you kidding me?
Blue or pink
Black or yellow
I'm selfish
It's dangerous
I just have to stick it out
The manhole guitar show
I'm going to run away
I'm leaving the men
I'm going to chase you
Forever now
I'm sorry
You're a never ending story
Without saying what you want to say
The continuation that everyone thinks
Where will it appear?
"MAX LIVE"
The manhole guitar show
I'm going to run away
I'm chasing you
All men
Just hurt
End
You are especially dangerous
Disappearing without noticing
I can't pretend to be
What are you doing?
Oh yeah
What you say we do
Come and tell your story
"MAX LIVE"
When did it get rusty?
I was standing in front of the garden
My bicycle
I didn't forget
I hate you
The time I can't see
I love you on my own
I love you
Hey, I love you
Where is your heart?
I've found it
The unpleasant sound of the gears
"Buddy"
What I wanted
It's my bad part
Always close
If you cherish it
I wonder if I could stay shiny
It doesn't change since I met you
I'm the only one who has such an
illusion
With oil
It's over
It's useless to polish
I want to take it
I wonder if kindness is foolish
It's natural to take it
It's not just you
It's obvious
In your story
I want to shine
Emotions
Calm
I'm going to kill you
I'm sorry
Yes, forever
It's a new moment
It's just what I thought
I didn't expect time to flow
and change
The rust is not bad
I'm just going to participate
Return to the original
Ordinary
Natural phenomenon
Someday we
It was fun
I want to go back to that time
Did only the surface change?
If this doesn't work for some reason
If you put oil
What will happen?
I didn't care
It's my bad part
Always close
If you cherish it
I wonder if I could stay shiny
It doesn't change since I met you
What kind of phenomenon is it?
Am I the only one?
Put oil
Thank you.
The next song is the last song.
This time, I'm standing in the center
position as an original.
I didn't know why I was chosen, and I
was worried.
I was wondering what I could do.
I thought about it a lot.
I have love and passion for Sakurazaka
46.
It may not be the same as what I have in
my heart,
but I want to give my heart to
Sakurazaka46,
the only group in the world,
I was drawn to the group called
"Sakurazaka 46".
I'm standing here with respect and love
and determination.
I want you to see us as we are.
Please listen to us.
Love each other.
[applause]
Please subscribe to my channel!
Born in this era, I was born poor
No matter what I dream, it doesn't seem
to come true
I'm helpless
At this rate, our country will perish
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel and follow us on Twitter!
♪Why? What made you despair?
♪Are you not going to say anything?
♪I feel like there were things I wanted
to do in the past
♪But I can't remember
♪What can I do now?
♪The gears of fate
There's only one thing I can say
As a virtual girl
The opportunity won't come again
It's just that today continues without
stopping
The opportunity won't come again
Defeat the dominoes
Do it, do it, do it
I'll find a way
Thank you for watching!
Dreaming, dreaming, I'm waiting for
someone to move
There's no meaning in such a world
Revolution, the sigh that wakes the wind
Is it me?
I want to love
I want to be loved
Is there someone important to you?
Even if you live alone
Don't give up on your daily life
Someone's warmth is good
Don't hold back
Get involved
Be honest
People are lonely
I'm not good at it
It doesn't matter if it's stupid
Love
There's someone I want to love
Thank you very much for coming to the
Night Jingle Box Live today!
I hope you can never forget this moment
at this live!
It was really, really fun to be able to
make such a wonderful and hot live with
everyone today!
Thank you everyone!
This has been Sakura Naka46!
Thank you very much!
Sankaku-san, O-bishi! (Sankaku-san,
O-bishi!)
Thank you for the encore!
Let's enjoy this with everyone until the
end!
I was happy that you noticed
when I cut my hair
I can't see what love is
But I feel it when I fall in love
When the wind passes by
I wait for the scent of flowers
I'm not as lonely as I thought
Even if I'm walking alone
I might be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
There's no point in peeling off the sun
Because the sun is moving
Towards the sun
No matter where we go
If you're distracted by the scenery
around you
You'll miss the flowers by your feet
There's someone watching over me
Who's clumsy like this
Love isn't something you can find
It's something you can only meet on that
day
I'm sure the season will come
When you remember who it was
I was stronger than I thought
It's okay
I was more calm than I thought
Look up at the sky that's different from
yesterday
Life changes and changes
Clouds and snow are piling up
Happiness is somewhere in the middle of
the future
Let's look ahead and move forward
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
There's someone watching over me
Who's clumsy like this
Love isn't something you can find
It's something you can only meet on that
day
I'm sure the season will come
When you remember who it was
I was stronger than I thought
It's okay
I was more calm than I thought
It's something you can only meet on that
day
I'm sure the season will come
When you remember who it was
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
There's someone watching over me
Who's clumsy like this
I'm not as lonely as I thought
Even if I walk alone
I might be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
No matter where
Thank you!
Thank you, encore!
I was able to hear so many voices
I took off my earmuffs a little bit, but
it was so cool, wasn't it?
It was a great voice.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
This time, I changed the song of the
encore for 3 days.
Today is the heavy chorus, so it's not
as lonely as I thought it would be.
I sometimes do pair dance, and I have a
lot of eyes.
I was able to get excited with everyone
in BUDDYS and enjoy it.
How was everyone?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming to MAX LIVE today.
It's been three days since the 9th
single "MAX LIVE" was released.
I'd like to hear your impressions.
Next to me, the one who has always
supported me, Kira-san.
Me?
Yes.
I'm happy.
Well, I really can't stop talking about
my impressions in these three days.
There's something I really want to say
today.
Isn't Rika-chan's rap amazing?
It was amazing.
It's not just about rap.
This live...
It started with Rika-chan's song, and
ended with Rika-chan's rap.
I think it's really cool to end with
Rika-chan's rap.
I'm not as lonely as I thought I would
be, and I sometimes show off my
"kirappu".
I thought I could do it because Ten-san
did it so well.
But when I actually did it, it was
really hard.
I have to listen to the clicks well, and
if I do that, I become a robot.
So it's really hard to listen to the
song while listening to the clicks and
memorizing the lyrics.
Rika-chan's "rirappu"... "rikarappu"...
Rika-chan's "rikarappu"...
Wow!
I'm so glad.
I like Rika's singing voice.
I want her to challenge many things in
the next three days.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.
Welcome back.
Well,
Kira,
When I was feeling a bit down,
I messaged Kira-san and said, "I want to
see your weird face."
And she sent me a lot of weird faces.
She sent me so many of them.
I thought, "Is it okay for me to say it
like that?"
"Is there a senpai like that?"
I was very grateful for that, and I was
cheered up by that weird face.
I'm so happy.
The members are really great, and I saw
that they were talking to Rika-chan
about a lot of things.
I can't support her in that way, so I
just wanted to do what I could do.
If the members have anything sad to say
in the future, feel free to say it.
The same goes for the BUDDIES.
If I have anything to say, I'll say it.
I can't say it now.
I was very happy. Thank you.
I'd like to hear from one more person.
Thank you so much for being by my side.
Takemoto-san!
Thank you so much.
I could hear the voices of BUDDIES from
my earphones.
Thank you so much for today!
It was the best, really!
I was so surprised.
Every time we do a live,
the BUDDIES and I feel like we're making
a live together.
I don't think it's a matter of course
for us to sing together and get excited.
I've never heard that voice before.
The BUDDIES who update it every time are
the best!
I really thought about it again.
Above all, I was very happy to be able
to participate in this live,
which Rika-chan thought about and worked
hard to create.
Thank you for your hard work!
This is the third time we are doing the
9th single "Backslide"
It's the same venue as the last time,
but this time we are doing it for 3 days
The "Backslide" is getting bigger and
bigger
Thanks to everyone's help, we were able
to hold the "Backslide" every time.
At first, we were very nervous.
But, well...
I had the confidence that BUDDIES would
definitely enjoy it.
Today, this day, for this day,
I think that there are many people who
give me a job, school, and so on.
Even though there is such a thing,
I think it's for this day.
There are so many people who are looking
forward to this day.
I'm so happy that so many people have
come to see us.
We have a live stream today, so I'm glad
that there are people who are watching
us from afar.
We will continue to bring you the best
of SAKURAZAKA46.
Backsliding is one of the hot things in
SAKURAZAKA46.
I'm glad I was able to make a live with
these wonderful 13 people today.
And thank you so much to everyone at
BUDDIES.
It's a little sad, but the 9th single
"Backslide" will also be the last song
on this tour.
It was a very short period of time, but
I would be very happy if you could join
us in singing this song together with
everyone.
Everyone, are you ready for the last
song?
Thank you.
Here we go.
"I WIN"
Once again, thank you very much for
today.
I hope you enjoyed it.
We had a lot of fun.
Finally, let's say it together.
Let's go, everyone!
I'll try to stretch it as much as I can
I wonder if the tip of my finger will
reach the sky
I'll raise my heels as high as I can
I'll reach the limit of stretching my
back
I can touch the dream
I sigh at the blue sky that's too far
away
Will I give up?
Or will I keep trying?
I'm me!
I want you to be my friend
I can't look away
I don't care if I'm small
I want to share my strength with you
I'm me!
I want to try it
Come on, baby!
One day, I'll reach my dream
That's right, I'll believe in that
I want to stretch my arms with everyone
Finally, the tip of my finger seems to
touch
I can't reach it a little more
Sometimes, I want to run away
I'll do my best
If I let go of my chest now
Everything will be over
I'll bite it
Crying is a dream
Even if I get dizzy by the brightness of
the sun
I won't turn my back
I'm me!
How long have you been here?
Are you looking up without a doubt?
Even if you deny that it won't come true
I'm me!
I want to try it with you
Our arms will become one
Until we can go beyond the blue sky
I have no choice but to try more and
more
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
I'm me!
You're me!
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Let's break through the atmosphere
Come on, the universe will begin
No matter how far away dreams and hopes
are
Come on, grab it
If you let go now, you'll lose
I'll try to stretch my arms as much as I
can
Will the tip of my finger reach the sky?
I'll raise my heels as high as I can
I'll reach the limit I've reached
Finally, I'll be able to touch my dreams
I'm me!
I want you to let me join you
No matter how far away dreams and hopes
are
You're not alone
I'm me!
I want to try to help you
(I want to teach you)
When you're far away from your dreams
When you're in pain, look around
Everyone is aiming for the same sky
I'll try to stretch my arms as much as I
can
Thank you so much for coming today
I love you all so much!
Let's do the last one!
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, oh, oh
I'm your
Thank you very much for coming to the
single backstripe and watching the live
stream.
The reason why we are standing on the
stage today is because of our Buddies.
We were so happy to see your big smiles
and open mouths.
We will never forget this day.
We look forward to your continued
support for Sakurazaka46.
That's all from Sakurazaka46.
Thank you very much.
I've never had this kind of experience
before, so I'm a little nervous, but I'm
glad I was able to call everyone like
this.
Can I sing one more song?
Thank you.
Since we're all here, why don't we sing
together?
Is that okay?
I'm sure the Buffies know what song
we're going to sing.
I'll say, "Ready, set, go!"
You say the title of the song, and I'll
say the song title.
Ready, set, go!
Thank you very much.
Well, let's do it.
Everyone, please make a really loud
voice.
Let's do it.
One, two...
Let's love each other!
Born in this era, I drew a pinball
lottery
No matter what dream I have, I feel like
it won't come true
I'm out of energy
At this rate, we'll all fall apart
Is there someone important to you?
Even if you live alone
Don't give up on your everyday life
Someone's warmth
Don't let it all go to waste
Thank you for watching!
I can only be one of the gears
I'll lock the clutch
There's no more chance
It's just going to continue today
I'll knock down the dominoes
Do it, do it, do it
I'll turn the wheel
Keep it going
明日こそは Flying! Flying!
熱い情熱 Keep it going!
叶えたいよ Dreaming! Dreaming!
I'm waiting for the time when someone
else will come
That kind of reception is meaningless
Revolution!
In order to raise the wind
I want to love myself
I want to be loved
Is there anyone important to you?
Even if you live alone
Don't give up on your daily life
Someone's warmth is good
Don't be lazy
Get involved
Be honest
People are not good at loneliness
It doesn't matter if you're stupid
Love yourself
Is there anyone you want to love?
Thank you very much for today
I will never forget
It was such a wonderful day
I hope it will be a day like that for
everyone
Once again, I really love you
Thank you for your support
Please stay with us forever
That's all from Sakurazaka46
Thank you very much
Everyone, please take a picture of the
stage and the audience
And leave it as a memory
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for watching the
live stream
Thank you very much for today
Thank you very much