Good evening, everyone! We are
SAKURAZUKA46!
Our 8th single "MAX LIFE" has just been
released!
Are you all excited?
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much for giving us so much
support from the start!
Your voices are our strength, and we are
able to deliver it with our full power.
Today, let's keep this up until the end,
and forget about everything else and
follow us!
Thank you!
Also, we have a live stream today,
so if you're watching, are you watching?
Good evening!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best to deliver the heat to
everyone who is watching the live
broadcast, so I hope you can get
excited.
Yes, so I'd like to hear everyone's
enthusiasm for today.
First of all, Riko.
Yes, Riko-chan.
I'm Riko Enzo.
Yes.
In the last Backslide,
Backslide is...
I felt that I might never be able to do
it again with the same members,
so I was really sad to come here today,
but I'm really excited to be able to
show BUDDIES the results of our 8th
member's hard work in this big venue.
It's something that only these members
can do.
I feel like I can explode today.
It's going to explode.
As Riko said, we've been working really
hard on this.
We're going to deliver it with
confidence.
I'd be happy if you could take it all.
Thank you.
Next up is Reina.
How was it?
Actually, in the second song "Koizetsu
no Toki",
there was a part where I had to do this
with Shuke-san,
and I always had a really bad face.
I was like, "I'll do it!"
You were making fun of her, weren't you?
You were laughing, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
I was like, "I'll do it! I'll do it,
too!"
How was it?
You always do it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I was looking at everyone's lively faces
in the middle of the song,
and I thought it would be a good live
performance, so I was looking forward to
it.
Thank you very much.
You two are always doing it.
I'll do it.
When I meet the members, I feel like I'm
going to go even further.
I hope we can get excited more and more
while looking at each other and the
BUDDIES.
We've just started the BUDDIES LIVE.
From now on, each member will show you a
variety of worlds.
I hope everyone will join us and get
excited.
I hope you can make a lot of memories in
this space.
Please enjoy it to the end today.
Tomorrow is the truth
"I don't like you"
I've always denied it
As I thought, my tears flow
The scent of flowers
That I can feel in the wind
Not just one
I couldn't say it
It's the love that sways my heart
Suddenly, my feelings overlapped
As if I didn't know
I want to put on a cardigan
The feeling of summer
I felt like someone was calling my name
As I turned around
As if I'm searching in the city
The one I'm always curious about
Is you
Tears flow
The real me
Surely didn't know anything
On the other side of the blue sky
It's not always sunny
It's like a snowstorm
It's a light love
It makes me want to see you again
The fact that I'm conscious of someone
Never happened to me
For some reason, I was so focused
I heard a single voice
It's you
The wind blows
And all the sounds are erased
Ah, I was searching
For that person close to me
It's usually just a dream
I felt like someone was calling my name
As I turned around
As if I'm searching in the city
The one I'm always curious about
Is you
Never happened to me
For some reason, I was so focused
I heard a single voice
It's you
I felt like someone was calling my name
Maybe it's just an illusion
It's you
I've always been shy
Saying "I don't love you"
It's you
I've always been shy
"I love you"
Blue Moon Kiss
Don't look at me with that face
I'm sorry for surprising you
The moon was beautiful tonight
That's why I miss you so much
Suddenly, I held your shoulder
Suddenly, I stole your lips
Making excuses is painful
I've always wished for that time
To be honest, I should have said it
"I love you"
Like a fragile glass
Ah, I kissed you
The wind blew through my nose
I was jealous
How awkward
We were awkward
I was afraid of loneliness
I shouldn't have done that
I should have just let you go
If I was going to regret it
I could have predicted
That this would happen
On the way home
Blue Moon Kiss
What should I do with my face?
Should I just walk away without saying
anything?
Actually, I was hiding it
I've always been afraid
Suddenly, I thought of it
It's like we're meeting for the first
time
That's what I thought
Soft feelings
I'm not good at imagining love
It's such a painful moment
It's so convenient
My moment
Ah, I love you so much
The beat of my heart
Is it something to be so excited about?
I'm sure I heard it
It's like I'm in a hurry
How awkward
I was calm
I tried to act cool
It's too late now
Can I be your lover?
I have to let go of something now
If I wait like this
It'll be the worst day
I want to joke
But it's too romantic
I can't think of anything
Blue Moon
The beat of my heart
Is it something to be so excited about?
I'm sure I heard it
It's like I'm in a hurry
The wind blew through
The light sank
How awkward
We're awkward
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I shouldn't have done it
If I regret it
I should have come as it was
The way home
In a roundabout way
I could predict it would be like this
Blue Moon
One day you told me
The secret story of my childhood
The lipstick you put on
Is what I wanted the most in the world
You said you'd give it to me when I grew
up
I knew it myself
But every time I saw it
It was about to disappear
So one day I quietly took it out
And put it in my bathroom
And then, Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I tried putting it on myself
What kind of Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Was reflected in the mirror?
The lipstick you put on
Was a back that couldn't reach
But Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
It was more beautiful than usual
(Sonia, Sonia, Sonia, Sonia)
I think I knew
What I'd been hiding on my desk
But I was still a little worried
Because I wasn't scolded
After a while, time passed
When I found someone I liked
I started to look for a color that
suited me
What kind of Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I tried putting on a lot of things
But today, Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I can't decide on my own
The image I had until now
I don't care if I'm an adult or a child
So Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I want to be the most wonderful me
Did you try putting it on yourself?
What kind of Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Was reflected in the mirror?
Because Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I fell in love many times
With the lipstick that changed my
expression
The diary I kept drawing that day
Again today, Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
What color should I make my mood?
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Everyone in the audience and everyone
watching the live stream, are you having
fun?
Thank you very much
It's been only a few songs since the
beginning, but I'm so happy to be
together with everyone.
Thank you very much.
So, let's get started.
First of all, how about Hikarin, who
will participate in the backslide for
the first time in a while?
Yes.
It's been a while since I've been on
Backslide, since the third single.
Thank you.
It's been a while.
Last time, everyone was on the stage of
Backslide with the 7th single.
At first, I was very anxious because I
was going to perform with Yui-chan,
but the color of Backslide, which we all
made together, became very solid.
I thought it would be okay, but when I
came in, everyone treated me as if I had
been there from the beginning, and I had
a lot of opportunities to talk to
everyone in the 3rd grade naturally, and
I talked to Ika-chan in the break time.
I think that I was able to spend a lot
of time with everyone.
Thank you very much.
That's right. Hikarin is really kind.
She's been talking to me since I joined
the 3rd generation.
During this time, she found each and
every good point.
She said, "Rika-chan, that was good."
She praised me honestly. She's very
kind.
I'm happy to be able to stand on stage
with her this time.
I'm happy.
I'd like to ask one more person.
Marino-san, are you ready?
I'd like to talk about my enthusiasm.
There was a big happening just now.
I noticed it!
You noticed?
During the intro of "Koijutsu", the
rubber band of this ponytail came off.
It was a ponytail?
Yes, it was.
I didn't know that.
It was a lion-like hairstyle.
I was so embarrassed to dance
"Koijutsu".
Did you notice it?
I'm a little embarrassed.
I was wondering if people who were
watching the live stream would think,
"Who is this girl?"
I was a little embarrassed, but I did my
best today.
You look beautiful.
You're cute.
I thought I could do it in the next
song, so I did my best.
Thank you very much.
But the reason why Marino's hair came
undone was because she was dancing so
hard.
In my impression of Marino, you wrote
your goal for the last SEVENTH SINGLE
"Backstripe", didn't you?
Yes.
And you wrote, "That's Jizo."
Yes, I did.
I was able to see various faces of
Marino in the SEVENTH SINGLE.
This time, too.
I can see Marino dancing so hard that
her head is shaking from the first song.
And in the next song, too.
I think it's a live show where you can
see a lot of things like, "Oh, this girl
can do this kind of face," or "Oh, she
can do this kind of thing."
I hope you don't take your eyes off us
until the end.
Thank you.
It's about time.
The seniors are starting to want to
dance and sing.
And they're starting to want to get
closer to everyone.
It's about time, everyone.
Can you get ready to get excited?
Can you shout more and more?
Let's get excited until the end!
[Ninja!]
I was hesitating
I was in a hurry
[Ninja!]
Little by little
I got confused
[Ninja!]
Okay, I'm gonna get closer to you from
here!
Please look at each other a lot!
Let's get excited together!
Why am I with you?
I wonder if it's easy like this
I didn't think about love
Now I can see it clearly
Confidence, I wonder if it's necessary
Somehow
[Just a little, just a little]
I think I can do it
I've heard it many times
My feelings
Hey, really
[Just a little, just a little]
I already know
Confidence, I love you
[Just a little, just a little]
Snowman
I fell
[Just a little, just a little]
I fell down
I don't even know how to eat it
It's a meaningless relationship
Where is the certainty?
Even if I look for it
[Just a little, just a little]
When I was an adult
Somehow I confirmed
The truth
Without lying
[Just a little, just a little]
Let's live straight
It's okay to look
I can't stop myself
What should I do?
You're the only one who knows
Confidence
It's nowhere
Everyone
Confidence
Is it necessary?
Somehow
[Just a little, just a little]
I don't even know how to eat it
I heard it many times
My feelings
Hey, really
[Just a little, just a little]
I already know
Hey, really
[Just a little, just a little]
I already know
Confidence
I thought so
[Just a little, just a little]
I tried to change
I couldn't live
Even though I tried my best with all of
my heart
My own stubbornness
The sweat I spit out
The messy days
My weak heart
It has nothing to do with anything
I have to go to that place
I can't be noticed
Hot passion
How far can I run?
Will the blue sea come?
I'm getting closer to my dream
How far can I run?
I wonder if I can be a bird
Until the day I can fly
I'll keep running
No matter how hard I try
I have to have a fight
I don't have time
No one knows
The important thing
Did you forget?
The tears that flowed
The blurred red blood
The pain in my chest
I can't win anything
Ignored by anyone
It's over
Worthless
How far can I run?
Will I reach the horizon?
Will it become reality?
How far can I run?
I wonder if I can call you my friend
It didn't turn out the way I thought
I was frustrated
Unfortunate
How far can I run?
I wonder if I can be a bird
Until the day I can fly
I'll keep running
I didn't even think
I wasn't appreciated
In the end, I don't have enough strength
That's how it is
How far can I run?
Will the blue sea come?
Will I get closer to my dream?
How far can I run?
I wonder if I can be a bird
Until the day I can fly
I'll keep running
Someday, my chest
I'm sorry
Swaying, swaying, swaying
Swaying, swaying
I've never heard
The name of the town
How far can I run?
I don't know
That's what I think
Ever since you told me
The petals have fallen
Should I accept it?
Should I oppose it?
While searching for clues in your eyes
I held back
If I wish for happiness
Sadness overflows
Even the cherry blossoms in full bloom
Will be blown by the wind
The shining youth
Is not eternal
I thought I understood
But I didn't understand
Forever, forever
Can't I stay like this?
Swaying, swaying, swaying
Swaying, swaying
If your future
Is connected to that town
Then I have no choice
But to send you off here
Even if I try to say
Some kind words or voice
It's awkward, so I wave my hand
"University is fine
No matter where it is"
If I were to stop you
How would you answer?
Happiness is always
Something you can't get
You have to choose
One or the other
With a moment of kindness
And a lifetime of regret
We're living
With a smile on our face
More, more
To the faraway mountains
Swaying, swaying, swaying
Swaying, swaying
You're all, all mine
I won't give you to anyone else
As soon as I let go of your hand
Where are you going?
Opera Kei-san
That's right, there's no turning back
In front of the children
I hugged you
I held your hand
And brought you here
Oh yeah
There were a lot of people
Playing around here and there
Everyone knows that
We're being watched together
I was the only one
Who didn't care about that
I have to do something
Or the world will end
You're all, all mine
I'm declaring it here and now
If I don't say it clearly
You'll misunderstand
Because you're all, all my treasure
A special existence created by love
I won't let anyone else
Touch that part of me
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
What's wrong with you?
Are you going my way?
Oh yeah
I don't want to be bound by anyone
I want to be free
I'm angry, but I'll protect you
Because I'm here
I'm free
Being alone is lonely
You know that, don't you?
That's why we're
Yes, we're together with someone
Love is definitely, definitely someone's
Gently, gently warm it up
Carefully, carefully nurture it
I want to make a beautiful flower garden
Maybe, yes, that's a sweet scent
You and I, we're attracted to each other
A beautiful life
Until eternity ends
Let's dream
Take my hand now
Let's start running somewhere
So that no one can catch up
You're everything, everything to me
I'm declaring it here and now
If I don't say "I love you"
I'll be mistaken
Because everything, everything is a
treasure
A special existence made with love
No one can catch up
You're everything, everything to me
I'm declaring it here and now
"One-Sided Love"
One-Sided Love
"Who do you like?"
It doesn't matter
"Who do you choose?"
I'm not alone
We're all working hard
I support you
The places where light shines
There are places that don't shine
The beauty of trying to live as hard as
you can
One-Sided Love
Let's sing as much as we can
So that I can convey my feelings to you
Until that wind blooms someday
Let's keep shining
One-Sided Love
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
From the other side of the stage
Ah, I can see
The wind, the sun, and the rain
I want to raise you
BUDDIES!
Are you excited for the second day of
BIRTHLESS LIVE?
You can still hear our voices, right?
Yeah!
Let's make the best memories together!
One-Sided Love
Don't compare yourself to others
You are not yourself
You know your own BIRTHLESS LIFE
What's important is the determination
I want to do what I want to do
I want to live a life without regret
One-Sided Love
Let's start with our shoulders
I want to be friends with you
I want to show you my good and bad sides
I want to be your friend
One-Sided Love
Let's play a song and dance to the
rhythm
Let's resonate with your message
Let's make the best of the best
Thank you for being such a member
Please keep it in your memory
You, who still have a long way to go
Please believe that you can blossom a
big flower
Until the day you graduate
Let me see everything
It's aрои-Send-Time
Let's sing as loud as you can
Let's sing, so that the feelings I have
for you can be conveyed
Until that sweat starts to flow again
someday
Let's keep shining
Keep dancing time
Let's raise our hearts one by one
Let's have the courage to say just that
From the other side of the stage, I can
clearly see
With the wind and the sound of the sun
I want to raise you
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Are you all having fun?
Are you all having fun watching the live
stream?
The live stream will continue, so please
relax and have fun!
It's the last day of the second day of
Bacchus Live.
It's already over, but I'm a little
lonely today.
I've been lonely since this morning.
During this time, I've been supported
and helped by so many people.
There are many days when I feel like I
can't go on like this.
Thank you for watching until the end.
But I'm sure there are things that don't
change unless you move on your own, so I
tried a lot of things with Backslide.
It's really nice to have someone who
recognizes that challenge and someone
who supports it.
I'm glad I'm here, and I'm doing
Backslide.
Thank you very much.
Well, this is the last time, so I'd like
to ask you a few questions.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
What do you think?
It's the best!
It really is!
It's fun!
It's really fun, isn't it?
If I were to say something personal, I'm
the first one to come out.
I'm really nervous.
I'm the only one.
I'm going to come out from here.
Thanks to everyone's enthusiasm, I was
able to dance to my heart's content.
Thank you so much!
It was amazing!
It was really cool!
When I saw Juki-san's solo dance, I
thought, "Let's do our best too!"
Juki-san's back is really amazing.
Juki-san's incredible...
When I saw Juki-san's back, I thought
that Juki-san would make this live a
wonderful one.
I thought we should do our best, too.
It was cool, wasn't it, everyone?
It was really cool.
This time, I choreographed it myself.
Thank you very much.
I've always had a goal in my mind.
I'm very happy to hear that.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Next, Nagi.
Everyone.
KONMARI!
Thank you very much.
I did it yesterday because I wanted to
do it.
Don't get too excited.
Really?
Because it's KONMARI.
That's good.
I also have something to thank Tsuke-san
for.
As I said earlier, Tsuke-san,
in the first opening dance track,
there were a lot of center songs.
I think it was really hard.
During rehearsals and during lessons,
when I was worried that I couldn't do
the choreography,
even though I didn't say anything,
Tsuke-san said, "Let's do it together."
I think everyone did it.
It was really cool.
I also relied on Tsuke-san.
The day before yesterday?
Before the first day started, he
personally contacted me.
He knew that I was having a hard time
with Bacchus Live.
He said, "There are only two days left,
so let's enjoy the rest."
I was able to show a lot of explosive
power in these two days.
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's embarrassing!
Thank you very much!
We were saved by everyone.
We couldn't do anything at all.
Thanks to everyone, we are standing
here.
I want to pay back to everyone on this
stage.
Thank you very much!
This live is a live that we all helped
make.
I tried it yesterday and today.
I thought that everyone from BUDDIES was
helping me a lot.
I'm really happy that you gave me a lot
of fan lights and gave me a lot of
voices.
I think I'm saved.
So, let's get excited until the end!
You can shout more and more, right?
Let's get excited until the end!
Let's go!
You can't say important words to anyone
Your heart will fly away in an instant
No matter how beautiful the words you
choose
They will turn into something so sad
that it's sad
Everyone believes in love
But if you touch the air
It will turn into a weakness
So I'll throw my heart away
Yes, I'll be a cowardly man
Who doesn't fall in love with anyone
I'll pretend it doesn't matter
I want to be a man who is
straightforward
Even if you look at me like that
I'll become uninterested
I'll keep resisting
I don't want to be an adult
I want to be a fool like this
I want to do it steadily
I want to realize the true me
(Love! Love! Love! ..)
My heart withers at anytime
I wrap it up
I made sure no one cares
I don't want anyone to care about me
If I'm lonely, I can be sober
Kindness and love
can be a knife that can't be seen at
times
Even my friends who are by my side
don't know, don't know, they're hurting
me
There's no distance like that
Yes, the distance between people
is more difficult than I thought
If I were to say this,
of course I wouldn't be able to do it
I've come to live in a world where I
don't feel any emotions
I won't be afraid, I'll let you do
whatever you want
I don't want to be bound
You can't ask for normal
Nothing will change
You can't leave me alone
The last thing I want is a rule, a rule,
a rule
[Music]
[Applause]
I was able to live up to my parents' and
teachers' expectations
But I'm not the kind of person who can
do that
I want to do what I want to do
How can you forgive me for that?
If that's the case, then I'd rather
I'd rather have a carefree life
Where does the open space in my heart
come from?
Before I knew it, I realized
That I was lonely until today
With the power to sigh
Only my true feelings are leaking out
little by little
With a quiet power that I can't even
notice
I pull my feet
A faint wind that only I can feel
When I look at something dazzling
It makes me dizzy
I just need to close my eyes for a
moment
How long will it take?
Even though it's not a big dream
Do I have to see it?
Even if I just pretend to be like that
I hate myself
Yes, I'm told that I'm strange
I can't accept it
But I still have to ignore the world
If that's the case, then please
Don't put me in the number
I'm crying without a sound because
there's a gap
I don't feel it because I'm used to
being hurt
I don't want to know anything
Because I'm saying no myself
I don't know what to do
Every time I breathe
The sound of the clouds running away
I've been hesitating
The air of hope that I secretly inhaled
I can't tell anyone
I'm sure there's something in my heart
Little by little without knowing
I feel like I'm falling in love with the
words
I don't know what to do
Because I'm saying no myself
If that's the case, then please
Open your heart wide
In the middle of this chest
Come out to the wind
Where does the gap in the back of the
chest come from?
I hurt myself until today
I was lonely and sighed
I'm out of breath
Only the true heart is getting buried
little by little
I can't notice
With a quiet force
Pulling my legs
A faint wind that only I can feel
"Cherry Blossom"
Even if we talk, it's a waste of time
What we're seeing is completely
different
It's okay to cry
I don't ask for understanding anymore
Identity that has been suppressed
To the pessimistic adults
Don't push the cheap love
That people say over and over again
A small world in the countryside
If you run through with all your might
What do you understand?
A dead end
There is an end to the world
What do you do from here?
It's pitch black in front of you
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
When you've seen too much
I can't help being here
I was wrong
A dead end
Where do you live now that connects the
past and the future?
"Cherry Blossom"
Even if we compete with each other
To see what we can do
As long as we make a detour
We will become a kindred spirit
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
When you've seen too much
I can't help being here
I was wrong
A dead end
Where do you live now that connects the
past and the future?
"Cherry Blossom"
Even if we compete with each other
To see what we can do
As long as we make a detour
We will become a kindred spirit
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
A dead end
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
Even if we keep eating
What should we answer?
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will you go back to the way you came?
When you've seen too much
The one who made a mistake was me
A dead end
While knocking on the wall in front of
you
Are you screaming in your heart?
How do you live in the present
That gently connects the future?
(The audience is cheering)
Is this the true value of the VARIES?
You can still go, right?
(The audience is cheering)
Everyone, make some noise for the last
battle!
(The audience is cheering)
Pinky-heel
Throw away the asphalt
You're barefoot
A clear expression
Oh
To the north, to the south
What happens on a gloomy night?
I don't know him now
Where did you meet him in the past?
It just makes sense
It's a good thing
To suppress the troublesome bad things
If you're going to have a new love
On top of the magic lid
Any man will end up just hurting you
You're especially dangerous
Disappearing without realizing it
I'm going to change the way you suddenly
disappear
What are you going to do?
Oh yeah
On top of the fragile collar
You're quietly
Take a deep breath
Oh
Get in the way
Passionate gaze
What do you see?
I want to stop it
I want to make it work
I can't decide
Are you kidding me?
You and me
I've said it many times
There's no need to be selfish
Just make it work
On top of the magic lid
Every time you try to run away
You're fooling the men
I'm not going to chase you like this
I'm sorry
You're a never ending story
Without saying what you want to say
No one thinks about the continuation
Where will it appear?
Surprise!
What should we do?
Come closer, get down
Let's go!
On top of the magic lid
Every time you try to run away
You're fooling the men
I'm not going to chase you like this
I'm sorry
You're especially dangerous
You disappear before I notice
It's more effective to be free
What should we do?
Surprise!
Come closer, get down
What should we do?
Thank you very much.
The next song I'm going to perform is
the last song.
From the moment I met this song, to this
day,
I can't even remember the lyrics, the
choreography, and the sound.
I learned countless emotions from this
song.
I believed that Wax would show me a new
form,
and I moved forward with this song.
I would like to perform this song as a
culmination of that.
I would be happy if you could enjoy it
with your own voices.
I will do my best to deliver it.
Please listen to it.
"Rust"
When did it become rusty?
My bicycle was standing at the end of
the garden
It's not like I forgot
The time I can't see
I hate it on my own
I like to keep an eye on you
It means that somewhere in my heart is
rusted
I can hear the unpleasant sound of the
car
If love doesn't go well
What should I do if I put oil on it?
It's my fault that I didn't take care of
you
If I always took care of you closely
I wonder if I could stay shiny
It doesn't change since I met you
Am I the only one crying in such an
illusion?
Even if I put oil on it and polish it
It's useless, it's like I took it
Kindness is a foolish and unnatural
behavior
It's not just you, it's us
In the rainstorm, I'm lonely
I'm sorry
Yes, I just thought it would be boring
forever
I can't believe time is passing by
The rust isn't bad
It's just oxidizing
It's a normal natural phenomenon that
goes back and forth
We used to have fun together
I want to go back to that time
Did only the surface change?
If love doesn't go well
What should I do if I put oil on it?
It's my fault that I didn't take care of
you
If I always took care of you closely
I wonder if I could stay shiny
It doesn't change since I met you
Am I the only one crying in such an
illusion?
Even if I put oil on it
Thank you so much for today
Thanks to the hot space you made
We were able to perform with all our
might
I'm looking forward to the day we can
meet again
That's all
We are 4T-6
Thank you very much
Thank you
Bye-bye
тЩк "Digital Signage" тЩк "Digital Signage"
тЩк "Digital Signage"
тЩк "Loser"
I'll do it, from here
Love you, love you, love you
The soul is always
As long as life goes on
My song will exist forever
Love you, love you, love you
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for the encore!
Thank you!
Thank you for the past two days
I'm trying to end it like this, but I
really got a lot of power from
everyone's close-up expressions.
Thank you so much for getting so excited
today, and thank you so much for coming
all the way to Mikiriseki to see a lot
of people.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to hear your thoughts on
today's performance.
First of all, NUMA!
Yes!
NUMA!
I was really nervous for the past two
days.
But thanks to everyone, I had a lot of
fun.
Thank you so much!
I was in charge of the "Munen" center.
When I found out about the "Munen"
center,
I thought a lot about why I was in
charge of the "Munen."
About two years ago, I received the song
"Munen" as a back-up song.
When I first heard it, I cried.
I was so moved that I thought it was a
song about my feelings.
When I first heard it, I thought it was
a song that I couldn't listen to without
shedding tears.
Two years have passed, and I listened to
it again.
At the end, I was very positive.
I think it's a song I can get used to.
That's why I decided to stand in the
center of the backslide.
I'm going to let go of this regret
together.
I'm definitely going to finish this song
with a positive feeling.
I'm performing with my heart and my
will.
I've been doing this for two days.
I really like the lyrics.
I was able to face myself, but I was
also able to face forward.
I was able to feel my own growth.
I'm glad I was able to perform like
this.
This is our 4th BAX Live, and we've been
doing a lot of different things since
our first BAX Live.
In this BAX Live, I want to show you a
different side of me.
I want to show you a side of me that
looks forward and moves forward.
That's what I've been hoping for since
the beginning.
I'd be happy if you could feel that way.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you.
I'll ask one more person. Fuka-san.
Fuka-san, please.
I think the audience felt it at the
backslide.
Each one of you showed us how to shine
the most.
I think this is the kind of live
performance we can do.
During the rehearsals, the staff and the
director tried to make the members stand
out and shine.
They thought about it to the very end.
Each of us had our own song.
She thought about the song that would
shine the most.
She also thought about how to make the
song look good.
I think we all feel the same way, and we
all practiced really hard for this.
I'm really thankful for this concert.
As a member of BUCKS, I'm really
thankful for this concert.
The fact that we can have a concert like
this in Sakuradaka is really...
I think it's a wonderful group.
Also, Ii-chan, right?
Well, it's still...
Next time...
Ah, it's nothing. I'll read it.
Eh?
Really?
I'll read it.
Eh?
It's okay.
Was that okay?
I've talked to Yui-chan about a lot of
things.
I hope we can meet again.
Please tell us.
Everyone is smiling. Why can't you tell
us?
I'm glad I was able to share my thoughts
with you today.
Thank you.
Thank you very much for having me.
If it wasn't for Fuuka-san, I wouldn't
have been able to come this far.
I'm very grateful for that. Thank you.
As Fuuka-san said, in my opinion,
Wax Live is a place where you can do
whatever you want to do.
You can do whatever you want to do.
That's the image of Wax Live.
I thought it was a place like that.
I'm sure each of the 12 members will be
at the center of their own song.
I think we've been facing each other
with a lot of passion.
I think that's why we were able to get
together on stage like this.
I'd be happy if you could feel that way.
Above all, I think the most important
thing is that the people who came here
remember today's scenery.
I'm sure you'll be able to do your best
at the moment when you're excited about
your daily life.
It was one of our goals to create a lot
of those moments.
If you think that way, I think we'll be
able to say that this live was a
success.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, it seems like you're saying
that you're not good enough yet.
I think we'll do one more song. Is that
okay?
Can you make more noise?
Let's get excited for the last song!
Thank you very much for the past two
days.
BUDDIES have always been watching over
us.
We will continue to challenge.
Thank you so much for always being my
best ally!
Will it reach the sky?
KAKATO!
I'll raise it as high as I can
To the limit where I can reach
I'll do it to the end
So I can touch my dreams
The blue sky is too heavy
I can't make it
Will I give up?
Not yet
Shall we take on the challenge?
Let's do it!
I want to shake hands with everyone
Finally, the tip of my finger is about
to fall
I can't reach it a little more
Sometimes I want to run away
Let's do our best
If I let go of my arm now
Everything will be over
I'm just staring at the back
I don't cry
Even if the sun is dazzling
Even if I feel dizzy
I won't bow my back
Cute!
Since when have you been doing it here?
Girl!
Are you looking up at the sky?
I don't care if you deny it
I want to be next to you
I want to see you
Many arms become one
Until I can fly over the blue sky
I have no choice but to do more
Wow...
Let's go! Let's break through!
Now the universe begins
No matter how far it is, dreams and
hopes
Come on, grab it
If I let go of my arm now, I'll lose
I try to stretch my arm as much as I can
Will the tip of my finger reach the sky?
Raise your heels as high as you can
The limit of stretching your back
I can finally touch my dream
I think!
I want you to let me join
I want you to let me hear your voice
You're not alone at all
I think!
I want to be useful to you
I'm so excited
Someday I'll reach my dream
When I'm having a hard time, I look
around
Everyone is aiming for the same sky
Everyone is stretching their arms
Wow...
Thank you for showing me the best view
today
Let's be one with everyone here and
everyone watching the live show
Please let me hear your favorite voice a
lot!
One, two!
Thank you! I love you!
I'm in!
Thank you so much for today
It's a lifetime treasure for us to be
able to make such wonderful memories
with everyone today
You're not alone, just like the lyrics
say
Let's continue to walk together
We'll do our best to show you how much
we've grown
That's all
This was Sakura Gakuen 46!
Thank you!
Sakura!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Let's meet again soon!
Let's hang out again!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
What should we do?
Let's play one more song.
Let's do it.
Yes, I prepared it.
Please bring that.
What do you mean?
Are you ready to make some noise?
Let's go!
Well then, please listen.
Make some noise!
"My Bicycle"
When did it become rusty?
I was riding my bicycle,
thinking it was too weak.
It's not like I forgot about it.
The time I can't see
is too selfish.
I let go of your hand
and my heart became rusty.
"My Bicycle"
I can hear it.
If love doesn't work out for some
reason,
I wonder what will happen if I put oil
on it.
It's my fault that I didn't take care of
it.
If I had always cherished it close to
me,
I wonder if I could have stayed shiny.
It hasn't changed since I met you.
Am I the only one who has such an
illusion?
I put oil on it.
It's useless to hurry up and polish it.
It's not just a dream, it's a reality
In the rainstorm, I endure the
loneliness
What continues is the silence of
emotions
A lie that predicts tranquility
I'm sorry
That's right, forever
It's just what I thought it would be
I never thought that time would flow
It's not a bad thing to grow up
I'm just going to participate
It's just a normal natural phenomenon
That makes you want to go back to the
beginning
We used to have fun together
I just want to go back to that time
Did only the surface change?
If love doesn't go well for some reason
What happens if you put oil on it?
I didn't care
It's my fault
If I had always been close and cherished
Could I have stayed shiny?
It hasn't changed since I met you
I'm the only one who's chasing such an
illusion
Put oil on it
Thank you
Thank you so much, Fusion
Burning is the best!
Let's meet again
Thank you so much for today
Thank you
It was fun!
See you
Thank you