We're the best-growing group so far, and
we're in the 1st place.
I wonder how much we've practiced in a
place where no one is watching.
I'm relieved just by looking at you.
He's the one who gave me the hope that I
might be able to do this someday if I
work hard.
I'm glad he's here.
I was able to make sure that my juniors
would never go in the wrong direction.
I don't feel like this is the last
concert.
But this is the last one.
To be continued...
Congratulations on your graduation,
Komae-san.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Good luck!
Now, I'm sure some of the students in
the audience have questions, but I'll
give you a brief explanation.
I'm imagining a stage like this, with a
little bit of reddish pink on top of the
picture.
I hope you can see the image and style
of the piece.
This time, I'm going to focus on things
that didn't go well.
We're going to make a video of the cover
performance.
In other words, we're going to make a
video of the cover performance of the
next song,
and we're going to create a world view
of the song and put it in the song.
We're going to have a big screen here to
get a big shot of the cover performance.
Setori really picks up all the songs I
want to do and puts them side by side
like this.
I told him that I wanted to do this kind
of staging because there was a staging
that I wanted to do.
"Sakurazuki" is also a song with a
story, so I wanted to make it a little
more fresh.
Also, there weren't many parts with the
3rd generation students in the past
year, so I wanted to make a song with
the 3rd generation students.
I would like to have fun with the fans,
members, and the staff.
To be continued
(Yui's part is coming up)
Yui's part is coming up with the LED on
the 2nd floor
(Yui's part is coming up)
I want you to stop at the sound of the
piano
For the first time, I'll do it as it is.
Ah, I see.
How is it?
It's been a long time, and it feels
different than before.
I love it, too. I'm glad I finally did
it.
The first time I did it was when
Kobayashi-san was on leave.
It was Jamaica Beer, so I have a lot of
memories.
Kobayashi-san had a lot of meetings with
the set list.
I'm happy to be able to do the set list,
but I don't feel it yet.
It's always like that, but when the
graduates are gone and the juniors are
in that position, I feel like I've
graduated.
I don't feel lonely at all.
I don't feel reality at all.
(Clapping)
Over?
Is this a good song?
No, it's a secret.
It's almost time.
It's really sad, and this is the last
show for Yui, so I hope Yui can have a
great time and we can do our best to
make a great show for her.
During the rehearsal, Yui talked a lot
with the live team staff.
I often see Yui talking with the live
team staff, so I want to show Yui's
particularity.
The rehearsal period is shorter than
usual, but I want to concentrate and do
my best.
This time, I'm going to do it at the
Drift Center, where I'm going to be with
Kei-chan.
And then, I'm going to make a car that
doesn't have a front and a rear.
Please look forward to it.
It's a Senpai!
It's time for everyone to spread out.
Let's spread out a little.
As usual.
This is where the screen changes.
0.75, 0.75, 1.5
That's it.
It's here.
Beautiful.
That's it.
When I was in 3rd grade, my teacher told
me that I wanted to do a concert at the
Double Center.
I thought it would be great to do this
song when I graduate.
I think it's perfect for a graduation
concert.
As a 3rd grader, Yui is a senior who
helped me a lot.
I want them to think that they can rely
on their juniors in the future.
I want to be the best self-improvement
I've ever had.
I want to be the best junior I've ever
had.
I want to be cheerful and energetic.
I'm very happy.
I didn't have a song that I could
participate with.
So I'm very happy that Yui is with me
when I'm dancing.
I'm very happy.
I want to make this concert to show my
gratitude.
I want my fans to think that it was a
good concert.
I want to make this concert to show my
gratitude to Yui.
The view is changing.
Oh, I see.
Is this okay?
No, no, no.
Then, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Be kind.
You're supposed to put your hands on it
like this.
Is this really okay?
Put your hands on it.
Put your hands on it like this.
And put your face on it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Lower your eyes.
Not your eyes.
My eyes are so small.
Eyes?
For today,
this is the end of Day 2.
We're going to do a break block.
We're going to fix this connection,
and when we have a little more time,
we're going to do the one-sided part,
and then we're going to move on to the
next part.
Yes, that's it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
That's it.
Please do it like this.
I'm the one who opens the door.
When I got the set list, I thought it
was very Yui-like.
I thought it was great.
We perform together in some scenes.
I want to cherish that.
I've seen only Yui's solo songs in the
music video.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to seeing how she
will perform.
She was the one who I had the most
opportunities to work with since I
joined the company.
I'm grateful to her.
I want to give her a good show with
gratitude.
I think the best thing is to send her a
message with a smile.
Thank you.
Yui.
I hope we can have a live show that
everyone can enjoy.
♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪
Can I put this on my ear?
I will put this on the back of my ear.
Every time, I feel like I'm going to
graduate, but I don't know when it's
going to end.
He was a senior who always showed me on
my back, and he kept pulling my juniors
with his actions.
He was a senior who always showed me on
my back, and he kept pulling my juniors
with his actions.
I thought it was very difficult to
continue to be such a person, and I
thought it was not something anyone
could do.
He was doing a lot of work for the group
to continue to be such a person, and I
thought he was doing it while listening
to us.
I was able to welcome this graduation in
a wonderful way and send it out with a
smile.
I think it's amazing that we were able
to create a perfect stage and send Yui-
san out in the best way possible.
This concert is called "Graduation
Concert".
But I don't feel like this is the last
concert.
But this is the last concert, so I hope
I can do my best so that I won't have
any regrets.
Good morning! We are Sakurazuka46.
The rehearsal has begun.
We are going to start the rehearsal.
How many times do we have to spread out?
We have to go, so we have to spread out
as much as we can.
Jump. Next position.
One, two, next position.
One more time. One, two, bang.
Let's go.
I can't raise my towel yet.
I didn't go to the site the day before.
I went to the site two days ago, checked
it, and took time.
There were a lot of scenes like the next
day's performance.
Thank you for watching.
I'm in a hurry today.
I've only been able to check the set for
one day.
Kobayashi-san was really in all the
songs.
I saw him doing all the songs.
I thought I couldn't be in a hurry.
I'm feeling like I'm hitting him right
now.
The production is amazing.
Kobayashi-san's impressive scenes are
increasing.
There were two main characters.
That kind of thing.
It's not just the fans, but we can see
it.
There's a lot of directing where we turn
to Kobayashi-san and perform.
I don't want to miss any of that.
My goal is to get a good look at
Kobayashi-san.
I want to do my best.
I'm happy to be on stage with you.
It's lonely, but everyone seems to be
having fun.
I had fun, too.
I felt happy.
Every song has the feeling that
Kobayashi-san is making a story.
I think it's wonderful through the
whole.
I want to boast the most.
There is such a person in Sakurazaka.
I want to boast that there is such a
senior.
person.
I want people all over the world to see
it.
I was lonely when I saw Yui on the
screen pretending to look back.
I realized it and saw the stage.
At that time, I was really lonely
because I was going to graduate.
Since I joined the 3rd generation, I
will graduate in about a year.
I learned a lot in a year.
I want to perform all of them at the
concert the day after tomorrow.
I want to give a concert that makes Yui-
san happy,
and I want to give a concert that makes
Sakurazaka-san happy.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you
tomorrow.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is the last performance with Mr.
Kobayashi, so of course I feel lonely,
but now I really want to send it with a
smile from the bottom of my heart, so
I'm really lonely, but I'm looking
forward to the live performance.
But it's still day 1, so I'm looking
forward to it.
I'll do my best.
That's all.
I'm going to watch Kobayashi-san all the
time today.
I'll try not to cry tomorrow.
Kobayashi-san's solo song is going to
make me cry.
I'll start when the audience is sitting.
Then I'll be like, "Wow!"
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
This time, Sanzuki-chan is in the
original formation, so it's fresh and
I'm looking forward to it.
The Jamaica Beer rehearsal color has
been decided, so the costume is perfect,
isn't it?
This costume is definitely for Jamaica
Beer.
Please look at it perfectly.
This is the first live show for everyone
this year.
I think it was a very exciting year last
year.
I want to make it even more exciting
this year.
I think it's Yui's graduation concert.
I think it's the first live show for
everyone.
Let's do our best.
That's how great the seniors are.
I think there are a lot of things to
learn, so I'd like to absorb what
everyone learns in the next two days and
make it a live performance that can be
used for future activities.
So let's all do our best for the next
two days with Yui-chan's back on us.
Thank you.
But I've done a lot of rehearsals.
Are you ready?
That's right.
It's a lot more than usual.
I was able to do a lot of rehearsals,
and I think I've done it twice already.
I don't usually do this, so I feel
pretty safe.
I feel like I'm being careful.
I'm so happy to be able to do
"Love&Rose" for two days.
Actually, we were going to make a heart
together.
I wanted to hug Yui, so we're all going
to hug her.
Is it a surprise?
It's a surprise.
I don't know if she'll be happy, but
it's a surprise.
Good evening, everyone.
I want to burn it.
I want to burn it, but I love solo
songs, so I want to see it from the
audience.
I want to see it from the audience.
I'll burn it.
I want to burn it.
Yui-san gave me a lot of ideas, and I
made each one with a lot of commitment.
I thought it was Yui-san's way of
starting and ending.
I really like it when it starts with
Jamaican beer.
I'm so happy that I want to see Jamaican
beer as a customer.
I don't think everyone expected it.
It's cool.
I thought it was nice to start with Yuu-
san.
It was a song that we couldn't perform
well.
Yuu-san, the center, said, "Let's do it
with three people."
And we were able to perform the first
song.
I'm glad we were able to make a unit
with these three people.
We were able to choose this song as one
of the big events that define the life
of an idol.
I'm very happy about that.
I'll do my best.
If you have that feeling, it's okay.
Let's do our best!
We'll do our best!
Let's go!
Yui-san
I was very happy and lonely at the same
time when I was able to perform with
Umi-san.
But today, rather than being lonely, I
was happy to be able to perform
together.
After all, there are many times when I
think Umi-san is cool.
I think I got a lot of power.
"Once in a Time" is a song about the
life of an idol.
It's a song from the idol's point of
view and also from the fan's point of
view.
There's a link between the two.
I was really happy when we danced
together.
I felt that I should cherish it.
He was very kind when we talked.
She is very reliable and I admire her as
a senpai.
Just looking at Yui-san makes me feel at
ease.
I think she has a wonderful back.
When I joined Keyakizaka, I was in the
"Nensho" group, but I couldn't do much
Nensho-like things.
But after I joined SAKURAZAKA, I felt
that my sisters supported me a lot, and
I was very happy about that.
I was able to be obedient to everyone.
I was able to enjoy more and more.
Because there was a student like me.
I'm glad.
She has been leading us since the days
of Keyakizaka.
She has been carrying a lot of things by
herself.
She was the one who was leading the
group.
Just being in Sakurazaka made the group
strong.
Her performance was so good that even
her brother was impressed.
She was such a great person.
It was so much fun.
It's been a while since I've been with
Nippon.
The moment I was caught by the wind, I
took off my earring.
I thought she would say "Thank you" to
me.
I was so happy.
This is the last one for Yui-san.
I'm going to look at her back with all
my heart.
I want to enjoy Kobayashi-san's
sparkling beauty without any regrets.
Do you have time?
No, I don't.
I haven't had time since yesterday.
I don't know what to do.
I can't hear laughter.
I don't think so.
I don't feel like I'm graduating.
I don't feel like it.
I don't feel it.
It's too much.
I don't feel like it.
I don't know what to do.
I thought it was a big festival.
I thought it was a big stage.
But I think it's the person.
I don't know why.
I can't say anything.
I don't feel like it.
You look cool.
I'm Minami Koiki.
I'm on a break, but I'll do my best.
I need the courage to make my own
decision.
What if...
I don't know what to do if something
happens to me.
But rather than thinking about it,
I want to see Yui's last appearance in
front of me.
She has been leading me from the
previous group.
I want to be honest with her.
I wanted to spend some time with her
until the last moment.
That's all.
Do you like Kobayashi?
Yes.
Me too!
When Kobayashi first joined the team, he
was in high school, right?
Kobayashi, who was in high school,
thought about himself,
looked at the people around him, and
gradually improved his skills.
Now he is a person everyone admires.
I think his path is very cool.
He is shining now, but I think his path
is very cool.
In this concert, there is a saying that
"Kobayashi is the last one, so don't be
ahead of him."
Each song has its own meaning, and the
center of each song is very important.
I think it's important to think about
how to face it while making the center
shine.
I think about both the present and the
future, so please share Kobayashi's
thoughts and make the best thing today.
Congratulations on your graduation. I'm
looking forward to it.
I'm the last one, but I'd like you to
think that you like me, so that you can
convey the charm of SAKURAZAKA.
I want everyone to enjoy it together.
I wish I had eyes.
Thank you for having us.
Today, I'm so happy to be on the last
stage of Yui-san with Min-chan, Rei-chan
and Mion.
I want to have a good time with Yui-san.
I want to have a good time with Yui-san
and Yui-san's fans.
Let's have a good time!
Ouch!
It'll be bad if we're on stage.
It's the last one.
What should I do?
I feel like I'm in a dress rehearsal.
I'm nervous.
You're cute.
You're really cute.
I'm nervous.
I felt a little lonely, but I want
everyone to enjoy it, so I will do my
best to deliver the best live
performance.
I want to make sure that I can remember
the time I spent with this music as much
as possible.
I want to make sure that I can remember
the time I spent with this music as much
as possible.
When Yui graduated, we talked about what
kind of scene we would like to have, and
she said, "I don't know what you're
talking about."
The song "Shinmei no Position" is a song
where Yui's answer is a coincidence.
I want to have a scene where she sings
with me.
I was born because I was told by the
director that I wanted to have a scene
where she sings with me.
When I first received the set list, I
was told, "This is a song for you and
me."
I was told, "This is a song for you and
Are you ready to sing?
Have you forgotten?
More!
Wait until your arms break!
More! More!
"You're a good girl."
I don't say that, but
You don't understand that easily, do
you?
Appearance is a thing that conceals
flaws
What kind of girl am I?
I'm looking forward to it
I'm standing at the bus stop
On the way, you're standing next to me
And you're calling out to me
It's like a dangerous squad
It's impossible, it's disgusting
I'm sorry, I'll follow you
If it's a light prayer, it's easy
I'll invite you to my world
The cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
It was a performance where we were
dancing on the center stage, but it was
my personal favorite performance, and I
was about to cry, but I did it with
tears in my eyes, but there was a place
where we did our hands around the end of
the chorus, but it was also dangerous.
I was so moved that I would cry if I saw
any more.
There were a lot of things.
In the lyrics, the main character thinks
about you and the memories with you.
Until now, I've been doing a lot of
things for you as a person.
I wanted to express the existence of
you.
I thought it would be easier to convey
the world view of the lyrics and the
world view of the song by expressing it
concretely on the stage.
Graduation is also involved, and if I
could leave the part of the person I
loved to me,
I think it would be nice if I could
convey the world view of the lyrics and
the world view of the song.
I want to do my best.
That's what I wanted to say.
Towards the edge of the shade.
The sun is different from yesterday, and
it's a morning I don't want to be
noticed.
From head to toe, I wonder how hard they
worked.
I really think so.
Even when I listen to the song, even
when I watch the dance,
I wonder how much they practiced in a
place where no one is watching.
I wonder how long it took them to face
themselves.
I can feel it even from a distance.
He is a person who gave me the hope that
if I keep working hard, I might be able
to do this someday.
He is always a cool senior.
Even when I watch his performance in the
rehearsal, I can't help but look at him.
I like his performance the most.
When I was watching them from behind, I
was convinced that this group would
never go in the wrong direction.
I was really grateful for their
presence.
I think I was able to graduate because I
was able to convey what I had left to my
juniors.
I'm grateful.
Sankisei joined us a year ago, and the
atmosphere of SAKURAZAKA has become
brighter.
We don't have to get hurt, so I hope you
can have fun and enjoy the group life.
And...
2nd generation.
I feel sorry that I couldn't make you do
what you wanted to do.
I'm so happy that I'm so bright that I
don't feel it.
I'm so happy that I'm getting closer to
everyone.
As Sakurazaka, no doubt.
I think that IKISEI has taken the lead
and made Sakurazaka a group that is
loved so far, so I would be happy if
everyone shared their sense of
responsibility and made Sakurazaka a
group that is loved more and more.
Thank you very much.
And IKISEI.
We've been together every day for 8 and
a half years.
We've been sharing all our feelings.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you
all on TV with a smile.
And to all of you in Paris.
Without you, we wouldn't be here.
I learned why I exist, thanks to all of
you.
I'm not that strange of a person,
but I was doing something that affected
my life.
It was a strange feeling, and I found
myself there.
I'm so proud of it.
Thank you so much for letting me be
myself.
She's such a great person.
I can't imagine what would happen to her
when she left this group.
She's so great that I can't imagine.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
I'm afraid that I'm going to feel it all
of a sudden.
We know that Yui couldn't do anything
for Kisei for a long time.
I'm so grateful that Yui came all the
way here for me.
Thank you so much.
Of course, I do feel that way.
Yui's expression was really clear.
I could see a lot of fun things in the
song.
It's Yui's graduation concert.
I think it was a successful concert with
a lot of things Yui wanted to do.
I think I was able to do that.
When I saw Yui's dress at the end of the
stage, I was full of lonely feelings.
Yui was the senior I longed for the
most, so there was a hole in my heart.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
If someone asks me, I would say "I want
to be Nii-san's idol"
That's my dream
To be honest, I don't really feel it yet
I think it's a cool way of saying it
that's different from being moved
At the end, when I came out in my dress,
everyone was waiting for me
She said, "You're so cool!"
She didn't even cry
She came down the stairs with a smile
I thought, "She's so cool until the end"
You're so pretty!
Really!
I've been looking at you for a long time
You're so pretty
You're so pretty!
You're the prettiest flower in the world
Thank you!
You're so cool!
I wonder what that is
I've been going to say hello to the
graduates and say thank you, but I don't
think it's going to end.
I don't know if I can feel it until the
end.
I don't know if it's too much, but it's
a unique feeling.
I haven't told you anything about what
I'm going to do in the future.
I haven't decided yet, but if I think
about it for a long time,
I'm sure I'll be able to do it.
I hope I can enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Nobody cares about me
I thought you weren't interested
So I was happy that you noticed
Just a little bit
I can't see love
But I feel it when I drop it
When the wind passes by
I can feel the scent of the leaves
I'm not as lonely as I thought
I was walking alone
I might be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
It doesn't make much sense to look
around
Because the sun is moving
Towards the sun
Let's go!
No matter where we are
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
If you take my heart, I'll miss the
flower at your feet
There's someone who'll watch over me,
who's so clumsy
Eternity isn't something you can bloom
It's something you'll only encounter one
day
I'm sure
Ah, that's right, I remember
The season
I was more prepared than I was
I might have been fine
I was surprisingly strong
It's OK
I was more prepared than I was
It's a peaceful everyday
Look up at the sky that's different from
yesterday
Life is like the sun rising, setting,
and setting
Cloudy days are passing by
The happiness now is the path to the
future
Let's do what we want to do and move
forward
Smile
Everyone was afraid
The darkness of loneliness
Even if I'm alone
I can live forever
I'm sure I'll be fine
I wanted the sky
The loneliness overflowing in my lungs
is confusing
Someone's voice, someone's warmth
Saved me from not being alone
Until today
Don't think too much
It's not as lonely as I thought
Even if I walk alone, don't worry
It may be happier than I thought
Let's walk on a different path than
usual
(Even if I walk alone, don't worry)
Anywhere
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[MUSIC]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
I heard that, but...
I told you I didn't want to, but...
I pushed you with a tulip
You don't seem to be wary
I'm a man, after all
Yes, I've been nervous for a while
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough"
I'm sorry for being a little reckless
It's the first time that a meteor has
come
So I haven't been able to calm down
since morning
Even if I suddenly clean it up
It seems like someone is there
I'm opening the door a little
My heart is crying
I wanted you to understand
I'm a beginner
The laundry you started to fold
I hope this time will continue
I'm wandering around
But I was happy
I was happy
Rather than having a special date
I want to spend my daily life with you
My scattered room
So that we can see each other
Become beautiful
What should we do next?
From the other side of this stardust
It is dyed with twilight
When will it rain this time?
Because it's cool
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough"
I'm sorry for being a little reckless
I want to brag to everyone
"Towel"
Everyone, are you ready for the towel?
It's finally started
The first day of the graduation concert
Let's make wonderful memories with
everyone in Paris
Wait for the chime and jump out on the
skateboard
I want to catch up with you on the pony
tail
I can't catch up with you
With my love
I can only see you off
"One, two, three"
From the bus stop
I'm going at full speed
I can't catch up with you
I can't breathe
Come on, fly through the sky
From here, you, you, you, you
Wherever I look for you
Instead of my eyes
Let's control the distance
I want to be looking at you at any time
At the intersection
I see you crossing
Look, I found you
Nice to meet you
I love you
"Doron Doron Senkaiju"
Paris, I'm going to everyone's heart
Like a bird
I cut through the sky freely
I've been aiming for something I
absolutely want
From here, I'm going at full speed
I thought your heart was my number one
priority
"One, two, three"
If I look at you from a distance
At the intersection
Somehow it makes me sad
I'm here, but you don't notice
Ah, my existence
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on
One-sided love
This is love, love, love, love
Look over here
You're too precious
I can't touch you
I want to know more about you
"Parties, are you having fun?"
"Are you having fun?"
"Today is Nippon's graduation concert"
"No one is looking down, right?"
"Let's all have fun until the end!"
Please notice my heart
Ah, you in the distance
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on
Fly in the sky
From here, you, you, you, you
I'm looking for you, wherever you are
Instead of my eyes
No matter how long the distance is, I'll
control it
I want to always be looking at you
Oh oh, at the intersection
Oh oh, as we cross
Oh oh, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh oh, about you
Oh oh, I love you
Oh oh, I want to fall in love from here
"Wait!"
"Yui, say something!"
"One, two!"
"I love you!"
That's the way
The dry leaves flutter, flutter
As they descend from the sky
That's the way
Until they touch the waves
I'll gather up the time
That's the way
The earth is spinning slower than I
thought
That's the way
The words floating in my chest
Gather them up
That's the way
We've known each other for a long time
I wonder why we're friends
I couldn't imagine
The two of us
Looking at each other like that
Even if I'm blown by the wind
Nothing will start
I'll just be carried somewhere
This kind of relationship
Isn't it good sometimes?
Love is something that changes, right?
That's the way
No matter how much I think about it
It can't be helped
That's the way
"Wow! The venue is green!"
"It's green!"
"Everyone, please say 'That's the way'
with this song!"
"Please sing it with a loud voice!"
"Come on!"
I'm swaying in the rain
Like a one-mile wave
That's the way
I couldn't imagine
How you'd feel in the future
That's the way
Why do I miss
This miraculous chance?
That's the way
As time passes, I look back
All I can do is sigh
That's right!
When I suddenly approach you like that
I wonder if it makes you feel awkward
Hey, I know
I don't notice at the entrance
It's easy to fall in love
Even if the wind blows
I can be happy
I just need to be by your side
That's not a bad way to say it
Our love will continue forever
It's not a hug or a kiss
It's so good as it is
If you're swept away by the snow, where
will you go?
On such a dazzling sunny day
Until the fading memories disappear
Let's wait in the air
Life is
(Leave it to the wind)
I have to enjoy it until goodbye
Even if the wind blows
Nothing starts
I just get carried somewhere
Such a relationship
Isn't it good sometimes?
Love is something that goes on, right?
Even if the wind blows
I can be happy
I just need to be by your side
That's not a bad way to say it
Our love will continue forever
It's not a hug or a kiss
It's so good as it is
Translated by Releska