I don't like the beer in Jamaica
I just happened to wait in the fridge
He let me drink it on his own
The expiration date is already over
But all my memories are in the storage
I can't even throw away big tears that
have become beautiful
Ah, if it's a love that's about to be
born,
I won't fall in love from the start
There's no way I can be a single person
If I could see you, I might still make
it in time
Speaking of which is the past,
I wonder what will happen to the two of
us
Translated by Releska
You instinctively realized that you
couldn't go on with her
Love is just a waste of time
A heart that can't keep up with either
It's annoying, it's annoying
Kindness and indifference
It's a woman who can't be distinguished
Ah, if it's enough to cry bitterly
I won't leave you
I'm the worst at forgetting
I'm not good at remembering
What should I do from now on?
If you talk to me politely
Can you give me some accurate advice?
From this room of 1LDK
She's gone
After all, it looks wide
The existence that was lost is big
I want to be spoiled
Jamaica, beer, let's drink
Ah, if it's a love that's about to be
born
There's no way I can fall in love from
the start
There's no way I can become a single man
If it's a regret, da-da-da-da
If it's now, I might still be in time
If I had to choose,
I wonder what would happen to us
(1, 2, 3, 4)
I wonder what it means to become an
adult
Even if I take it seriously,
I won't be understood
Even if I get along well with people,
I don't have to say anything
Now, I'm listening as if I understand
I can't be pushed around like that
If I try to change myself,
I won't be me anymore
Foolish
No matter what I do,
Even if I just do that,
What do I have to put up with?
That's right
Shut up and don't lose
Tell me what you want to say
Even if I just stare at you,
I won't be understood
That's right
If you're angry, then be angry
In fact, just be in a bad mood
Now, I have no choice but to tell you
Rather than being hit,
I'll be hit
It's definitely not good for your body
to swallow words
I'll use my heart somewhere
I'll make it flutter
The things I want to say won't disappear
I'll put it in my pocket
I'll throw away my self-respect
and stand up
I don't care if I'm a genius anymore
No one can see
I'm full of myself
Everyone laughs at me
for my uncool knowledge
I'll do as I please
See?
Don't run away
It's just the beginning
I'm not afraid
I'll be hit
Don't be shy anymore
See?
Anger is a living proof
It's a rope to tie up society
Pull it out and be free
Come closer
What should I do?
Can it be stopped?
Is it over?
I have no choice but to confront each
other
and share my pain
I'm sorry, but I can't let it go
Can it get even hotter?
One, two, three, four
Well, I'll shut up
I want to say what I want to say
I'm a bit shy
I can't say anything
Well, if you're angry, don't be angry
If you're not happy with yourself, you
have no choice but to kill yourself
It's better to be beaten than to be
beaten
If you don't like it, say it clearly
Why don't you turn the table over?
You should say what you want to say
Don't be shy
If you can't convince me, I'll beat you
You have no choice but to hurt me with
words
Each person has different values
Hit each other and decide
It's a violation of the rules to take a
seat and jump out
Don't run away
Even if you keep refusing, it won't end
What are you betting on your heart?
I knocked once, but the door won't open
Don't you notice? Are you ignoring me? I
don't know
There's someone in the room, I feel a
presence
The heartless door knob won't move
Are you not happy that I'm coming?
Are you not welcomed?
So what should I do? Should I go home
like this?
I knocked once, but the door won't open
Don't look forward to it
The world isn't that kind
I'm not trying to convince you
I'm just looking at you
Is this door still closed? Can I open
it?
If you're done with your final warning,
answer me
I don't need an excuse
Yes or no?
Which one?
In life, there's a weapon
that you have to make the biggest
decision
If you're not sure,
don't rush
I don't care which one
Da Da Da
No matter how many times you knock,
the door won't open
The language is different here and there
It's a different world
No one knows what's right
What's important is to break the rule
Just because this door exists
doesn't mean we can understand each
other
We're raising our ears
to that door of our own
Before we know it, it'll be locked
and cut off
6th floor, 6th floor, I knocked,
but the door won't open
Don't you notice? Are you ignoring me?
I don't know, but
there's someone in the room
I can feel their presence
The door knob won't move
Don't let them know
that I'm coming
Don't they welcome me?
Then what should I do?
Should I go home like this?
If I knock one more time,
I'll be cut off
Good evening, BUDDIES!
One, two...
We're Sakurazaka46!
Welcome to the Sobayashi Graduation
Concert!
Welcome!
Thank you for coming to the venue today
to send off the first generation of
Sakurazaka46, Kobayashi Yui.
Thank you.
First of all, I have an announcement to
make.
The members, Koike and Minami, have
suspended their activities at
Sakurazaka46 and are currently on leave.
I hope that Min-chan can rest at her own
pace without rushing.
The members are always waiting for Min-
chan to return.
I hope the fans will continue to watch
over us warmly.
And one more thing.
Thank you very much.
I, Mio Mato, am taking a day off because
of my new coronavirus infection.
Today, I would like to share my feelings
with these three members.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Yes, so...
Finally, it's been 2 days since Yui's
graduation.
Yui-san, how do you feel right now?
Eh, it's like...
It's like...
It doesn't feel real.
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
But it's not over with such a strange
feeling.
I want to cheer up and do my best.
Let's all spend this time carefully.
Akira, how about the last one with Yui?
Well, Kobayashi-san is really...
I've been taking care of her a lot, but
I've always wanted to tell Kobayashi-san
one day.
If you watch the dance practice video of
"Start Over", you'll know.
Do you know that the five of us are
moving in a "pyoko-pyoko" when we do
"2B"?
I know.
It's pretty hard.
And I'm pretty late.
But Kobayashi-san is behind me.
You look fast.
I know.
Kobayashi-san was so close to my nose.
What kind of expression is that?
He was so close to my nose.
Thanks to that, I was able to get to the
destination safely.
If it wasn't for Kobayashi-san, I would
have given up halfway.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad you were behind me.
Thank you very much.
Next is...
Morita Hikaru-chan, how do you feel?
It's the last time I can perform with
Yui-san.
So I want to enjoy each song.
I want to keep in touch with Yui-san.
I think everyone is aiming for Yui-san.
I think the fans are also aiming for me.
Today, I want to look at Yui-san with
everyone and spend this time carefully.
And I want to make a live that makes
Yui-san think that it was the best fun
today,
so I want to do the best live with
BUDDIES.
Are you ready?
Let's do the best live with BUDDIES.
I'm looking forward to your birthday.
Rina of the group is gathering this
time.
I thought about it when I was doing the
convention.
[Rina's snoring is so loud!]
It hurts once, doesn't it?
It's a beautiful time with beautiful
flowers,
and my family is also in the garden.
So, I'm going to take a walk in the
garden.
A few days later, I arrived at the
I was surprised to see a cat on the
street in front of the house.
I heard a cat's name, but I didn't know
what it was.
I'm going to take a walk in the garden.
Let's go home together.
Let's go.
Bye-bye.
It's amazing.
It was good.
I was screaming in the cloudy sky
Is it going to stop?
I don't know what's going to happen
I'm falling in love with you
It might be easier if I just accept it
But I can't say "from my side"
What is not clear is
The weather and feelings are the same
The wind is blowing, I don't know which
way
I don't care if I'm just a friend
So I'll stay inside your heart
When the clouds disappear, I'll wait for
the sun here
Come on, look at me, please
My love is pouring out
Even if I look up, it doesn't change
I'm looking forward to a rainbow
somewhere
Come on, look at me, please
When will that day come?
I have an unbreakable umbrella
So I can meet you right now
No matter what happens, I'll never
change
I believe in eternity
There's no rain that doesn't stop
Everyone says that, but
Is it really like that?
I'm getting more and more attracted to
you
Do I open this door now?
Do I give up?
I'm asking myself, who doesn't care
It's painful, when I think of you
I can't even breathe
I hate halfway, but
I can't decide which way
I don't care if I'm just a friend
I should jump out of anxiety
If I had that courage
Even if it's raining, I'm sure it'll
stop
Without doing anything, I'm being chased
by the hot clouds
I can't tell you
If I had that courage
Even if it's raining, I'm sure it'll
stop
Without doing anything, I'm being chased
by the hot clouds
I can't tell you
If I had that courage
Even if it's raining, I'm sure it'll
stop
Even if it doesn't change, I'm expecting
a rainbow somewhere
Come on, my darling, it'll be painful
When will that day come?
I want to be strong, that's what I think
Right now, I'm going to see you, darling
No matter what happens, I won't be able
to endure
I believe in eternal love
There's no way I can get an answer
That's love
I'm falling in love with you
Even if it's raining, I'm sure it'll
stop
"Rainbow"
I always choose the last subway
So why?
I feel like I'm really alone when I'm
standing in the car
The tunnel in front of the scenery is
like life, and the sound is amazing
If you look down, it will be the last
stop
Even if someone is in the same car
I don't feel any sympathy at all
Ah
I got drunk on the bench at the station
The salaryman said a little
But when tomorrow comes
As usual
I'm buried in the rush hour
I want to go to a world where no one is
I thought that
Was I sick at that time?
When I noticed the glass window, I was
wearing a mask
Why do people still live every day while
enduring?
It was strange to me
It's not that I don't like it
Smiling by force
I don't need happiness
Thank you for watching!
I'm not interested at all
Ah
The important thing is the destination
from now on
This subway
I wonder how far I'll go if I get
carried away
I can't go back anymore
Yesterday, I thought that I wanted to go
to a world I didn't know yet
This world is repeating yesterday
I understand that there is nothing to
make my heart beat
Hey, it's not a hard thing to have to
live
I can't stand it
But I won't die right now
Because if I don't hurry, everyone will
die
Ah...
Ever since I finished my part-time job,
I've always been riding the last subway
When will I be able to choose a
different way of living?
I thought that it was like a world
without anyone
Did I stop at that time?
When I noticed the gloomy glass window,
I put my forehead on it
Even so, why do people live every day
while enduring it?
That was mysterious to me
It's not like I hate anything
I don't need happiness that makes me
smile
I don't have any expectations for my
future life
You are all, all mine
I won't give you to anyone anymore
I won't let you go
Where are you going?
I'll give you a hand
I was in the wolves' herd without a care
I hurriedly pulled your hand and brought
you here
Oh yeah
Because I'm a curious voice
I'm playing here and there
We're all sleeping together
It doesn't matter
I was a fool
I have to do something
I'm sure the world will end
You're all, all mine
I declare it here and now
I have to say it clearly
Because I'll be misunderstood
Because you're all, all my treasure
A special existence created by love
No one can have
All of me
I won't let you touch me
I declare it here and now
Hey, what's wrong?
With a frown on your face, you're
looking at me
Is it stupidity? Or is it going my way?
Oh yeah
I don't want to be bound by anyone
I want to be free, but I'm angry
Because I'm here to protect you, I'm
free
It's lonely to be alone
You know that, don't you?
That's why we're together with someone
Love is surely, surely someone else's
Gently, gently warm it up
Carefully, carefully nurture it
I want to make a beautiful flower
Baby, yes, it's a sweet scent
You and I are both attracted to each
other
A beautiful life, until the end of
eternity
Let's grab your hand and start running
somewhere
So that no one can catch up
You're all, all mine
I'm going to declare it here and now
If I don't say it clearly,
I'll be misunderstood
Because you're all, all my treasure
A special existence made with love
I won't let anyone else
Touch all of me
I'm going to declare it here and now
More!
Last one!
Let's go all the way to the end!
I'm told that I'm a quiet girl
You don't understand that, do you?
Reunion is a thing that hides a
guarantee
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind
of girl I'll be
Hey, hey, if you're standing there,
line up next to me and shout out
It's dangerous, like a scout,
it's definitely impossible, it's
disgusting
I'm sorry, I'll follow you right away
I'm going to declare it here and now
Because you're all, all my treasure
That's right, the button on your shirt
It's like it's fastened to the top
It's a good feeling
Don't decide on a step
Come on, buy a uniform
Let's open it at the station door
It's not a bonus, it's a bonus
Always, either way, I'll be the only one
You can't even fake it, can you?
It's not easy to wander around the image
information
I've experienced it, yeah
A dangerous plan
If you think about it, you can't go to
the beach
I've been going to the gym all summer
That's right, the festival, the
fireworks
I've been waiting for the summer to come
I don't know where to go in a few days
I don't know if anyone else can do it
The price of life
Then I'll tell you to get off here
I'm not a scapegoat
I want to dance with a ponytail
I want to be free
I'm going to ask my friends later
I don't know what to do
Come on, buy a uniform
Let's forget what we were protecting
It's not summer, let's stretch a little
Let's go in a new order, different from
yesterday
It's natural to grow up
Fall in love with something
It's not summer, let's take a break
Let's go in a new order
Someday, I'll notice somewhere
There was no one to take it off
Another relationship
I don't even have clothes to wear
I don't want to lose to the sun that
shines in the sky
If everyone gets tired of dreams
Let's play with a ponytail
I'll entrust you to the crab of love
I'll disappear in the toilet at the
station
I'm not a summer, I'm a man
I always get lost in myself
I can't even put on makeup
I wander around in my imagination
I'm not a summer, let's experience it
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
We are always incomplete.
I want to be in a perfect condition
before my debut.
Every day, I repeat the same lessons,
and sometimes I'm worried if I'm really
moving forward.
I'm sure there's no one who's confident
from the start.
I want to grow up so that I can become a
person who is admired by someone, just
as I longed for Agizaka46.
I wonder if it's okay for me to be here.
Because I'm not used to it, I long for
it.
I was passionate and absorbed.
I don't think I've ever looked forward
like this.
I wanted to join.
Thank you for watching.
I can't sing or dance, so I auditioned
just because I felt like it.
If you have that feeling, you'll be
fine.
Always be beautiful and strong.
Like a cherry blossom, just trust
yourself.
Sake Sakura Saka 46
Manzai!
It's Manzai time!
Who likes who?
It doesn't matter.
The flowers that bloom.
Who can choose?
It's not just one person.
Everyone is doing their best.
I support the flowers.
The place where the light hits.
There are places you don't hit.
The beauty that tries to live hard.
It's Manzai time!
Let's find the limit of the voice.
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed.
Until the day that sweat still opens.
Let's keep shining.
It's Manzai time!
Let's raise one heart.
Just that alone gives me courage.
I can see the autumn from the other side
of the stage.
With the wind and the sun.
I want to raise you.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
No matter what kind of flower it is.
It's different, isn't it?
Until the day that sweat still opens.
The day and the month are different.
Don't compare yourself to others.
Aren't you yourself?
Someday you'll understand your own pace.
The important thing is to be desperate.
To live without hesitation.
I don't want to do what I want to do.
A life without regret.
It's Manzai time!
Let's sing with our shoulders together.
Let's be friends who can't say anything.
Good points and bad points.
Let's expose everything.
I want to be your friend.
Go! Anzen time!
Let's hit the floor and take the rhythm.
Your message.
Let's resonate today.
Let's sing.
Let's get ready for the best.
I want to be a member like that.
Please keep it in your memory.
You're not yet ready.
Put the buds in your eyes.
Believe that big flowers can bloom.
Until the day you graduate someday.
Let me see everything.
It's Anzen time!
Let's sing as loud as you can.
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed.
Until the day you graduate someday.
Let's keep shining.
It's Anzen time!
Let's raise our hearts.
That alone gives me courage.
I can see the waterfall from the other
side of the stage.
I want to raise you
with the wind and the sound of the sun.
Hey!
How are you? I wanted to see you.
I'm not laughing. The sky is so clear.
Hey!
The world hasn't changed at all.
We're still the same as we were back
then.
Hey!
The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers.
Hey!
The green trees, the sun's light.
Let's live.
The foot that took everything
has already passed.
As if nothing had happened,
this earth is peaceful.
Everything is over.
I can't stop here.
Hey!
Let's step forward with our own feet.
My heart is looking somewhere far away.
Hey!
Is there really hope?
If I'm with you, I'm sure I can go.
Hey!
If I'm with you, I'll get there.
Let's walk.
My dreams.
Like a wonder, we are bunnies
Even if we lose something
Tomorrow will come again
The ice will fall
The rain and wind of sadness are
darkness
A new day will dawn
Let's start again from here
It's freedom, because we don't have
anything
We can go anywhere
Let's throw away despair with tears
Yo! I've been waiting for you
To the future, to the future, to the
future
We are friends
Yo! How are you? I wanted to see you
Yo! Let's laugh in this city and sky
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We are the same as we were
Yo! The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the leaking
sunlight
Let's go, let's go, let's go
We are bunnies
Like a wonder, we are bunnies
Everyone, are you having fun?
Everyone, please take a break and
recharge yourselves.
I hope you can enjoy the show with us
until the end.
Well, today is the last day of Yui's
concert.
It's the last day of Yui's graduation
We, the 3rd generation, have a lot of
feelings.
First, I'd like to hear from Yui.
Yui-san.
Yes.
We just performed "ANTHEM TIME" with 3rd
Gen students. How was it?
Thank you very much.
Before "ANTHEM TIME" started, there were
videos of 3rd Gen students'
documentaries and my early videos.
It reminded me of "ANTHEM TIME" when we
were dancing.
It was like energy. It reminded me of
when I first joined the group.
It made me feel nostalgic.
It was fun to be able to do this with
everyone with a smile.
Thank you very much.
We didn't expect to be able to do this
with Yui's graduation concert.
We were very happy to have Yui's
penlight set up for us.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to ask the third generation as
well.
Yu-chan!
I'm Murai Yu.
Today, I was able to perform with the
feeling that I really love Yui-san.
There was a moment when I had an eye
contact with Yui-san during the song at
Anthem Time.
I was really happy from the bottom of my
heart.
And there was a part where I hugged Yui-
san and everyone in the 3rd grade.
I was really happy, but...
I want you to hug me one more time.
Can you do it now?
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
We've been hoping for the third
generation for the past two days.
We've been spoiled by Yui.
I'd like to ask one more person, Airi.
I'm Airi Toriguchi.
During the lesson period,
he brought me a gift in the lesson room.
I was so happy that I went home and said
"Thank you very much" and contacted him
right away.
At that time, he sent me a reply saying,
"Do your best so that you don't overdo
it."
If I say "Do your best" too much, I feel
like I'm going to feel a little
depressed in myself.
I think there is something like that,
but Yui-san's way of conveying it is
really not too heavy and not too light.
It may be a little contradictory, but
it's just the right amount of "Do your
best".
Thanks to those words, I was able to
convey it well.
I'm really grateful.
That's a wonderful story.
Thank you, Airi.
As Airi just said, the three of us have
been working together with Yui for a
year.
She taught us a lot of things and guided
us with kindness.
She is a wonderful senior who makes us
feel like juniors.
Thank you for your kindness.
I'm so happy to be able to be in this
wonderful space with my beloved Yui and
the BUDDIES who have been supporting Yui
for a long time.
I hope we can cheerfully and brightly
send Yui out today.
So, the live performance will continue.
Are you ready to have fun?
Let's have fun with us until the end!
"Destiny"
We'll always be together
I met you in the crowd that day
I don't want to go out to Shibuya
I changed my schedule that day and went
alone
When I got off the train and was about
to go home
I climbed the stairs and met you
For some reason, we laughed
Why are we here?
We were surprised by each other
I'll make sure to calculate all of it
No matter how many times I try, I can't
find the answer
Even if we meet, there are times when we
can't see each other
But somehow, I'm drawn to a mysterious
power
I'm being noticed by those three
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
While walking together towards the
center of the world
If someone sees me, I'll be
misunderstood
I suddenly thought, "Don't be hated"
The fact that we met here must have a
meaning
It's a coincidence
Will you tell me the answer?
Even if I think about it
There are so many things I can't say
But today is different
It's not me
Where does the courage come from?
If it's a coincidence, we'll stay like
this
"It's okay to go out with me, right?"
I tried to put it in words like a joke
But what should I do?
I saw you nodding
Is that serious?
The next time we meet
I want you to hug me
Why am I here? Why am I here?
Surprised at each other
Even if I calculate the probability of
coincidence
I can't answer
Even if we meet
There are things we can't meet
Even so, somehow
I'm drawn to a mysterious power
I'm drawn to that secret
Translated by Releska
I've never liked anyone this much
I feel like that
Rather than hurting myself
"I don't want to hurt you"
I thought to myself
While I was waiting for the final
punishment
The timing was just right
We were facing each other
To the point where we couldn't even feel
the cold
If that's the case, there's no point
Ah, how many days until the graduation
ceremony?
What will change from that day?
It's just that the place we're going to
is going to change
Just having new friends is enough to
keep me going
Leaving behind something precious, I'm
called an adult
The cherry blossoms that think of you,
blown by the wind, soar up in my heart
If only you could stay a little longer
No matter how much I love you, the
seasons pass
In the blink of an eye, they all fall
down
That day was the cherry blossom season
Turururuturu, Turururuturu, Tururururu
What I'm trying to say right now is
I feel like I'm going to say something
else
If you don't reach your goal, you'll
feel relieved
I can't do that
I'm going on a trip to Tokyo
With determination, I want to push your
back
Someday, you'll be able to smile and
think "I'm glad I met you"
Amatsutai Seishun
What are you trying to look cool for?
I'm sick of being alone
At least when I remember you
It was such a beautiful love
I don't care if I'm alone
I want to praise the me who gave it to
you
If I can't be like this
So that there's no flower that keeps
blooming forever
I thought about how to make it beautiful
Fly up in the sky
So that I can remember it many times
Fall slowly and regretfully
So that you don't notice me
While I'm confused
Your voice
Listen to it
I tried to leave it in my memory
Beyond the dark night sky
Certainly, even now
I can see the cherry blossoms in full
bloom
I loved that flower
People
Become an adult
Dreams and ideals
Even if I can't think of them
If I can make such a beautiful flower
Cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up in my heart
If only you could be a little more
cheerful
No matter how much I love you
The season will pass
And everything will fall in a blink of
an eye
Don't cry
Cherry blossoms
Cherry Blossoms
Music by Uratanuki
Illustration by Uratanuki
Movie by Uratanuki
I'm not trying to change this world
The sky I swore to the side that I
didn't know
didn't know is a knife to the universe
The window I closed with the breath and
soul I wanted to exhale
soul I wanted to exhale is a common
sense
Let's change the neck of the heart
Even so, if you want to dream
No! No! No! Don't blame people
Who is the voice reflected in the
mirror?
I'm despairing on my own
Because there is no nature, notice it
already
No! No! No! Even if it's someone else's
fault
There is only one history game
If that's the case, loneliness is a
lamina
No! No! No! Nobody's fault
I try to change my way of living
Is it okay to cry?
I grew up somehow
I'm sick and tired of making excuses
I don't want to hear you cry
No matter how much you hate me, I'll
scream
Is that all there is to it?
If I were to be born again
No, no, no, don't say such beautiful
things
I won't do it, I won't do it, I won't do
it
Even so, I'll live on
Believe in your strength
No, no, no, nobody's fault
No matter how deep the forest is
A single tree will gather and grow
You'll understand when the wind blows
No matter how many times the light and
shadow overlap
It'll become a big forest
Don't blame yourself
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Don't hold a grudge against me
No, no, no, don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
The reason you're despairing
Is because you don't believe in yourself
No, no, no, even if it's someone else's
fault
There's only one thing left to do
If that's the case, I'd rather choose
solitude
No, no, no, nobody's fault
Translated by Releska
I was watching TV on my phone
There's no way I'm going to be hated
I was late for everything
I skipped class again today
I should've just given up on love
I'm going to do it, I won't do it, I
won't do it, I won't do it
What do you want to do? What do you want
to do?
You're tired, aren't you? You're not
waking up
While you were playing games
You became an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why is it so boring?
Wait a minute
You're still the same
I'm the only one who knows the power of
life
Even if I'm judged, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told I'm no good
It's not like I can be a different
person now
Even if I'm judged, even if I'm
forbidden
Even if I'm told I'm no good
I get it, I won't regret it
God, is there something I can't do?
I wonder if that's the standard
Hey!
The sand of the time we spent together
Disappears without knowing anything
When I became that age
I thought I could do anything
What am I doing here?
I'm the only one playing
Someone tell me
Is it something that has to change?
I'm about to die
I was disqualified
What should I do if I get punched?
I just didn't know
One more time
Give me a chance to start over
What should I do if I get punched?
Is it a mistake?
I believed that it was for the sake of
my sister
Please forgive me for this
I didn't know it would be so sudden
Hey!
The sun is too bright
It leaks from the bottom of the wind
Until the darkness comes
I can still make it
Even if I get punched, even if I get
disqualified
Even if I'm told it's no good
It's too late
There's no way I can become a different
person
Even if I get punched, even if I get
disqualified
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I won't throw it away again
God, what is it?
Can't I run away?
I wonder if that's the standard
Even if I'm driven into a situation I
want to know
I'll definitely get punched
Hey!
God, what is it?
I don't know
Even if I get punched, even if I get
disqualified
Even if I'm driven into a situation I
want to know
I'll definitely get punched
Hey!
"Wandering"
The city goes crazy with the digital age
Oh oh oh oh
It's so annoying
Even if it's messaged in such a hurry
Oh oh oh oh
A short-term sense of reality
The world is always creative
I keep screaming "I love you"
I, I, me
Can can
Is there anything you want to tell me?
I can't be replaced by anyone
You, you, you
Jump Jump
Hey, I wave my hand in my heart
Do you know I'm here?
(Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce)
Everyone is too strong to be a witness
Can't you believe in yourself?
I want to see more, but I can't stop
SNS
I'm saying I'm watching you
(Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce)
Listen to me, nod more
I want you to praise me
What is different from others?
You are only you
A special existence called "me"
When will you notice me?
Hey, what's wrong with you?
I can see it in your eyes, you know
The same thing for both of us
Misunderstandings, we were mad
We were always like this
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind
Shut up, I'm so confused
Jump, jump
I'm trying so hard to live
But no one understands me, is it a
trial?
I run away at night, I can't catch up
Jump, jump
Hey, communication
What should I do with my efforts?
Jump, jump, jump, jump
It's a victim, that's what it is
I'm looking after you
If I'm accepted by someone, it's a
terrible mistake
I don't want to lose you
Tears won't stop coming
I won't let you go
I'm going to die
Why? I don't have any hope
I'm always like this
Hey, hey
I don't care who it is
(I don't, I don't)
Everyone is too strong to admit
Is that all you can do for yourself?
I want to see more, I want to see more
SNS
I'm telling you I'm watching you
But you're greedy
Listen to me, nod more
I want you to praise me specifically
You're different from others, you're
selfish
You're just you
(I don't, I don't)
I've got the hang of it
Jump until your legs are torn
Jump, jump, jump, jump
Come on
You can still go
Jump, jump, jump, jump
Hurry up
Come on
Jump, jump, jump, jump
Hurry up
You can still go
Jump
(I don't, I don't)
Do you have a dream or something?
I'm sure there's a reason why you want
to do it someday
I don't want to do this tomorrow
So don't sleep
People all forget what they don't want
If you get over today
Let me hear you say "I'll do it somehow"
At night like this
In the convenience store microwave
Warm your lunch
What kind of miracle are you waiting
for?
I'm sure you know
That you're giving up before you know it
But
Pretend you don't notice
Stand over
If you think you're going to do it again
Now is the only time
There's no turning back
Wake up, the you who's running away
In the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to laugh or lose
But the moment I open the door
I can't stand it
What's important is
Where to start over
That's a few seconds before you give up
Then what am I?
Can I say anything about anyone?
I don't know, I don't know
I want to be safe
Like a critic
Look from above
What should I do?
Let's get out of the warm environment
Even if I fail anyway
I want to be a good person
Rather than being protected by a
security camera
I just want freedom that no one can see
I wonder if I can sacrifice anything
It's better to be a two-faced coward
So don't worry about other people
Make it, make it
Until today, I didn't have anything
It doesn't matter
Don't be mean
Don't be cool
If I wake up, I'll be a two-faced coward
Even if I'm energetic
I'm not stupid
I'm a little better
Baby, hey
Toward you
I want to be a good person
In the end, I'm just a nuisance
Translated by ST Translates
I'll be there for you in the future
Anyway, self-destruction
The lump of time
Start over, start over
If you think you can do it again
There's no other way but now
Wake up your sleeping eyes
The reality reflected in the glass
window
Makes my heart unable to turn my back
But the moment I opened the door
There was no other way
What's important is
Where to start over
That's what I thought a few seconds ago
"Self-Destruct"
The gap in my heart
Where does it come from?
I've been hurt before I knew it
I've been lonely and sighed
Only my broken heart
Is slowly getting buried
I can't notice it
With a quiet force
I pull my legs
I can only feel it
With a faint wind
I've been looking at something dazzling
I'm getting dizzy
I just need to close my eyes for a
moment
It will be easier
It's not a big dream
Do I have to see it?
Even if I just pretend to be like that
I hate myself
Yes, I'm like this
I can't convince you that I'm different,
but I'll ignore the world and go around
If that's the case, don't know me
forever
Don't say "I love you"
I'm crying without a sound in the gap
I don't feel it because I'm used to
being hurt
If you want to know anything, you can
say it yourself
I don't understand the obvious
Every time I breathe
I've been hiding what I'm running away
from
It's like a hope that I secretly sucked
in
I can't tell anyone
I'm sure there's something in my heart
I don't know, little by little
I feel like I'm drowning in words
If you don't mind, open that hole wide
A little bit of this chest
Get out of the wind
A gap in the back of my chest
Where does it come from?
I hurt myself before I knew it
I'm lonely, I'm worried, I'm out of
breath
Only this is leaking little by little
With a quiet power that I don't notice
I pull my feet
I only feel a faint wind
Translated by Releska
I don't want to be noticed by the sun
that is different from yesterday, which
dawns as if it were a dream
There are so many kind words on the
floor
Even if I touch it, I close my eyes
without picking it up
We were just waiting
What kind of reason is there?
It's too late to ask
I'm getting sick of myself
I know the truth
Let's shine our eyes so much
The days when we talked about our dreams
Even if you don't want to say goodbye
I can't say it
I know how many
Memories are scattered
I can't sort out love
How long will the sadness be kind?
Don't look back anymore
Until the day we can meet again
When I opened the last door
I was exposed to a dazzling light
That I couldn't reach
I couldn't see anything
What was outside until now
The world I've always believed in
Whose thought was it?
It's like something was wrong
The way to stop it
I don't think it's left anymore
The time I've been eating here
For a new dream
Even if I hurt my wings in an unfamiliar
city
I hope you won't come back
If I can do something
I'll do anything
I don't need you anymore
I've decided to live alone
I've become more compassionate than
anyone else
I just look up at the far sky
I don't want to get in the way of the
future
Let me forget today
I've been watching from afar
If I can do something
I'll do anything
I don't need you anymore
I've decided to live alone
I've become more compassionate than
anyone else
If you say goodbye
I can't say it
I know how many
Memories scatter
I can't get love
How long will the sadness be kind?
Don't look back anymore
Until the day we meet again
Translated by Releska
I really joined when I was in the first
year of high school,
so all my youth was here.
I didn't know how to live other than
here.
I'm 16-year-old Yui Kobayashi in the
first year of high school.
I'm a normal girl who grew up in a
normal family.
Someday I want to be someone
who can be admired by someone.
I don't know what it's like to be an
idol.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm getting emotional.
I'm like, "Oh!"
I'm not very good at telling people
about myself.
I'm not good at showing myself.
But if I can convey it to the people who
can convey it...
I want to convey it to the people who
To the members who have overcome many
things so far...
I want to convey it to the people who
can convey it.
Thank you.
I will graduate from this group.
I look forward to working with you for
the rest of my life.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
I think I've done everything I can, so
I'm satisfied.
I'll do my best.
(Applause)
(Music)
Yeah
Once again, I'm Yui Kobayashi from
SAKURAZAKA46
Thank you to everyone who came to see
Kobayashi Yu's graduation concert and
watched the live stream today.
It feels like this day has finally come.
It's been about two months since I told
you about my graduation.
It's been two months for me, and I've
had a really good time.
I've been able to spend every day of my
life taking great care of the group's
activities, and I'm looking forward to
today.
What are you doing here?
I've been thinking a lot about what to
talk about, but there are some parts
that are not very organized, so I think
there are some parts that are not
organized for a long time, but I would
be happy if you could listen to it while
sitting down.
First of all, can I borrow this place?
First of all, I would like to express my
gratitude to everyone who supported me.
First of all, Sankisei.
The 3rd generation came in a year ago,
and the atmosphere of SAKURAZAKA became
even brighter.
The 1st and 2nd generation are really
cute, and they are very important.
From now on, I don't have to worry or
get hurt.
I hope you enjoy your life as a group.
Thank you for coming in.
And...
I'm Mikisei.
Miki-sensei really came to me as a
keyakizaka at first,
and I felt that I couldn't let her do
what she wanted to do.
I felt sorry for her for coming to me at
first.
She came to me at first, but she was so
bright that I couldn't feel it, and when
I noticed it, she started to play with
me a lot, and I'm so happy that I'm
getting closer and closer to everyone.
As a member of SAKURAZAKA, I'm sure
Mikise will take the lead and make
SAKURAZAKA a group that is loved so far.
Mikise is always full of gratitude, and
I think that's what I'm going to
graduate from today and Mikise is going
to take the lead and lead the group.
We all share a sense of responsibility.
I hope everyone will continue to love
Sakura Zakawa.
Thank you very much.
And...
Ikkisei.
I think that the remaining members are
very mysterious.
But they all have a lot of guts and are
kind.
They are good people who can think of
people's feelings.
Thank you very much.
You've been with us for a long time, and
I think you've done a great job as a
group of young girls.
I'm really grateful.
We've been together every day for eight
and a half years, and we've been able to
express all of our feelings.
We've been together for eight and a half
years, and we've been able to express
all of our feelings.
I hope that we can continue to have fun
and be happy in the future.
I'm looking forward to seeing you on TV.
Thank you very much.
And...
The staff...
To be alone with the staff,
I was supported by a lot of people.
I can't talk to the members much.
It's better to talk to an adult.
I had a lot of feelings of comfort, and
I was supported a lot, and I was
answered to a lot of selfishness.
I was a high school student, but I think
it was the staff who raised me in this
world.
Really.
I want to say thank you for supporting
me as a child for a long time.
And I can't always say thank you to my
family, even though they came here
today.
I would like to tell you
Really
Without denying my feelings
My family has always been on my side
I want to tell you a lot of things
So I want to say thank you for letting
me be spoiled
and I hope you'll continue to spoil me.
That's all. Thank you very much.
And to all the Buddy's,
sorry to keep you waiting.
I wonder how many of you have been
supporting me since the time of
Keyakizaka.
Of course, some of you may have left us
during the time of "Kaimei".
I'm sure there are some BUDDIES who fell
in love with me because they got to know
the charm of SAKURASAKA and became
SAKURASAKA.
Each and every one of you gave us a lot
of love in your own way.
Thank you so much.
If it wasn't for all of you, we wouldn't
be here today.
I was able to know the reason why I
exist.
One blog, one talk, one selfie, everyone
was so happy
Even though I'm not that kind of person
I was able to do something that could
have an impact on a person's life
I was able to have a very mysterious
feeling and I was able to exist there
I'm very proud of that
Thank you so much for letting me be who
I am
It's been a long time, but I'm really
grateful to so many people.
8 and a half years.
What is it?
It was very hard, of course.
It was really fun.
It was fun to be able to perform with
everyone like this.
Thank you.
I had a lot of fun being in the dressing
room with the members.
I think that time was youth for me.
When I remembered the youth in everyone,
I thought of Yui Kobayashi.
I'm happy just to be remembered, and I'd
be happy if I could be a little bit in
the corner of everyone's memory.
Well, isn't it a little organized?
I've been supported by a lot of people
for 8 and a half years, and I'm happy to
be here today.
I was able to live.
Thank you very much.
So, I think I'll call the members.
Are you there?
Yes.
Ah!
I'm here.
Welcome back.
Wow.
I'm alive.
I was listening to all the speeches.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I didn't get to hear all of
them.
I think Yui-pon's feelings were conveyed
to a lot of people.
Thank you.
How do you all like Yui-pon's dress?
It's beautiful.
It's Yui-pon-like.
It's fashionable.
That's right.
It has flowers on it.
I like it.
The fabric is also leather.
Yes, it is.
It's a little different design from the
ones we've seen so far.
I think it's a good one.
Yes, it is.
It's cute.
So, the three of us will be the MCs from
now on.
Yes.
I'd like to talk to you a little bit.
So, Yuipon, you showed us the solo song
"Kimi ga Sayonara Ietatte" yesterday.
Yes.
How was it today?
Yesterday, I felt like I was doing my
best, but today, I felt like I was
walking forward without looking back.
I think I was able to sing with that
kind of feeling. Thank you very much.
That's great.
Everyone was looking at us.
It's embarrassing.
Rina, this is the last time we're going
to have a concert with you.
How do you feel?
I haven't realized it yet.
But I was often behind Yui-pon rather
than next to her.
I was often dancing while looking at
Yui-pon, so I had that song today, and I
was thinking, "Is this the last one?"
I remembered that I learned this
choreography from Yui-pon, and I danced
a lot in front of Yui-pon in terms of
performance.
I'm so grateful to Yui-pon for taking
care of me, and I'm so happy to be able
to send Yui-pon, who has been working
hard for 8 and a half years, to such a
wonderful graduation concert in a
beautiful way.
Thank you.
How about you, Fuyu-chan?
I'm really grateful to Yui-pon.
To be honest, I don't think I've been
able to show my cool back to my juniors.
Yui-pon has been standing in front of me
for a long time as a first-generation
student.
Do you have it?
He has always shown the correct way of
being to all of the members.
To be honest, I think I've had the
timing to think about graduation several
times in the last 8 and a half years.
But I'm really grateful that he's still
here today.
I'm grateful for that, and I'm proud to
be a member of IKISEI.
I can only say thank you.
Thank you.
That's how we feel.
That's how IKISEI is now.
I'd like to sing one more song, but
before that, there's one more IKISEI.
She's here today.
Can we all call her?
Let's call her.
One, two...
Mii-chan!
It's been a long time.
I'm Minami Koike.
I'm taking a break now.
I'd like to see the last of Yui-pon.
I wanted to be on stage with you.
Thank you.
Then, the four of us will play that song
for the last time.
Music, start!
Yeah, I'll go close to everyone.
Hi, everyone.
Which way are you going?
Wait for me.
I'll go close to everyone.
Hello.
Thank you.
I'll go close to everyone.
All right.
Let's go.
Time machine.
Yeah!
(Music)
How are you?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Let's go back to that time while saying
hello.
Yeah!
What have you been doing since then?
We can't get in touch with each other.
Yeah!
I can't believe we're meeting in a place
like this.
Yeah!
It's a miracle.
It's an unbelievable certainty.
Yeah!
Let's go on a time machine.
I still can't forget the time when I
loved you.
Let's go on a time machine.
(ai sareta jidai ni naru) The
era of being loved will come to an end.
I love you (mou modorenai I love
you) I can't go back, I love you
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
! (minasan no koe
takusan kikasete kudasai!) Please let me
hear everyone's voice a lot!
! (arigatou!) Thank you!
Yeah!  Yeah! Sayonara
nante ittandarou Yeah! Why did I say
goodbye?
douka shite itanda What was I
doing?
It's all because of me that day
Yeah!
Let me say "I'm sorry"
It's too late now, but
I've always wanted to apologize
Yeah!
God!
I didn't throw it away
Thank you, for meeting you again
Time machine, anywhere
I'll go find love
The two of us in the picture from that
day
Time machine girl
I know
I can't tell you
I miss you
mou ichido Once again
Let's do it again
Let's overwrite our lives
If I had a time machine
I would be able to cope with this pain
Let's ride on the time machine
I still haven't forgotten the times when
I loved you
Let's ride on the time machine
I still haven't forgotten the times when
I loved you
I love you
Let's ride on the time machine
Thank you very much!
I was really happy to be able to listen
to that song with all four of you.
And from now on,
Reina and Mio came to the encore!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Let's spend the rest of the time
together.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
So, in a blink of an eye, two days are
about to end, but Yui-san, how do you
feel now that you've come this far?
I'm very satisfied.
Thank you.
Today's live was really fun, and
yesterday's live was fun, and I'm really
satisfied.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that from Yui.
I'd like to ask the members.
Ten-chan, what do you think?
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
Well...
Yes, well...
Yes, that's right.
Second generation.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Second generation.
Since I was a child, I have been
admiring and admiring Keyakizaka.
I am very happy to be able to sing and
dance next to such a person.
Thank you.
Just having Yui-san by my side makes me
feel at ease.
When she's in front of me, I feel like
my back is too big and I'm desperate to
follow her.
But her back is so cool, so we can learn
a lot from her.
I learned a lot from Yui's dance, her
expressiveness, her acting, her work as
a model,
and she led the group in many aspects.
I'm worried that I won't be able to come
back with Yui from the next single.
When I think about it, I feel a lot of
anxiety, but when I graduate and look at
it from the outside, I want to do my
best so that people will think that I
have become a little stronger, or that I
have grown up.
I hope that Yui's life from now on will
be a life full of happiness.
We are also supporting Yui with all our
might, so I love you.
Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you for telling me a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I have another question for Hono-chan.
I've been thinking a lot about what to
talk about,
and I thought about this.
It's very similar to Ten-chan.
I'm glad that we're together.
I've been watching Ikisei-san and
Yuupon-san in front of the TV.
Even if I'm doing a live show,
I want to share the same pain, the same
joy, the same sadness, the same
happiness, and the same smile with you.
I want to make a lot of songs, do a lot
of live shows, and rehearse together.
We did a lot of lessons together, and
the number of times we said "the same"
and "together" increased a lot, and I
was really happy about that.
For us juniors, that time is a great
asset, and we had a lot to learn from
each other until the very end of the
day.
We want to continue to connect with
Sakurazaka46, who loved us so much until
the very end,
and we want to do our best so that
Yuipon-san and BUDDIES can think that
this group is still fun.
Thank you so much. I love you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure everyone has their own feelings
about Yui.
Yui has a lot of past photos on VTR.
Looking at that, there was a time when I
didn't know her.
When we were working together, I was
also full of myself.
That's why Yui...
I really can't imagine what kind of
things she had to carry and what she had
to think about when she was working.
I'm sure there were times when she
worked hard while holding it all to
herself.
She carried a lot of things and kept
pulling the group together.
Even when she became Sakurazuka, she
continued to do it.
We have something to aim for.
We have been able to pursue our cool
appearance and back.
I think that's why we have the current
Sakurazuka.
I think there are many people who have
taken their eyes off us in our
performances.
In terms of the performance of
"SAKURAZAKA",
Yui was there, so the power to raise it
was really amazing.
That's why I think we have to work
harder from now on.
Yui showed us a lot of cool back,
so we should aim for it.
Thank you very much.
I'm not aiming for it, but I have a
desire to achieve it.
I'm sure it will be there forever.
If we keep improving ourselves,
I'm sure what Yui left and showed us
will live on in Sakurazaka.
I'm really grateful for Yui's activities
so far.
I'm afraid that time is running out, and
I'm worried that I'm going to be active
without Yui, but I'm going to get over
that anxiety and work together again.
I want to do activities that can exceed
Yui's and everyone's expectations.
And I got an encore from everyone.
Can I perform one more song?
Thank you very much.
I hope everyone here can see Yui's
figure and enjoy this time together.
Everyone, can you make the siren pink?
Thank you.
That was fast.
Since we're already here,
Yui-san, can you play the song for us?
Yes, I'll play it for you.
One, two...
"Sakurazaka no Uta"
I thought ordinary days were not natural
I couldn't meet you until today
There was a hole in my heart
Who is the real loneliness?
It's not that there's no one else
It's just that there's no one else
The fact that I can't see the person I
love
I don't know what happened
But I'm sure you can overcome it
The day of the full bloom cherry
blossoms
I've never forgotten
Even if spring passes and flowers fall
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that I can suddenly remember
We gather here
If I can talk about you
I feel like I can meet you again
There were sad things that no one could
tell
I was looking at you from afar and
worried
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to stand up
Oh, oh, oh
The day of the full bloom cherry
blossoms
I was blown by the summer, fall, and
winter winds
What was I waiting for
On that branch of a wild rose?
Even if people who pass by
Forget the flowers of that day
The scenery of the next spring
We'll always remember
Oh, oh, oh
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
My heart trembles with nostalgia
Like the petals of each flower
Cherry blossoms will be in full bloom
Oh, oh, oh
Thank you for coming to Kobayashi's
graduation concert today.
I've been with Sakurazaka46 for 3 years.
I really love this group.
I think it will be a group that everyone
will love in the future.
Everyone, please continue to support
Sakurazaka46.
Thank you very much.
Take your time, you'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'll hurry up.
Take your time.
Is this okay?
Yes, that's perfect.
Thank you very much.
From the 3rd generation.
And the representative.
Mio.
Then, the 3rd graders, please come
closer.
Yui-san.
I think it's the last time we can work
together.
I'm really lonely and my heart is about
to be crushed,
but I'm also about to be crushed
tomorrow,
and if I think that Yui-san won't be
here from tomorrow,
I'm really lonely and I'm filled with
lonely feelings,
but Yui-san...
No matter where I live, not on Earth,
but on Mars or somewhere I don't know,
I'll always admire you and love you.
From now on, I'll remember the time I've
spent with you.
I'll make sure to take what you've left
behind.
I did my best.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
I wish you happiness.
Yes.
Thank you.
I did it.
Thank you!
Congratulations!
Thank you...!
Thank you!!!
Let's move on to the second-year
students.
I'll represent the second-year students.
Hikaru-chan, please.
Yui-san, congratulations on your
graduation.
It's really beautiful.
I'm happy.
Since the second-year students joined
us, they have taken great care of us.
There are many members who have been
helped by Yui-san, and I am one of them.
Yui-san's presence is really big for the
group and for the members.
I'm really sad that she'll be gone from
tomorrow.
But more than that, I'm very grateful.
As I said in my speech,
I was told that I couldn't do anything
for them.
Rather, there are so many things they've
done for me.
I don't know if I can express how
grateful I am.
We're really grateful.
I was really happy and happy that Yuu-
san was smiling and looking happy at
today's live.
The rehearsal period of this live was
also spent very Yuu-san-like.
Yuu-san's back was big, and it was very
Yuu-san-like.
I think that's what I like the most, and
it was a period of time when I was
struck by the fact that I was cool no
matter where I went.
I think that there are various things
that Yuu-san will graduate from now on,
but when I look at it from the outside,
I think that's what I like the most.
We will do our best so that you can
think that it was good to leave it to
us, so please come to the live show
again.
I really love you. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I had fun.
I love you.
Thank you.
I was too moved to get flowers.
Next, please send a message to the
first-year students one by one.
Thank you for your hard work for 8 and a
half years.
I think I was able to do a lot of things
for the first-year students because they
were unreliable and unreliable members.
But you've been doing your best so far,
so I think this group has continued, so
thank you very much.
I'm rooting for you from now on.
Thank you very much.
Yuinpon, yes.
I'm really sorry that I couldn't be with
you until the end.
I'm really full.
I think there were a lot of things that
I couldn't notice about Yuinpon or
Yuinpon.
I've been thinking a lot about what I
can do for Yuinpon.
Sometimes, Yuinpon comes to me and
pamper me.
I think that's what I can do.
I thought it would be nice if there was
a place where I could be pampered.
I don't rely on her at all.
I treated Yuinpon as my sister.
Yuinpon!
I'm really sorry, but I'm really happy
that I was able to make a lot of
memories with Yukon and get active.
There are many things that will be new
year after the cherry blossoms have
fallen.
I don't say anything to each other, but
I think that it is connected in the
performance.
That's what I want to say.
I was very happy and motivated to do
activities.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
Even after many years and decades,
there are such wonderful members.
I want to be remembered by them.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Yui-san, thank you for your hard work
for 8 and a half years.
Please support Kobayashi Yui-san who is
going to take a new path.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you for coming to the venue and
watching the live stream today.
I'm really happy to be able to spend
these two days with you and have fun
with you.
I hope that the members will be happy
that there is a lot of happiness waiting
for Yui's future.
BUDDIES, together with us,
I'm really looking forward to it.
I would be happy if you could support
Yui-san together.
And SAKURAZAKA46 will also move forward
with strength.
Support for SAKURAZAKA46 and support for
Kobayashi Yui-san!
That's all! We are SAKURAZAKA46!
Thank you very much!
Translated by Releska