Today is Sakurazaka 46th.
Thank you for coming to SAKURAZAKA 46
ARENA TOUR 2024 in Tokyo Dome for the
2024 FOURTH ARENA TOUR.
Thank you for coming to SAKURAZAKA 46
ARENA TOUR 2024 in Tokyo Dome for the
2024 FOURTH ARENA TOUR.
We would like to invite you to the
venue.
Before the concert begins, we have a
request for our audience.
Please refrain from ringing and using
cameras, video cameras, or any other
type of recording device, including
binoculars with recording functions,
inside the venue.
People are also asked to refrain from
using mobile phones in all seating
areas.
Please switch all phones to silent mode
so they do not emit any sounds.
Photography, recording, and recording in
the audience will be strictly
prohibited.
Eating and smoking in the audience will
be prohibited.
Please eat and smoke only at designated
places.
Eating and smoking in the audience
seating area are also prohibited.
People are asked to eat and smoke only
in the designated areas.
It is dangerous to leave your seat and
run forward.
Throwing things to the stage is very
dangerous.
It will also be a nuisance to other
customers, so please do not do it.
Please wear a mask again.
Please place your handkerchiefs,
sketchbooks, and uchiwa at chest level.
and other such items be hung or held no
higher than the chest.
There may be times during the
performance when the emergency lights
and aisle lights will be turned off due
to the nature of the performance.
Staff will assist with evacuation
procedures in the event of an emergency,
so people are asked to check the
locations of the nearest emergency exits
in advance.
There will be cameras for recording,
streaming, and photography.
Please note that you may be shown in the
video.
Please wait a moment until the
performance.
Please note that you may appear in such
videos and photographs.
We would like to ask you for your
understanding and cooperation.
The performance will begin shortly.
Thank you for waiting.
"Sakurazaka 46"
Thank you very much for coming to
"FORCE ARENA TOUR 2024 SHIN
SAKURAZENSEI"
"GONE BACK IN TOKYO DOME".
I'm Ten Yamasaki of "Sakurazaka 46".
I'm Shizuki Yamashita of "Sakurazaka
46".
Before the performance, I would like to
ask the audience for guidance.
The camera in the venue, video camera,
recording function with binoculars, etc.
Recording equipment.
Please refrain from using it with fire.
Also, please refrain from using your
mobile phone in the audience.
Please set your mobile phone to "manner
mode" and make sure it doesn't make any
noise.
No photographing, recording, or video
recording is allowed in the audience.
No eating or performing is allowed in
the audience.
Please eat and perform at the venue.
Thank you for watching.
The act of running away from your own
seat and throwing things towards the
stage is very dangerous, and it will be
a nuisance to other customers, so please
do not do it.
Also, please hold a towel, sketchbook,
and a fan at the height of your chest.
For the sake of performance
During the performance, there is a
chance to turn off the emergency and
guidance lights in the venue.
When the emergency occurs, the staff
will evacuate and guide you, so please
check the emergency exit nearby in
advance.
Video recording
There will be a camera for live
streaming and photo shooting.
Please understand in advance in case the
appearance of the audience is reflected
in the video.
After the performance, there will be a
regular meeting.
Please wait in your seat until the staff
instructs you.
Then, we will soon start the
performance.
BUDDIES, are you excited?
BUDDIES, are you ready?
You can still shout, right?
TOKYO DOME, let's get excited!
I want to do my best with all of you
today.
Thank you for coming today.
And we have a live broadcast today.
Let's get excited together.
Thank you for coming today.
By the way, I have a question.
Is there anyone who came to Sakurazaki's
live for the first time?
I think there are about 10,000 people
today.
I'm so happy. Thank you for coming
And this time, we have foreign BUDDIES.
Hello, BUDDIES.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you for coming today.
I hope we can have fun together.
Let's ask the members.
Yuzu.
Are you having fun?
I'm having fun, too.
This time, we have foreign BUDDIES.
I'd like to say hello in English.
I'd like to say thank you to all
BUDDIES.
We will show you the best stage.
Let's enjoy and have fun together.
Let's have fun together.
Next is Karin.
I'll speak Korean.
Hello.
Thank you for coming today.
Let's play together until the end
Thank you for coming today, let's have
fun!
Let's have fun!
Let's have fun together!
Next is Hono-chan!
Tokyo Dome is amazing!
It's really 360 degrees, and today we
sold out all seats including the
additional back seats!
I'm really happy that you brought me to
this place, and I'm really happy that
you came with me.
I'm really happy.
But I still have a long way to go.
You always tell me that I can go
anywhere with everyone.
I really believe in that.
I want you to keep up with us.
First of all, I had a lot of fun today.
I want to make today an unforgettable
day.
I'm looking forward to it. Thank you.
As Hana-chan said, I want to spend an
unforgettable time with everyone here
today.
It's heavy.
The Tokyo Dome is big, so I think it's
physically far away.
But the distance of my heart is zero.
That's right.
I'm here. I'm here.
I really want to have fun with everyone
here today.
Are you ready to enjoy the Tokyo Dome?
Let's all have fun!
Tokyo Dome
If that's the case, I'd rather choose
solitude
No, no, no
Nobody's fault
Trying to change the way I live
There's no way I can do it
Before I knew it, I've become an adult
All I do is make excuses
I want to hear what you have to say
No matter how much you hate me, I'll
still shout
Whether I want to do it or not, that's
all
If I could be reborn
No, no, no
Don't say such beautiful things
Even if I wash it, even if I wash it, it
won't fall
Even so, I'll live
Believe in my strength
No, no, no
Nobody's fault
No matter how deep the forest is
I feel like I can take one step forward
When the wind blows, you'll understand
Love and shadow overlap again and again
It's going to be a big forest
If you blame yourself
Oh
No, no, no
No matter whose fault it is
Don't hold a grudge
Oh
No, no, no
Don't blame others
Who are you reflected in the mirror?
The reason you despair
Is because you don't believe in yourself
No, no, no
Even if you blame someone
One thing remains
It's a story game
If that's the case
Loneliness is tears
No, no, no
Nobody's fault
"Precious"
You can't tell anyone what's important
If you let your heart out, it'll rot in
an instant
No matter how beautiful the words you
choose
They'll turn into something as painful
as sadness
Even though everyone believes in love
If you let your heart out
It'll become a weakness
So I'll throw my heart away
Yes, I'll be a man who doesn't fall in
love with anyone
I'll act like I don't care
I'll act like it doesn't matter
I want to look away and be confident
Even if you look at me like that
I'll become uninterested
I'll keep resisting
I don't want to be an adult
I want to be a fool like this
I want to change
My true feelings
I want you to notice
"Precious"
I'll always keep my heart tight
I'll make sure no one can touch it
I don't want to be forgotten by anyone
around me
I can be lonely, but I can also be happy
Kindness and love
Can become a knife that can't be seen
I don't even know how to be by your side
I'm hurting you
I didn't know that
Yes, the distance between people
It's more difficult than I thought
If you tell me to protect you
Of course, I can't do it
I've lived without feeling any emotions
I can laugh at my lonely past
I'll let you do whatever you want
I don't want to be bound
I can't go back to normal
Nothing will change
Won't you stay by my side?
Rule, my last wish
Rule, rule, let's break it
Ah, so let me be cool
I'm already the real me
It doesn't matter
Cool, I'll act like I don't care
I'll act like it doesn't matter
I want to be confident
Cool, don't look at me like that
Cool, I'm not interested
Cool, I'll keep resisting
I don't want to be an adult
I want to be a fool like this
Cool, don't look at me like that
Cool, my true feelings
Cool, cool, notice me
No matter what I do, it's a waste of
time
What I see is completely different
It's okay to cry
I'm not asking for understanding anymore
I've been denied my identity
I'm a pessimistic adult
I repeat myself again and again
Don't push me into a cheap love
Shutters are closed
The shopping street is full of people
If I run through with all my might
What will I find?
Tokyo Dome, take off!
A dead end, a dead end
There's an end to the world
What should I do from here?
It's pitch black in front of me
A dead end, a dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will I go back to the way I came?
When I dream too much
Even if I'm here, I can't help it
I was wrong
A dead end, a dead end
How can I live in the present
Connecting the past and the future?
Even if I resist
Even if I resist, it's the same result
The more I look around
I become a cautious person
Even if I keep being shocked
What should I answer?
I was contacted by my parents
That's where I was born
If it's the end, if it's the end
Where will I start next?
What will happen from here?
The future of despair, yeah
If it's the end, if it's the end
I'll find a way out
Is there no continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
Until dawn, I'll wait and wait
If it's the end, if it's the end
I'll rewind the bright days
Will I start over?
No matter where I run
There's no way
Right and left
A wall that blocks me
The neon is out
The rusty back street
It's impossible, I dashed
But I was caught
If it's the end, if it's the end
Where will I start next?
What will happen from here?
The future of despair, yeah
A dead end, a dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will I go back to the way I came?
When I dream too much
Even if I'm here, it can't be helped
I was wrong
A dead end, a dead end
While hitting the wall in front of me
Inside my chest, I'm screaming
Connecting the past and the future
How do I live in the present?
Translated by Releska
I don't think I've ever loved anyone
this much
I don't want to hurt you more than I
hurt myself
That's what I thought
While waiting for the last place
I wonder how many times I've waited for
that timing
We were facing each other so coldly
There's no meaning in "what if"
Ah, how many days until graduation?
What will change from that day?
Just by changing where we go
Just by making more new friends
Leaving behind something precious
I'm being called an adult
The cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least for a little longer
Please stay by my side
No matter how much I love you
The seasons pass
In a blink of an eye, everything fades
away
The cherry blossoms from that day
What we're talking about now
Are just words
That seem to come out of my mouth
If I don't climb up on my own
I'll only make myself feel bad
I can't do that
I heard the sound of the train leaving
Tokyo
And I wanted to push your back
The delusion I always had
I think it would've been better if I had
it
The sweet and sour youth
I wonder what I'm trying to be cool
about
I'm tired of being the only one
That's right, when I remember you
It was such a beautiful love
I don't mind being alone
I want to praise myself for looking back
I'll keep blooming forever
So that there won't be flowers
If I can't stay like this
How should I make it beautiful?
That's what I thought
Fly up into the sky
Just flutter
So that I can remember it over and over
I want you to fall slowly
So that you won't notice me
I'll close my eyes
And listen to your voice
I tried to leave it in my memories
The waterfall in the dark night sky
I can still see the cherry blossoms in
full bloom
Those flowers are the people I loved
I wonder if I'll have a dream when I
grow up
Even if I can't remember
If only I could be in such a beautiful
place
The cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least stay a little longer
No matter how much I love you
The seasons pass
In a blink of an eye
The cherry blossoms that are about to
fall
"Cherry Blossom"
The cherry blossoms that are about to
fall
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least stay a little longer
The cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least stay a little longer
The cherry blossoms that are about to
fall
Even if I can't remember
If only I could be in such a beautiful
place
The cherry blossoms that think of you
Are blown by the wind
And fly up into my heart
At least stay a little longer
The cherry blossoms that are about to
fall
Are blown by the wind
I'm a good girl, so don't worry
Hey, if you do something like this
No one will leave the house
Let's talk, let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah, I'm not kidding, you're a playboy
It has nothing to do with that
Baby, what did you say?
In the midnight club, I'm the only one
here
Did he do it?
I'm taking it seriously
It's a lie, I'm running away
I'm apologizing to you
Den, den, den
Get lost in the crowd
Den, den
The eye-catching person is knocking on
the bag
Den, den
Even before you came here
Are you shooting from that side?
Because if I didn't do it, I would have
lost
I don't care if it's just to sleep
Tomorrow is tomorrow, with someone else
Endless party
If a trial is held
Of course, I have to crush it
It's too early
I'm sick of it, but no one can stop
I'm a playboy
Let's believe, let's believe
If we don't believe each other, the
world will end
Where did it come from?
I was shot by an unknown love
I didn't feel the pain
I'm tired of talking
I don't know what to do
I was shot by an unknown love
I'm tired of talking
I don't know what to do
I'm a playboy
The party is going to end
I won't say anything about anyone else
Everyone only talks about themselves
(I don't want to talk about myself)
I see, everyone is just someone who
wants to talk to someone
Yeah
(I don't want to talk about myself)
I'll be a good girl so that I won't be a
shadow
Hey, if you do something like this, no
one will leave the house
Let's talk, let's look at each other
If there's no love, the world will end
Yeah
I don't want to talk about myself
I don't look outside the window
I can't hear the bell in the city on the
weekend night
(I don't want to talk about myself)
Love will definitely become a habit
Why did I look back on those lyrics?
It became painful without thinking
I'm sure everyone is the same
It's someone's experience writing such
lyrics
I want you to understand my feelings
I can't sleep at night when I fell in
love
(I don't want to talk about myself)
I can't sleep at night when I fell in
love
I want to write a love song for everyone
who can't sleep
I don't want to get a reason for my
insomnia
It's just a delusion, an endless
Why did I look back on those lyrics?
It became painful without thinking
I'm sure everyone is the same
It's someone's experience writing such
lyrics
I want you to understand my feelings
I can't sleep at night when I fell in
love
(I don't want to talk about myself)
Everyone, are you having fun?
Thank you very much
I've been struggling in the first half
so far
Everyone, how are you? Are you having
fun?
Thank you very much
I talked about it on MC earlier
Not only before, but today there are 360
degrees BUDDIES
I was so excited that I couldn't say
what I wanted to say
I want to talk a little
I think everyone feels the same, not
just time
I'm happy to see this view
BUDDIES are the same
I'd be happy if we could do that.
I'm glad that we can share not only time
but also our feelings.
That's what I wanted to say.
I'm glad I said it.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to hear from the members as
well.
Kira-chan, how do you like Tokyo Dome?
Tokyo Dome is big.
Can I play a little?
Let's play! Let's play!
If I shout out loud without passing the
microphone,
I want to see how far I can get.
That's true.
I'll shout a few times.
I'll shout "Yahoo!"
I want you to shout "Yahoo!" as loud as
you can.
Are you ready?
I'll get louder and louder.
Can I do it?
Here I go.
Yahoo!
No way!
Really?
Do you want to try again?
No way!
I'll do it again.
I'll do my best.
If you can hear me, please shout.
Here I go.
One, two.
Kira-chan!
Really?
Tamura-san, you can do your best.
I'm watching you.
No way!
You've done this before, haven't you?
Do you know this?
When I first stood on the stage at
Omotenashi-kai,
I had to show off my special skills.
There weren't too many of them.
It's been a while since I've seen Kira
in such a loud voice.
If you can hear me, please respond in
the same way.
Here we go.
Did you hear that?
No way!
You can hear me?
I don't have that much time, but I'm
having so much fun that I want everyone
to do it.
Thank you so much. It was so much fun.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Today's tour was fun.
It was fun to sing in a loud voice like
this during the rehearsal.
I wonder if there's an episode during
the rehearsal, Rena-chan.
It's me.
During rehearsals, there were times when
we rehearsed from morning to night, and
there were times when we finished a
little earlier.
The day we finished a little earlier,
the sun was rising, and we opened the
door of the lesson studio.
When we opened the door, it was still
evening, but I thought it was bright,
and I was so happy that I was excited.
I thought I had no choice but to go to
the shaved ice shop I wanted to eat.
I thought it was a waste of time and I
wanted to go, so I went alone to eat
shaved ice.
It was after I sweated a lot, so I was
very happy.
It was really delicious!
We had a really fun time, even after the
rehearsal.
I'm really jealous. I like shaved ice
too.
But it was the same day as Hii-chan.
We were talking about how we wanted to
eat shaved ice.
But isn't it a little too much to eat
alone?
That's right.
That's what we ended up with.
Can you eat alone?
Is there anyone who can eat alone?
Mii-chan?
I can eat alone.
Isn't there a group of two people around
you?
There was a group of two people, but it
was like a space for one person.
I wasn't scared at all.
That's so sad.
Last summer, Matsu, Hono-chan and I went
to eat kakigori.
You went to eat!
I want to go again.
We don't really come here.
It's rare for you to come to our
concert.
It's my first time.
I'm glad.
It was fun.
Speaking of Rei-chan, you went abroad
alone, right?
I went abroad alone.
I went to Denmark alone.
I failed to board the plane.
Is there anyone who said, "I used the
plane before I came to this dome today"?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Please listen to the broadcast and make
sure you don't make a mistake on your
way home.
Please be careful on your way home.
Today, I went abroad, to Japan, by
plane, bullet train, hotel reservation,
and so on.
I think you all came here to see us.
Until we go back, everyone,
Until we go back, what was it? A
concert?
It's not a concert, but
It's a concert, so everyone,
please be careful on your way back.
We'll do a call and response, and then
we'll move on to the next one.
Is that okay?
We'll do our best.
BUDDIES, here we go.
BUDDIES, are you still excited?
Can you shout louder?
Yeah!
Are you ready to make the best memory of
your life with SAKURAZE46?
Yeah!
Let's get excited until the end!
"SAKURAZE46"
I'll stop.
I'm not good at love
If I think too much
I might be able to
I'm not good at love
I'm too bad
Now I'm lonely
I'm not good at love
The direction of the wind has changed a
little
The atmosphere is different somewhere
Before I knew it, the strong sunlight
I want to take off my uniform
I'm planning to go to the sea
I talk to my classmates
I'm worried about what kind of swimsuit
to buy
This year's trend is
It's still summer time
Hey, hey, hey
I wonder if something will happen in
midsummer
I'm worried
If I think too much
I don't have a chance
I'm just imagining
I don't want to get sunburned
The sea is a bit of a hassle
But I don't do anything
It's a waste
I want memories
Vacation
Hey, hey, hey
Everyone becomes an adult in midsummer
It's a secret story
If there's no one to tell me
In the end, it's just a delusion
I'm sure there's something
Dream love
Even if I look at my smartphone
I don't have any information
Even if I ask someone
I can't answer
Where did everyone go?
Can you tell me something about summer?
I wonder if something will happen in
midsummer
I'm worried
If I think too much
I don't have a chance
I'm just imagining
I don't want to get sunburned
"Summer Love"
In a colorful town
How many windows are lit?
I'm sure happiness is
Like a powder keg
It's an illusion
Even if I think about love
I can't get an answer
You said you liked me
I can't forget that night
I stopped chasing after myself
If you don't feel like it
Even if I turn around
It can't be helped
Someday
From you
Come see me
"Summer Love"
I can't like the entrance design
That draws a loose arm
I feel the coldness
That rejects my love
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
Will you ever come back to me?
With a smile
Saying "It's been a while"
I naturally put my arms around you
We went for a walk
Once a couple breaks up
They usually don't go back
It's not like we don't want to see each
other
It's just a little unlikely
"Summer Love"
I wonder if I'm the only one who knows
You said you liked me
I can't forget that night
I stopped chasing after myself
If you don't feel like it
Even if I turn around
It can't be helped
Someday
From you
Come see me
"Summer Love"
I can't like the entrance design
That draws a loose arm
I feel the coldness
That rejects my love
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
Will you ever come back to me?
With a smile
Saying "It's been a while"
I naturally put my arms around you
We went for a walk
Once a couple breaks up
They usually don't go back
It's not like we don't want to see each
other
It's just a little unlikely
"Summer Love"
I can't like the entrance design
That draws a loose arm
I feel the coldness
That rejects my love
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
Will you ever come back to me?
With a smile
Saying "It's been a while"
"Summer Love"
I can't like the entrance design
That draws a loose arm
I feel the coldness
That rejects my love
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
Will you ever come back to me?
With a smile
Saying "It's been a while"
I naturally put my arms around you
We went for a walk
Once a couple breaks up
They usually don't go back
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
"Summer Love"
I can't like the entrance design
That draws a loose arm
I feel the coldness
That rejects my love
It's my delusion
I wonder why
I can't forget when we were dating
Will you ever come back to me?
"Summer Love"
When did it get so rusty?
I was standing in front of the garden
My bicycle
It's not like I forgot
The time I can't see
Passes by on its own
When I let go of your hand
Somewhere in my heart
It got rusty
I can hear the sound of the gears
I can hear it
If love doesn't work
What can I do?
It's my fault
That I didn't take care of you
If I always took care of you
Would I be able to stay shiny?
It hasn't changed since we met
I'm the only one
Who has that delusion
Even if I hurry and polish it
It's no use
I want to keep it
Kindness is a foolish
Natural behavior
It's not just you
It's obvious
In the storm
Endure the loneliness
What rusts is
Emotional scars
I expect peace
I'm sorry
Yes, forever
I just thought
It was a new way
I never thought
Time would flow
And pass by
Rust isn't bad
It just passes by
Back and forth
It's normal
It's a natural phenomenon
Someday
We had fun
I want to go back to that time
Only the surface has changed
If love doesn't work
What can I do?
It's my fault
That I didn't take care of you
If I always took care of you
Would I be able to stay shiny?
It hasn't changed since we met
I'm the only one
Who has that delusion
Even if I hurry and polish it
I'm the only one
Translated by Releska
"Koishin no Furu Yoru" (Night of Falling
Stars)
I hate the time when it's too quiet
I can't even breathe
On a night of falling stars
Why am I in love with someone?
The ceiling of the room that turned off
the light
Listen to the voice in my heart
I can't sleep even if I think about this
and that
What should I dream of with my eyes
closed?
I think silence is a form of violence
Don't hurt me any more
The infinite space that was quiet
It's like being sucked into the darkness
Everything is in vain
I was denied the light
By my side
Did someone, did you see it?
I'm not afraid
"Koishin no Furu Yoru" (Night of Falling
Stars)
Is the city already asleep?
Or is it already dead?
The noise from the world disappears
It makes everyone lonely
In this world, there is someone other
than me
Because it's noisy
I'm relieved by the presence of people
I want to believe that I'm not alone
Nothing is happening
The hands of the clock are spinning
I feel like I'm spinning in vain
It's like sinking into the bed
My body is dry
My lips are so dry
I can't speak
There is a sound called silence
I definitely heard it
I was about to say
"Koishin no Furu Yoru" (Night of Falling
Stars)
I want to give up my desire to speak
Can I love silence?
It's normal to imagine everyday life
Even if I'm told it's a delusion
I can't answer the correct answer
I'll put a blanket over my head
I won't get any more love
Until dawn
Don't blink
I'm jealous
I want to shout from myself
It's okay to cry
I want to shout my voice
I want to let you know that I'm here
If I keep silent, you won't notice
Even if I love, I can be forgotten
I want you to stop ignoring me
Just waiting is suffocating
What are you trying to take away from
me?
The silence that makes me think is
violence
"Koishin no Furu Yoru" (Night of Falling
Stars)
What shall we do?
What's your story?
Pinky-look
I'm on the asphalt
You're bare-faced
I'm afraid
What will happen on a romantic night?
I'll break up with my current boyfriend
I'll meet up with my ex-boyfriend
It's time to make sense
The past that I'm entangled in
is a troublesome bad luck
If I try to fall in love again
I'll put a spell on it
I'll always be left behind
If I chase after you
Any man will just get hurt
and end
You're especially dangerous
You disappear before I notice
The more you disappear, the more
effective it is
What are you trying to do?
Oh, no!
You're quietly resting your hand on
my almost-broken kneecap
Breathe in
Get in my way
(Get in my way)
Your passionate gaze
(What do you see?)
I want to stop it
I want to make you go
I can't decide
Are you kidding me?
"Ah" or "Go"
We said a lot of things
But selfishness is an extra problem
I just want to tease you
One fall, two wins
Every time I try to run away
I make men laugh
I don't intend to chase after you
I'm sorry
You're a never-ending story
You don't say what you want to say
Everyone thinks about the continuation
Where will it appear?
Surprise!
What should we do?
Come here and get down
You're especially dangerous
You disappear before I notice
It's more effective not to say it out of
the blue
What are you trying to do?
Oh yeah
What you say we do?
Hurry up and get down
I was watching a video on my smartphone
until dawn
I can't get up anymore
I was late for everything
I skipped class again today
I rushed to the bathroom
I should have gone on a date
When I yawned, my nostrils grew
What do you want to do?
What do you want to say?
When did you start not dreaming?
While I was playing games
I became an adult
Where did everyone go?
Why are you so busy?
Wait a minute
There was so much time
So that I can have energy for the rest
of my life
I'm okay
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told I can't
I can't be a different person now
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm banned
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I'll do it again
I won't regret it
God, can I ask you something?
I want to know what the standard is
"I want to know what the standard is"
The sand of time that was full
Disappears without doing anything
If I were that time
I shouldn't have been able to do
anything
What are you doing here?
Am I playing alone?
Please tell me something
Is it something that has to change?
Suddenly, I was disqualified
From that one step
If I'm banned, what should I do?
I just didn't know
Give me a chance
So that I can do it again
If I'm banned, what should I do?
Do you think you're alive?
I believe that stupid people say that
For the sake of failure
God, please forgive me
Suddenly, I was disqualified
The sun that is too bright
Is leaking from the bottom of the
curtain
Until the darkness comes
We can still make it
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
disqualified
Even if I'm told that I can't do it
I can't become a different person
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
disqualified
Even if I'm told to stop
I understand
I'll do it again
Even if I'm banned, even if I'm
disqualified
I understand
I'll do it again
I won't regret it
God, is there something I can't do?
Where is that standard?
I want to know
Even if I'm forced into a difficult
situation
I will definitely be banned
"Ban"
A digital youth overflowing in the city
Oh, oh, oh, oh
It's so annoying
Even if I'm messaged by such a voice
Oh, oh, oh, oh
It's a little uncertain
The world is always in a hurry
I keep screaming "I love you"
Me, me, me
Jump, jump
There's something I want to say
But I can't say it to everyone
You, you, you
Jump, jump
Hey, I'm waving my hand in my heart
Do you know I'm here?
"Ban, ban, ban, ban"
Everyone is too strong to admit
Don't you have that much confidence in
yourself?
Even if I look more, I can't stop
SNS
I'm saying I'm looking at it properly
But I'm greedy
"Ban, ban, ban, ban"
Listen to me
Stutter more
I want you to praise me concretely
It's different from people
What is it?
You're the only one
A special existence called "self"
When will you notice it?
Hey, why do you ignore me?
I can see it in your eyes, you know
The same thing for each other
Misunderstanding, I was angry
I'm lonely all the time
My mental is about to collapse
It's overflowing, overflowing,
overflowing
Jump, jump
I'm trying so hard to live
But no one understands me
I can't run away at night
Jump, jump
Hey, communication
I don't have any ability
What should I do?
"Ban, ban, ban, ban"
That's what you are
I'm looking at you properly
If you are convinced by someone
It's the same thing
There's no end to it
I can't stop next time
Love me now
I want you to praise me concretely
It's different from people
What is it?
You're the only one
"Ban, ban, ban, ban"
I want you to praise me concretely
Everyone is fine
(I want, I want)
Everyone is too strong to be a witness
Don't you have that much confidence in
yourself?
I want to see more and more of your SNS
I'm telling you I'm watching you
properly
But you're so greedy
Listen to me, nod more
I want you two to praise me
You're different from others, you're so
selfish
You're the only one for me
(Subbed By VocaloidLiveConcerts Any
Mistakes, Please Inform Us)
Do you have a dream?
There must be a reason for you to live
To think that you want to do something
someday
You want to do this tomorrow, that's
your wish
That's why you sleep
Everyone does it to forget bad things
If you get through today's day
You'll hear that something will happen
Late at night
In the convenience store's microwave
Warm up your lunch
What kind of miracle is waiting for you?
I'm sure you know
That you're giving up before you know it
But pretend you don't notice
Start over, start over
If you want to start over just one more
time
There's no other way
There's no turning back
You're running away from yourself right
now
Wake up
The reality reflected in your charisma
Makes you want to turn your back on your
heart
But the moment you open the door
You can become a different person
What's important is
Where do you start over from?
That's a few seconds before you give up
Then what am I?
Can I say something nice about someone?
I don't know, I don't know, I'm a
security guard
I'm like a critic, I'm a messenger
If you try to go all out, you'll be
swayed
If you're going to get out of the battle
today
Even if you fail, you'll meet the same
person
The security camera
Protects your heart
Nobody's watching
All you want is freedom
What can you do?
It's a competitive battle
So don't worry about a single thing
Make it yourself
What you've been holding on to until
today
Doesn't matter
Don't try to act cool
When you wake up, you'll be like a two-
story building
Even if you're blown away by the wind
I'm not as stupid as that guy over there
I don't care if I'm a little better than
you
I want to face you with all my might
In the end, I'm just an innocent girl
I'm a security guard
I'm like a critic, I'm a messenger
If you try to go all out, you'll be
swayed
If you're going to get out of the battle
today
Even if you fail, you'll meet the same
person
The security camera
Protects your heart
What can you do?
It's a competitive battle
So don't worry about a single thing
Make it yourself
You're like my past
I'll be your future
A lump of self-hatred
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over from here
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over from here
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over just one
more time
There's only now
There's no later
Na na na na na
It's not a joke
I don't need such selfishness
It's not too late
Let's go out again
There's definitely no later
I said
Nobody knows
What the future holds
I wanted you to notice
If you think you can start over
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
Wake up now
To the reality reflected in the glass
window
I want to give you my heart
But what's important is
To start over
Start over
If you think you can start over
There's only now
There's no later
I'm running away
From the loneliness
What kind of emotions
Did you lose?
It's more cruel than memories
Betray me
Even if you're crying
It's not like you
I wanted you to be
Impatient all the time
Even if you turn around
Yes, nothing will start
Regret is the worst process
Stop it
It's just a word
I don't care
Even if you get hurt
We'll get through it
How much
Did we love each other?
The blood is still flowing
I want to cover it up
I don't want to
Love is a question
What's right?
It seems like
I got the right answer
Before I knew it
It became a pain
I'm coming back
How many times
I'm running away from the fantasy
I love you from you
If you forgive me
I'll just start over
I sing I sing I sing
I sing song
I sing I sing
If you're still lost
Live with emotions
More than anything
It's better to be over
In the audience's body
You just have to start
You know
Love is a question
What's right?
It seems like
I got the right answer
Before I knew it
It became a pain
I'm coming back
How many times
I'm running away from the fantasy
I love you from you
If you forgive me
I'll just start over
I sing I sing I sing
I sing I sing
[music ends]
[gun cocks]
[gunshot]
[cheers and applause]
[crowd chanting]
Thank you, Encore!
"TOKYO DOME"
is concluding,
let's go!
It's suspend time!
[cheers and applause]
[singing]
I'm not alone, everyone is doing their
best
I support the flowers
The place where the light stands
The beauty that tries not to hit
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Let's keep shining
It's sunset time
Let's raise our hearts
Just that will give us courage
From the other side of the stage
I can clearly see
The wind, the sun, and the rain
I want to raise you
Thank you, everyone!
Let's get excited with the amp!
I'll become a butterfly and fly off on a
skateboard
I want to chase after you on a ponytail
But I can't catch up with you with my
voice
Can I only look at your back?
My heart is beating so fast
I can only go at full speed
I'll be behind you
It's not cool, I can't breathe anymore
Come on, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly,
fly
Fly through the sky
From here, I'll search for you, you,
you, you, wherever you are
Instead of my eyes, no matter how long
the distance is, I'll control it
I want to be able to look at you at any
time
Oh oh, crossing over
Oh oh, the way you sing
Oh oh, oh oh oh
Look, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh oh, about you
Oh oh, I love you
Oh oh, oh oh oh
Falling, falling, I'm in full bloom
You, who is only for me
Put a bud in your eyes
Believe that you can bloom a big flower
Until the day you graduate
Let me see everything
It's awesome time
Let's sing as loud as we can
So that my feelings for you can be
conveyed
Until that sweat blooms someday
Let's keep shining
It's awesome time
Let's raise our hearts
That's all it takes to be brave
From the other side of the stage, I can
clearly see
The wind and the sun
I want to raise you
Buddies, do you like me?
Do you love me more?
We love you too!
Oh oh, oh oh oh
Listen to my words
You in the distance
Come on, drift drift drift drift
Drift, drift across the sky
From here, I'll look for you, you, you,
you
No matter where I go
Instead of my eyes, let's control any
distance
I want to be looking at you at any time
Oh oh, cross step
Oh oh, crossing figure
Oh oh, oh oh oh
Look, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh oh, about you
Oh oh, I love you
Oh oh, oh oh oh
I want to fall in love with you
"I want to meet you"
Yo! How are you? I wanted to meet you
Yo! Look at this blue sky
Yo! The world hasn't changed a bit
Yo! We are the same as we were back then
Yo! The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the leaking
sunlight
Yo! Let's live, let's live, let's live
The bridge that took everything
Has already passed through
As if nothing had happened
This land is peaceful
Yo! I can't stop here
Yo! Let's move forward with our own feet
Yo! My heart is looking somewhere far
away
Yo! Is there really hope?
Yo! If I'm with you, I can surely go
Yo! If I'm with you, I can reach
Yo! Let's walk, let's walk, let's walk
Let's drink while ringing the bell
Let's drink and enjoy
Let's drink and dance
Let's drink with our friends
We are buddies
Even if we lose something
Tomorrow will come again
Tomorrow will come
The rain and wind of joy are darkness
Because a new dawn will come
Let's start again from here
Because freedom has nothing
We can go anywhere
Let's throw away despair with tears
I've been waiting for you
To the future
We are friends
In this world
How are you? I've missed you
Look at this blue sky
The world hasn't changed at all
We are the same as we were
The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
The green trees, the sun
Let's live, let's live, let's live
We are buddies
We are dreaming
We are friends
We are buddies
Thank you for giving us such a wonderful
view on the last day of Tokyo Dome.
There may be days when we have to work
hard again from tomorrow,
but we want to make your life even
greener.
I was happy to have you here.
I will do my best to be a living force.
I will do my best to deliver excitement
and excitement in the future.
I love you, ARISU!
How was it?
Did you have fun?
Please stay with us from now on!
Let's sing together at the end!
One, two!
Let's sing together!
Thank you!
Thank you for the encore!
Did you have fun today?
Thank you!
We had a lot of fun, too!
I really don't want this time to end,
but before I go and talk to the members,
I have an announcement for everyone!
First of all, please take a look at
this!
Thank you!
Fun!
Ah, fun!
Uh!
Yeah!
Woo!
So, the Revolutionary and Aniversary
Live is now confirmed!
We are also at Zozomarin Stadium!
How do you feel?
I didn't expect to be able to hold a 4th
Anniversary Live at Zozomarin Stadium
this year, so I'm really, really
grateful.
I'm very happy about it, but I hope
everyone here can come to the Stadium as
well!
That's right!
Thank you!
Together!
I hope we can celebrate our 4th
anniversary together.
Hika-chan, how was it?
It was really fun.
I was like, "Do I really sweat this
much?"
I think you'll understand if you watch
it.
I sweated a lot, and the space was
really hot.
I thought it was really nice to get so
hot.
It was nice to be here.
I think there are many people who have
gathered here for the first time today,
and of course there are people who have
come several times and thought it was
fun,
but it's only now that people who are
here gather at this time, right?
That's why this tour is really...
The theme of "How long do I want to go
back to" is still very important to me,
so it's a great link to that.
I was able to perform each song with a
lot of emotion,
and I think I was able to show that I
had grown a little more than two years
ago at the Tokyo Dome.
Let's listen to it again.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to everyone who always
supports me.
It's all thanks to the staff of Team
Sakurazaka 46 and everyone who always
supports me.
Thank you so much for being my buddies
again.
Thank you so much for meeting me.
Thank you.
I hope we can continue to support each
other and walk together.
I look forward to working with you.
Next, Yuzu.
Yes, I'm Yuzu.
I'm Yuzu.
For me, this is the last time I saw
Sakurazaka46's live.
As a guest, this is the last time I saw
it.
It's a place I've never seen before, so
I'm very happy and grateful to be able
to perform with everyone like this.
And I think there have been various
changes in the group since I joined
Sankisei,
but I've always done it while thinking
that I want such changes to be good for
the group.
So I'm very happy to be on stage with
everyone like this.
Thank you very much.
I can't express how grateful I am to
everyone.
So I want to tell you more and more from
now on.
I still have a lot of emotions, songs,
performances, and members that I want to
deliver to everyone.
The Anniversary Live was just announced,
but I want to meet everyone in various
places from now on.
I want you to love it again. Let's walk
together from now on. Thank you very
much.
Finally, Ten-chan, who was in charge of
the center of "How many times do you
want to go back?"
How was this tour?
I'm glad to see such a wonderful view.
I didn't think I'd be able to see it, so
I'm really happy.
After all, what is it?
In such a big venue, from corner to
corner,
These buddies who have gathered just to
meet us.
And everyone who's watching the stream.
Live is a very precious opportunity to
feel the love from buddies.
I love it so much.
It's not just about us having fun.
I want to make a live show that buddies
can say, "It was the best day of my
life."
That's what I've been thinking.
I've been on a lot of tours.
I've been asked a lot about the pressure
of being in the center.
Thanks to the members, I didn't feel any
pressure at all.
In a good way.
I've been able to overcome a lot of
pressure with everyone.
I'm so happy to be able to perform at
the Tokyo Dome for the last time.
But I think there's still a long way to
go.
We're still active.
Buddies, with that big, big love,
I want you to support us more and more.
I hope we can see a lot of wonderful
scenery together in the future.
That's right.
I think there are still a lot of things
to do, such as work, school, housework,
and childcare.
When you're having a hard time, I hope
you'll remember us and feel a little
lighter.
We're all on your side, so don't worry.
I hope you'll continue to follow us.
You love WINNER BUDDIES, don't you?
We love you!
You love us even more, don't you?
Thank you!
It was so much fun!
I can't believe what all the members
have just said.
I'm so happy to be on the Tokyo Dome
stage with so many BUDDIES.
And even after they wanted to see it,
they gave us tickets,
and until they came here today, they
thought about how to get here,
and how to work hard until that day,
and with a lot of different thoughts,
they all gathered here,
and watched the stream.
But even though they're not here today,
I'm sure there are people who couldn't
come because they wanted to,
and there are people who couldn't watch
the stream,
but even though they're not here today,
we received a lot of support from the
BUDDIES here,
and we're really supported.
And before we gather here,
I'm really happy that they first fell in
love with Sakurazaka,
and met Sakurazaka.
Because you met us,
we will definitely make you happy,
so I hope you'll continue to follow us.
Now that we've received the encore,
we'd like to perform one last song.
Everyone, is it okay if we perform one
last song?
Thank you very much.
Now, we'd like to perform one last song.
Then, please listen to it.
One, two...
"Sakurazaka No Ja!"
Everyone, please listen to "Sakura Pink"
too!
Let's bloom the cherry blossoms
together!
I thought ordinary days were normal
But they weren't
Until the day I couldn't see you
There were holes in my heart
The real loneliness isn't when no one's
around
It's when you can't see your loved ones
I don't know what happened
But I'm sure you can overcome it
I've never forgotten the day
When the cherry blossoms were in full
bloom
Even if spring comes and the flowers
fall
Dreams will repeat and bloom here
So that I can remember
If we gather here
And talk about our days
I feel like we'll be able to meet again
I'm sure there were sad things
That you couldn't tell anyone
That you were afraid to see from afar
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to stand up
The day when the cherry blossoms were in
full bloom
Faced the summer, fall, and winter winds
What were you waiting for
On that branch of a wild rose?
I'm sure there were sad things
That you couldn't tell anyone
Even if people who pass by
Forget the flowers of that day
We'll always remember
The scenery of the next spring
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
My heart trembles with nostalgia
Like the petals of each flower
The cherry blossoms are in full bloom
Oh, oh, oh
I'm sure there were sad things
That you couldn't tell anyone
That you were afraid to see from afar
There's nothing we can do
I was waiting for you to stand up
The day when the cherry blossoms were in
full bloom
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that we can remember forever
We'll gather on this hill
And talk about you
I feel like I can see you again
Oh, oh, oh
Thank you very much for coming to the
Tokyo Dome
And thank you very much for streaming
today.
It was a great time and I was really
happy.
And the 9th single will be released next
week.
I hope you'll look forward to it.
I hope you'll take a picture of the
stage
and leave it as a memory.
I'd be happy if you could share that
memory with someone.
I was really happy to be able to spend
this time with you
and stand on this stage.
Thank you very much.
It was a great time that we couldn't
forget.
I hope it will be such an important
memory for everyone.
I really love BUDDIES.
That's all.
It was SAKURAZUKA46.
Thank you very much.
See you in the future.
I love you.
Thank you for everything.
Bye bye.