This...
I'm sorry, I can't do it anymore.
It's been a year, but...
For the past year...
I released 3 singles.
I was able to go on tours.
And now, please stand for the Tokyo Dome performance.
Thanks for watching!
I was able to spend a year in love.
After that...
I'm very happy to be able to stand on this stage and share the same time with everyone.
I'm really looking forward to the live performance after this.
Today, I'm going to show you the live performance that will be the culmination of this year.
Are you all ready?
KURASUKU HOUSE!
Thank you for coming to this venue.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!
And...
Even if it's overseas...
It's a bit...
Since it's a competition...
Can I ask you to do the Maton dance in English?
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to our live today.
Are you ready to have fun with me?
Thank you! I love you!
It's a pera-pera.
That's right!
Last time in Korea too
Since you said it, Airi-chan, can you say it in Korean?
Yes, I want to say it!
Ladies and gentlemen, hello!
Hello!
How have you been?
Have you eaten?
And...
We, Kokkiriman Kocha, love you!
Kawaii!
Right now, we're saying hello to BUDDIES.
How are you? Did you eat?
Kawaii!
Let's go down the path of happiness!
Ari-chan, did you eat?
I ate!
That's great!
Ari-chan ate!
Everyone ate.
Thank you!
And at the end of this month, we will be participating in an event in Hong Kong.
The reason we are able to perform overseas is because of BUDDIES' support.
We want to give it our all in Hong Kong.
Since we're here, let's do it in Cantonese.
Thank you so much!
We love you all! Thank you!
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Well, I'd like to ask you again about your enthusiasm for this concert.
Zono-chan! Ozone!
Zono!
We are...
I'm 4 years old!
Thank you so much!
Ehhhh
4 years ago
In the first single, there's a song called BUDDIES by TENCHAN CENTER.
We'll sing the song, Nakama Da, and call out to everyone who supports us as BUDDIES.
I'm so happy.
We've spent a lot of time together.
Since the birth of BUDDIES.
I'll be 4 years old, right?
Should we sing Happy Birthday?
Let's do both!
Let's start with Happy Birthday.
Let's sing Happy Birthday and end with Happy Birthday.
Thank you!
Let's sing!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy Birthday, Dear Buzz!
Let's grow old together!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Everyone here today is 4 years old.
That's right.
It's a group, so I'd like to celebrate and have fun today.
One more person, Inoue!
Yes!
It's me, Mino!
I was really into it from the start
I said thank you earlier
But I was more like
Thank you!
Can I have a voice that's as loud as me?
I want to hear it!
That was amazing!
I felt it in my heart.
At the beginning, I was at the end of my left hand.
I was there, but I should have been a little closer.
But when I saw the BUDDIES,
I have to get closer!
That's how much I'm into it.
Let's all have fun!
Let's have fun!
Yes, that's right. All the members are full of energy.
I want to have a fun time with everyone here today.
And we will deliver the best live performance of the day.
Are you all ready?
Yeah!
After this, let's all have fun together!
I've been waiting for you.
In the scenery
We also receive a lot of power. Thank you very much as always.
We were able to perform a few of those songs.
How was it so far, Mi-san?
Thank you for watching!
Bye!
My...
Can I talk about what I'm thinking?
Yes!
Last year, I was in this ZOZO MARIE STUDIO...
I wasn't able to stand up and I was looking at everyone from the audience seats.
At that time, to be honest, I thought that I might not be able to go back to Sakurazaka.
The end.
No!
Risa!
Thank you for watching!
What should I do?
All the members were so warm.
Everyone was so warm.
I can't do it.
I thought about a lot of things, but...
Thank you for watching!
I want to do it again.
I'm very happy to be able to celebrate my 4th anniversary here,
and I'm very happy to be able to meet everyone and be on stage with all the members.
I'm so happy
That's what I thought.
Teh!
Yes, everyone, really...
Thank you very much.
We've been waiting for this for a long time.
This year, being able to stand with Min-san,
the members, and BUDDIES,
we're happy happy, right?
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
Let's do our best together!
Let's do our best!
Next is...
Yutan!
You should have said that!
I said it!
Yuzu!
Everyone!
How are you?
Thank you!
I'm fine too!
I love it when Kyo comes
I was really looking forward to it.
I remember last year's 3rd anniversary live very vividly,
and I've been working hard on it for the past year.
At the last year's anniversary live,
I was able to see the color of the music.
I could really feel it.
I don't know what to say.
The choreography, the production, and the live performances we've done with Team Sakurazaka 46.
When we did it on stage, the BUDDIES were like,
Oh, this is how it's going to be.
I felt like, Oh, this is how it's going to be.
I felt like, Oh, this is how BUDDIES and I are going to make a live performance together.
I felt that a lot last year.
I was really looking forward to Kyoga-kun this year.
Did you all look forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm very grateful and happy that there are songs that can be delivered in a new way this time as well as songs that can be performed for the first time.
Speaking of Hatsuhiro...
What do you think of the 3rd generation song, Honitsu-Teki na Koto, performed by Riko-chan of CENTER?
Riko-chan of CENTER!
I got goose bumps!
Thank you!
At first, there was a scene where I walked from the CENTER stage to the main stage.
If I were a year ago, I wouldn't have imagined it.
I never imagined it.
360 degrees!
The PUDDYs are...
I never imagined that I would be walking alone in a place where so many people are gathered.
I was very surprised.
I was a bit nervous, but most of all, my...
I would like to perform my favorite songs in front of my beloved BUDDIES.
I felt very happy.
The members were also very happy.
BUDDIES,
I really like this song.
She said she likes me.
Every time I hear that, I...
I like this song more and more
I want to do my best to make it a song that will be loved by everyone in the future as well.
Thank you very much.
Really?
Riko-chan, you like this song, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Many seniors say they like this song, too.
I like it a lot.
Really?
Rina-san?
Akiho-san?
Akiho-san!
Thank you.
I was looking forward to seeing you perform today.
I'm so happy to perform here for the first time.
There's one more member I'd like to ask,
Rina-san!
It's our 40th anniversary, how do you feel?
That's right.
Until last year's 3rd anniversary...
I think there were a lot of times when we were divided into 1st and 2nd generation songs and 3rd generation songs, but in the 4th year this year, there were a lot of live performances from January, and the live rehearsal
I spend most of my time with the members, from morning to night.
All three of us.
We've spent a lot of time together, and I think we've gotten really close.
So today...
From the first song.
In the second song, there was a song with all of us, and it was amazing.
I'm so happy that we were able to make a song together for the 4th anniversary.
Thank you very much!
Everyone was really involved in the fan meeting.
We're very happy about that.
Of course, the other Senpais too, how should I put it...
This year, like...
I think I was able to deepen the bond between the seniors and juniors.
I think this year was a year when I was able to deepen the bond and trust between the members.
Today is the last day of the year, so I'd like to have a great time with all the members and BUDDIES.
Everyone!
Are you ready to have fun?
Let's celebrate Terazaka46's anniversary together!
Yeah!
Please enjoy the rest of the show!
During the MC, we were able to remember the things we love and the memories of this year.
While feeling fun and happiness
I hope you enjoy the live performance.
Is everyone ready?
Mio!
Thank you very much.
In this MC, I would like to ask the members about their memories of this year.
First of all,
Miu-chan!
Yes, I'm Miu Murayama.
This year, SAKURAZAKA...
This year, I was able to experience the kindness of people.
I think it was a year when I felt that way and was saved.
I tend to get really nervous.
Yeah.
Yeah, I tend to get nervous.
I tend to get nervous, but...
At that time, there was someone who told me to enjoy being nervous.
That's all I have to say.
I was saved.
so that you can enjoy the tension little by little.
That's how it has become.
Ruto...
The moment I dropped it, it was like...
I feel like I'm going to cry.
There are times when it gets hard, right?
It's not like that.
Even if it's just for a moment, I will never leave Sakurazaka alone.
So...
That's how it is.
How do I say this?
Where will you be by my side?
I really love that side of Sakurazaka.
The kindness I received...
I want to be a person who can connect with others.
I think it's very strong, recently.
See you next time!
Thank you.
Miyu said it too, but in Sakurazaka, everyone is so considerate and kind.
Miyu said she was kind, but we get a lot of kindness from Miyu, so thank you so much.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm sure everyone knows Miyu's kindness, but we love Miyu too.
Let's continue to walk together.
Let's do our best.
Thank you.
I'll listen to the other person's song.
Yu-chan!
I forgive you.
Hey!
Thank you for watching!
Looking back on this year, I think I've grown a lot this year.
I wonder what that is.
I don't know how I can contribute more to SAKURAZAKA
I don't know if I can do it.
I'll do what I can.
It was a year when I thought about what I could do for the group.
Hmm...
Last year's anniversary live was probably...
Rather than that, I'd like to participate now.
Thankfully, the number of songs has increased.
It's not just that, what is it?
Hmm...
But the most important thing for me is...
I...
Not last year, but at the beginning of this year.
Kobayashi-san's graduation concert was a big deal for me.
What was it? The group...
I feel like I'm being supported.
For that reason, or...
It's for my own sake, but it's also for the sake of the group.
What do you think you are?
He was a person who thought a lot about what I could do and supported me, and when I saw his big back, I thought that I could do it too.
That's what I really wanted to do.
What is it? I also...
It's difficult, but I get it.
Maybe there will be new members next year,
but I want them to be able to do something for their big back and the group.
I'm going to keep that feeling in my heart.
I want to keep that feeling.
I think it was a very big thing in this year that I thought so.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I couldn't put it together.
Certainly, Yui's graduation concert, Kobayashi's graduation concert, and Uemura and Fuuka's graduation.
This time, we're in a position to be seniors, so I hope we can show our big backs like Yui said.
This year was a year where I felt that there were a lot of big evolutions and changes.
Up until a year ago, the three of us would talk a lot and share a lot of emotions.
Recently, I've been able to share a lot of fun and sad things with my seniors.
I often have the opportunity to say to the BUDDIES that Sakurazaka46 is very close to their seniors and juniors.
The seniors are really kind, and we've grown up watching them.
I hope that the charm of Sakurazaka46 will continue to be transmitted to the new 4th generation and the BUDDIES, along with the good changes and evolutions.
And Sakurazaka46 in 2024 is not over yet.
Thank you, everyone.
The 4th year anniversary tour is still going on!
Buddies!
I'm ready to get fired up!
Thank you for watching!
To everyone in the back seats, stand-by, and in the front seats...
Thank you for coming.
I was really happy
I'd like to ask the members their thoughts on today's performance.
Bye.
Shizuki!
Yes, I'm Yamashita Shizuki.
Well, since I woke up this morning, I thought that the 4th anniversary live would be over in these two days.
I was very lonely, so I thought that I would like to take advantage of it while riding the float, but
there were a lot of songs that I performed for the first time in this live, but
the 10th single that I performed at the end earlier, I want tomorrow to come, but
Sakurazaka's big venue, Sakurazaka's overall live, for the first time
It was a great opportunity for me to show my talent to the world.
I love this song very much, and there are a lot of days when I don't want tomorrow to come,
but I'm sure everyone who came here had such a day at least once.
On such a day...
This song...
Thank you.
I know, right?
We met, right?
Yeah, we met.
I see.
I'm really...
Listen to this song.
I feel like my heart has been saved.
I...
I hope you feel the same way.
I'm so happy!
That's what I thought.
That's what I wanted to show you today.
Like this.
I like the band called Sakurazaka.
and all of you who have gathered here today.
We also love the group, and it's a place where we can share what we like with everyone.
I think it's wonderful that it happens so many times a year.
That's what I thought.
I've been so happy for the past two days, and 2020 is not over yet, but it's a year that I've come to realize a lot.
Like this.
What a beautiful view.
It was really fun. Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
There was Shizuki's center, so Aori was really cool, too.
It was cool.
It was a blast.
It was the best. Thank you.
Next, Ten-chan!
I'm Rin-chan!
Thank you for watching!
It's the first time I've done it, but...
That's right, isn't it?
What do you mean by that?
I'm sorry.
I'll talk seriously, then.
Um...
Since it's Sakurazaka's 4th anniversary,
I thought back on a long time ago.
I knew it.
When I just made my debut, I was quite...
I wonder what's going to happen in the future, and I wonder what sakurazakarashisa is, while searching for that kind of thing.
There were times when I was anxious, but I wonder why I was able to come this far.
I knew it.
BUDDIES!
It's going to be better than we thought.
and cheering me on.
I think we were able to come this far because we wanted to meet everyone's expectations.
I want to express my gratitude for everyone's daily life.
I think it's a wonderful place where you can express your gratitude directly at a live performance.
All the BUDDIES out there...
They look so happy when they see us,
and they look so happy when they call us.
It would be nice if I could return the favor a little.
And...
That's right.
BUDDIES, thank you so much!
I think there are times when it's hard.
When Sakurazaka was in a pinch or when we needed help,
BUDDIES were there to help us.
When we, BUDDIES, are in a pinch, we'll be there for you, too.
Stay close to your heart, even if it's just a little bit.
It makes me feel better.
It's like a place in my heart.
Bye!
I wish I could be in a group like that.
That's what I think.
I want to do my best in the future as well.
I knew it.
It's my 5th year, so from now on, Sakurazaka!
It's not what you think it is!
That's right.
Your voice echoes.
It's not like that!
I suddenly get excited.
That's how it is.
By all means!
I want to deliver as much as I can
By all means, by all means, by all means, by all means,
By all means, by all means, by all means,
I hope you will continue to watch over us from now on.
We won't let you down.
That's what I'm going to do.
That's what I'm prepared for.
Yes.
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad to hear that, P-chan!
That's why I don't want to change my name from Sakurazaka to Oshihen!
It's a promise.
Thank you very much.
We received a lot of power today.
We'll give you a lot more power.
Please be careful on your way home.
Thank you.
I love you.
There's a lot of Sen-chan-ness.
Thank you.
Lastly, Hono-chan!
Yes, I'm Hono-chan!
After Ten-chan, it's tough!
I also wanted to say something, but I thought it was similar to Ten-chan.
I'm glad that I felt the same way in a good way.
I've been doing it since the first single.
I've been doing it for four years, and I'm about to enter my fifth year.
That's the beginning.
There's something about Sakurazaka and Tsuyomi.
I knew it.
I wonder what it is.
We're doing it desperately, but when we're asked that, it's very difficult to answer in words.
There was a time when I thought.
But...
It's all thanks to the members.
It's like...
The reason why we are standing here today is because...
We are standing here today because we are all standing together,
and we are all standing together,
They've been supporting us as we are, and that's why we're doing what we're doing now.
I'm standing on this stage as I am.
How do I put this, you guys are amazing.
There are so many different characters.
I'm a member of Sakura-Zaka, but I've recently come to think that it's Sakura-Zaka to be able to stay in this place as it is.
I personally feel that it is thanks to BUDDIES and the members.
I'm here for you, BUDDIES.
What is it? Life is already...
I think there are a lot of things, like work and school.
I think it really depends on each person, but in your lives, we, SAKURAZAKA,
will support you and support you, so let's support each other like that.
I want to be in a group where I can live my life while pushing, pushing, pushing, pushing.
At the end of the day, we were all like...
I was doing it with my hands tied up in the flow, but I really felt like I was doing it with all the BUDDIES here and all the BUDDIES who are watching the stream.
I'm serious.
I'm not lying, I'm holding your hand
I was there. I was actually holding hands with everyone, so that's about it.
I love you all and I truly trust you all.
I hope you will continue to look forward to us.
Thank you for your continued support of SAKURAZAKA.
I love you so much!
Thank you very much for today.
It's really...
The story of the three people I just heard
I think it's up to each member to have their own opinion.
We're always Buddies.
We often talk about how much we love you,
and today we were able to celebrate Sakura-zaka and BUDDY's 4th birthday together.
It was really fun.
A little bug came in though.
It's a little...
BUDDY's have increased.
That's right.
We talked about it yesterday,
but I think that the present is really wonderful.
The past, the future, and the present.
Every moment is a moment when we face each other wholeheartedly and deliver with all our might.
I hope that everyone...
What you've seen and felt about Sakurazaka is important to you, isn't it?
Like...
I think it would be great if it could be a happy memory or a wonderful memory.
Recently, I've been getting a lot of expectations from BUDDIES.
That's why I want to live up to everyone's expectations, but I also want to live up to everyone's expectations more and more in the future.
But for that, I think the growth of the group is necessary, but compared to last year, I think Sakurazaka has grown a little.
No, I think we're definitely growing.
But that growth is because each member has grown.
It's also connected to the growth of the group.
But it's not just us.
I think BUDDIES have their own lives and their own growth.
That's why we are...
What is it?
SAKURA ZAKATO BUDDIES!
For me, it's like walking side by side and walking together.
I still have a long way to go.
I think there are still a lot of sceneries that I haven't seen yet.
So I want to take a picture with you all.
That...
As long as there is Sakurazaka, I don't think there is a goal.
So that's...
I don't know if I can say it well, but for example, I was very happy to be able to stand on the Tokyo Dome, and it was my goal.
But, like...
Right there!
So I think there is a way up, or a way forward.
That's why I have Sakurazaka!
Scenery I haven't seen yet?
That's why I want to go see it a lot with Men-san.
From now on, Sakurazaka46 will continue to deliver exciting things and things that will be of help to everyone, so please look forward to it.
Would you like to walk with me to Sakurazaka?
Ayamu!
Of course!
We're buddies!
We've been buddies since yesterday!
Of course!
Thank you!
Forever!
Sakurazaka and Buddies are forever!
For the 5th year!
For the 5th year, Sakurazaka 46!
Please take care of us!
The next song is going to be the last one.
Who wants to have fun with me?
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much!
Can you make it cherry blossom pink?
There's a lot in pink, too.
Thank you very much!
See you next time!
Well then, let's go!
SAKURAZAKA NO UTA
Of course, it's not like that
I didn't know