♪ "Sakura"
♪ "Kanashidatte"
♪ "Yuugan no Jikan"
♪ "Nitori mono ga matta ichigaru"
泣いてたって スルーでいい 理解なんて もう止めちゃいない
偽りされた アイデンティティ 悲観的な大人たちへ
振り返って 一言言う 安い針を 押し付けないで
シャッターしまった 地元のショートケーカー
全力で走り抜けたら 何かわかる?
行き止まり 行き止まり 世界にだって 果てはあるんだ
ここから どうする? 目の前は真っ暗だ
行き止まり 行き止まり 壁だから壊せるけれど
来た道 戻るか 歩いて過ぎた時
ここにいてもしょうがないさ 間違ってたのは自分だ
行き止まり 行き止まり 過去と未来繋ぐ 今をどう生きるか
行き止まり 行き止まり 歩いて過ぎた時
僕をなんてするものかと 抵抗しても同じ結果
頬回りをした分だけ 幼虫命 罰になる
ショックし続けても 何も答えればいい
親にまで連絡されて どこへ積んだ?
終わりなら 終わりなら 次はどこで始まるんだろう?
この先 どうなる? 絶望の未来計
終わりなら 終わりなら 退場する 出口を探せ
続きはないのか? 失くした現在地
何を待てばいいのだろう? 夜明けまで待たなかった
終わりなら 終わりなら 眩しい日々巻き戻してやり直すか?
どこへ逃げたって どこにも道はない
右も左も塞がれたって
僕が決めてる 錆びれた裏通りも
あり得ないダッシュしたのに疲れただけ
もう 行き止まり 行き止まり 世界にだって果てはあるんだ
ここから どうする? 目の前は真っ暗さ
行き止まり 行き止まり 壁だったら壊せるけれど
来た道 戻るか? 夢見て過ぎた時
ここにいてもしょうがないさ 間違ってたのは自分だ
行き止まり 行き止まり 誰の壁を叩きながら
胸の奥で叫んでいる 過去と未来繋げ今をどう生きるか
心打ち切りだって沈まれれば 目の前を塞いでる
でっかい肩幅が邪魔なだけだし
半信半疑で愛し合ったっていいことなんかない
誰でもよかったそういうもんでしょとでもないけど
半信半疑で見つめ合ったってねえ 何が変わるの
本当の気持ちを教えてちょうだい 話はそれから
さあ恋愛をするって天道
そんな目で見たことない その顔勢のその瞳
特別じゃないんだよ 何も感情感じない
反省されるのが大嫌いだって言いながら
この胸の片隅は誰かの影を探す
偶然あった日のことに 別の方法で反応されて
夢までの濃厚な衣装だけ 今だけが受け付けない
シナリオ通りに覚えてしまうの 計算してるでしょ
ああしてこうしてそうすればこうなる 疑い深いのよ
シナリオ通りに見解したくない そうしてこうしてしまう
何かがざわつく自分の内容が 信じたくなる
ああ心で鳴り響く アナタ
「ハッピーバースデー」
激しいハッピーバースデー 本能傷ついてくれない
初めての恋は臆病すぎるの チャンスが逃げても
半信半疑で愛し合ったって いいこと数がない
誰でもよかった そういうことでしょ とてもいいけど
半信半疑で見つめ合ったって ねえ何が変わるの?
本当の気持ちを教えて頂戴 話はそれから
ああ恋愛をするって 面倒
ハッピーバースデー
バースデーズ! バックスライム盛り上がっていくぞ!
ハッピーバースデー ハッピーバースデー
明日のことなんてどうだっていいのに この先笑い出すようになった
重なって振り返ると残って現れる楽しかった なんて思ってくるものなんだな
ただの中途半端 久しぶりで変わった でも変わってないよ
あの日だけここを歩いたならきっと 二人で
手を繋いだ日 キスをしたして ここしこしこした私だし 私
条件排斥者で負けてくる 黄昏の坂の途中
なんで なんで なんで 地平線と誰かの背中 消えてくるから
景色が滲んで 泣けてくる 愛なんてほんの一瞬
永遠の幸せはないんだ どんな一日もあるように 元気で生きたい
間違い好きだった 本気だった 不器用だった 僕がいけないんだ
今更気づいたって後悔したって 当たり前の十番端
作り込んだとこはない結果だったり 君に会えるんじゃないんだって
静かに言ってしまったらしい
入り込んで 買い物して 何をやって 泣いてきただけ
同じポスター持っちゃうなんて 切ないね
新しい恋も違う恋もいっぱいしたし 頑張ってきたんだけど
無理だったんだ
「情景反射」
情景反射じゃしょうがない 自分の気持ちに抗えない
情景反射で抜けてくる 黄昏の坂の途中
なんて なんて なんて 地平線の誰かの背が消えてくから
景色が滲んで抜けてくる 愛なんてほんの一瞬
永遠を知らざる愛だ どんな一日も両手にできているから
もっと!
まだまだ愛が足りないな!
もっと私たちに愛を叫べ!
愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!
愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!
愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!愛!
いつも呆れてしまうような 自分勝手な事ばかり言ってる
最低な人間だね あなた わかってるの?
Even if I don't have much experience
That's how I feel
I don't want to see you again
But I want to do something
I want to do something
You don't have to worry, come here
I'll hold you in my arms
It's not that I can't take care of you,
I feel sorry for you
Even if I do the same thing over and
over
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I want to throw it away because I don't
want to
Even if I'm more stupid than my friends
I can't see you anymore, that's love
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Even if I'm alone in this world
I can't imagine being alone
I want you to give me back
The love I gave you
I want you to give it back
I want to give up on you
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I can't see you anymore, that's love
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I want you to give me back
The love I gave you
I want you to give it back
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I can't see you anymore, that's love
I want you to give me back
The love I gave you
I want you to give it back
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I can't see you anymore, that's love
I want you to give me back
The love I gave you
I want you to give it back
I can't see you anymore, that's love
I can't say it out loud in my heart
I want you to give me back
The love I gave you
I want you to give it back
I can't see you anymore, that's love
Buddies, turn the towel around!
Let's get excited!
I stand in front of the camera and jump
out of the gate
Even if you look away, I'll keep chasing
you
If I push the button, you won't catch up
That's love
Can't I just look you in the eye?
My heart is beating so fast
I'm going at full speed
I'm going to follow you
Don't stop
I can't breathe anymore
Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly to the
sky
From here on, I'll keep looking for you,
you, you, you
I'll run to you
I'll take your place in the world
I always want to see you
Oh, oh, I'm excited
Oh, oh, I can't see you anymore
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I've been aiming for something that no
one knows about
Ah, I'm so excited
Your heart is beating so fast
I thought it was the loneliest day of my
life
I'm looking at you with my eyes closed
I'm getting more and more sad
I can't see you here
Ah, my existence
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on
This is love, love, love, love, love
Look at me
I want to touch you more than you are
precious to me
I want to get closer to you
Back drive, step on it!
Thank you so much for coming and
watching the stream!
I love you, Sakura Takano!
We love you too!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
My heart
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
My dear
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on
Fly in the sky
From here, I'll look for you, you, you,
you, you
No matter where you go
Instead of me, whatever distance we
travel, let's go for it
I want to be able to look at you at any
time
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I want to fall in love
Good evening, everyone!
One, two!
We're Sakurazaka46!
Thank you!
Welcome to our 7th single, "MAX LIFE"!
Welcome!
Wow!
I can feel the enthusiasm of everyone
here!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Thank you!
For those of you who are watching this
live, are you watching?
Are you watching?
Wow, I'm so happy.
I can feel your feelings from the front
of the screen.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the backstage.
It's been about 2 years since the last
time we had a backslide live.
This is the first time for the 3rd
generation to have a backslide live,
and for the 1st and 2nd generation, it's
the 3rd time.
We all came to this backslide live with
a lot of passion,
so I hope you remember all of our charms
today.
Thank you!
From now on, Konnagi, please be the MC.
Everyone, please get ready.
I'll do my best.
Konnagi.
From now on, I, Kojima Nagisa, will be
the MC.
I'll do my best.
I want to do this.
There's one thing I want to say, is it
okay?
What is it?
If I say "everyone" will you give me
back the gift?
I want to say it!
Everyone, everyone before the
broadcast...
Everyone in the audience, let's go!
Everyone!
Thank you very much!
I'm very happy!
The VAX Live has started.
I've been wanting to do it for a long
time, so I'm very happy to be able to do
it with you all. Thank you very much.
So, the backslide started at Toyosu Pit
yesterday, but it's already the second
day.
It's too soon, isn't it?
Yes, it's too soon, but we're more
powered up than the first day.
We're full of energy, so please enjoy it
until the end!
And today, not only the audience, but
also the streamers will be able to watch
the stream.
Everyone in front of the stream...
Everyone across the screen!
The streamers may be separated, but
their hearts are connected.
So please have fun until the end!
Yay! Thank you!
So, let's get straight to the main
topic.
I'd like to hear everyone's enthusiasm
for today.
First, Uemura Rina-san!
It's my first time to perform in front
of a small audience.
It's important to be able to see each
and every one of you.
So I'm very nervous and anxious.
But...
I think it's a live that can only be
done with this member, so I don't think
there are many live performances that
can be done with this member, so the
next single is also decided, so I would
like to do my best.
Thank you very much.
It's true that this is the only live
performance we can do with these 12
people.
I want to do my best while enjoying the
happiness that we can do together like
this.
Thank you very much.
Next is...
Akiho-san!
Yes.
That's right.
Well, I think there are a lot of lyrics
that I think are wonderful in Sakura-
Zaka's songs,
but I think it would be nice if we could
deliver it to everyone with a variety of
feelings and a sense of "rasshi" with
all the members of Bacchus who are here
now.
Thank you very much.
It's not just a song, it's a
performance.
I think there's a lot of things that can
be conveyed.
I hope you'll pay attention to that as
well.
Next up is Fuyuka.
I said this at the 3rd Anniversary Live
at Zozomarin Stadium.
The performance of the BACKS members at
that time was 0.
I told them to look forward to it today.
It's really hard to make it from 0 to 1.
I thought about it again.
At first, everyone had their own
thoughts about BAX, so it didn't feel
like it was all put together.
At first, there was, but as the
rehearsals piled up, I personally felt
that I could see each and every one of
the 3rd generation's way of working on
live performances.
Now that I think about it, it was my
first BAX live, and it was the 2nd
generation.
I think I was able to see that side of
BAX for the first time.
I think that's what BAX live is all
about.
I think it's a place where you can get
to know each other, whether you're a
senpai or a kohai.
I think I'm standing here now after that
period of time.
I hope everyone can see that today.
0 to 1.
I hope we can get 1st place today, so
please look forward to it.
I hope we can get 1st place.
Thank you.
During the rehearsal of BACK SLIME,
I often get close to Fuyuka-san.
She helped me a lot with the
choreography and everything.
She's like an older sister to me.
Am I growing up?
Of course. I was being pulled by
Sankisei's physical strength.
We're both so full of energy.
Last year, we only had Sankisei and
Shinsanmono live.
I'm so happy and grateful that Senpai is
watching us closely.
Today, we have a lot of BUDDIES with us.
After this, can we make a fun live
together with BUDDIES?
Can we make it more exciting?
Then, let's go to the next song!
Let's have fun!
"Moon Kiss"
Moon Kiss
Don't look at me with that face
I'm sorry for surprising you
"Moon Kiss"
The moon was beautiful tonight
That's why I miss you so much
I hug your shoulder
I want to steal your heart
It's painful to make excuses
I've been aiming for this moment
I wish I could be honest
But my youth is a cowardly emotion
Like a worn-out glass pipe
Ah, I kissed you
The wind blew by and the sun set
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's awkward
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
Moon Kiss
What should I do with my face?
Let's start walking without saying
anything
Actually, I hid it
I've always been afraid
Suddenly, I thought of it
It's like a weak syndrome
I've thought about it so many times
A soft feeling
I'm not good at imagining love
It's a painful moment
I've always been too weak
Ah, I love you so much
My heart is beating so fast
I'm sure you can hear it
I'm in a hurry
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's awkward
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
Ah, I love you so much
My heart is beating so fast
I'm sure you can hear it
I'm in a hurry
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's awkward
I wish I hadn't
I'm in a hurry
The wind blew through
The sun set
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's awkward
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
I'm in a hurry
It's awkward
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
If I look at the streetlight
I turn it into a line
I just look for the sound I want to hear
If I slowly turn my back
It becomes the end
If someone gets in the same car
I don't have to worry at all
Ah
It's awkward
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
I wish I hadn't
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
If I look at the streetlight
I turn it into a line
I should have given it to you as it is
I wish I hadn't
If I look at the streetlight
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
I should have given it to you as it is
Ah
I wish I hadn't
If I look at the streetlight
I should have given it to you as it is
I wish I hadn't
If I look at the streetlight
I should have given it to you as it is
On this road
In a roundabout
I could predict it
I should have given it to you as it is
Hey, isn't it pretty difficult
to have to live?
I can't stand that
But even now
I don't doubt it
Because even if I don't realize it
I'm right in front of that star
(Music)
After the concert
As always
We're riding on the last subway
When will we be able to
live in a different time zone?
I wonder
I want to live in a world without anyone
What was I thinking?
Was I sick because I was a child?
Even though it's a glass that's
glistening
When I realized it, I was wearing a cat
But even so, people live every day
while enduring it, right?
I was really curious about that
It's not that I'm selfish
Even if I pretend to be, I'm already
sleeping
I don't need to be strong
I don't have any expectations
for my future life
(Applause)
(Music)
I'm still in a daze
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
"I don't need this anymore"
I say, as if I'm going to throw it away
It's the first time I've had a meteor
shower
That's why I've been calm since this
morning
Even if I clean up all of a sudden
It's like you're my girlfriend
I can't open my mouth
I don't have a heart
I wanted you to be my girlfriend
The laundry you washed for me
I hope this time will continue
I'm still in a daze
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
Rather than having a special date
I want to spend everyday with you
The room we shared
Has become more beautiful than it used
to be
What should we do next?
I'm still in a daze
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
"I don't need this anymore"
I say, as if I'm going to throw it away
It's the first time I've had a meteor
shower
That's why I've been calm since this
morning
"I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed"
I say, as if I'm going to throw it away
It's the first time I've had a meteor
shower
That's why I've been calm since this
morning
I'm still in a daze
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
"I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed"
I'm still in a daze
The laundry you washed for me
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
"I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed"
I say, as if I'm going to throw it away
It's the first time I've had a meteor
shower
That's why I've been calm since this
morning
I'm happy, but I'm also embarrassed
"MIC DROP"
MIC DROP
I don't want to sleep
Because, you know, I'm just a half-
hearted existence
Can't I?
A doll in uniform
Everyone called me that
Because someday I'll return to the sea
It's fate, isn't it?
If I don't wipe it all off
It won't become a legend
Even I know that
I'm just a half-hearted girl
I don't expect anything
Are you all having fun?
Thank you very much
Thank you
It's the second time I'm here in front
of BUDDIES
I don't know what to say
Even if I do it every day, I can't get
rid of the tension.
But I practice a lot at home.
I was a little nervous, but the song I'm
going to sing now is a song that I think
everyone will like, and it's a song that
I really like, and it's a song that I
feel like I'm being cheered on by.
I'd like to make everyone feel that way
today, and I think it's been really
exciting with the penlight so far, but
I'd be happy if you could listen to it
with a calm mind.
I'll practice a little.
All right.
Thank you.
Well then, please listen
I don't know what to do next
If it's good now, that's fine, isn't it?
Even if I think about it
I just get even more tired
I won't resist, don't worry about it
I won't be swept away by my own emotions
I'm on my way
The road to my dream
I'm still in the middle of going here
and there and making mistakes
I'm on my way
I don't have to hurry
I have to be motivated
I'll do only what I like
Selfishly on my way
Let's walk straight
Straight on my own feet
Let's do what we want to do
Even if I'm pointed at by someone and
laughed at
My heart is calm
I'm on my way
Thank you for watching!
It doesn't matter how people look at me
Somedays I'm feeling
If I get tired
My favorite tunes
My favorite songs and kisses
Where are you now?
Even if I'm a little lost somewhere
That's fine too
Where are you now?
I won't be tied down by anyone
If it's a long way
I won't get lost
I'll take it easy and freely
Goodbye, adults
Goodbye, I don't care
Goodbye, I want you to love me
Until the sunset
I'll make it
No matter how far I walk
In my life
I'm on my way
The road to my dream
Let's go here and there
Even if I make mistakes
I'm still on the way
I'm on my way
I don't have to hurry
I have to be motivated
I'll do only what I like
Selfishly
On my way
I'll walk straight
With my own feet
I'll do what I want to do
Thank you very much
The MC from now on is
3rd Gen. Mukai Itaha
Thank you
Everyone, the live has started
Are you having fun?
How was Inoue-san's performance?
It was the best
Since yesterday
I've been watching you from behind, and
I've been looking forward to it since
the rehearsal, but of course I really
like "On My Way" by Inoue-san, and I'm
sure you all think so, but I like it so
much that I sing it at karaoke.
Is that so?
Yes.
I didn't know.
I didn't say it. It's embarrassing.
I'm glad.
I can't sing as well as Inoue-san, but I
really like it.
I really like the feeling of being
warmly supported, and I'm really glad I
got to hear it today.
Thank you!
It was wonderful!
I'm glad!
Also, since this live is an all-
standing, it's a little different from
usual, so if you're not feeling well,
please ask the people around you or the
staff nearby for help right away.
Let's have a lot of fun in the
impossible range!
This is our first live in 2020, so we'd
like to ask our members for their
personal wishes.
Who should we ask?
Since we have our eyes on you, Mio-chan!
What are your wishes for 2020?
It's a personal wish, right?
Yes
My wish for 2024 is to never look at the
inside of the fridge again
What does that mean?
When I'm bored, I get lost at home
Wait, wait, wait
Can you say it again?
No, I'm not.
You're wrong.
I look at the inside of the fridge when
I'm bored at home.
I look at the inside of the fridge.
No matter how many times I look at it,
the inside doesn't change.
If I open the fridge, I wonder if
there's any rice crackers in it.
Do you put rice crackers in the fridge?
I don't put much in it.
That's true.
I don't put much in it, but I found out
that there is no such miracle.
In 2024, I would like to try not to open
it three times in 10 seconds.
There is no way such a miracle will
happen, so please stop and look for
other hobbies.
I would like to look for a hobby that I
can do.
Next is Inoue-san!
Me?
Thank you!
I want to do a lot of work, I want to do
a lot of work like this, and I want to
make everyone have fun, and I don't want
to hate what I like and don't want to
hate what I don't like.
As for food, I noticed that everyone
told me to change my diet.
They told me to eat vegetables and bell
peppers.
So I decided to eat them.
And this year, I got a fortune-telling
for the new year.
It said that I won't change my diet for
my health.
So I thought, "Oh, this is a god's
message."
This year, I swore to myself that I
would eat all the vegetables and bitter
things.
Please support me.
I saw it.
What?
I saw Inoue-san eating salad before the
show.
Are you aware of that?
Yes.
Wow!
During rehearsal, I get hungry and eat
junk food.
But I realized that I didn't take
vegetables.
So I went home and bought vegetables.
I saw it.
Wow!
- Thank you. - I'll keep an eye on you.
Please keep an eye on me.
Lastly, Miyu-chan.
My goal is to play with snow.
That's amazing.
What do you do with snow?
- I make snowmen. - That's cute.
I want to throw snow.
That's amazing.
I can throw it.
I think everyone knows that I like rain.
I think everyone knows that.
I also like snow, so please remember
that.
If it snows this year, everyone will
think of you as "Niu-chan".
I want to have a snowball fight with
everyone.
That's true.
How about you, Itoha?
Me?
I was surprised to hear that Inoue-san
said that she doesn't dislike me.
I'm turning 18 this year.
I'm turning 18, so I thought I should be
more mature.
That's right.
I don't like the first step of an
adult's steps.
My mother sent me a meal the other day.
There was a bell pepper that I didn't
like in it.
I thought I could be an adult by eating
this.
That's right.
I don't usually look at my mom or anyone
else.
A little while ago, I was just eating
green peppers.
But there were about four of them, and I
ate them all.
Wow!
I'm amazing!
That's amazing!
So, everyone, please watch me grow up!
I want to see it!
The live will continue!
Everyone, please continue to enjoy it!
Thank you very much!
It's not a joke
It's the first time I've realized
If we start talking about love even just
a little
The serious feeling of "I love you"
Is something that burns from the heart
So that the unknown blood will run away
We can't feel each other
It's because there's something objective
Why is it important?
What's the point of thinking about it?
I've lost my reason for loving you
If you were to disappear from my sight
here
What kind of action would you take?
If you imagine it, you'll understand
How many hours do I have to wait for you
to come back?
I'll definitely come back
There's no place like home in this world
I want to look for it, I want to crush
it
We'll sing forever in that
I won't let it go
The truth is always vague
It's useless, it's useless
I don't have to say anything
I believe in love
Rather than trying to teach someone
It's better to stay silent
In the universe in the night sky
I want you to bring that light
And bring it back to me
Even if I'm overwhelmed by passion
I won't move
You don't have to let go
Until the day you understand me
Even if I don't say anything
Everything will be conveyed
Words don't matter
Conversations are the minimum
Lovers are always just looking at each
other
Silence is beautiful
In a world without sound
The pulse of love keeps beating
The heart beats
Let's have fun
If you start talking about love even a
little
The serious feeling of loving
It's going to leak from the heart
Don't run away without knowing
Please feel it
Even if it's objective
It's because you see it
Who is important?
Is it important?
No matter how much I think
I love you for no reason
"I love you"
The true wind that blows through my
heart
I want you to bring that light
And bring it back to me
Even if I'm overwhelmed by passion
I won't move
You don't have to let go
Until the day you understand me
What are you going to get?
I can't see the answer
Because I'm me
I'm not me
Dilemma
I have to go right now
I know
I can't move my legs
Even if it's a dilemma
I can't leave you alone
Because my heart is torn
What is important in life
Is to choose
"Let's get that hand"
It's too much
I saw a dream when I was a kid
I believe it will come true
Someone closest to me
I realized the existence that can't be
replaced
Even my selfish goodbyes
"It can't be helped"
You smiled at me
And gave me a white flag
I can't do it
I won't go anywhere
I don't care if I'm called a coward
I can't do it
I have to go right now
I can't leave you alone
Because my heart is torn
What is important in life
Is to choose "Let's get that hand"
It's too much
I saw a dream when I was a kid
I found my own way
While taking several detours
And several footsteps
Dilemma
I have to go right now
I know it
But my feet won't move
Dilemma
I have to leave you alone
Because my heart is torn
Where should I go?
I don't know
"Let's get that hand"
Yo! I wanted to meet you
Yo! The sky is so blue
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We're still the same as we were
Yo! The seasons change, the scent of the
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the burning sun
Let's go, let's go, let's go
I have to leave you alone
Because my heart is torn
It's too much
I saw a dream when I was a kid
I found my own way
While taking several detours
Yo! I have to go right now
Yo! The sky is so blue
Yo! My heart is looking somewhere far
away
Yo! Hope is really a bad thing
Yo! If I'm with you, I can go
Yo! If I'm with you, I can reach
Let's go, let's go, let's go
We are burning
Even if we lose our tears
Tomorrow will come again
Tomorrow will come
The wind of sorrow will stop
A new day will come
The sun is rising
Yo! Let's start again from here
Yo! Because freedom has nothing
Yo! We can go anywhere
Yo! Let's throw away despair with tears
Yo! I've been waiting for you
We are young
We are brave
We are breathing
We are young
We are brave
Yo! I've been waiting for you
Yo! Look at this blue sky
Yo! The world hasn't changed
Yo! We are the same as we were
Yo! The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the burning sun
Let's live, let's live, let's live
We are burning
Thank you for coming to the BAX Live
today
We are BAX members of SAKURAZUKA46
We have a lot of feelings for SAKURAZUKA
We want to cheer you up more and more
I hope your every day will be filled
with smiles
Power!
We are burning
Thank you very much.
The live is still going on, but are you
all having fun?
Thank you very much.
It's my first time standing, so I'm more
tired than usual.
I think it was easy to understand.
Don't push yourself too hard.
If you get sick, please take a break.
Thank you.
In the last MC, Ito-chan was talking
about her personal goal.
In this MC, I would like to announce the
big goal of the whole group to everyone.
Thank you.
This time, since the year 2024 has
started,
I made a new year's resolution.
I would like to show it to everyone and
announce it!
Ah, it's here!
It's here!
Well then, first...
Well then, Riko-chan, please!
Eh, what is it?
What is it?
Here I go!
Ta-da!
In the end...
You're good!
Well then...
This year, not only the 3rd Gen, but
also the Senpais, I want to have a lot
of communication and try a lot of new
things, so that I can grow a little
more.
Buddies, let's have a lot of active
conversations with me!
Thank you. Actually, when Riko-chan was
drawing this, I was there with her.
Riko-chan was smiling and said, "I'm
going to be more active this year."
So cute.
I'm going to be more active.
Please support her.
Next, Marino-san, please.
What is it, Marino-san?
Which one is it?
Wait a moment.
Here I go.
Please.
+15.
Wow.
Yes, that's right.
I don't think everyone can imagine it
yet, but I'm very energetic in front of
all the members.
I often talk about it, so I want to do
my best this year so that I can do it in
front of everyone in BUDDIES.
I will do my best.
Thank you very much.
The three of us get along really well.
When everyone finds Marino-san, we all
go up to her and say, "Marino-san!"
We're really close.
She's really funny.
We love her.
We all love her.
Thank you.
This year, we'll be able to see Marino-
san from Datsujizo.
Everyone, please check it out.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next, Rena-chan, please.
What is it?
My goal for this year is...
1 day 1 fanmeeting!
You're good!
I'm really happy.
You're good, aren't you?
Thank you very much.
In 2023, Ohtani Shohei was very active
in WBC.
He was making a dream note.
He was writing down what he should do
for his dream.
I thought it was really cool and I
wanted to be like him.
So...
There's a section called "Luck", and it
says that you have to take care of your
tools and pick up trash.
So I thought that if I did something
good for a day, my luck would
accumulate.
In order to grow as a group, both skill
and luck are important, so I chose this.
That's wonderful!
That's wonderful.
I hope all of us can achieve this goal
one day at a time.
Please.
What is your goal, Rika-chan?
I'm curious.
What is it?
This one.
My big goal for this year, as a group,
is...
Ta-da!
This is...
Sunao!
I wrote "Honest heart".
When I talk with my seniors, I always
try to tell them what I think honestly.
Sometimes I feel embarrassed and I can't
talk to them.
But I can't talk to them if I don't
express my honest feelings.
So I thought it would be great if
everyone could have an honest heart.
That's why I chose this.
It's wonderful.
It's going to be a world peace.
Let's make it a world peace.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Well, I think it's about time for
everyone to see everyone's faces.
You want to see it, don't you?
Well, I'd like to invite everyone here.
When I say, "One, two," please say,
"Come on!"
Are you ready?
Here we go, everyone. One, two.
Come on!
We're here.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We're here.
Wow.
Wow, I'm so happy.
Well, everyone's so full of energy.
I'm glad.
It was a good hope that something good
would happen.
Let's do it together.
It's the second half from here.
Are you ready to get excited?
Are you guys getting excited?
We're going to play a cute song, but can
you guys be cuter?
Can you guys be cuter than BUDDIES?
Let's have fun!
I was hesitating, but gradually I got
used to it
BUDDIES, are you ready?
When I'm with you, how can I feel at
ease?
I didn't think about love
Now I can see it clearly
Is confidence necessary?
Somehow, I feel like that
That's why I'm so proud of you
I've heard it many times
My feelings
Is confidence necessary?
When I'm with you, how can I feel at
ease?
I didn't think about love
Now I can see it clearly
Is confidence necessary?
Where is the certainty?
I've been looking for it
Since I became an adult
Somehow, I found it
The truth
I won't lie
I'll live straight
It looks good
I just need to be myself
No matter how I look at it
There's a me that only I don't know
There's no such thing as certainty
Everyone
Depends on their intuition
Is confidence necessary?
Somehow, I feel like that
That's why I'm so proud of you
I've heard it many times
My feelings
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!)
You told me
About our secret when we were young
The one thing I wanted the most in the
world was a pink sticker with a flower
on it
Ah
I knew that it would increase when I
grew up
But the more I looked at it, the smaller
it got, and I was about to throw up
So I decided to throw it away
And wrote it in a yellow classroom
And then, SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
What did I do to deserve this?
What kind of SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
Was wrapped in a mirror?
The one thing that came out of my lips
Was a world where I couldn't reach
But SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
Was more beautiful than usual
I think I knew very well
That I had always hidden it on my desk
But even so, I couldn't grasp it, so I
laughed
Eventually, time passed
And I found someone I liked
I started to look for a color that
suited me
What kind of SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
I was able to do a lot of things
But today, SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
I can't decide by myself
The image I had up until now
Is different from that of an adult
So SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
I want to be the most wonderful me
(SONIA, SONIA, SONIA)
So SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
Did you try painting it yourself?
What kind of SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
Was reflected in the mirror?
Because SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
Every time I fall in love
It's different, SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
My expression changes
The diary I kept drawing since that day
Today, SONIA, SONIA, SONIA
What color should I paint myself today?
Thank you!
Everyone, did you enjoy it so far?
Thank you very much.
It's been 2 years.
This is my second time participating in
BACK'S LIVE.
There are members who are participating
for the first time, and there are
members who are participating for the
third time.
Each member has a different situation
and position,
but we all have the same passion for
BACK'S LIVE.
That's how passionate I am.
I came here with the intention of
challenging VAXLIVE.
The last song I'm going to perform is
I think it will be able to convey our
passionate feelings to the maximum.
Then please listen.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
I've been watching you through the phone
all morning
I can't help but notice
I was late for everything I had to do,
and I ended up being late again today
I poured hot water on the cup, but I
still couldn't make it
I yelled, "What's wrong?" and the
noodles got soggy
I don't know why, but I just want to cry
I don't know when, but I just want to
cry
I've been playing games all this time,
but I can't help but cry
Everyone's always like this
Why are you in such a hurry?
Wait a minute
There was so much time
I want to be the only one
who can be energetic
Even if I'm told I can't do it
even if I'm told I can't do it
I don't want to be negative again
Even if I'm told I can't do it
even if I'm told I can't do it
I get it
I don't want to do it
God, can't you say something?
I want to know where that standard is
The sand of time that was full
disappears without doing anything
When I was that age
I thought I could do anything
What am I doing here?
I'm playing alone
Someone tell me
I'm going to take a step forward
I've come to a place where I don't know
the future
What should I do if I'm banned?
I just didn't know
I don't want to go again
Please give me a chance
What should I do if I'm banned?
I'm afraid of saying it
I believe in the power of my heart
God, please forgive me
I don't want to be like that all of a
sudden
The sun that is too bright
is leaking from the wind
I wonder if I can still make it
before the darkness comes
Even if I'm told to be a soldier or a
knight
I can't be a different person now
Even if I'm told to be a bandit or a
knight
I understand
I don't want to be abandoned
God, please don't run away
I want to know what the standard is
Even if I'm driven into a bad situation
I will never be banned
Thank you very much for coming to the
7th single "MAX LIVE" today.
Did you feel our passionate feelings?
Thank you very much.
We're still just getting started,
but thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
We will do our best to become more and
more attractive people,
so please continue to support us.
That's all.
This has been Sakurazaka46.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
"Akradka, Podniesie! Akradka,
Podniesie!"
(Sakata! Motegi!)
Thank you for the encore!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
We've come this far,
but each member of Backslide
really wants to deliver something to
everyone.
We've worked really hard to get this
far,
but I'd like to hear from some of you
today.
First of all, Konnagi!
What was that?
I wasn't paying attention.
How was it?
I'm sure you had a lot of feelings.
I didn't think I'd be able to be with my
seniors for so long.
Even when we're rehearsing together,
I'm still with the 3rd generation.
I'm still with my seniors.
I thought there was a small distance
before the BAX LIVE started, but the 3rd
generation joined the selection members.
There was a time when the 3rd generation
was divided through the 7th single.
I'm sorry.
I also felt very frustrated.
It's okay.
(audience cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
I realized that not only my body, but
also my heart was swollen, and I felt
both sad and frustrated.
But when I thought that I couldn't get
rid of this feeling somewhere, I got a
story about BAXLIVE,
and here, what was it? Uzuuzu, what was
it? If I was mumbling,
I realized that I couldn't get rid of
this feeling somewhere.
At that time, I thought it wouldn't
start, and I got used to the feeling
that I would definitely be able to do a
backslide.
After I decided to do a backslide, I had
a goal.
I've been with the 3rd generation all
the time, but as a member of the
seniors, I thought it would be nice if I
could have a conversation or a lesson
without a wall.
I've come this far with a great goal in
mind.
When I was rehearsing for Backslive,
I was able to achieve my goal.
I fell in love with my senpais.
Backslive is...
I think we all have our own reasons for
doing what we do,
but my goal is to be a role model for my
seniors,
without any barriers, from the bottom of
my heart.
I respect them, and I've always wanted
to get closer to them.
So now, I've learned a lot from them,
like the choreography and the rehearsal.
And I've also learned a lot from myself,
like how to do this,
and how to make a promise to go play
with Marino.
Anyway, a few months ago, I couldn't
have imagined a world like that.
I'm so happy to be able to backslide
with my seniors and third-year students
like this.
I'm so happy to be able to spend a lot
of time with my seniors like this.
There are still two days left, but I
feel like I'm glad I was able to do
BACK'S LIVE from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you.
I'm sure you'll be able to get stronger
after seeing BACK'S LIVE, and I'm sure a
lot of people will love you. Let's do
our best for the rest.
Inoue-senpai, do you love me too?
I love you.
I hugged you
Thank you
Next is Murayama Miyu
Yes
I'm Murayama Miyu
I might be a little bit similar to Nagi
When I was active as a main vocalist in
3rd Gen
This is my 7th single
There was a schedule announcement, and
all of a sudden, the 3rd generation
members had to move around on separate
schedules,
so there was a lot of frustration and
sadness, and I felt like I couldn't do
it all.
But through this backslide, I feel that
this period was a very necessary period
for me.
With these 12 people, I was able to do a
backslide.
I'm very happy.
Thank you.
Miyu-chan, do you not like me doing
backslides?
No, I don't.
When I was in the Philippines, she sent
me an e-mail saying, "I'm lonely because
Inoue-san isn't here, but I'll do my
best."
This time, I felt that I had to be in a
position to pull everyone a little bit
as a second-generation student, but I
was relieved that there was already a
strong presence like this, and I was
able to participate in the rehearsal
later.
Miyu-chan, as well as the other members,
were also very supportive.
I felt that a lot of strong-willed kids
were gathered here today.
Thank you.
I had a lot of feelings since I was in
the 3rd grade,
but I wasn't the only one in the 7th
grade.
I think it was from the beginning.
I think I was able to express my
feelings quite well.
There were times when I made my fans
sad,
and I felt the same way for the 7th
album.
But no matter who I am,
I feel like I want to support them.
Even if I expressed my frustrations,
I wanted to tell them that I enjoyed
watching Inori and that I wanted to
support them.
I felt strongly again that there are
BUDDIES who love me so much.
I really thought that I couldn't lose
here.
When I decided to hold a backslide,
it was a time when I was having a hard
time.
But I think people who can overcome this
Bacchus Live will definitely become
stronger.
So I think I still have a long way to
go.
There are still things that I haven't
found yet, but I'm going to find them
all with this Backslide, and I'm going
to turn them all into my own charm.
I always think that it is because
everyone supports me that I am who I am
now.
Everyone who is watching this Backslide,
and everyone who is cheering for me.
I think we can move forward and do our
best at any time because we have that
feeling.
Thank you, everyone.
This live is not over yet.
There are two more days next week, so
this is not the end.
We have to look ahead and move forward.
We have to work harder together.
There are Bacchus and Senbatsu members,
but I want to work with these members.
"Sakurazaka46 is the best!"
I'll do my best to make you think that
way!
Thank you very much.
Some of us are talking seriously, some
of us are crying,
but can you make the last song more
exciting?
More!
Can you make the song more exciting?
Let's enjoy the last song!
BABYMETAL!
BLACK DRIVE is the best!
Let's get excited until the end!
BABYMETAL!
BLACK DRIVE is the best!
Let's get excited until the end!
BABYMETAL!
BLACK DRIVE is the best!
Let's take a deep breath, the universe
is about to begin
No matter how far away the dreams and
hopes are
Come on, take a look
If you do it now, you'll understand
I'll try to stretch my arms as much as I
can
I wonder if the tip of my fingers will
reach the sky
I'll raise my heels as high as I can
I'll reach the limit I've reached
And finally, I'll be able to touch my
dreams
I want you to let me feel love
I can't explain it
I'll call your name
No matter what happens, you're not alone
I want to do something for you
Someday, I'll reach my dreams
I'll turn around when the time comes
Everyone is aiming for the same sky
Everyone is stretching their arms
Wow...
Thank you so much for coming to the
FANAMIME SINGLE FACTS LIVE today.
We will continue to aim for the future.
We will do our best to create a happy
space for everyone in the future.
Please continue to support us.
That's all.
We are Sakura Chika 4D Six.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[Music]
[Applause]