Backslide Senshuura-kun
Everyone, scream!
RU-HI! RU-HI! RU-HI!
It's a waste of time to be sad
It's completely different from what you
see
It's okay to cry
I'm not asking for understanding
RU-HI! RU-HI! RU-HI!
The suppressed identity
To the pessimistic adults
I repeat and say one thing
Don't push for cheap love
The boy from my hometown
If you run through with all your might,
you'll understand
RU-HI! RU-HI! RU-HI!
What are you going to do from here?
The world is dark
RU-HI! RU-HI! RU-HI!
Do you want to go back to the north
road?
When you've seen too much
It can't be helped to stay here
I was wrong
A dead end
Where will you live in the future?
Even if you try to do something
It's the same result
Just turn around
Become a person of both sides
What should I answer when I lose my
mind?
I was contacted by my parents and I
lived there
If it's over, if it's over
Where will it start next?
What will happen after that?
Open your despair
If it's over, if it's over
Find the exit to the top
Is there no continuation?
The lost present
What should I wait for?
Until dawn, I'll wait again
If it's over, if it's over
Will you do it again on a bright day?
Will you do it again?
No matter where you run
There is no way
A wall that blocks both right and left
I can't see it anymore
It's impossible
I shook hands, but I was just tired
A dead end
There is a limit to the world
What should I do from here?
It's still pitch black
A dead end
If it's a wall, I can break it
Will I go back to the way I came?
When I'm too old
I can't help being here
I made a mistake
A dead end
While knocking on someone's wall
I'm screaming in my heart
I can't see it anymore
A dead end
Will I go back to the way I came?
When I'm too old
I can't help being here
I made a mistake
A dead end
While knocking on someone's wall
I'm screaming in my heart
I can't see it anymore
A dead end
Will I go back to the way I came?
Hype
(Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!)
(Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!)
(Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight!)
Sorry, it's not a trip
I don't want you to understand
When did it start, when did it start
The pain was the easiest
My bangs are long
I want to hide my gaze
Go away, go away
I'm not here
Even if I'm suddenly confessed
I can't believe it
I'm covering my eyes
I just want to see you
It's just a joke
Half-heartedly loving each other
It's not a good thing
It was good for everyone
That's how it is, right?
I don't care
Half-heartedly staring at each other
Hey, what are you afraid of?
Tell me your true feelings
It's just a joke
Ah, falling in love is a pain
I've never seen you like that
You're the only one
It's not special
I don't feel anything
I hate being interfered with
The corner of my chest
I'm afraid of someone's shadow
It was a coincidence
I feel like I'm being forced to live
The corner of my chest
I can't accept it for the rest of my
life
I'll remember the scenario
You know what to do, right?
Ah, if you do this and that, it'll be
like this
It's a deep, deep night
I don't want to go along with the
scenario
I might just pass out
I want to believe in my own content
Ah, it resonates in my heart
"Hanshin Hanki" by Hatsune Miku
I don't want to hurt a girl who's
serious and serious
The first love is too cowardly
Even if the chance escapes me
It's not good to love each other half-
heartedly
It's good for everyone, isn't it?
It's okay, but
Even if we look at each other half-
heartedly
What's the big deal?
Tell me your true feelings
Is that the way to talk about love?
Ah, it's a pain in the ass to be in love
"Hanshin Hanki" by Hatsune Miku
I don't care what happens to me
At least I'm starting to remember the
last time
When I look back on it later
I remember how fun it was
To be able to laugh and laugh
It's been a long time since I've changed
No, I haven't changed
If I could just walk here
I'm sure we'd hold hands and kiss
But maybe it was a mistake
Ah, it's embarrassing
The reflection of the upper limit is
throwing me
In the middle of the hill of twilight
Why? Why? Why?
I wonder if it's because of the horizon
Because it's disappearing
The scenery is blurring and throwing me
Love is just for a moment
Hey, shut your mind up
No matter what, I'll hold your hand
So that we can laugh every day
I was naive, I was serious
I was clumsy, I was a coward
Even if I realize it now, even if I
regret it
In the middle of the hill of twilight
If I just walk here
I'm sure I'll meet you
Because my feet have turned on their own
I want to see you
What are you doing?
I want to meet you
It's painful to look at the same thing
over and over again
New love and different love
I've done my best, but
I couldn't do it
(Hey, hey, hey!)
The reflection of the upper limit can't
be helped
I can't help it
I can't express my feelings
I can't cry because of the conditions
I'm in the middle of the twilight
Why? Why? Why?
Because the back of someone on the
horizon is disappearing
The scenery is blurred and I'm crying
Love is just for a moment
What kind of happiness is it?
What kind of day is it?
Is it good?
Can you shout more?
One more time!
More!
There's still not enough love!
One more time!
More!
Shout more love to us!
Love! Love! Love!
I'm always writing self-centered words
that make me lose my mind
You're the worst person
Do you understand?
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
I don't want to go back to the beginning
Thank you!
But the back of someone on the horizon
is disappearing
The scenery is blurred and I'm crying
Love is just for a moment
What kind of happiness is it?
It's okay if you don't cry
Come here
I'll hug you for a moment
I don't want to cry anymore
I feel sorry for you
No matter how many times the sun is the
same
Come here
I'll hug you for a moment
I don't want to go back to the beginning
Thank you!
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Ready?
I'm alone in this world
I can't imagine the world around me
I can't doubt it
I want you to help me
I've always believed in my own choice
I have my own hope
I want to dream with God
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
I'm alone in this world
I can't imagine the world around me
I want you to help me
I've always believed in my own choice
I have my own hope
I want to dream with God
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Come here
I'll hold you tight
Don't leave me alone
I feel sorry for you
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Even if I have less experience
That's not true
That's love
Let's get excited with Buddy!
I don't know if I can say it with that
power
I'll leave a mark, don't worry
If I can live
Come on!
Dron Dron Dron Dron Dron
Dron Dron Dron Dron Dome
From here, you, you, you, you
I'll look for you and go anywhere
Instead of my eyes, no matter how long
the distance is
I'll look for you
I always want to look at you
Oh, cross over
Oh, the two of us
Oh, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh, about you
Oh, I love you
Oh, Dron Dron
Dron Dron Dron Dron Dron
Dron Dron Dron Dron Dron Dron Dron
Like a fairy tale
I want to be free
I've been aiming for the absolute star
Oh, the two of us
While mumbling
Your face
I thought it was the star
Nice to meet you
Oh, the two of us
Oh, about you
I've been waiting for you for a long
time
I'm here, but I can't hear you
Oh, my existence
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on
One-sided love
This is love, love, love, love
Look over there
The fingers you hold so dearly
I can't touch them anymore
Somehow, I want to know you more
I'm back, last week!
Thank you so much for coming and
watching the live stream.
I was really happy to be able to make
everyone's voice heard through this
backslide.
When you're having a hard time, when
you're in trouble,
I hope you'll be the closest person to
me and cheer me on.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I've been waiting for you for a long
time
I'm here, but I can't hear you
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on
Fly through the sky
From here, I'll find you, you, you, you,
you
No matter where you go
Instead of my eyes
No matter how far apart we are, let's
operate
I want to be able to look at you at any
time
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Look, I found you
Oh, oh, I love you
Oh, oh, oh, oh
I want to fall in love from here
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Good evening, everyone!
One, two!
We're Sakurazaka46!
Thank you!
Wow, everyone, from the beginning,
I can feel your excitement!
Thank you!
Today, everyone is watching the live
broadcast.
Can you see everyone on the live
broadcast?
Thank you!
It's still going to get exciting from
here,
so let's get excited together!
Yeah!
And today,
yesterday, I was a little sick and took
a break.
From today, I'm going to get better and
come back!
Yeah!
Thank you!
That's great!
I had a really hard time last year,
and I caused a lot of trouble for those
who were looking forward to it.
Today is the last Wax Live 7th single,
so I want to do my best!
I'm going to do my best as a full member
today,
so thank you!
Thank you!
Yes, from now on,
who can be the next MC?
Konnagi!
Yeah!
Let's get ready, everyone!
Yes!
Thank you, Konnagi!
Yes, please leave it to me!
Thank you!
See you later!
Yes, from now on,
Konnagi and Nagisa Kojima will be in
charge of MCing!
Thank you, everyone!
Yeah!
It's already early,
and today is...
last week?
The backslide has started, but today is
the 4th day, and it's already the last
week, so I'm really sad.
It's so fast.
It's so fast. It was so fast, wasn't it?
In the high school backslide, the four
of us were often in charge of MCing,
so when I thought that this would be the
last time, I was really sad.
That's what I'm really sad about.
These three senpais as well, but it
might be the last time we'll be able to
do a live with just the 12 of us.
I hope we can get through all of that
loneliness and have a wonderful live.
Everyone, please take care of me until
the end!
Please take care of us!
Yes, and also, since we have a live
stream today, can you all see it?
Wow!
Everyone!
Yeah, that's all for today.
To all the BUDDIES at this venue, and to
everyone watching the live stream,
I hope you can do your best to make this
the most fun live show in 2020.
It's 2024.
Huh? What was it?
It's 2021.
Oh, that's right!
2024!
I was a bit careless.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best to make this the most
fun live show in 2024.
Everyone, please take care of me until
the end!
Please!
I have a lot of energy, but the senpais
also have a lot of energy, right?
That's right.
That's good.
Well then, I'd like to hear your
enthusiasm right away.
First of all, let's start with Fuyuka-
san, please.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
It's the last one.
Well, this is the last time, so I'd like
to say what I think.
After all, the world is all about the
result, isn't it?
I'm often told that the result is
everything, but I think there is always
a process to the result.
I think it's very important.
If the whole live performance of
"Sakurazaka" is completed,
I think the live performance of
"Backslide" is not completed yet,
but I think it's a very beautiful live
performance that you can see the
process.
Thanks to everyone who is watching
"Backslide" today,
we were able to find meaning in our
existence.
I'm really grateful for that.
I'm sure the members will perform a lot
at today's concert,
so I'd be happy if you could receive
that.
Please enjoy it with all your might!
I'm sure the BUDDIES are also looking
forward to it.
Of course, they are watching our family,
but I feel that they are especially
watching the growth of the 3rd
generation, especially Fuyuka-san.
I'm glad to hear that the seniors who
are close to us are watching us kindly,
so we will do our best.
We will do our best.
I'm sorry. I'm a little nervous.
I'm very sad that this backslide is the
last, but many BUDDIES have come to see
us, so we will do our best until the
end.
Thank you very much.
Next, Rina.
I'm very nervous.
When I heard that I was going to do this
backslide, I thought that I could learn
a lot of songs and dances.
It's rare.
I'm sorry. I'm a first-year student, and
I'm doing this, and I'm saying this, but
I don't know if I can remember it.
I was worried, but I'm sorry.
I've been spending a lot of time with
them during rehearsals,
and I've been doing the 3-chorus,
and I'm really enjoying being with these
members.
I'm really sad that this is the last
time, but today I want to do my best to
show all the things I've practiced so
far.
Thank you.
Don't cry.
I'm crying, too.
During this BAX Live, I was able to
experience a lot of moments that were
saved by BUDDIES and the members of BAX.
I'm so happy that Uemura-san thought so.
Thank you for making me laugh a lot.
I'm so happy.
I'm so lonely at the end of this
precious time, but I'll do my best to
wipe away my tears.
Thank you very much.
Next, Akiho, please.
During the rehearsal period, I felt that
everyone's bond was born, and there were
days when I laughed a lot, and there
were many times when someone cried and
everyone hugged each other.
It's amazing that there are members who
can show their weakness like this.
I'm so happy. I also showed my weakness
during this period.
I was able to overcome it thanks to
everyone's help.
I'm sure each one of us said what we
really wanted to say,
or what we should do.
During this period, one team...
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
I feel like I've become a part of a
team.
This is the end of the day.
We all stood up today.
I hope we can finish without regrets and
finish with a smile.
Thank you.
I hope we can finish with a smile.
Two out of four people are crying.
The live will continue, so are you ready
to get excited?
Can you shout louder?
Louder!
Thank you very much.
Let's enjoy the show until the end!
"Blue Kiss"
The moon was beautiful tonight
That's why I want you so much
I hug your shoulder
Your lips that I suddenly stole
It's hard for me to make excuses
I've been hoping for this moment
I wish I could be honest
But love is a cowardly emotion
Like a fragile glass
Oh, I kissed you.
The wind blew by and the sun set
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's so awkward
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I wish I hadn't done it
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it was
I could have predicted
That this would happen
Blue Kiss
I wonder what kind of face I should make
Let's walk forward without saying
anything
Actually, I've been hiding it
I've been planning it all along
I suddenly remembered
It's a good meeting
That's what I thought
It's a soft feeling
I can't imagine love
Because it's a momentary moment
My concentration is too weak
Ah, I love you so much
Is the sound of my heart
Something that makes me so excited?
I'm sure I heard it
I feel like I'm in a hurry
It's awkward, isn't it?
Come on, let's make a dance
It's too late now
Can I be your lover?
I wish I hadn't done it
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it was
I could have predicted
Ah, I love you so much
Is the sound of my heart
Something that makes me so excited?
I'm sure I heard it
I feel like I'm in a hurry
It's awkward, isn't it?
Come on, let's make a dance
I feel like I'm in a hurry
The wind blew through
The light sank
It's awkward, isn't it?
I was afraid of this atmosphere
I wish I hadn't done it
If I regret it
I should have given it to you as it was
I could have predicted
It would be like this
I always choose the subway in the city
When I get on the empty train
I feel like I'm really lonely
The tunnel without scenery is like life
I love the sound of it
When I look down
I feel like I'm in a hurry
When I get on the same train
Ah
It's awkward, isn't it?
I feel like I'm in a hurry
When tomorrow comes
It's like always
It's like a rush hour
I want to go to a world where no one is
That's what I thought
I was sick at that time
I noticed the glittering glass window
I was wearing a blue coat
Why do people still live every day
while being patient?
It was strange to me
It's not that I don't like it
But I can pretend to be happy
I don't need to be happy
That's how I am now
I could have predicted it from the city
But now
I don't care anymore
I don't care where I am
or what I'm doing
Ah
What's important is where I'm going
I don't know how to use this power
I wonder where I'm going
I can't go back
I want to go to a world I don't know yet
That's what I thought
I repeated yesterday in this world
I cried and laughed
because I was nervous
Hey, that's okay
Isn't it pretty hard
to have a sudden experience?
I can't stand that
But now
I don't care anymore
I don't need to be hurry
I don't care where I'm going
After the party
I always get on the last subway
just the same as always
I wonder when I'll be able to choose a
different way of living for a different
time
I wanted to live in a world where no one
was there
That's what I thought
That's what I was worried about at that
time
When it's cool and summer
I noticed that I was wearing a shirt
Why am I living every day while
deceiving people?
That's what I thought
It's not like I'm thinking
Even if I pretend, I'm not happy anymore
I don't have any expectations in my life
"Sunday Afternoon"
It's a sunny Sunday afternoon
I'm not good at playing
I hate it because it's messy
I tried to push it with a pendulum
I don't have any limits
I'm a man
I've been crying since this morning
What you wanted
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough"
I just said to the piano
I'm sorry
"Sunday Afternoon"
It's the first time I've ever been here
That's why I haven't been home since
this morning
Even if I put it here
Someone seems to want to see
I'm pushing the door open
I've been crying since this morning
What should I do?
I'm a beginner
The laundry you started to fold
I hope this time will continue
I'm going around
But it's messy
Somehow I was happy
Rather than having a special date
I want to spend the day with you
My room that was close
It's more beautiful than I thought
What should we do next?
From the bottom of my heart
It's dyed in twilight
I don't want to cry this time
Because it's cool
What you wanted
I'm happy, but I'm embarrassed
"That's enough"
I just said to the piano
I want to boast to everyone
"Thank you"
Let's go, Microscope!
I didn't know I'd fall in love with you
so much
(I love you, I love you)
I feel like I'm going crazy again
I'm getting anxious
(I can't forget you)
I've fallen in love with you
I should've kept my mouth shut
(Hey!)
I'm so embarrassed
I don't know what to do
Let's go, Microscope!
I want to know more about you
Baby, I don't know about you anymore
Yeah, it's different than usual
Because I'm in love with you
I can't hide anything from you
I'm so nervous
Let's go, Microscope!
I don't know what to do
(I can't forget you)
I've fallen in love with you
I should've kept my mouth shut
(I can't forget you)
I want to know more about you
I can't hide anything from you
(Hey!)
I want to know more about you
Baby, I don't know about you anymore
Let's go, Microscope!
I don't know what to do
I want to know more about you
I can't hide anything from you
Baby, I don't know about you
I've fallen in love with you
I should've kept my mouth shut
(I can't forget you)
I want to know more about you
Microscope!
I've been playing in the middle of
summer
If the sun is here
I can explain anything
Microscope!
I want to know more about you
Baby, I don't know about you anymore
Yes, it's different from usual
I've fallen in love with you
I can't miss anything
Ah, I'm so excited
Come on, let's go to the parade
Microscope!
Woo woo
Let's start this last life
You know?
You can't say that
Mongaet people say
Mongloet is in the market
from les-de-mer
Pretending to be lost
In the end, today is the last day
I can't decide what to do
I'm sure I'll be in a good mood in the
morning
I have to go to school
Who decides the rules?
Even if I take a little break
I'm not bothering
(Woo)
My body is tired
Forget the difficult things
(Woo)
Float in the rhythm
Like a fish
In the LED aquarium
I have a good feeling
I've been waiting for a long time
I don't want to be an adult
Let me love you a little more
A doll in uniform
Everyone called me that
Because someday
I'm going back to that sea
It's fate, isn't it?
I have to throw everything away
It's not a legend
Even I know
Somehow
I'm a high school girl
I don't want to answer anything
I don't expect anything
I'm a high school girl
Only people I don't know
I won't be scolded
Such a beautiful world
I love you, I'm not stretching my back
Misery, yeah
Is that a sin?
I can't do the things I want to do
Because my feelings are cruel
That's why I wanted to change quickly
It's natural, isn't it?
I still haven't changed
I just want to have fun for now
I can't stay like this
Why is it like this?
It's fine, isn't it?
Please show me your love
Even if I get rejected
Who will prove it to me?
Because I am who I am
I'm just an ordinary teenager
I'm not even a child
I'm not even an adult
I'm just a half-hearted existence
Can't I say it?
I'm a doll in uniform
Everyone called me that
Because someday I'll return to that sea
It's fate, isn't it?
I have to throw away everything
So that I won't become a legend
I know that
I'm just an ordinary teenager
I'm not even a child
I'm not even an adult
I'm just a half-hearted existence
How are you?
Are you having fun?
This is the 4th time
I'm performing in front of everyone
Yes
No matter how many times I do it, I get
nervous
Usually, it's a song we sing together
I think it's fun to sing this song
I want to show everyone this song
I want this song to reach you, so I'll
put my heart into it.
Can I practice a little?
Please listen to it.
"Saki Nante Wakaranai" (I Don't Know
What's Next)
I don't know what's going to happen
next.
Isn't it fine if I don't think about it
now?
Even if I think about this and that,
I just get more and more tired.
I can't do it.
I won't resist.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be swept away by my own emotions.
I'm on my way.
The road to my dream.
Let's go here and there.
Let's just fail.
I'm still on my way.
I'm on my way.
I don't have to hurry.
I have to be motivated.
I'll do what I like.
Selfishly.
On my way.
Let's walk straight.
Straight on my own feet.
Let's do what we want to do.
Even if someone points fingers at me and
laughs at me,
my heart is calm.
If I'm having fun,
I don't care about what other people
think.
If I get tired,
I'll sing my favorite song.
Where are you now?
Even if I'm a little out of place,
that's okay.
Where are you now?
I won't be bound by anyone.
I'll take it easy and freely.
Goodbye, adults.
Goodbye.
I don't care.
I want you to let me do whatever I want.
I'll get there before sunset.
No matter where I walk.
It's my life.
I'm on my way.
The road to my dream.
No matter where I go.
No matter how many mistakes I make.
I'm still on my way.
I'm on my way.
I don't have to hurry.
I'll walk straight ahead.
I'll do what I want to do.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We're going to keep on performing, but
are you enjoying yourselves?
Thank you.
How did you like Inoue's performance?
It was good, wasn't it?
During rehearsals, he brings his guitar
every day.
We've been watching you practice for a
long time, and we've been listening to
these four performances on earphones
every time, and we're really moved.
I was really moved by the singing voice
earlier, and everyone was wonderful,
wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
And today, we're going to sing "All
Star".
This is all standing, so everyone is
sitting on the second floor, but there
are a lot of people standing.
Are you standing?
This is all standing, so everyone is
sitting on the second floor, but there
are a lot of people standing.
It's a little different from usual, so
if you feel unwell, please tell the
people around you and enjoy the live as
much as you can until the end.
Thank you very much.
This is the last show of the 7th single
"Backslide"
So I'd like to ask everyone about what
they enjoyed, what they struggled with,
and what made them happy during this
time.
Thank you
First of all, Reina-chan, please
I'm Reina Horakura
During the practice period of BAX Live,
there was one thing that made me smile.
It was when Rika Ishimori said,
"I love Mio Mato."
She had been thinking about this for a
long time before her debut,
but recently she was finally able to
convey her feelings to Mio Mato.
She was actively saying "Mio-chan, Mio-
chan"
but she was smiling too much
and it was bad for my heart
so I decided to go to her directly
and when she said "Mio-chan"
I said "Hey, Mio"
and when I said "Hey, Mio"
Riku stopped her
"Rena-chan, do it again!"
That was cute, too
Yeah, it was cute
And that is...
This is the part that healed my heart
during this period
That's right
When I'm with Mio-chan, Rena-chan comes
in with a big smile
"What are you doing?"
"I did this for you"
When I see her face, I can't help but
smile
That's why I'm always being teased
But I love Mio-chan
Next is Riko-chan
Hello, I'm Riko Endo
I was going to talk about something
serious after this
When I'm doing this kind of activity, I
always feel like I'm turning my back on
something.
But through this Backs Live, I realized
that there are people who support me
like this.
Even when I'm depressed because I can't
do it well, I think about everyone and I
feel like I'll do my best tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
So, today, I...
What should I say?
For the sake of everyone here, I want to
keep moving forward and do my best.
Today, I want to make a promise with
everyone here.
Thank you.
Like Riko-chan just said, when we do a
live like this,
we can really see and hear the fan
lights, towels,
the warm cheers during the MC, and the
calls during the live.
Your support is a great help to us.
Thank you.
Lastly, let's have our senpai, Marino-
san.
Thank you.
I'll be nervous at the end.
Well, I've done a lot of rehearsals
before coming to Bacchus Live,
but the number of songs I remember
depends on the person,
and even the songs I used to participate
in changed positions,
and I had to start over from the
beginning.
There were a lot of difficult things,
but I've done rehearsals with my seniors
and juniors.
It's really good.
I talked with my seniors and juniors a
little before the rehearsal, but we got
along very well after the rehearsal.
We played together in private and stayed
over several times.
We get along very well.
I see.
It's really...
I've been supported by a lot of members,
and the BUDDIES who have come here have
also given me a lot of voices today, and
they have made a great expression and
made me excited.
I'm really grateful for your support.
Thank you very much.
As Marina just said, the three of us,
the students and the seniors,
We've talked about this a lot before,
but I feel like we've gotten really
close to all the seniors during this
time.
We were told that this Backslide was
going to be held,
a little while before it started,
in a tight schedule.
However,
During that time, our seniors welcomed
us warmly, and we were able to do our
best thanks to them, so I think the
distance has shortened a lot.
This 7th single "Backslide" will end
today, but everyone, it will continue,
so are you ready to get excited until
the end?
Well then, let's get excited until the
end!
"Backslide"
Why are we staring at each other here?
You may think it's strange now
But it's really strange
We're playing with each other by chance
I can't get used to it
Even though there are many people in
this wide world
I can't believe we're in the same time
That's a miracle
The reason I can't get used to it
Is because I'm not here
I don't know why I feel like I'm living
more than destiny
I realized for the first time that I
don't have words
If I start talking about love even a
little
The serious feelings of "I love you"
Will burn from my heart
So that the white blood won't run away
We can't feel each other
It's because we're looking at a perfect
heart
Why is what's important important?
No matter how much I think about it
I can't help but love you
"Backslide"
Even if one of us disappears from sight
here
No matter what action we take
I can see it if I imagine it
I don't know, I don't know
I wonder what you're thinking
I'm sure you'll come back
There's no way we can be like this
In a place like this
I'm not looking for it, I'm crushing it
We're forever like that
We won't let go
Friendship
Belief
Love
Affection
Relationship
Useless things
Even if I don't say it
I can feel it
Rather than pushing someone to do
something
It's better to stay silent
In the universe of the situation
I want you to bring the light
I want you to bring that light
Even if you're passionate
Even if you're a child
Things that don't move won't move
You don't have to let go
Until the day you understand me
Even if you don't say it
I can feel it
The words we exchange
The first time we met
Lovers are always just looking at each
other
Silence is beautiful
In a world where sound has disappeared
I can feel it
I can hear it
I don't know
Even if you're passionate
Even if you're a child
I love you
That serious feeling
It's burning from my heart
We're more than strangers
We'll become closer
We'll become more objective
We'll see things
We'll become important things
No matter how much I think about what's
important
I love you for no reason
I love you
The sound blows through everything
The true wind
The world goes round and round
Until it comes back
Without hesitation
I wonder if I can see it
The price of chasing dreams
It's time to go cruelly
What are you going to get by giving up?
I can't see the answer
In order for me to be me
It's not me anymore
I have to go to the next stage right now
I know that
But my feet won't move
I can't leave you alone
Even for ten years
Because my heart can't live
The most important thing in life
Is to choose
But I don't want to get it
The more I love you
The more I want to see you
Believe me
From the closest person
I can't change
I realize that
I'm selfish
Even goodbyes
I can't help it
I was gently smiled at by you
And I gave you a white flag
I can't do it
I won't go anywhere anymore
I don't care if you say
I'm indecisive
I can't do it
Let's choose only one
If you tell me to choose
I'll regret it
There's nothing in this world
That I can live with
I can't live
I can't walk
I know that
There are so many paths
There are so many footprints
Someday I'll find my own way
Dilemma
I have to go right now
I know that
But I can't move my feet
I can't leave you alone
Even for ten years
My heart is torn apart
I don't know which way to go
"Dilemma"
Yo! How are you?
I wanted to see you
Yo! What is this?
The sky is so full
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We are now
We are now the same as we were then
Yo! The wind of the season
The scent of flowers
Yo! The green trees
The sunlight that shines on us
Let's live
I took everything away
I went too far
I didn't have anything
This road is peaceful
I wanted to see you
Yo! I can't stop here
Yo! Let's walk
Now with my own feet
Yo! My heart is looking somewhere else
Yo! Is there really hope?
Yo! If I'm with you, I can go
Yo! If I'm with you, I can reach
Let's walk
Even if I lose something
Tomorrow will come again
The wind of the season
A new day begins
The sun is rising
Yo! Let's start over from here
Yo! Because freedom has nothing
Yo! We can go anywhere
Yo! Just for one
Let's do something together
Yo! Because you've been waiting
Yo! Because you've been waiting for me
To the future
Let's walk
Let's think about it
We are friends
Yo! How are you? I wanted to see you
Yo! Look at the beautiful sky
Yo! The world hasn't changed at all
Yo! We are the same as you
Yo! The wind of the season, the scent of
flowers
Yo! The green trees, the falling stars
Let's live, let's live, let's live
We are buddies
You and me
We are friends
We are buddies
Thank you so much for coming to our last
concert
We just released our 8th single
Even if we don't win, we have to keep
going
Because you are here to support us
We won't give up so that we can make you
happy
Limitless possibilities
We are buddies
Thank you so much
I will be in charge of the live scene
from now on
Thank you
We will do the live in the second half
I'm starting to feel a bit dizzy, are
you guys okay?
If it's too hard, I can't do it.
Everyone, please take a break.
I'm sure you've all heard what Rika had
to say about this 4-day backslide.
I'd like to talk about it from here.
I think this backslide is a time when
I've done a lot of new things.
For example, this MC.
I've never been the MC of a performance
before, so I felt like I was a newbie.
But I got to be the MC of something like
this,
and it was my first time doing an aori
performance.
And I also did something else.
Huh? I didn't do it? Did I?
What did I do?
I'm curious.
I'll let you know when I find out.
That's right. I did a lot of things.
I think it was a backslide that made me
realize a lot of things.
To be honest, I thought I couldn't be an
MC and I couldn't be Aori.
But if I keep working hard, maybe I'll
do well a few times out of four times.
That's why I kept doing my best.
When I thought it was okay, everyone
praised me and said I did a good job.
I was really worried about this MC
today.
I thought I could do it.
Before the show, Nori-san said, "You can
do it."
This time, I decided to be in charge of
this MC.
I've never been told that I can do it.
I've never done it by myself.
This time, I was able to do a lot of
things by myself at BAX LIVE.
I thought that I could do one more thing
by myself.
That led to a lot of confidence.
I've been talking a lot like this.
See you next time!
I think it's going to be useful in the
future.
Thank you very much.
Not only the members of Backslide, but
also the other members told me to do my
best.
When I was about to give up, I got a lot
of words.
I thought I shouldn't be small.
I think it was a period when I could
look forward many times.
I'm going to talk to everyone.
Mr. Murayama
Distance
From Miu
I'm Murayama Miu.
I'd like to talk about what I thought
was good.
I'm Murayama Miu.
At that time, Uemura-san said, "I want
to have one dressing room. I want
everyone to be together."
And the dressing room became one.
We gathered in one dressing room and
talked a lot.
I thought it was nice to be together.
I'm so happy to have these 12 people.
I'm so sad that this period is over.
So I want to do my best today.
I'll do my best until the end.
Thank you so much.
It's been a long time since we've all
been together, and we've all been eating
together, and we've all been talking
together.
I think it's a very fun and precious
time for me.
I've been thinking about how I don't
want today to end, but...
We're a group, so I think we'll always
be together.
Let's stay together forever.
Let's do it.
I'm embarrassed. I made a mistake. I
don't want to. I'm embarrassed.
- I'm looking forward to it. - Thank
you.
Okay, next up is Mio from MAD.
Thank you.
Personally, I don't think it's easy to
do a live like this.
Especially this kind of backslide.
I think it's a place where each member's
dreams and frustrations can be exploded.
I think it's a place where we can
express the bonds between the members.
If it wasn't for BUDDY's love and
support, we wouldn't have been able to
do it.
So I'm really happy that you came to see
us.
I was really happy to be able to make a
live performance with the members for
the 7th single "Wax Live".
I'll lose my vocabulary for a moment.
It was a lot of fun.
When I dance, I feel like I don't have
the gravity of the earth.
It's hard.
I feel lighter.
I can dance and perform happily.
I was able to feel that yesterday.
I was able to rest in the middle of the
night,
but it felt like three days.
I was very happy to be able to
participate.
That smile is really nice. It was fun.
It was fun.
I'm sure it was fun because it had a lot
of meanings.
To be honest, there were many days when
I felt like I was going to give up
during the rehearsal,
but in the end, I thought it was fun
because everyone was there.
I think it's really rare to be able to
share this time.
I'm very happy to be able to say that
everyone had fun.
Finally, Inori-san, would you like to
say something?
Thank you very much.
I thought that all the members of
SAKURAZAKA were very honest.
The reason is that I'm in a position
where I have to lead them.
That's why I'm a little nervous.
Of course, there are a lot of things
that I have to fix, and I've told you a
lot of things that I think you should
do.
It was very heartbreaking for me to tell
you while everyone was doing their best.
I don't think Inoue has a heart.
No, I don't think so.
I want to make Backstreet Live a good
thing.
I've never done it before, but I've said
a lot of things.
Everyone said, "I'll do my best,"
without a bad look on their faces.
The next day, it got so much better.
I was watching everyone's feelings
change.
I said, "I have to do my best."
When I saw that, I was moved.
This group has a lot of honest girls, so
I thought it was good.
Inoue-san really noticed a lot of
things.
I think it's better to do this here.
I'm sure it's not something everyone can
say.
I think it's a very courageous thing to
People who say that really have a lot of
things piled up.
I have a lot of thoughts.
I think it's something I can say because
I'm doing my best.
I'm so happy about that.
Not only did they notice things that I
didn't notice, but they also made me
laugh and said, "You've improved a lot."
I think it was a time when I felt that
they were warm and wonderful people.
Well, I'd like to get more excited, but
can you get excited?
Can you get excited?
Well, I'd like to call everyone
together.
When I say, "One, two," let's say, "Come
on!"
One, two, come on!
Yeah!
Cute!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you all here?
Yes!
Are you ready, Buddies?
Yeah!
Are you ready to stream?
Let's get excited for the second half!
Yeah!
We're going to sing cute songs.
Can you be cuter than us, Buddies?
Yeah!
Let's get excited for the next song!
"Kizuna AI"
I was lost
(Kizuna AI)
I was lost (Kizuna AI)
Little by little
(Kizuna AI)
Little by little (Kizuna AI)
AI, AI, AI, AI, AI
Why am I so happy
(Thank you!)
When I'm with you?
I didn't even think about
(Thank you!)
Meeting you
Now I can see it clearly
Do you need confidence?
Somehow
(That's how I feel)
Somehow (That's how I feel)
That's how I feel (That's how I feel)
I've seen it many times
My feelings
Hey, really
(That's how I feel)
I know it already
I like you with conviction
(Thank you!)
Mr. Kuroha
Please bite me
(Thank you!)
Hey, more
I'll drop the skin
(Thank you!)
I won't even
Blame your eating habits
(Thank you!)
We're not related
Where is the certainty?
Even if I look for it
(I've lost it)
I've become an adult
(I've become an adult)
I've confirmed it many times
The truth
(The truth)
Without lying
(Without lying)
Let's just live on
I don't care how I look
I just want to be myself
You're the only one who knows
There's no certainty
No one is perfect
Only the first impression is the
priority
Do you need to be sure?
Somehow
(Somehow)
I've heard many times
That you can do it
Your feelings
Hey, really
(Hey, really)
I know it already
Hatsune Miku
The little girl who told me
The secret story when she was young
The lipstick she was wearing
Was the one she wanted the most in the
world
Ah
I knew that I could do it
When I became an adult
But every time I saw it
It was getting smaller and smaller
So one day
I stole it
And put it in my bathroom
And then
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Did you try to be yourself?
Was it reflected in the mirror?
I stole it from your lips
But it didn't reach you
But Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
It was more beautiful than usual
(Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey)
I think you already knew
That I was hiding it on my desk
But even so
I was a little worried that you wouldn't
notice
(Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey)
Because as time passed
When the person you like appeared
(Hey)
I started to look for a color that would
go well with you
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I was able to do a lot
But today
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I can't decide on my own
Until now
The age is different
It doesn't matter if you're an adult or
a child
That's why
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
I want to be the most wonderful me
And so
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Did you try to paint it yourself?
What kind of Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Did you see occasionally?
Because
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
Every time I think about it
It's different
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
The expression is changing
(Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey)
It's beautiful, isn't it?
The diary I've been drawing since that
day
Again today
Sonia, Sonia, Sonia
What color should today's mood be?
[Cheering]
Miyu-chan!
Everyone...
Did you enjoy it up to this point?
Thank you very much.
It's been 2 years since the last time we
held a BAXLIVE.
Some of us are participating for the
first time,
and some of us are participating for the
3rd time.
We may have different opinions on our
positions and situations.
But we all have the same passion for
BAXLIVE.
Today is the last day of BAXLIVE.
These passionate feelings I have now...
As long as we are here in Sakurazaka, we
will never forget you.
The next song we will perform is...
...the song that we have been holding on
to for so long.
We will do our best to give it our all.
Please enjoy.
"Kagoshima"
I was looking at you on my smartphone.
I can't get up
I was late for everything
I poured hot water on the screen
I should have left
I pretended to be sick
Hey!
I was in a hurry
Where has everyone go?
Why am I so busy?
Wait a minute
What the heck is this time of the day?
Getting yourself off track
This is all you can think of
You either belly out or you severe
Though I'm told I shouldn't
I can't be the
Largest influence
You either belly out or you sever
Though I'm told to stop
I can't do anything
Where is that standard?
The sand of time that was full
Disappears without doing anything
If I get serious
I can do anything
What are you doing here?
What do you play with?
Tell me the answer
Is it something that can't be changed?
It's about to start
Ideally
The future has been set
What should I do?
I just don't know
I can't do it anymore
Give me a chance
What should I do?
Is it the warmth of the moon?
I don't know
I'm worried
But I believe in myself
God, please forgive me
What kind of selfishness is this?
Hey!
The sun is too bright
It burns from the bottom of the wind
Until darkness comes
I can still make it
Sometimes I want to be told
But I can't do anything
If you're already here
You can't be different
Sometimes I want to be loved
But I can't do anything
I understand
God, please forgive me
Is it something that can't be changed?
I want to know what the standard is
Even if I'm forced into a bad situation
I will definitely be punished
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you so much for coming to the MAX
LIVE
Did you feel our feelings?
[Applause]
I will not give up here
I want to shake more and more
I want to do my best
That's all
It was SAKURAKURA46
Thank you very much
[Applause]
Thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
Even if I'm waiting for happiness
Yes, I fell in love with you
I'm getting excited
Because this is a love story
It's not a drama
I should have noticed earlier
Love should be the main character
I'm excited, I'm nervous, I'm nervous
People who are lost
Confess to me right now
I'm watching you from the side
Let's look at each other, hug each other
And kiss
Hey
Happiness is to look for it
Why?
I've never been in love
I've always been a fool
Because this guy and that guy
I love you
I'm such a fool
But I fell in love
I understand now
What people live for
Let's look at each other, hug each other
And kiss
I've found something that isn't me
Yeah
Thank you for the encore!
Thank you!
I thought it would be great if everyone
could say "wow"
when we performed "Why Love?"
Thank you!
I'm happy to see everyone's reactions.
We've come this far, but I'd like to
hear what the members have to say.
I think so, but...
Who should I choose today?
Who was it?
The person I chose was...
Kyoshu?
Awadakimashita!
Hi, I'm Yua Mikami.
Nice to meet you.
When I think about the time I spent in
VAX,
it's a very personal thing,
but I feel like I was able to be honest
and honest.
Well, the relationship with the members
is changing little by little.
Thank you.
When I was a 3rd grader, I was wondering
what I should do to my seniors.
I was lost at that time.
I was always thinking about what I
should do.
When I was practicing or on the move,
I was talking with my seniors or
juniors,
or laughing with them,
or laughing with them.
It's been a while since I've danced with
them,
and I'm glad that I didn't have to think
about such difficult things.
It's all thanks to the members next to
me who always make me feel at ease.
I'm really glad that we've come this far
together.
Thank you.
I think Reina is really strong.
I think she has the power to do
something on her own.
But if there's a lot of things going on,
I'm sure there are seniors and
colleagues who are always there for you.
Let's do our best from now on.
Thank you.
Next is...
Rika-chan!
Hello, I'm Rika Higashiyama.
Well, I knew that I would be the last MC
to speak here, so I've been thinking
about it all the time.
You knew, didn't you?
I've been thinking about it all the
time.
It's the last day, and I thought I'd say
something proper.
But today is the last day.
I'm going to talk about what I thought
when I was performing on the last day of
the tour.
During the 7th JINGLE BACK TO LIFE
period,
I became to love everyone, including my
seniors.
I respect each and every one of them,
I think they're cool and cute.
I'm the type of person who takes a long
time to open up to people,
but I was finally able to open up to the
3rd generation.
I've always loved my seniors, and I
respect each and every one of them.
Thank you very much.
Even though I have a lot of
shortcomings, I have not been able to
talk to my seniors in that state for a
long time.
I still feel that way, but my seniors
are really kind.
Even in lessons, they tell us what to
do.
But other than that, they make me laugh
and talk to me in a kind way.
I feel their kindness.
This 7th single period was very good for
me.
I feel they are still close to me.
There may be some parts that are not
enough,
but I think everyone here really loves
each other.
I think everyone thinks so.
I thought so when I was doing this live
today.
I think everyone can feel it.
Thank you for watching.
I think it's rare to have such an
experience because everyone's faces are
so clearly visible and close because
it's the first standing live like this.
I think it's a lot of fun to perform at
a big venue, and I think I like it.
I'm glad I was able to experience this
kind of live.
Thank you very much.
No matter who you look at, each and
every one of you is really wonderful, so
I hope that it will be a live that will
be conveyed to everyone.
It was really fun today. Thank you very
much.
Thank you.
I'm sure you can feel it.
You can feel it, can't you?
Thank you.
Rika-chan is also a solid person.
Rika-chan is always an idol to me.
I've always thought that.
When will this person stop being an
idol?
It's really amazing.
No matter where I look, what do you call
it?
Thank you for watching.
There were many things that I thought
were wonderful, not just that I was an
idol, but that I was doing what I
thought I was doing.
I thought so.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I also want to talk about something.
How do you feel about the word "VAX"?
I think it depends on each person.
I've never been happy to be told that
I'm a VAX member.
Thank you very much.
I often feel frustrated.
I think that those who support me and
the members here
feel it even more.
I had such a negative feeling.
But this VAX LIVE is really a chance for
each one of us.
I'd like to take this opportunity.
I don't want to miss it.
I've been here so far, and I've had so
many chances.
I think I'm the one who hasn't grasped
it somewhere.
I've made people who support me feel
sad.
But there's VAX selection.
I love the members of Sakurazaka.
I want you to think that I like you.
I want you to think that I like you,
Sakura.
I've come this far to convey my
feelings.
That's how I felt, and that's what I
learned from BAX Live.
I think I was able to do something that
I could believe in.
What I mean by that is,
I was doing this as a member of BAX, and
I was very frustrated.
But I thought I would definitely change
myself, and I did.
To be honest, I've been missing out on a
lot of opportunities.
Unfortunately, my fans and people around
me have all left me.
There was a moment when I thought, "Am I
really going to leave?"
But everyone never left me.
If I could deliver the feeling of "I
want to do my best,"
I would like to thank all the Buddies,
staff, and members who followed my
feelings.
How should I put it? My feelings?
Honestly, the results of my hard work
may or may not come out,
and I may be betrayed,
but I think I can definitely believe in
the feelings of the fans.
I've been thinking about it for a long
time, but during this period,
I was able to believe in everyone again,
and they believe in me, and I believe in
myself,
so I was able to do it thinking that I
would definitely do my best.
Thank you as always.
(Applause)
So, I will continue to move forward with
"Sakurazaka" as my 8th song,
but in my heart, I thought that I had to
make this Wax Live a success in order to
move forward.
Well, I'm moving forward, but in terms
of my feelings, I thought that I had to
make it a success.
Today, I want to express my feelings to
everyone.
I'd be happy if you could feel it.
Thank you.
I've been talking about my feelings for
a long time.
Shall we play the last song?
Are you ready to have fun until the end?
Are you ready to have fun in front of
the screen?
Are you still not enough?
Let's enjoy this song together!
BUDDIES!
Thank you so much for coming to MaxLive!
We love you so much!
Please come back!
I'll try to reach out my arm
Will my fingertips reach the sky?
Now, the universe will begin
No matter how far away dreams and hopes
are
Come on, grab them
If you let go now, you'll lose
I'll try to reach out my arm
Will my fingertips reach the sky?
Raise your heels as high as you can
Reach the limit you've reached
If you do that, you'll finally be able
to touch your dreams
I wish you'd let me fly
No matter how far away you are
You're not alone anymore, are you?
I want to do something useful
I'll try to reach out my arm
Everyone at the party!
Did you have fun today?
At the end of the end, you'll be able to
sing more, right?
Let's sing together!
Wow...
More!
Thank you!
Wow...
Thank you so much for coming to see the
live performance of our new single
"Backslide".
We'll continue to believe in everyone
and do our best without giving up!
That's all!
We're SAKURAZAKA46!
Thank you!
Thank you everyone next to me!
Thank you next to me!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!!!
See you again!
O-B-C-O, O-B-C-O, O-B-C-O...
Double Encore! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
I'm so surprised!
I'm so happy!
Double Encore! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
I didn't expect to be so excited!
I was so surprised!
I'm so happy!
We were wondering what kind of song
we're going to sing.
Speaking of this member's song, let's
sing that song!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's start!
Let's go!
Please listen to "Kakushinteki Kurowasu-
san"!
It was blurry.
The whole picture.
Little by little.
I understood.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
If I'm with you.
You will always be like this.
I didn't think I'd be able to meet you
Now I can see it clearly
I don't know if I need to be sure
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
I've heard it over and over again
My feelings, hey, really
I already know
Confidently, I love you
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
I'm wearing a black shirt
I'm wearing a leather shirt
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
I don't even know how to eat
I'm wearing a leather shirt
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
Where is the real thing?
Even if I look for it, I can't find it
The real thing
Without lying
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
Let's just live straight
I don't care how I look
I just want to be myself
I don't care
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
You're the only one who knows
Confidently, everyone
Only a moment of reliance
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
I don't know if I need to be sure
I've heard it many times
My feelings
(I don't know if I need to be sure)
I know it well
Everyone, thank you for the double
encore
Thank you
Today, this back drive
It's definitely a help for us
Also, to everyone
I want you to think that you want to
support SAKURAZAKA in the future
I want to do my best
Please continue to support us
That's all from SAKURAZAKA46
Thank you
Let's go this way
Everyone on the 2nd floor, thank you
I can see you
Thank you
Everyone, be careful on your way home!
Thank you!
[Music]
[Applause]