[Music]
[Applause]
Nice to meet you, everyone!
One, two, three!
We are Sakurazaka Honten Six!
[Applause]
Dear Buddies, thank you so much for
coming to the venue and watching the
live stream today.
I will do my best to make you have a lot
of fun today.
First of all, I would like to introduce
myself little by little.
[Applause]
I'm Asai Konomi, 20 years old, from
Saitama prefecture.
I'm Mahina Inakuma, 19 years old, from
Aichi prefecture.
Hi, I'm Haru Katsumata, 21 years old,
from Kyoto. Nice to meet you.
I'm 18-year-old Sato Neo from Kagawa
prefecture.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Chihiro Nakagawa, 17 years old, from
Nagasaki.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Wako Matsumoto, 20 years old, from
Chiba.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Meguro Hiiro, 19
years old, from Saitama prefecture.
I'm Ui Yamakawa, 19 years old, from
Miyagi prefecture.
I'm Momomi Yamada, 16 years old, from
Okayama prefecture.
I would be happy if you could call our
names a lot and liven up the atmosphere.
Thank you very much.
Now, I would like to call the person who
will be the MC today.
This is Umeka Shoji, who is familiar
with the narration of Sakurazaka.
Hello, everyone of BUDDIES. Good
evening.
I'm Umeka Shoji.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
It's warm. Thank you very much.
Today,
We will do our best to bring out the
charms of the 4th generation.
Please take care of us until the end.
Please take care of us.
Now, let's start over.
And now, I'd like to announce today's
title call.
Here we go.
"Sakurazaka 46 4th Generation 1st
Showcase"
Yes, this spring, Sakura Saka46 has
newly joined the 4th generation 9
members' first performance stage.
First of all, everyone in the 4th
generation, congratulations on joining
Sakura Saka46.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it's cute.
As you can see in the video, Naba is
really cute, isn't she?
She's cute, isn't she?
Yes, there's a warm applause, but...
Let's ask Inaguma-chan...
Are you okay?
Can you talk?
Yes.
How is it?
How does it feel to stand in front of
the Hatsu Buddies?
How is it?
It's my first time on stage, and I'm so
nervous to have so many FANATICS here.
Thank you so much for being so warm to
me.
It's true.
I've been on stage in Sakurazaka a few
times before.
Thank you so much, everyone.
You're warm and kind, so it's okay.
You're going to call out to me and cheer
for me, right?
Then I'd like to ask the four of you to
cheer for me, too.
You're going to cheer for me, right?
Everyone, please cheer for them with a
lot of voices.
There will be a live performance in the
second half of the game, so let's enjoy
it for a day today.
Then, the members who are on standby
after this, please head to the standby.
See you later.
So, I'd like to hear what the other
members have to say about today's
performance.
First, Matsumoto Wako-san.
Yes.
Well, I'm a little nervous, but I've
been working hard so that the 4th
generation can overwhelm everyone, so I
hope we can get excited.
Yes.
The opening was amazing, too.
It was really cool, wasn't it?
I'm glad.
I did my best.
Did you practice a lot?
Yes, I did my best with NEO.
I've been practicing, so I'm glad you
thought it was cool.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you for the wonderful opening
performance.
Next is...
Meguro Hiiro-san!
How do you feel standing in front of
your first BUDDIES?
I'm very nervous, but I'm very happy to
be able to meet you here for the first
time.
Today, the nine of us will show you the
best performance, so please enjoy it!
I heard that you are very good at
dancing.
Yes, I am.
Did you get interested in dancing?
Yes, I've always wanted to be an idol.
Really?
I was impressed by the idols I saw on
TV.
Thank you.
I want to start dancing.
By the way, who do you think is cool
among Sakura's senior members?
Ten Yamazaki.
I love her.
I'm sure this word will be conveyed.
Please appeal.
I heard you like Ten.
I love it.
It's cool, isn't it?
It's cool.
I hope you look forward to whether or
not there will be a dance after this.
Thank you very much.
Next, Ui Yamakawa.
Yes.
How do you feel about being on the stage
in front of BUDDIES for the first time?
Today is a special day that I can meet
BUDDIES for the first time.
I want to do my best to make BUDDIES
like us more and more.
You're the only member from Tohoku,
right?
That's right.
You're the only member from Tohoku,
right?
Yes.
Personally, I want to go eat the ramen I
ate in Sendai.
I really recommend it.
I want to go eat it too. It looked
delicious, right?
Right?
Please continue to look forward to our
sparkling stage.
Now that we've heard everyone's
enthusiasm and thoughts,
Next, I'd like you to show us your
special skills that the 4th generation
members are curious about.
Then, Yamakawa-san, please give the
BUDDIES a word of encouragement.
We will do our best, so please give us
your warm support.
First, here you go.
Let's go!
[Music]
Which one do you like?
I'm Asai Konomi, 20 years old from
Saitama prefecture.
I have one request for BUDDIES.
I'll say the catchphrase one more time.
When I finish saying "Dono Konomi",
I want you to shout "Asai Konomi" with
all your might.
Here we go.
Your favorite is "Dono Konomi".
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much! I'm so happy to have
you call my name with such a loud voice.
I've been practicing a song to cheer you
up, so please listen to it if you like.
Please listen to it.
I've been practicing a song to cheer you
up, so please listen to it if you like.
Please listen to it.
I've been practicing a song to cheer you
up, so please listen to it if you like.
I hope you find your favorite.
Of course, it's about me, but I'd be
happy if you could know a lot about the
charms of the 4th generation.
Thank you.
Let's get started.
I'm 19-year-old Hina Inaguma from Aichi
prefecture.
Thank you very much for coming to the
venue and watching the live broadcast
today.
The first showcase of "Sakurazaka 46 4th
Generation" has just begun, but are you
all enjoying it?
Thank you very much.
Today, I will do my best to show you the
charms of the 9 members of the 4th
generation, so please support me.
And from now on, I will use my
specialty, Naginata, to show you the
rhythm Naginata.
Please support me.
Naginata
I'm sure many of you think I'm a
crybaby, but I laugh more than that, so
I'd appreciate it if you could pay
attention to me.
Let's continue to liven up the first
showcase.
That's all.
That's all. I'm Hina Inaguma. Thank you
very much.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Nice to meet you, everyone. I'm Haru
Katsumata, 21 years old from Kyoto
prefecture.
Today, I'm going to play a song using
the guitar that appeared in the VLOG.
What song do you think it is?
I've heard a lot of things, but I
haven't heard the correct answer yet.
I'm a little nervous, so I hope you'll
watch me warmly.
Please listen to it, if only it were
always spring
"Spring"
The feelings of being strong
And you who are doing your best
I understand, it can't be helped
We are on a different path
If only it were always, always spring
I'm sorry
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying
Swaying, swaying
Even if I'm told the name of a town I've
never heard of
How far it is
I don't know
That's right, ever since you told me
The petals fluttered
It's better to agree
It's better to oppose
While looking for clues in your eyes
I kept silent
If you wish for happiness, sadness will
overflow
Even the cherry blossoms in full bloom
will be blown by the wind
The shining youth is not eternal
I thought I understood
But I didn't understand
Forever, forever
Is it no good like this?
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying
Thank you
I am
As a member of SAKURAZAKA46, I'm still
at the beginning of my life.
But from now on, I'll work hard every
day, and I want to be twice, four times,
eight times, sixteen times more
attractive than I am now.
Finally, I'll ask a question in Kansai
dialect, so please listen carefully.
Do you know me?
It's "Promise Night". Thank you very
much.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, I'm Neo Sato, 18 years old from
Saga prefecture.
Today, I'm going to play my favorite
song
with the violin I've been learning for
about 3 years.
Please listen to it.
Thank you.
I just performed "Sakurazuki" by
Sakurazaka46.
How was it, everyone?
Thank you.
Next, I would like to write my future
goals in calligraphy.
When I was in elementary school, I
learned a little calligraphy.
Have you ever done calligraphy?
You do calligraphy a lot during summer
vacation, don't you?
Thank you very much.
Well then, I'll start.
[Music]
I wrote it.
My future goal is...
Ta-da!
Overwhelming!
Thank you very much.
"Overwhelming" is a slogan of the 4th
generation, but I will do my best to
overwhelm the BUDDIES through my
performance.
I look forward to working with you.
"Overwhelming"
Nice to meet you, everyone. I'm Chihiro
Akagawa, a 17-year-old high school 3rd
year student from Nagasaki Prefecture.
I'm so happy to be able to meet everyone
today.
I'll do my best to make sure everyone
has fun.
But it's a little hard to do it alone,
so I called a helper today.
Torikichi-kun
Yes
I'm Torikichi
I'm a friend of Ninten when I was in
junior high school.
Yes, Torikichi-kun came to see me.
Everyone, did you watch my VLOG?
Yes, actually Torikichi-kun also
appeared in my VLOG, right?
Yeah, it was fun!
Right?
But recently I've been worried about
something.
Eh?
What? What?
Chii-tan has a lot of stuffed animals,
but
your favorite will change soon, right?
That's why I'm worried that you won't
throw them away.
Then...
I'm going to use Torikichi-kun's special
skill, "Flash Anzan", and if I get 2
questions right, I'm going to give it to
you without throwing it away!
Really?
Then I'll do my best!
Torikichi-kun...
Tanikichi-kun, can you do the flash
sound?
I can!
Really?
Then, I'll look forward to it.
Yeah!
Then, let's go straight to the question.
Here is the question.
Huh?
What do you think?
Did you get it?
Torikichi-kun, how was it?
I don't have confidence
The answer is, here it is
1,500 yen
The correct answer is this
No, I still have a lot to do.
Then, I'll go to the second question.
This one.
[What is the answer?]
[Answer]
Yes.
Everyone, what do you think?
Harukichi-kun, what do you think?
What do you think?
The correct answer is, please
2799?
The correct answer is this
There's still more.
Let's go to the 3rd question.
Here it is.
[The 3rd question]
Then, let's have them say the correct
answer.
Um...
¥3,431?
The correct answer is this!
Ahaha!
You okay?
I'm going to change the name of the song
This one!
Yes!
It was a bit difficult, wasn't it?
How was it, Torikichi-kun?
I'm confident!
The correct answer is...
*squeak*
*ding*
*laughs*
Yes
But after all, I thought it was cute
when I saw Torikichi-kun's face, so I'm
going to cherish it for a long time
without throwing it away.
I'm satisfied because I always got it
right.
I'm still inexperienced, but I'll do my
best from now on, so please don't miss a
moment and keep watching.
Thank you.
(Music)
(Applause)
Your gaze is here and there
I'm Wako Matsumoto, 20 years old from
Chiba Prefecture.
How did you like my performance?
Thank you very much.
I've been learning the violin for about
10 years, so I was a little confident.
Today, I'd like to try one more thing in
front of you, so please watch over me.
Do you know what it is?
I don't know.
What? You don't know?
It's not curry-making, is it?
The answer is...
Ta-da!
Basketball!
Actually, I was in the basketball club
when I was in junior high school.
Aiming to join Sakurazaka Basketball
Club, today...
I would like to try shooting!
I'll do my best for the first try
I'll do it one more time
Can I try to do a lay-up?
Here I go
Amazing
Thank you very much
It might be thanks to everyone's support
I wasn't in the practice at all, so I
was surprised myself, but I may always
be supported by everyone in the future,
but I will do my best to be of help to
everyone in the future, so please
support me.
Finally, I will do a catch copy again,
so if you say that your gaze is here and
there, please say that it is here and
there.
I will do it.
Your eyes are here and there.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best to keep your eyes on
me.
I'm Wako Matsumoto.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone. I'm 19-year-old
Meguro Hiro from Saitama prefecture.
I usually like to take pictures of
beautiful scenery and my favorite
moments,
so today I would like to show you some
pictures.
This is the first photo.
This is a photo of the sunset I took on
my way home at the 3 o'clock screening
of the Sakurazuka 46 audition.
I strongly hoped that I would pass the 3
o'clock screening toward this sunset, so
it is a very impressive photo.
And this is the second photo.
What do you think this photo is?
I heard a regrettable answer, but this
is actually a picture of me trying to
drink water during practice and looking
at it from the top of the cup, but isn't
it beautiful?
And here's the next picture
Everyone
I don't know if you know, but this is a
picture of Hockey that Murai-san and
Yamashita-san gave me during the
training camp.
In the documentary, it is said that only
Hina-chan ate it, but in fact, Ui-chan
and I also ate it.
After eating this...
I was able to do my best with the
feeling that I will do my best tomorrow
and the day after.
I'm grateful.
And this is the next picture.
This is a picture of cherry blossoms
falling on the river during the cherry
blossom season this year.
It's a very fantastic and my favorite
picture.
And today I drew a picture.
Together with everyone.
I would like to finish it with everyone.
This year, there was really a cherry
blossom garden.
From the cherry blossoms in full bloom
to the cherry blossoms in full bloom
I had the opportunity to see a lot of
cherry blossoms.
I want to make a lot of memories with
BUDDIES from now on.
See you in the next video!
Then I will draw a picture.
First, I will put out the paint.
I will put out the white paint.
And I will also put out the red paint.
Thank you very much.
I want to make a pink one, so I'll put a
little more red
and mix it
Yes
I'm going to draw the petals
One
Nima-i
3-ma-i
4-ma-i
5-ma-i
6-ma-i
7-ma-i
8-ma-i
And 9-ma-i
Yes, it's done!
Thank you very much.
I want to be a person who can give hope
and courage to BUDDIES with a strong and
unwavering heart like this cherry tree,
a tree that shines even in the dark, and
this thick trunk.
I look forward to working with you in
the future.
That's all from Megu.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Yamakawa Ui - "It's Ansen Time"]
It's Ansen Time!
I'm Ui Yamakawa, 19 years old from
Miyagi.
I'll be performing a special cheer
dance.
It's the first time we're doing a stage
performance together, and I'm really
nervous.
I'd be happy if you could cheer us on as
freely as you can.
I'll deliver a great cheer to everyone!
It doesn't matter who you like.
It's not just one person who can choose
the blooming flowers.
We're all doing our best.
I'll be cheering on the flowers.
It's Ansen Time!
Please, you, my friend,
Until the day we meet again, until the
day the rain stops,
Let's keep shining.
It's Ansen Time!
If you raise just one fist, it will
disappear.
I can see you clearly from the other
side of the bridge.
Beyond the wind and the sun, I want to
raise you.
I want to raise you.
I'm still inexperienced, but I'll do my
best to be a member of Sakurazaka.
Thank you for your support.
That's it. I'm Yamakawa Ui. Thank you.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Momomi Yamada, 16
years old from Okayama Prefecture.
I'm so happy to meet BUDDIES today.
Today, I'm going to show you the hurdles
that I've been doing for 4 years.
I'd like to run right away, but I can't
get hurt.
First of all, I'd like to do some warm-
up exercises with you.
I'll do my best.
If I say 1, 2, 3, 4, I would be happy if
you could say 5, 6, 7, 8 according to
that.
First, put your right arm to the side.
And bend it.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3, 4.
The other side.
2, 2, 3, 4.
That's good.
BUDDIES, you can still make a voice,
right?
Let's do one more.
Let's go.
Put your hands together and raise them
up.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3, 4.
2, 2, 3, 4.
That's good.
Let's do one more.
Next, put your hand forward and stretch
it.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3, 4.
The other side.
Thank you.
This is the end of the warm-up.
I'm going to run now.
When I run,
I would be happy if you could make a
wave by raising the penlight in the
order from the left of the standing
seat.
Then I will run, so I would be happy if
the person in the arena could raise the
penlight in the order of running and
make a wave.
Are the people in the stands ready?
Then, please start from the left.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Wow, it's good.
Wow, it's good. It's so beautiful.
Thank you.
Are the people in the stands ready?
It was so beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Now, I'm going to jump the hurdles.
The height of the hurdles I will jump
today is about 76 cm, which is the
height of a junior high school girl.
It looks very low, but it's actually
very high.
If I were to actually fly, it would be
really high, and I'd be scared.
And today, I'm going to fly.
Sakurazaka 4th generation
I'm going to fly the 4th generation.
I'll do my best to fly the 4th
generation.
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
I'm going to fly the 4th generation.
I'm very happy.
As a member of SAKURAZAKA46,
I think there are times when a big wall
stands in my way,
but I will overcome any wall like this
hurdle.
This is Momomi Yamada.
Thank you very much.
You've shown us your special skills.
You've shown us so many special skills
that you could catch a cold in Raksa.
It was amazing, wasn't it, everyone?
It was amazing, wasn't it?
I'd like to ask you a lot of questions
while we have time.
Can I touch this?
She showed us a shocking Fukuwa-jutsu
and Flash Anzan.
Chihiro Nakagawa-san.
Yes.
It was interesting.
Thank you.
I think the BUDDIES were also very
excited, but I was also very excited
behind the scenes.
When I thought of doing a special skill,
I thought of doing this, and I thought
of doing martial arts.
I really don't have any special skills,
but I thought I could do my best if I
was with Tarikichi-kun, so I tried it.
I see, I see.
In the preliminary survey, it was
written that your favorite word is
"somehow", but today it's "somehow".
Yes, because the buddies did something
about it.
I was able to do it. Thank you very
much.
It was a wonderful talent.
Thank you very much.
It was very wonderful. Thank you very
much.
I think it left a great impact on
everyone.
Thank you very much.
Next, Sato Neo-san.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
How was it with "Sakurazuki Violin"?
It was a wonderful talent from the
opening.
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous backstage.
But everyone listened to my performance
warmly, so I was able to finish the
performance.
It was wonderful, wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
It was a sense of unity that created a
great atmosphere.
It was really wonderful.
It was wonderful.
And you're very good at writing, too.
Thank you very much.
You were very good at it, weren't you?
It's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
I want you to be overwhelmed at home.
I want to decorate it.
It's powerful.
I'm glad.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Please continue to overwhelm everyone.
Yes, I will.
Thank you for the wonderful performance.
Thank you very much.
Next, Haru Katsumata.
Yes.
How was it?
I was really nervous.
I was like, "I'm not nervous. Yay!"
before the actual performance.
I was nervous right before I went on
stage.
Right before?
Yes.
I see. But you didn't look nervous at
all. You were so confident.
You were so transparent.
Thank you.
I thought it was a wonderful voice,
didn't you?
As expected.
Thank you.
There's something I'm curious about.
Yes?
Can I say it?
Yes.
According to the survey,
it seems that you have already mastered
the impersonation of the 4th generation.
Based on this information,
can you do it?
Yes.
It's a bit like that, isn't it?
Who is it?
No.
I'll say "this girl" and do it.
I see.
So, which girl will you imitate?
Which girl should I imitate?
From there?
There are so many.
Since we have met, I'll imitate Yamada.
Oh, no.
The theme is...
When we, 4th Gen, received our uniforms
for the first time,
Yamada's one word.
This uniform is for real!
It was very similar, wasn't it?
It was very similar.
It was similar.
I thought you were being very careful.
Was it similar?
I see.
It was like you were doing a
impersonation that I couldn't confirm.
I see.
How was it?
Receiving it.
It wasn't similar.
It wasn't similar, it seems.
There seems to be more, so please check
it out.
I'll practice a little more someday.
I'm looking forward to it. Thank you
very much.
Thank you very much.
Yamada Momomi, who was imitated a little
like that.
Yes.
How was it? Showing your special skills.
It was a great hurdle.
I was very nervous.
Were you nervous?
Yes.
This is the first time I've heard such a
grand warm-up exercise.
Everyone was amazing.
Yes.
It was a great warm-up exercise thanks
to the BUDDIES.
When you said you wanted to show your
special skills, did you choose hurdles
because you were good at hurdles?
Yes, I was doing track and field, so I
wanted to show my hurdles, so I chose
hurdles.
By the way, are there any other sports
that you are good at?
I don't have any sports, but I like
running.
I'm also good at running.
In a program called "Sokosaku"?
Yes, I'm good at running.
I think there will be a lot of sports
programs that will be shown, so I'm
looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm also looking forward to being able
to read it in the program.
Thank you very much.
So, it was a special performance corner.
Yes, then, everyone.
This is the corner you've been waiting
for.
"Omiyokuriren" member lottery.
Hi Buddies! I'm sure you've found the
members you've been waiting for.
Today, after the event is over,
the 4th generation will hold their first
gift-giving event!
I'd like you to go through each member's
gift-giving lane and leave the venue.
Which member's lane will it be?
I'd like to decide that now by drawing
lots in this box.
Now then...
Could you draw lots one by one?
Yes.
Those of you who have come to the venue,
I'm sure you have a card with a number
written on it when you enter.
First, please check that.
That number will be the number of the
gift-giving lane.
Yes, in the box over there,
There is a piece of paper with the
number of the lane written on it.
The number drawn by the 4th generation.
In the lane with the number on it...
We will send it to you.
This is also fate.
Whose lane will it be?
What kind of fate is waiting for you?
Yes.
Are you done drawing?
Well then...
I would like you to open the number at
once.
Well then, go ahead!
Ah, then...
From Asahi-chan...
Please tell us your name and number.
I'm Aikonomi. I'm number 4.
I'm Inaguma Hina. I drew number 9.
I'm Tatsumata Haru. I drew number 7.
I'm Sato Neo. I drew number 8.
I'm Nakagawa Chihiro. I drew number 6.
I'm Matsumoto Wako. I drew number 3.
I'm Meguro Hiiro. I drew number 2.
I'm Yamakawa Ui. I drew number 1.
I'm Yamada Momomi. I drew number 5.
All the members of the Re-en have been
decided.
The send-off party will be held after
the show. Please look forward to it.
The next member who is ready, please
stand by.
I'm looking forward to the send-off
party.
Well then, I would like to hear the
story of these three people.
First of all, Mr. Asai Konomi.
You were really cool, weren't you?
It was really cool, wasn't it?
It was really cool from this soft
atmosphere.
I'm glad you said so.
Did you practice?
Well, I practiced a lot. It was my first
time to sing on such a big stage, so I
practiced a lot hoping that I could
deliver a wonderful performance to
BUDDIES.
It was wonderful. Is there a reason why
you chose the name of the song?
I have a favorite song called "On My
Way". It's a song that cheers you up
just by listening to it, so I think it's
a great song to cheer you up.
I thought it was a great song, so I
chose "On My Way".
It was a very exciting and wonderful
performance.
Thank you very much.
Next is Hina Inaguma.
Your costume is wonderful.
Thank you.
Next is Naginata.
It was "Rhythm Naginata".
How did you meet "Rhythm Naginata"?
It was "Sahinagura".
I saw "Rhythm Naginata" for the first
time in my life.
I thought it was wonderful and I thought
it was not something that can be started
right away.
It's amazing.
Is that so? Thank you.
Did you practice a lot?
I've been practicing hard for 3 years in
high school.
Wow.
Thank you.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
Your shouts were perfect.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Don't cry.
I won't cry anymore.
Thank you.
Oh, I have a question.
You said you like ninjas, didn't you?
Do you want to be a ninja?
I long for it.
You long for it?
Yes, I long for it.
When I was a kid, I used to play with
the shurikens I made with origami.
I fell in love with it when I was
actually in a ninja theme park and was
held by a ninja.
Ninja Talk is a new ninja character,
isn't it?
If you dress up as a ninja, you might be
popular.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for adding a new episode.
It was Hina from Inazuma.
Next is Wako Matsumoto.
It was a wonderful blue moon kiss.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it was wonderful.
Were you nervous?
I was nervous, but it was better than I
thought.
Oh, that's great.
Are you confident and good at playing
the violin?
I haven't played it recently, so I was a
little worried.
At the opening, everyone was warmly
watching over me, so I was a little
relieved.
It's a great help, isn't it?
Yes.
Also, I heard that you're not only good
at playing the violin, but also good at
tongue twisters. Is that true?
Yes.
Oh!
Do you want to try it?
Yes.
Oh!
Well...
I can only do it a little.
Let's try it.
Pigs are hitting each other.
I'll say the tongue twister.
Pigs are hitting each other and falling
down.
I'll say it.
When the pig hit the pig, the pig that
was hit hit the pig that was hit, so the
pig that was hit and the pig that was
hit fell down.
Wow, the pig fell down beautifully.
Yes.
Wow, thank you very much.
It's amazing.
I thought it would be fun to have a
tongue-twister competition or a program.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
That's all.
Thank you for the special corner.
Next, I'd like to move on to that
corner.
It's the usual corner.
You get it, right?
It's a cute one, you get it, right?
I hope you can see it clearly
I'm looking forward to it
Before that, let's listen to this VTR
Good evening everyone, I'm Masahisa Rina
Are you enjoying the first showcase?
Looks like you're enjoying it
Thank you
I'm looking forward to it
Speaking of hospitality, I thought that
I had a lot of hospitality, and when I
looked back, there was a theater club, a
music club, and a K-on club, wasn't
there?
There was. I was in the theater club,
but I had to do it with ad-lib, and it
was very difficult, and even if I was
told to do it now, it was absolutely
impossible.
When I think that I was doing it at that
time, I think that I did a good job, and
I played a lot of music, such as playing
the piano.
Rina Inoue was playing the marimba.
Everyone was doing their best with
various instruments.
I have a lot of memories, but I think
that the 4th generation is showing
various performances while being very
excited.
I'm sure everyone is watching warmly and
having fun, so I hope you can continue
to enjoy it in a warm atmosphere.
Everyone, it's still in the middle, but
let's get excited!
It's not enough yet, let's go more!
Can you enjoy it?
Nice!
Please enjoy the fashion show after
this!
[Music]
[Applause]
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
I'm sure I'll be seeing you again when I
get back to the hotel.
I'll be waiting for you.
See you.
Yeah.
Bye.
See you.
*Cheering*
*Cheering and applause*
Aah, everyone was so sparkly and cute.
Did you burn it?
It was cute, wasn't it?
Up until now, we've done a lot of corner
projects
Did you feel the charm of the 4th
generation?
Even though they are young and cute,
they already have the feeling of
Sakurazaka.
I'm also looking forward to their
future.
I hope I can support them with everyone.
And everyone, please look forward to it.
It will be the first live performance of
the 4th generation.
Thank you very much.
Are you ready to get excited?
Are you ready to shout out loud?
Let's watch the 9 members of U.C.
Now, Sakura Saka46's 4th Gen live,
starts now!
I'll choose one.
I'm sure you're all tired, but as a
staff, I can't say that you're the real
Sakurazaka46 yet.
I want you to do your best to the point
where you're the best in your life.
I feel like I'm anxious and anxious.
I think it would be nice if the people
who saw the performance could connect to
this hope.
I have no choice but to keep this
feeling inside me.
I did it!
I want you to surprise me more when I
meet you next time.
Thank you very much.
Until now, it was just a lesson for
young people.
Various staff members have been involved
in this way.
I feel like I'm finally going to be a
member of SAKURAZAKA46.
Thank you very much.
We will proceed with the silent violence
as a formation version of 9 people.
Yes, number one center, Sato-chan
I'm afraid because I know the greatness
of this song, but I want to do my best
with a strong feeling because it's like
this.
Welcome to Sokurozaka, everyone!
I met you at this distance
It's like a dream
This is the first showcase
I want to do a live performance that is
unique to Yonsei
I think I was able to show a cool
performance
so that I can show everything I've
practiced so far
I'm going to make a Yonsei song
Thank you
I have no choice but to pretend to be
dead
What am I living for?
I'm Sakura, a 2nd year student at B6
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura!
But I still don't understand
Why?
I wanted you to notice me sooner
If I could turn back time
I wouldn't have had to say goodbye that
day
I would have walked anywhere with your
arms
Love is a cheat, cheat
Even if the answer I gave in the past is
wrong
It's not anyone's fault
I was the one who made the decision
It's a lie
It's a cheat, cheat
Don't run away from loneliness
What emotions, what did you lose?
It's cruel like a memory
Picture me, picture me, picture me,
picture me
Even if I cry and sing, I don't feel
like myself
I want you to always be on top of my
head
Even if I turn around, nothing will
start
Repentance is the worst process
Stop it
I'm sure everyone here cares
I can't go back to the days when it was
over
We can understand each other by
realizing it
How much did we love each other?
The red blood is still flowing
It's time to fight
It's useless
Love is a cheat, cheat
Even if the answer I gave in the past is
wrong
Before I knew it
I became alone and went home
No matter how many times, it's a cheat,
cheat
I'll run away from fantasy
I love you from you
Forgive me
I just keep repeating
I sing, I sing, I sing, I sing song
I'm still lost
I hate you, I hate you
Live with emotions
Love that's over
It's already the other way around
I just have to start from the beginning
Love is a cheat, cheat
Even if the answer I gave in the past is
wrong
It's no one's fault
I decided on my own
No matter how many times, it's a cheat,
cheat
I'll run away from loneliness
What did I lose from the emotions I
chose?
It's cruel like a memory
It's a cheat, cheat, cheat
I'll jump out on the ticket board
I want to chase you, but I'm looking
away
I can't catch up with you
My body pain
I can only look back
Ready, set, go!
The direction of the bus that goes
I have no choice but to go at full speed
Don't follow me
I'm out of breath
Come on, drone, drone, drone, drone,
drone, drone
Fly in the sky
From here, you, you, you, you
Wherever I look for you
Instead of my eyes
No matter how long the distance is, I'll
control it
I want to always be looking at you
Oh, oh, oh, I'm so excited
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I found you, nice to meet you
Oh, oh, oh, I'm so excited
Oh, oh, oh, I love you so much
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Drone, drone, I'm flying high
Like a bird, I fly freely
I've been aiming for something I
absolutely want
I'm so confident
I thought I wanted your heart the most
I look up at you
I float and look at you
My tears flow painfully
I'm here, I'm sure
Ah, I exist
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on
This is love, love, love, love, love
Look at me
You're so precious that I can't even
touch you
I want to know more about you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Notice my heartbeat
Come on, my love
Come on, drone, drone, drone, drone,
drone, drone, drone
Fly through the sky
From here, you, you, you, you
I'll search for you and go anywhere
Instead of my eyes, no matter how long
the distance is
I'll control it
I want to look at you all the time
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hey, I found you
Nice to meet you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
About you
I love you
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I want to fall in love with you
Good evening to all the BUDDIES here and
watching the live stream
One, two
We are Sakurazaka46, the 4th generation
So, Sakurazaka46
Azaka46, 4th generation, 1st show...
The showcase live has started!
Thank you very much.
We've just performed 2 songs, "Jigou
Jitoku" and "Doron Senkaichu".
How was it, BUDDIES?
Thank you very much.
Since we're here, let's start with
"Jigou Jitoku", the center of the show.
I'd like to hear what the heroes have to
say.
Yes.
This is our very first song.
It's the first song we've practiced, so
we're all very confident.
We're going to perform this song here.
I'm really happy that I was able to
perform in front of so many people.
Everyone, was I cool?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Now, let's talk to Ui, who was in charge
of the center in the second song.
"Drone Senkai Chu" is a song that has a
different atmosphere from the first
song,
and I wanted to deliver a cool and cute
gap between the first song and the
second song.
How did you like it?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I think the distance between us and the
audience has shrunk thanks to the
performance of "Hanamichi".
I hope we can continue to have fun
together from now on.
Thank you very much.
The first showcase of "SAKURAZAKA 46"
has just begun.
Let's have fun together from now on.
[Cherry Blossom Festival]
This is the first song we, Sakurazaka46,
4th generation, received.
Please listen to it.
"Shinda Furi"
Should I pretend to be dead like this?
Don't move even a millimeter
I have no choice but to pretend to be
dead alone
I won't breathe anymore
"Shinda Furi"
Faith is the energy that burns life
This is the battle of a lifetime.
I hope that all 9 of us will be able to
face the same expression,
such as the violence of the 4th
generation, together.
I want to pass the training camp.
I've been through a lot of training
until today.
I've been working hard at every moment
while being supported by everyone.
I will show you the best performance so
that it can bloom in the hearts of those
who will see it.
Thank you.
I don't like the time when it's too
quiet
I can't even breathe
I'm shaking in my chest
Why do I love people?
The ceiling of the room that turned off
the lights
Can you hear the voice of my heart?
I can't sleep even if I think about this
and that
What should I dream with my eyes closed?
I think silence is a form of violence
Don't hurt me anymore
A deep, infinite space
Like being sucked into the darkness
Everything becomes nothing
I was denied the light
By my side
If someone, if you, if you
Would look at me
I'm not afraid
"Silence"
Has the city already fallen asleep?
Or has it already died?
Scars disappear from the world
Everyone becomes lonely
In this world, everyone else is making a
fuss
I'm relieved by the presence of people
I don't want to be alone, I want to
believe
Nothing is happening
The hands of the clock are spinning
I feel like I'm going around in vain
Like sinking more and more into the bed
My body is triangular
To the point where my lips dry up
A silent handwriting
There is a sound called silence
I could definitely hear it
The words I was about to say end
It's normal to imagine everyday life
Even if I'm told it's a delusion
I can't answer the correct answer
I'll put a blanket over my head
I won't get any more love
Until dawn
Don't blink
Be quiet
I want to shout from myself
I can cry, I can shout
I want to let you know that I'm here
If I keep silent, you won't notice
Even if I love you, I can't forget
I want you to stop ignoring me
I can't breathe when I open my eyes
Even if I try, I can't think
What are you going to do to me?
I'll make you stop thinking
Silence is violence
Translated by Releska
I'm Konomi Masai.
I didn't have anything until I joined
Sakurazaka46.
But I don't know what to do.
I couldn't help but fall in love with
myself.
I didn't like singing, and I never
learned how to dance.
Of course, there were many times when I
felt that it was difficult even after
joining SAKURAZAKA46.
But surprisingly, I was able to do my
best because I was not connected to
CHIRA.
I was able to spend such a wonderful and
fun and happy day.
In such a situation...
I think I was able to love myself a
little.
The scenery of this venue, which was
wrapped in the light that the BUDDIES
showed me today, was very beautiful.
It was warmer than anything I've ever
seen, and it was engraved in my
unforgettable memories.
I'm still inexperienced, but I want to
say thank you to BUDDIES.
I will continue to work hard while
looking for what I can do now so that I
can return the warmth and strength as
soon as possible.
I would be happy if you could continue
to watch over our growth in the future.
Thank you.
I'm Hiraguma Hina. Thank you so much for
coming to see us today.
I was so happy that the BUDDIES welcomed
us warmly from the day our VLOG was
released.
I've always wanted to say thank you.
To all the members, staff, family,
friends, and BUDDIES.
What I have received from BUDDIES is
very big.
Thank you so much for accepting me, who
has nothing yet, gently and warmly.
I've never been able to say that I've
achieved anything with my own strength.
I was very upset about that.
Someday, with my power, I will return
all the people who have been involved
with me with a smile.
Now, as an idol, I am still immature
like Hina, but
Someday, I will grow up and show you my
beautiful wings.
Please take care of me from now on.
I'm Haru Kitsumata.
January 24th, 2004.
It was a warm and warm day like a spring
day.
Since I was born, I've been supported by
many people with a lot of warmth like a
spring day.
Today as well.
Since I joined a group that I loved and
admired, there were days when I was
worried.
When I saw everyone who kindly lit up
the penlight, I felt very positive and
happy.
That's why I want to give warmth like
spring to people who are lonely or have
worries, and I want them to cheer up.
And I hope this time will be a chance
for someone to do their best tomorrow.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Neo Sato. Thank you so much for
welcoming us, 4th Gen, so warmly today.
I've been admiring your passion for
music, your wonderful expression, and
your powerful live performances,
and I joined because I wanted to be on
the same stage as you.
I'm really worried about my future.
There was a time when I didn't know what
to do, but at that time, I met
"Sakurazuki" and "Boku no Jirenma" by
Sakurazaka46, and I thought I'd do my
best a little more, so I'm glad I didn't
give up and did my best.
As I was supported by my seniors, this
time I will do my best.
I want to be a support for everyone's
life.
My name is NEO.
I want my parents to be loved by many
people like cherry blossoms.
NEO means new in English.
I will take good care of my seniors.
I want to protect the tradition of
Sakurazaka 46, which has been built up
for me, and become a person who can blow
a new wind like me.
I'm still inexperienced, but I will do
my best, so please take care of me.
I'm Chihiro Kagawa.
I'm very happy to be able to see the
scenery from the stage that I've always
longed for.
I really didn't have anything.
I've never tried my best at anything.
I was just living in a daze.
That's why I joined SAKURAZAKO46.
I learned how to dance a little earlier
than I did before.
I can sing while dancing.
I think I've grown up a little bit.
I feel like I'm trying harder and
harder.
I still have a lot to learn.
I haven't been able to contribute much
as a member of SAKURA TAKA46,
but I want to continue to work hard to
become a cool idol like my seniors.
I want to keep running up the hill.
I've just started my idol life.
I'd be happy if you could walk with me.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm Wako Matsumoto.
I've been listening to this group's
songs since I was young.
I loved them so much that I wanted to
join them someday.
But one day, I became too old to be an
idol.
I can't write "Shindokibousho"
It's a dream that I couldn't make come
true once
I'm glad I didn't give up
I think from the bottom of my heart
From the day of the final examination
I passed and was called by my name
"Sakurazuka46"
I didn't have the courage to say my name
Today...
Each and every one of you has made
PSYRIUM shine
And because of that, I can proudly say
that I am Matsumoto Wako of Sakurazaka46
No matter what you say, no matter how
strong the wind blows
Matsumoto Wako is your number one ally
For the rest of your life
I swear to be an idol
I'm looking forward to working with you
I'm Meguro Hiiro.
I've always wanted to be an idol or an
artist since I was young.
It's always been my dream to be able to
deliver a smile to someone in a big
venue like this.
And I'm really happy to be able to stand
in front of the BUDDIES like this.
Thank you.
And today, my family, friends, and
teachers who have been with me so far
have come to the venue, and I am really
grateful for them.
And I have one more goal.
It is a dream to impress someone.
I don't think it's easy to impress
someone.
But I think the seniors of Sakurazuka46
impress and overwhelm many people.
I want to look at the back of such
seniors, chase them, and someday impress
someone with my own expression.
I want to work hard to become a person
who can give courage to those who can
work hard tomorrow.
Thank you for coming to this venue
today. I will do my best from now on.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yamakawa Ui.
When I first stepped into the venue of
Sakurazaka 46,
I strongly wanted to find my place in
this shining world called Sakurazaka.
When I passed the audition and was
called an "editor",
I was so confident that I wondered if I
could really be here.
I didn't know it was such a fascinating
place.
I wondered if I had the value to stand
shoulder to shoulder with my fellow
students.
I was so confident that I even thought
about withdrawing from this place.
Even so, as I spent time with my fellow
students,
I strongly felt that I wanted to stay
here forever,
and that I didn't want to be separated
from everyone.
Now, I'm just so happy to spend every
day with my beloved fellow students.
I can't help but be grateful to all the
people around me who support us and
watch over us.
We will continue to do our best, so
please continue to support us.
Thank you very much for today.
I'm Momomi Yamada.
I'm shy, I don't like to lose, I'm not
good at socializing, and I have a tough
personality.
So I was very anxious about whether I
could accept the BUDDIES and the 4th
generation.
However, the 4th generation understood
me, and the BUDDIES also warmly watched
me today, so I was a little confident.
Not yet.
I'm still inexperienced, but I will
continue to work as SAKURAZAKA46, and I
will do my best to shine like my seniors
and to cherish my identity.
Thank you for today. I look forward to
working with you.
We, SAKURAZAKA46, are standing here with
passion in our hearts.
We are still inexperienced, but we will
do our best to keep moving forward, so
please support us.
Thank you.
Now, please listen to the last song of
the first showcase.
I sleep with the lights on because I'm
afraid of the dark
Even now that I've grown up, I'm
actually afraid of things I can't see
I'm just afraid of the dark
I look up at the day I can't shine, I'm
relieved
I finally fall asleep
♪ "Kizuna AI" ♪ "Kizuna AI" ♪ "Kizuna
AI"
♪ I'm such a coward ♪
♪ Everyone's mocking me ♪
♪ But if I don't wake up ♪
♪ Like this again ♪
♪ Ah, no one will find me, bye bye ♪
♪ I can't help but think about it ♪
♪ I'm still young ♪
♪ I'm not used to being comforted ♪
♪ I know that humans will die someday ♪
♪ But I want tomorrow to come ♪
♪ Hey, will tomorrow come? ♪
♪ Yes, there are things I want to do ♪
♪ And there are things I left behind ♪
♪ I'm sure that living means ♪
♪ Not watching the darkness ♪
♪ Someone is by my side ♪
♪ Tell me it's not lonely ♪
♪ Yes, I'm a tomorrow girl ♪
♪ I believe tomorrow will come ♪
♪ Then I'll be able to close my eyes ♪
♪ I'm sure there's nothing here ♪
♪ That means there's no one here ♪
♪ I'll overcome the night ♪
♪ And go to the future as planned ♪
♪ Line of sight, eye mask ♪
♪ It's a scary world with its mask on ♪
♪ I don't want to know about this world
♪
♪ I'll keep my dream inside of me ♪
It's a scary world
No matter what happens in the world
I don't want to know
If you dream
You'll wake up someday
If tomorrow doesn't come
If tomorrow is despair
There's no point in living
There's nothing good
Time passes by on its own
You know?
All the tears dry up before I know it
Yes, I want more to come
I believe more will come
Cursing myself with unhappiness
It's creating a lot of things
No matter how many times
Nothing will come out
A dizzying day will come
If someone could see my smile
That would make me happy
Like you coming to the bathroom
On the side of the road
On such a peaceful day
If I make a mistake
The morning will come
Tomorrow, tomorrow
For someone
Thank you very much!
This is the end of this video.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please share this video.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
SAKURAZAKA 14th ANNIVERSARY
Everyone, thank you for the encore!
Thank you!
SAKURAZAKA 14th ANNIVERSARY
The 1st showcase of the 4th season, our
first live and the last live of the
night, did you enjoy it?
Thank you very much.
Thanks to everyone's excitement, we were
able to finish this live somehow.
I have a little impression.
Just one person?
Just one person.
Let's hear it.
How was it, Nakagawa?
It was closer to everyone than I
imagined.
I could see everyone's faces and
expressions clearly.
I could see that they were welcoming us
warmly.
I wasn't nervous at all.
I thought I was happy. Thank you very
much.
It's a very short time from the
beginning to the end.
Actually, I want to spend this time
forever.
But I have time, so I'll sing a song.
We, the 4th generation, will work hard
to become a member of Sakurazaka46 with
our seniors.
Thank you very much.
Finally, I would like to sing this song
with everyone.
Ready?
"Sakurazaka no Uta"
I thought it was natural to have
ordinary days
I couldn't meet you because it wasn't a
matter of course until today
There was a hole in my heart
Thank you for watching!
I don't know what happened, but I'm sure
you can overcome it.
I've never forgotten the cherry tree in
full bloom.
Even if spring passes and flowers
wither,
dreams will bloom here over and over
again.
Just as we suddenly remember,
we will gather in this garden.
If we talk about you,
I feel like we can meet again.
I can't tell anyone.
There's nothing you can do in vain
I was waiting for you to stand up
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
The cherry tree in full bloom
is blown by the summer, autumn, winter
wind
What were you waiting for
in that branch of the rain shower?
Even if the people passing by
forget the flowers of that day
The scenery of the next spring
We were always thinking about it
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Why do people love cherry blossoms so
much?
In the nostalgia of increasing dreams
So that each and every petal can form a
shoulder
The cherry blossoms will be in full
bloom
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
The cherry tree in full bloom
I've never forgotten it
Even if spring passes and flowers fall
Dreams should repeat and bloom here
So that we can suddenly remember
We gather on this hill
If we talk about you
I feel like I can see you again
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Thank you very much for coming to the
first showcase of Sakurazaka46 today and
watching the live broadcast.
As one of the members of Sakurazaka46,
we will continue to write the slogan
"Unity, Overwhelming, Blooming" that we
have raised.
We will do our best to become a
wonderful existence like our seniors.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
This has been Sakurazaka46.
Thank you very much.
"Unity, Overwhelming, Blooming"