AISubs v3.1
I'm Daifon, a collaborator of SAKURA MEETS.
Wow, is it a collaboration with Oda Ueda? I'm glad.
In this program, members of SAKURAZAKA46 collaborate
with entertainers.
It's okay, exit.
It's an experimental variety show where they play games together.
Wow, I'm glad. Can I show you my first combo?
I'm glad. I'll keep it as a treasure. Thank you.
Akiho Onuma.
Secret. Oda Ueda.
Welcome. I'm Oda Ueda, Oda-san.
This time, they play a controversy involving a cook and a guest.
Here you go. Wow, it's Junk Food.
The point is that it's a joke like a service that can't
be found in a small restaurant.
Onuma plays the role of a young cook.
The point is whether or not he can breathe in the role of a cook.
I think it's fun to hold it down here.
Basically, it's the tension of a young cook.
It's more fun to hold it down.
Oh, it's done.
I don't need jelly beans.
You don't need it?
This is the ad-lib part.
I don't need it.
It's delicious.
If you shake the house too much, you can't tell if it's
a friend or not.
I see. I got it.
Let's fix it.
Are you a devil hunter?
The ad-lib part starts now.
Onuma Akiho
Mii-tsu
Oda Ueda
I'm tired of doing business outside.
I'm hungry.
I smell bonito broth.
There is a small restaurant with a good atmosphere here.
Let's go in.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Are you Devil Hunter?
No.
Are you Devil Hunter of Chainsaw Man?
I'm sorry.
Please take a seat.
Onuma-chan.
Please tell me.
Yes.
Are you Devil Hunter?
No.
Again.
I said no.
I thought you were Devil Hunter.
I'm Devil Hunter.
I'm doing business outside.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Chainsaw Man is popular.
Onuma-chan.
Please take a seat.
Thank you.
Please let me know if you have any order.
You are a kind lady.
May I order?
Yes.
I'd like to have a set meal.
Sure.
Please wait a moment.
Onuma-chan.
Yes.
What is a set meal?
I smelled bonito broth.
Is it a fish stew?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Wow! Junk food!
Hamburgers at a restaurant!
Where's the bonito broth?
Here, it's a side dish.
It's a huge miso!
It's not a side dish!
If it's bland, use this. Honey mustard.
Honey mustard?
Don't you usually use yuzu pepper?
I only use one honey mustard.
One honey mustard?
I'm sorry, I forgot to ask for a drink.
Do you have anything to drink?
I'm done with work, so I'll have a drink.
Good, we have a lot of drinks at our store.
Choose whatever you like.
Climbers!
The ones you drink at clubs!
They're so small, but they have a lot of alcohol!
This one.
My late husband loved it.
Your husband really loved it, didn't he?
That's not something you say with that kind of drink!
Onuma-chan, is that done?
It might be done.
It's done!
Is it oden? Can I have some?
I can finally eat Japanese food!
Jelly beans!
There's jelly beans in the oden container!
I don't need it!
You don't need it?
There's also G-A-M-U.
G-A-M-U?
Gum.
Gum?
She doesn't need gum!
Why?
G-A-M-U!
Gum?
Gum!
I don't need it!
You don't need it?
That's too bad, Onuma-chan.
There's also a new dish I made.
Would you like to try it?
What?
You don't have to order it.
I'm sorry.
I made a lot of things.
It's fried butter.
I'm sorry!
I'm going to die!
Don't say that!
Don't laugh at me!
Onuma-chan, I'll put up a sign, can you go get it?
A sign that lights up with a loud noise!
What is this place?
What's going on?
Onuma-chan, thank you, thank you.
Oh my, it's already this late?
I'm sorry.
I've been preparing for business at night.
Can I leave this place for a while?
Go ahead.
Thank you. Then, Onuma-chan, let's go.
Preparing for business at night...
Do they prepare for it?
What?
What is this sound?
They don't have a club at night!
They run a club at night!
Can I join them?
I'm a foreigner!
I'll definitely come back to this place!
Thank you very much!
Onuma-chan, thank you.
That was perfect!
That was the best!
I was really nervous, but before I went in, you two
created a world for me.
That's so cool!
I was just jumping in.
Really? I was more excited.
The world was a mess.
If you look at my sweat, you'll see.
You were doing the same thing?
Onuma-chan was holding it in.
She was so confident.
Thank you.
The last part of the club was really good.
Really?
You were dancing in the cherry blossoms.
I want to see that part again.
What kind of Gori Gori Daikon was that?
It was really good.
As for the ad-lib,
there's also G-A-M-U.
G-A-M-U?
Gum.
Gum?
I don't want to hear it.
I was wondering which ad-lib I should do.
During the rehearsal,
you said,
cauliflower.
I did?
That was really funny.
How about cauliflower?
Cauliflower?
Wait a minute.
I'm going to laugh.
How about cauliflower?
You mean something like this?
Something like this?
What should I do?
Wait a minute.
I'm going to laugh.
Here we go.
I might want to get some cauliflower.
Really?
It's my first time to be on the show,
so I'm really glad.
You look gorgeous.
I didn't think it was my first time.
I really want to be a young lady.
I want to follow you for the rest of my life.
Then,
let's do it in Kitashinchi.
Please.
Let's do it.
Thank you.
I'm so excited.
Don't worry.
It's the exit.
It's a game that's hard to say in a commercial.
I've been keeping it a secret.
I've been watching it since it started.
Why did you keep it a secret?
I'm a big fan.
When I was in Osaka or Tokyo, I didn't have any friends.
I saw the cherry blossoms and I thought they were my friends.
I've been watching it since I was in the first grade of
the second grade.
I'm about to cry.
We're about to cry, too.
You're a big sister.
Let's play with my sisters today.
What kind of game did Oda Ueda bring in?
It's a reverse game.
It's simple.
When I'm with Oda, I say the words that Oda says.
For example, TV Asahi.
It's like a newspaper in the dark.
King of Contents
M1 Grand Prix
That's fine, too.
Let's see how many you can answer.
It's hard.
I'll do my best.
Each member of Sakurazaka will be the answerer.
Except for Oda Ueda, the answerers will be eliminated.
The loser will be punished by Masumoto Kouan.
Are you OK, Masumoto-chan?
Yes, leave it to me.
It's really scary.
Scary thumbs-up.
The top batter is Onuma.
Start the game.
The person next to me.
A woman near the town.
Run, Melos.
A girl staying at a hotel.
Avoid cheese.
A boy.
A woman landing.
A woman getting on a plane.
A woman getting off on a bicycle.
The person next to her is Inoue.
Start the game.
A big plan.
A big failure.
Olive oil.
Rice oil.
An emergency door.
It's OK. It's OK.
An exit.
A double jump.
A single jump.
Crayon Shin-chan.
Chateau Honda.
Inoue will avoid the punishment game with 5 points.
The next challenger is Masumoto.
Start the game.
Sen and Chihiro's Kamikakushi.
Hyaku and Taro's Konnichiwa.
Ambulance.
Genki Dayo.
Harry Potter.
Harry Potaranai.
Carbonated water.
Shizukana Oyu.
Tanpopo no Watage.
Happa no Mosa Mosa.
Westland.
Harry Potaranai.
It's a character.
Harry Potter.
It's a person's name.
It's out.
It's Harry Potter.
It's a person with glasses from overseas.
It's a person with glasses from Japan.
It's Rokkaku Seiji.
Avoid the penalty game with 5 points.
It's a penalty game.
Takemoto, let's go.
Chukemon.
Start the game.
Pink lady.
Blue man.
Bean light bulb.
LED light.
Charlie and Chocolate Factory.
Is there anyone who is not Charlie?
Charlie?
Lip cream.
Kassakasa no...
Kassakasa no kuchibiru.
Dog walk.
Run around the cat.
Cameraman.
The one who is being filmed.
You are correct.
Charlie and Chocolate Factory.
It's a difficult one.
Charlie and Chocolate Factory is...
Tanaka's abstract art.
Let's go with this.
Takemoto is in the lead with 6 points.
The punishment game is decided.
We are going to have a moonwalk.
I've never heard of it.
It's a genre I don't know, but it sounds good.
Please do the moonwalk.
I can do it.
I think I can do it.
She did it at the end.
I'm going to be good at it from now on.
Moonwalk?
Ueda-san, have you ever done a crab-shaped moonwalk?
Actually, I can do it.
That's the worst.
Please do the crab-shaped moonwalk.
Mom, you can do it.
Next week, Inoue Rina and Takemoto Yui meet Zoffy.
Are you guys in love?
Gum?
I don't know.
G-A-M-U