AISubs v3.1
TAKEMOTO YUNYAMOTO
I, TAKEMOTO YUNYAMOTO, will collaborate with Zoffy.
You are my mother.
We are TAKEMOTO YUNYAMOTO.
That's why I said that.
I don't remember anything.
I'm sorry.
TAKEMOTO YUNYAMOTO
This program is a collaborative program with the
members of SAKURAZAKA46 and the entertainer.
I'm going to go out like this.
Are you in love?
This is an experimental variety show where they play
games together.
This is difficult.
This is a great development.
What does that mean?
Inoue and TAKEMOTO will be ad-libs from now on.
Hey, wait a minute.
This is dangerous.
Inoue Rina and TAKEMOTO Yui.
Mitsu.
Zoffy.
Give me a pencil.
I don't give you a pencil.
This time, KONTO will challenge the scene where an
unpopular actor asks her to marry him.
Where is such a guarantee?
I can act.
KONTO shows his acting ability as an actor from the
middle of the program.
I was acting.
Inoue, who plays her, and TAKEMOTO, who plays her
mother, also show their acting ability.
Inoue is over-acting as if he had been attacked by a zombie.
This is a deliberate act.
Father, look at this.
Look at the acting of the two of them.
I'm sorry.
I didn't make this up.
She asked me to play the role of her mother, too.
The story of their identity changes.
Shiiguma and KONTO by now.
Rina Inoue and Yui Takemoto
Miitsu
Zoffy
Dad, please!
Give me my daughter!
No, you can't!
You can't have her! Go home!
Dad, I know I'm not a successful actor.
But one day, I'll be successful and I'll make a name for myself!
What kind of guarantee is that?
You can't have a daughter from an unpopular actor!
Go home!
Then...
Then I'll quit being an actor!
What?
I'll quit being an actor and get a normal job!
Are you serious?
I'm serious!
So please!
Dad, please!
Give me my daughter!
Ueda-kun...
I can act like that, too!
Dad, that was acting!
Dad, I'm really good at acting, so I'll be successful!
Please! Give me my daughter!
No, you can't!
Why?
Because I don't want to!
But you're so good at acting!
I don't want a daughter! Go home!
Dad!
Kouhei-san!
Rina-chan!
Dad!
Why won't you let me marry you?
You can't have what you can't have!
Then...
Then I'll quit being an actor!
Dad! I'm serious! I really want to marry you! Please!
Please let me marry you!
Rina...
I can act like that too.
What?
Dad, I'm good at acting too. So please, let me marry you!
No!
Why?
Your acting has nothing to do with this!
Dad, please!
No! I'll never let you marry me!
Dad!
No! No!
Mom?
I'm in trouble!
There's a zombie rampage in town!
What?
Ouch!
It looks like I've been bitten by a zombie too.
Dad, leave me and run away!
What are you talking about?
Before I become a zombie!
Dad, you have to hurry!
Or I'll become a zombie too!
Mom!
I can act like that too.
What?
Dad, I'm good at acting too. So please, let me marry you!
Your acting has nothing to do with this!
Dad, please!
Stop it!
Dad, what are you doing?
It's because you guys are persistent!
Huh?
Why am I over there?
This isn't my body?
Could it be that we're...
Switched?!
We're not switched!
We're definitely not switched!
We're switched, dad!
There's no way we're switched!
Dad, look!
I don't know which one is which anymore!
Huh?
This is Takemoto-san, right?
Huh? It's Takemoto-san, right?
I've been in college for 4 years, but I'm almost there.
I can't make any friends.
Huh?
It's Takemoto-san!
It's Takemoto-san, right?
You don't have any friends?
I've been in college for 4 years, but I can't make any friends.
I always eat lunch alone.
Huh? That's sad.
Wait a minute.
This is Inoue-san, right?
I have a long neck bone.
You're bragging about that?
Was there anything else you could brag about?
At a sushi restaurant, I only eat tuna.
You sound like a rich woman.
At a yakiniku restaurant, I only eat red meat.
This is Inoue-san!
I like red meat.
I only eat asari pasta.
I'm Inoue Rina.
I have a long neck bone.
You keep saying that!
We're completely switched!
Dad, we're completely switched!
I can't make any friends!
You can't see anything!
There's no way you can see!
What are you guys doing?
Anyway...
Dad!
Please allow me to get married!
What's that?
I can act in a musical!
Go home!
How was it?
I think I could have done a little better
if I had been bitten by a zombie.
You're greedy.
You could have done a little better?
If I had been bitten by a zombie,
I think I would have become more of a zombie.
I think I should have been in a state where I was about
to become one.
Dad!
Mom!
That's good.
Takemoto-san,
you seem to be trying to make a good role.
For example?
For each other's ad-lib zone.
Are you trying to expose Inoue himself?
Or are you trying to expose the role of Inoue's daughter?
It's the same as the actor's approach.
That's right.
I didn't think that far either.
There was a part where I had to reflect on myself.
It was like an ad-lib battle.
It was terrible.
I was told that I should have kept it a secret.
I've been in college for four years,
but I can't make any friends.
You mean Takemoto-san?
It's a fact.
I've been in college for four years,
but I can't make any friends.
When I was exposed about college,
I thought I was trying to make a good role.
But when I look at it now,
I'm like,
are you saying that?
You were doing it.
You looked like you were going to say it.
I wasn't confident.
I don't want a daughter!
Go home!
Dad!
Kouhei-san!
He was like this.
I laughed at that.
He didn't come running.
He came back sliding.
I think it's good to exaggerate when doing a skit.
Basically.
It's better to be told to hold it down a little.
I learned that you told me to exaggerate more and more.
I don't know how much tension it is without much
experience in skits.
I was very grateful for your advice.
In rehearsal, if you exaggerate too much, the
performance may not be good.
So I held it down a little.
We all went up.
We did three rehearsals and sweated a little at the end.
Are you in love?
Continued in the next episode!
Impromptu Doremi's singing game!
Introduction Gakuya Game!
It's a game where comedians play a game in the dressing room.
What did Zoffy bring this time?
Impromptu Doremi's singing game!
Impromptu Doremi's singing game?
I've never heard of it.
You sing about a topic in a Doremi's song.
For example, if it's a baseball game,
Do is the Do of the draft meeting.
Re is the Re of the left.
If you do this and sing at the end, you'll clear the game.
If you clear it three times, you'll get a reward.
It's a delicious cake!
Let's start with the first topic.
What an idol seems to say at a live show.
Let's sing!
The Do is...
Please support me at any time!
Everyone's in love!
The Re is...
What?
This is no good!
It's my fault!
My fault?
Change the top batter to Takemoto and try again.
What's the next topic?
This is good!
Words that I think are cute!
Let's sing!
The Do is...
Dorayaki's Do
Re is...
Are you guys in a relationship?
Mi is...
Mixed Chuchu
Pa is...
Taito's Pa
So is...
Sofa?
Zozo
Ra is...
Lion's Ra
Sofa?
Sofa is...
Too shocking
Sofa is cute, right?
Saito is not good at all
What happened?
Re-challenge by changing the order
The theme is...
Words you think are cool
Let's sing!
The Do is...
Donguri
No, no, no, no!
What's the meaning of this?
Donguri
I don't think any of them are cool
Re-challenge by changing the order
Let's sing!
The Do is...
Dokkan
No, no, no, no!
Dokkan!
Wait!
It's Bakazon
Re-challenge by changing the order
They can't leave the battle to Inoue, so they change
the order again
I cleared it in one try
In one try?
What's the next theme?
The title of the song of Sakurazaka 46, which is likely
to be released this year
It's difficult
It's likely to be released
It's a title that Mr. Akimoto is likely to give
Let's sing!
The Do is...
I'll always be with you
The Re is...
I won't fall in love anymore
The Mi is...
Let's party with everyone
The Ma is...
Fire
The So is...
What's up in the sky?
The Ma is...
You can be a boyfriend of a rapper
I can't be a rapper
What's wrong with you?
Let's do it one more time
It's not good to do it one more time
It's not good to succeed
Let's do it one more time
Stop it!
I don't know
I don't know, but...
So, five people challenge without Saito
I think we can do this.
What is important to an idol?
Let's sing.
Do is
Dokyo's Do
Re is
Contact, consultation, report
Mi is
Everyone's feelings
Fa is
Taking care of the fans
Noba
So is
Working hard as a solo
Da is
Doing live as hard as possible
Noba
Si is
Delivering a happy smile
Si
Fa
Uta
Mi
Congrats from zobaczyka!
So, that was it.
What did you think today?
It was great.
To tell you the truth
I actually wanted to see Saito.
I saw him!
I wanted to see him.
I wanted to see Zoffy.
Really?
I think he's happy.
From the sky.
Don't go there!
Saito!
Stop it!
Stop it, everyone!
Next week
Inoue Rina meets Kinnokun
Seriously?
Scary!
An extremely difficult skit where you can't smile
One, two
Yes
And
Sakura and Zakao team up in a rakuya game
I can't be friends with any of them.
What?
It's Takemoto!
You're with Takemoto, right?
You're not friends?