AISubs v3.2
This is the script that Kano-san wrote for us.
Thank you.
Oh, it's a one-person version.
That's right. This is a one-person version.
There's no line.
I don't feel anything at all.
In this program,
Kano-san and the members of Sakurazaka46
will play the role of the main characters.
The members of Sakurazaka46
and the entertainer will do a collaboration skit.
I don't know.
They will play a game together.
It's an experimental variety show.
My face and actions
will be the theme this time.
I'm getting nervous.
Inoue Rina
Mii-tsu
Kin no Kuni
Kano-san
I'm getting nervous.
The skit they will try this time
is a situation at a bar at night.
The point is
the slightly suspicious atmosphere
of the regular customers who come silently.
Inoue will try
the regular customers like onigiri.
Will he be able to express the suspiciousness
with his face and actions alone?
He's laughing.
I want him to be in between being surprised and being surprised.
It's a bit of a waste to have him in the distance.
His face is too small.
He's got a lot of pressure.
I want him to do something with his ad-lib.
I think the entertainers are having a hard time.
He's laughing.
I don't know if I can say it properly.
Advertisement Nato, start!
I totally understand.
The manager is like that.
The other day...
Let's talk while drinking.
There's a bar.
It's a stylish atmosphere.
Let's go there.
There's someone who looks like a regular.
Is something wrong?
He's coming to see me.
When a stranger comes in, a regular comes in.
That's fine.
I don't care about that.
I've never been to a bar.
Let's go.
Two people.
Are you okay?
Can I sit here?
Thank you.
It's a stylish atmosphere.
What would you like?
Raw?
What should I do?
Highball?
Excuse me.
One raw and one highball, please.
You know, the manager.
He always makes a fuss about himself.
Do you know that there was a mistake in the order the other day?
The manager didn't order shampoo and conditioner at all,
and it was not enough.
On the same day,
the newbie Hosoda made a mistake in the reservation.
He made a mistake in the order of shampoo and conditioner.
He was very angry about it.
He made a fuss about himself.
It's not good, is it?
What?
Did that happen?
It's the worst.
Excuse me.
Are you still watching?
Oh, you're still watching.
What?
Oh, you're watching like this.
I didn't know.
Don't come into our territory.
I don't know.
Oh, thank you.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers!
Oh, there are more people.
What?
Oh, there were two regulars.
Is this a store that rejects first-come, first- served?
Oh, it may be a membership.
Let's ask.
Excuse me.
Is this a membership bar?
Oh, no?
Oh, I see.
Then it's okay to be here.
By the way, do you have a table seat?
In the back.
No?
Oh, then it's okay.
Yes.
He doesn't have it.
I see.
It can't be helped.
What?
Wow.
What is it?
What?
What is it? Seriously.
I'm going to look at her.
I think she's looking at me because I look like I'm scared.
It's okay.
She doesn't react at all.
She doesn't even react to what I see.
I'm going to look at the woman.
What?
I'm scared.
I don't know, but it might be very common.
I don't think this is allowed.
What?
Oh, it's a little bright.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll ask you directly.
Why are you looking at me?
Are we acquaintances?
Oh, no.
I'm asking you two.
I can't talk to you like this.
Oh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm sorry. I'll pay you.
Let's go. I can't talk to you.
Yes.
Oh, I got it.
I'll pay you with my card.
Yes.
Oh, I'm fine. I'll pay you in one go.
Oh, the password. Yes, yes.
What?
You have that common sense.
I was like, what's this strange thing?
With an expression that can't say anything.
I was advised that my expression might be good.
I don't know if it's because I'm nervous or my face.
My eyes were wide open.
I felt like I was a scary person.
Scary.
No, no, no.
You're so angry.
You're angry.
I was really nervous.
Card game.
Oh, I'm scared. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What should I do? I want to hear it later.
It's different to speak.
Oh, that's right.
Thank you.
It's different because I don't want to talk to you.
But what should I do?
I wanted to do it with more people.
Oh, that's true.
There are people who come in even more.
There are cases where there are regular people here.
Another person comes out of the toilet.
I don't know what's going on.
It looks fun.
It would be nice if all the members came out.
I wanted to do it.
Will you cry?
I don't know.
Let's work together to find the answer.
Onigiri-Nate
Mochikomi Gakuya Game!
It's a game where comedians play at home.
What did Kinokuni bring this time?
It's Onigiri-nator!
I've never heard of it.
Watabe Onigiri doesn't know anything about movies.
So we made a game called Onigiri-nator.
I'm going to give you a question.
And you have to answer it.
You can only answer yes or no.
I don't know if you know the answer.
So I don't know if you'll get the right answer.
You might be imagining it.
That's right.
You're an adult, so you know the answer.
This time, it's a team game.
The four of them will ask questions in order and
everyone will guess the answer.
There are two chances to answer.
Will they be able to answer the questions?
The point is to be able to ask good questions that are
close to the correct answer.
Here's the first question.
Which one are you laughing at?
I don't know.
Open your eyes.
Game start!
Is the main character a boy?
You don't know?
I don't know if it's a yes or a no.
I don't know.
You say the main character, don't you?
Wait a minute.
Does the person who saw it cry?
I don't know.
It can't be helped.
I don't have a clue.
What should I do?
Have you ever seen our age group?
No.
Is there a specific job theme?
I don't know.
I don't know that.
I don't know the main character.
I don't know, Takemoto.
I don't know.
Please give me one answer.
I don't have a clue.
I don't know if it's a generation or not.
I think it's the police.
Titanic?
I don't know.
I don't know the main character.
Are you ready?
Titanic.
That's right.
Don't get it wrong.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Titanic is a story of two people.
Did you know it was a story of two people?
I don't know.
I don't know that.
The second question is a little difficult.
The second question is this.
The second question is for everyone in front of the TV.
Please think about it with them.
The genre is animal.
Animal?
Game start.
Are your feet fast?
I don't know.
You'll find out later.
Is it blue?
Wait a minute.
Isn't it too obvious?
Isn't it Doraemon?
It's an animal.
Is it a four-legged walk?
No.
What kind of animal is it?
This is what I think.
Is it a land animal?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Is it the sea or land?
The first question is over.
Please give me an answer.
I thought it was a caterpillar.
Isn't it a bird?
Is it a monkey?
I don't know how fast it runs.
Penguin.
Incorrect.
It's a game like this.
I'm glad you got it right.
I'm glad you got it wrong.
I finally got it right.
Let's move on to the second round.
Inoue, please ask a question.
Is it an animal in the sea?
No.
Is there a reason to ask that question?
Oh, that's right.
I made a mistake.
No, you already said it.
I'm sorry.
I really made a mistake.
I got carried away by the Titanic.
I got carried away.
How tall is that animal?
Is it more than 80 cm?
No, I don't think so.
How about you, Masumoto-san?
Is it nocturnal?
Which one is it?
It's like you're saying you don't know.
No, I don't think so.
Wait a minute.
Can you see it in the zoo?
That's a great question.
I think I got it.
Please give me one answer.
Kangaroo?
Is it about 80 cm?
It's more than 80 cm.
Kangaroo?
It's that big?
Isn't it a flamingo?
Is a flamingo bigger?
Is it big?
It's like this.
It's not the time to do that.
You have 10 seconds left.
I thought the last one was a pig.
Did you get it?
Please give me one answer.
1, 2
Kujaku.
You got it wrong.
The answer is...
chimpanzee.
What?
Isn't it 4-speed?
I was a little confused.
Chimpanzee is 2-speed.
Isn't it 4-speed?
Sometimes 2-speed, sometimes 2-speed.
That's a bad question.
Next week, Onuma and Takemoto,
Mitsue,
and the troublemaker high school girls,
and the Nyankees.
Shut up!
And the Kansai dialect
Tsukkomi gesture game
will continue.