Good evening.
So let me say the title call.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry to keep you all busy.
Good evening. It's nice to see you again. I'm Marina Matsuda at 46 Sakuka. Pleased to meet you.
Wow, it's getting faster, so I've already looked at everyone's comments.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. Thank you.
"Congratulations" and "Congratulations."
(Laughter)
I was very happy to hear you say congratulations.
I'm here on YouTube to celebrate the opening photo collection of the first photograph of Kotizshi Matsuta Nara, which will be released on January 20th next January.
I'd like to share with you a little bit of the story that's going on in the photo collection today, and I really do have a lot to talk about.
So I'm really glad you're here today, so I hope you'll be able to meet me to the end.
(Laughter)
It's the opening day.
It's delicious.
It's done, Beaby Kasela.
It's a hit-and-run.
He said you're going to hit me.
Thanks for the big apple.
The Roasting Corn
What kind of corn?
It's like a floater. It's like a floater.
It's nice to see you. I don't know how you look.
It'll make you feel better.
There's a big apple.
SKYKY SKY
It's so cool.
I think I'm going to have a little bit of an initials and a little bit of a connection.
And it's cute, isn't it? It's really delicious.
Apples and rumne.
Cooking kites?
I really think I'll eat it later.
I'm so happy to be here.
I hope you're able to submit what you're feeling today to x, but I'd like to make a hash tag that you're going to post at that time.
Let's see if we can figure out what the hash tag is.
That's right!
Hashtag
Festivals and festivals.
Did you see that?
You see that?
The festival and the festival.
No, you're right.
You're with me today.
It's a festival day, so the hash tag may be a little longer, but it's a festival and a festival.
I'd like you all to post the hash-tags and festivals.
I'd like to thank you for sharing this story with me, and I'd really appreciate it if you didn't feel like it, or you didn't feel like it, or you didn't feel like it, and you didn't feel like it, and you didn't want to comment.
It's a sharp trend.
I'm counting on you.
Let's see if we can do that.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do that, but I'm going to be able to do that in this account.
There's a lot here.
It's going to be posted, and it's going to be up-to-date, and it's going to be up-to-date.
I'm glad you're doing this, sir.
Yes, sir.
(Laughter)
We've made provision for you.
It's from this delivery, and I'm sure you'd like to reserve a photo collection for me.
This one.
It's this size.
Free.
(Laughter)
The size of your face is about twice the size of your face. But it's about the size of your face.
It's nice to get this without a fold. I can't get into a line like this.
I'm happy.
I'll get it.
And then there's one more thing.
That's the other one.
Yes.
(Laughter)
Thank you.
It's this way.
It's this way. It's clear.
I'll give you a double gift.
Money up. Real credit card.
Look at this.
(Laughter)
And I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you a little bit of appreciation for.
It's just today, you all know.
Well...
How many hours?
I'd love to!
Until then, I'll be able to book you at the Sony Music Shop.
(Laughter)
So here's the pattern, and the first one is made up of a product tag at the bottom left of the screen, but if you press a product tag at the bottom of the screen, you'll see that it's a product tag at the bottom of the screen.
You can get access to the purchase pages of the Sony Music Shop.
And then it goes on.
It's called buying on the right side of the good button.
You can buy it from the button in the shopping bag
(Laughter)
I'd like you to turn it upside down and I'd like you to come out.
And I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you on the computer.
I'm going to show you how to do that.
Yes.
He said he couldn't find it.
Mr. Pata, there's still a third.
You can buy it from the sales page.
And I'm going to show you how to do that.
In the summary.
We're going to go to our browser, and we're going to go to our browser.
I'd like you to check it out for me.
We're going to go through all of the links that we've got.
I'm sure you'll be glad to find me at the Sony Music Shop, if you don't mind.
(Laughter)
Aaah!
An endless poster.
Thank you so much for watching.
(Laughter)
Bye.
Kingup Uncomplicated Cards
I'm going to show you a couple of examples.
Look at this.
Just like this.
(Laughter)
I don't know.
Wide
Maybe that's what it is, but the sea really is so wide
I don't know.
(Laughter)
I don't know if you know anything about cliffs. It's amazing.
It's like a big cliff and ocean collaboration, and I've done a lot of that myself.
It's really amazing. It's really amazing.
I can't forget it.
It's really, really, really, it's sunset.
Even at sunset, we're fighting this time.
It's like the sun doesn't shine or the sun doesn't shine.
(Laughter)
This is a bit of a day-to-day thing, so it's a miracle and a miracle. It's the moment when the sun comes up, isn't it?
It's a bad card for a kingup.
It's not really that big.
I can carry it in my wallet every day.
If you can imagine.
I don't have a card. I don't have a card. I don't have a card.
It's been a long time.
It's hard to tell, but if you do it by hand,
Really.
Your card is the easiest, isn't it? It's about the size of a card and it's going to fit in.
And my message is here, too, isn't it?
This New Zealand is really sheep, so these sheep are gathered for us.
And I'm afraid your money people will come too.
I want to put it in the bank, and I want to put it in the bank, and I want to do this as a financial up-to-date card.
And I'm going to tell you a little bit about this, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to tell you a little bit about it, and I'm going to show you a little bit about it, and I'm going to show you a little bit about it.
(Laughter)
Shoot last day
That's exactly what I said.
There was no rain, there was no rain, there was war, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain, there was no rain.
I was thinking, "Why don't we go out on a sunny day while we're shooting?"
It's never going to rain so hard.
Well, maybe it was raining, but I'm sure it was.
It's not like it's been raining so long that it's too hard to film.
It's a beautiful day. It's a miracle it's here.
I was able to film it.
(Laughter)
He's so smart.
Just for the first time.
I thought it might be scary.
You're so smart.
I've been feeding you.
I don't know.
(Laughter)
And when I tell him I'm not going to do this, he's going to go.
Oh, my God.
I think she's the kind of person who understands Japanese too.
I don't know.
I think it's a gesture.
(Laughter)
Yes, sir.
Let's start with a photograph.
Broadcasting
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm sure we're on board, too. I'm tired.
Oh, I'm in. I'm in. I'm good.
Oh, I didn't see it.
Free.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Yes, sir.
(Laughter)
I'm happy to do it for the first time.
You know, I've been thinking about it for a long time, but I don't think there's any time left to decide when that film will be taken.
I don't know how long it's been going to take to figure out what it's going to be.
Do you think he's going to film it?
What?
I feel like I'm okay with it. I'm starting to feel really nervous.
Is that really me?
Oh, my God.
I'm really nervous about what I'm going to do, and I'm going to talk to the staff about it, and I'm going to talk to them about what I'm going to do, and I'm going to talk to them about what I'm going to do, and I'm going to talk about what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do is I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do, and what I'm going to do.
So I'm going to show you how to do this.
(Laughter)
Hey.
What are you talking about?
It's cute!
Very much.
He praised me for being so cute.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Give me the pretty thing you really think you're doing out of your heart.
Despite the fact that you gave it to me,
(Laughter)
Something.
What are you doing?
It's not that I can't really take it seriously, but it's not that I can't believe what you're saying.
Let's see.
I'm not sure what I'm going to do. I don't know what I'm going to do.
No, it's true. He told me that you're so cute.
(Laughter)
I'll see you then.
He said, "Let's take a picture."
(Laughter)
I'm going to give you a couple of examples.
And there's nothing there.
And I'm like, "Oh my God, I'm so proud of you."
I'm really sorry that I'm so worried about myself.
You know, I've been telling people that they should have confidence because they're so nice.
(Laughter)
So for the rest of your life, you're so cute and you're so proud of yourself, you're so important.
I wish your mind would look so beautiful.
And I was able to do this because I was able to do it, but I really didn't want to challenge those photos.
I'm filled with so much gratitude. I think I made this photo collection with you guys.
That's why I feel like I've made something really good.
(Laughter)
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do that, but I don't think I'm going to be able to do that, because I'm sure I'm going to be able to get through these photos.
I thought, "Well, I'm not going to do this."
That was the story, wasn't it?
But isn't everything me? No matter where I look, do I have such a dream?
That's what I'm doing.
I was thinking that I wouldn't be able to be a good person if I didn't want to be a good person.
(Laughter)
I think it was a lot.
I guess I couldn't predict anything at all.
You're right.
Hey, dance. I do.
(Laughter)
That's what made my dream come true.
I'm going to go to New Zealand. I'm going to go to New Zealand. I'm going to go to New Zealand.
I'm glad I met you in New Zealand.
I don't know. The country was so beautiful.
It's been a long time since I got to the airport.
There's a lot of airport staff out there.
He was kind to me, and I think he's going to get a lot harder.
I don't know where it is anymore, but it's kind of friendly and warm.
Very much.
It was kind of you. I mean, I couldn't forget how warm people were, so I couldn't forget English.
He's so kind and he listens to me to the end.
I'll say it makes you happy.
You can say it with courage.
(Laughter)
Maybe it's natural.
Like I said, it's like the ocean.
It's like a corroboror in the ocean and mountains.
I was a good cosmonaut.
And... nature.
That's probably the case with the sheep.
You're so cute.
I don't want to go home anymore, so I'm so lonely that I'm going to miss my dick so much. The country of New Zealand is so delicious!
I'm sorry I ate it.
I ate a lot of food.
I couldn't stand it when I thought I was sorry for the photo collection.
That food is delicious.
And I ate it every day.
That's the photo collection. It's coming out next year on January 20th.
Yes.
I don't know. A little comment.
I think I'm going to read it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
How many days, how many days?
A week, maybe.
I went there for a week.
As a matter of fact,
It's nice to meet you, isn't it? &lt;i&gt;It's nice to meet you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;i&gt;It's nice to meet you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;i&gt;It's nice to meet you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt; &lt;i&gt;I love you.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;
That's the day.
Excuse me?
(Laughter)
It was the week I was picked up.
You know, 20.
I'm five years old, and I'm 26 years old.
(Laughter)
It's just me.
I'm sure some of you may have seen it, but I'm sure you're on the other side of Shinga.
I went hunting grass the day I was hunting grass.
I went to New Zealand after hunting grass.
I was in New Zealand, I was in New Zealand, I was in New Zealand, I was in New Zealand.
I'm going to go to this photo collection in the corner.
And I was in the middle of the night, and I was still in my head.
(Laughter) (Applause)
It's an honor to be here. Thank you so much for that.
I'm glad.
(Laughter)
You've got a lot of food, you've got lots of food, you've got lots of food, you've got lots of food, you've got to eat as much as you want, you've got to eat as much as you want, you've got to be kind, okay?
I ate a lot.
I went there on my birthday.
(Laughter)
You've been spending a lot of time, haven't you?
I think it's only been about a month lately.
He's gone.
I went to Mr. Alumi's.
We haven't seen each other yet.
And after that announcement,
I'm a little nervous.
I've had enough to eat.
It's a lot more than just a diet.
A lot of mornings, days, and nights.
I ate a lot.
Thank you for order.
New Zealand, what's so good about it?
Oh, but I also ate with the mullurs, but it was really delicious.
Also, it was usually delicious with hamburgers and potatoes.
I don't need potatoes.
(Laughter)
It's like a loving world. It's a kind world.
Yes. It was fun.
(Laughter)
There's a lot of them.
That's why you stretched your hair out.
(Laughter)
I just thought I'd grow up.
I've been stretching it out.
I don't know. It's just...
(Laughter)
But I got lost.
Oh, but it's been so short lately.
I thought it might be shorter.
I thought maybe I'd cut it off.
No, but I can.
Well, I'd like you to take a look at the ponytail.
It's like, there's a lot of space.
(Laughter)
With your hair.
Not much in my normal life.
It's not long.
(Laughter)
That's how long my hair is.
Thank you for taking the picture.
You were cutting rice in New Zealand, weren't you?
I've been to New Zealand since we had weeded in New Guinea.
It's dangerous. I'm on my way.
Yes, sir.
The response from the members, for sure, didn't come from the members.
That's why I told you.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
(Laughter)
I thought you'd be happy.
You're right.
(Laughter)
Four hours earlier than Japan.
It's like you've been asleep all the time.
I don't think so.
But it took me more than 10 hours to get there.
(Laughter)
That's right.
Oh, tell me again, there's a bird in there.
Thank you.
I didn't take pictures of them in Shinga.
Oh, ahead cut.
(Laughter)
This time.
It's a double privilege to be here in New Zealand.
I've got a lot of memories in this poster, and this one, but this one's special.
There's another cut that came out in the first place.
Let's start with a quick cut.
I don't know if I can see it from the bottom.
(Laughter)
I don't know what you're talking about.
He looked at me. He told me it was so cute.
I'm happy. I'm happy.
(Laughter)
Buy an apple.
Isn't this cute?
This supermarket is really fun, isn't it?
There's so many things that don't exist in Japan, isn't there?
But she's cute enough to want to change her face
It's a lot of different types.
I don't know what's going on here.
I asked him what he wanted me to do.
It's so delicious.
I was eating in the car.
I'm having dinner with you guys in the car.
It's almost gone.
It's too big already.
It's totally bigger than this one.
And I went to the store, and I said, "Well, you know, I don't know what I'm going to do."
That's what we came for after we ate it again.
You've had enough to be so happy.
Yes, it's a cafe.
I did it for Alistair. I actually did it for myself.
It's a café I made myself into.
It was really difficult.
It's the first time there's a beeping sound.
When I went to a café or something, I did it.
It's a pishu.
You know, it's nice to see you.
And like late art after that.
I was wondering if I could do it.
I couldn't, of course, but I knew it. I can tell by the way.
I couldn't. It was difficult, but it miraculously made a pretty picture.
It's a birdhouse in New Zealand.
It's like, if you close your eyes a little bit, you'll look like a kiwi.
I thought I already had it.
(Laughter)
It's nice to see you in this cafe.
It's delicious.
(Laughter)
I wonder which one of you likes it?
I turned it off.
I can't see the comment section anymore. I'm sorry. Please.
Yes, sir.
(Laughter)
This is the box.
Thank you. Thank you.
You know, I'd like to make a reservation for this.
I'm going to show you how to do this.
(Laughter)
I'd love to have you booked at the Sony Music Store.
It's just today. I get this.
And I'm going to show you what I'm going to show you in the next video.
And I'm going to show you some of the things that I'm going to show you, and I'm going to show you some messages and illustrations.
I hope you'll make a reservation.
(Laughter)
Oh, I've made a reservation.
I made a reservation.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Thank you for two more hours, right? Two more hours
It's only two hours. We've got it.
(Laughter)
Thank you.
That's right.
Mm-hmm.
It's almost done.
I like cafes. I'm glad.
I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak, I'm weak.
Goodbye.
Oh.
It's about time we did that.
Right this way.
(Laughter)
(Applause)
This way, please.
(Laughter)
It's in there. It's in there. It's in there.
It's just...
I think I'd like to talk to you.
I'll be right back.
Free.
Oh, my God.
You're making a noise. I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
One more thing.
(Laughter) (Applause)
And I'm not going to let you do that, but I'm going to put it in the box.
I don't think they've destroyed it, they've destroyed it, they've destroyed it, they've destroyed it, and I'm really sorry.
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry about that.
I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do that, but I'm not going to be able to do that.
You know, once you've had a bad look on your face, I'm sure of it.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Here we go.
I'm so glad you came out.
So I'm going to do it in one year, and I'm going to do it in a year, so I'm going to go far and expand, but I don't want to do that.
I'll see you soon.
Yes!
How about some of the food you ate after the shooting?
Wow, I'm coming home.
It's nice to see you at night.
It wasn't too late, but it was just a little late.
I don't know what to do, but I have to go to bed early.
(Laughter)
I have to go to bed. It's at home.
It's something that I've been putting up with for the whole time.
(Laughter)
I ate it.
I've eaten it. I've eaten it.
I don't get it.
I was wondering if I could make it a little pluripotent with turquoise.
I've been drinking citrus juice.
And a cup of ramen.
It was delicious. I don't know if it's possible.
I don't want to be a bad guy, but I don't want to be a bad guy, so I'm going to have to be patient.
You know, you've been eating it, you've been eating it, you've been eating it, and you've got a reward.
It's always been like a treat.
He didn't put up with it. He didn't put up with it.
Maybe they're eating it.
I feel like there's nothing to be afraid of.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're still here.
It's not that I can do it, but it's not that I can do it.
Stay with me.
Thank you very much.
I don't know if I can get this out of here.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out.
(Laughter)
That's right!
And what we're going to do is we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do, and we're going to do something that we're going to do.
I...
We had a lot of food, maybe some muscle, maybe a lot of food, something like that.
I wanted to eat a lot of food to be my ideal.
I tried my best, but then I ate a lot of food to make sure my skin didn't get too rough.
When I was a kid, I used to be careful that I didn't have to be too rough on oil as long as I could.
(Laughter)
Cooking.
It's... it's the basics.
Hey.
I'm just gonna...
Season 3 or something.
This way.
I was eating a lot of curry rice.
You're gonna be hungry for 300 grams, aren't you?
If you were a woman, you'd be eating 300 grams of rice.
I ate very well.
That's what I'm talking about. I'm talking about three hundred grams every day.
I really ate it. I thought I should eat it.
I really ate it. It was full.
Yes, I dare not.
It's just like the way you look.
I don't know if that's true, but it's true.
I've prepared a lot for the shooting.
Even in me.
Can I still take pictures?
Yes, sir.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, my God.
No.
Oh, my God, don't make this sound.
What?
Oh, here it is! Oh, here it is!
It's nice to meet you.
You don't sound the same at all.
Oh, yeah.
That's great. I'm kind of getting the hang of it.
All right, all right.
That's all.
Go on.
I'm glad I bought it at New Zealand's supermarket.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What did I buy? Super.
Um... there's an ice cream that I can't forget.
It's really delicious.
Something.
You're looking at fruit.
It was a peach.
Mango.
There were about three kinds of berries.
You look so real.
It's about this size.
Maybe this is what it looks like.
I'm going to show you an example of an apple.
She looked like she was.
It's so delicious, isn't it, smooth?
It was like white chocolate on the outside, but it wasn't a smooth chocolate and it wasn't pliable.
I wonder what the ice cream is inside.
So, I ate a piece of peach, but it tasted good.
It's like I've always wanted to eat it, and I still remember it.
I'm glad I bought that.
I also have juice and 100% juice.
Those orange juices are delicious.
I don't know what they're saying.
It's kind of smoothy.
It's like an orange juice.
It's so delicious.
(Laughter)
With a team.
It was my favorite drink on the team, wasn't it?
It was pretty good.
All right, let's keep going.
Let me in.
What?
I'll see you later.
It's okay. I didn't break it.
I didn't break it.
It's in here.
If you pull it out of here, it'll be fine.
I don't think he's getting a little bit of a size.
That's what I'm gonna do.
It's not like you broke it. It's not like you broke it.
Well, I didn't break it. I didn't break it at all.
I didn't break anything. I didn't break my heart.
It's normal.
It's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's like... it's like... it's like... it's like... it's like...
He's still out there.
(Laughter)
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I'm sorry, but I'm a little bit more comfortable with it.
I'm gonna get you in there.
Milk.
I'm really sorry about that, because I was so nervous about it, and I thought maybe if I did it harder, I'd probably go out.
Oh, my God. I want to take you to New Zealand with me. 46 Sakuraska members.
Oh, my God.
I don't know who that is.
But there's a member I want to tell him that he should definitely go to New Zealand.
Well, that Inoue Naina probably likes going abroad or something, and I'm sure she likes her.
It's already in New Zealand.
I said I wanted to say so.
I'd love to!
I'd like to take you to New Zealand.
It was delicious, too.
It's natural.
But it's so cool in the city.
It's beautiful.
I'd like to invite all of you to come with me, even if you'd like to, and I'd like to encourage all of you to do a great presentation on that country, New Zealand.
So I'm going to go to New Zealand, and I'm going to go to New Zealand, and I'm going to go to New Zealand, and I'm going to go to New Zealand, and I'm going to recommend it to my members.
Yes, sir.
Shit.
Oh, next, Rust.
I'd like to do it fast.
It wasn't going to happen.
Hmm.
I've been spending so much time already that I'm usually frustrated.
I told her to trust her.
(Music) (Music ends) (Music ends) (Music ends) (Music ends) (Music ends) (Music ends)
Well, I was on the move, and I was listening.
Did I hear anything?
Sakuza's song.
Oh, my God.
I love music. It's always spring.
I'm listening. I'm on the move.
Like onmeways or onmeways.
No, not at all.
Yes, sir.
Time is tight.
(Laughter)
What kind of music do you like to listen to while you're on the move?
So, what do you like?
Didn't you hear? Didn't you hear?
No, no, listen to me.
You know, spring all the time.
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's just spring.
New Zealand.
We met at a good time.
You're lying, aren't you?
No, I heard.
I heard you.
It's beautiful. Yeah, it works.
Are you guys saying, "Puplesses" or something?
I've always been a Halah.
It's been around for a long time now, and I hope you'll hear it as you move around.
And I'm going to tell you a little bit about this, because I'm here to tell you.
Oh, I'm just hiding.
What's the matter with you?
(Laughter)
Yes, sir. It's not going to get any more money.
So let's take a look at this one over here.
I've mentioned this a number of times, but it's only for today, so it's really up to 23 p.m., and it's only for today at the Sony Music Shop.
I'm sorry. I've said this over and over again, but this really is it.
It's sad to be told it's only today, isn't it?
I miss her.
Yes, sir.
This way.
That's cute. You like this, right? A shot with a sheep.
I'm so glad you're here, and I don't even have a chance to attack you.
I'm glad you're here.
The delivery archive will remain until 23:59.
We're supposed to stay until 23:59 today.
If anyone can't see it, please tell them now.
Even after this announcement was over.
I'm sure you'll be happy to share it with me, since I can see it until today.
Oh, I'm glad. If you're staying for a while, I'd be happy to.
I'm sure some of you are not at home today, or at work, and there's a lot of things you can't watch.
If you could see it until that time, you'd be glad to see it.
That's why we're going to end it quickly.
That's why I'm here.
Uh...
I'm not going to be able to do that.
I don't know if you'd like to say something, but I'm sure you have a really good feeling about this today.
I was happy.
I'm out of breath.
You talk too much.
I'm really embarrassed.
You've got a lot on your mind.
I'm sure you'd like me to leave you here forever.
It's not too late.
That's right.
What about your family?
You're pleased. I'm glad.
That's right.
I'm glad you're here.
That's good. That's good.
Thank you.
And, uh, there's a lot of things going wrong.
You're a dick.
It's just the timing. That's it.
It's coming through.
I'm glad you're here.
(Laughter)
Thank you.
You were cute today, too. Thank you.
Thank you so much for watching.
Scrap time.
Can you do that?
I don't know why I'm here.
(Laughter)
I don't know which one is better.
If it's only for today, I'll stay here.
Ending
I don't know if I can see it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry.
It won't work today.
It's always noisy, isn't it?
But it's Lambne.
Yeah, but it's in front of me.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh, my God. I'm so glad you're here.
Hey.
Oh, that's dangerous.
Let's do this. Come on.
Yes, sir.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
I'm so happy for you.
(Laughter)
It's like, "Oh, I can't do this."
Hey.
Yes, cheese.
Crap.
Do you understand?
It's time to move on. I can't help it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm doing this all the time.
I thought it was today, but I'm sorry, sir.
If you can't move, I put up with it a lot earlier, but I think I'm taking pictures.
I'm counting on you, ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, please.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna get up a little bit.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God. I'm going to sit here for a little while today.
I didn't break it.
I only took pictures.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what I'm doing.
Don't be such a destroyer anymore.
I don't want to break it. I'm sorry.
Yes.
(Laughter)
I was happy to show it in the photo collection.
I'll leave this with you too.
I'm so happy.
Something.
It's like, you know, it's like, "Oh, it's really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really,
Even after I released it, the voices of all my fans were very warm.
And I'm glad that I made the decision to do something that I didn't want to do.
I can't believe I'm still here.
I was happy.
(Laughter)
Yeah, I'm fine.
I don't want to do that next time, so that's where everyone's a little bit curious. Some people have failed.
I'm very happy to be able to get this photo collection to a lot of people just to enjoy this work.
Something.
(Laughter)
I think it's really important that you love me, because I hope I'm one of them.
I really wish this photo collection of mine would reach so many people.
I'm counting on you.
If you'd been enjoying yourself today,
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I'd love to hear that it's heavy, so I'll cherish it if it's heavy.
I don't know if it's been a happy time since I showed up for the photo show.
I don't know if that's a good idea, but I can't really speak it well, but I can't stop thanking you guys.
There's so many things that you can't do, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it, that you can't do it.
(Laughter)
If you'd like to book that photo collection on the air, you'd like to have it as a special, unscrambled poster.
Lock up this way.
Mm-hmm.
Ah, it's not this. I'm sorry I didn't look at you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't wear key warps, but this can be carried in my wallet, about the size of a card, in my wallet.
I'm going to give you an example.
I hope you'll get it for me at the Sony Music Shop at 23:59.
It's just today.
(Laughter) (Applause)
I hope you'll be happy to post that.
I'm going to give you a couple of examples.
(Laughter)
I don't want to end it because I'm so happy I'm the kind of guy who talks about things like this and starts talking about the same thing over and over and over and over again.
I just felt lonely, and I had to finish it, and I told him it's over.
It's the end of the world, isn't it? It's the end of the world.
I'm lonely. I'm not gonna talk anymore.
Thank you so much for coming to watch the broadcasts. &gt;&gt;Hugo Barra: &gt;&gt;Hugo Barra: Thank you very much. &gt;&gt;Hugo Barra:
I'm very attached to my love, and I'm deeply involved in the love of my team, and I feel like I'm deeply involved in the love of all of you who've seen this picture.
I hope that many of you will have access to it.
I'm sure you'll be glad to make a reservation, and I'll be very happy to finish.
So, good night. Thank you all.