The third single, Futari Sezon, was a
big hit with more than 600,000 copies.
Keyakizaka 46 with the momentum to make
a leap
This is the last episode of Care Bingo
2, where they challenged various
projects.
Wow, that was great!
The two of you from Keyakizaka are the
best!
You're the best!
No, I'm the best!
Who is it?
Her neck seems to be stuck in something.
For some reason, Natsuko Yokosawa has
entered the studio.
Nice to meet you!
I've been to 46 wedding parties in a
year!
I'm Natsuko Yokosawa, 46 years old!
She's here!
Yokosawa Natsuko 46
I really like the 2 people season
Really?
Yes, but I really wanted to dance
So I asked if I could dance in the
center
No, no, that's not true
It's not?
Yokosawa Natsuko, who loves Yakuzaka,
came to the center
Hey, everyone is going home
Yes
Yokosawa 46 vs the center
Good job
In this difficult situation
Is this going to be broadcast?
I don't want to make you do it.
First,
the table tennis match!
Yoko-san is really good at table tennis.
That's right.
I won first place in a tournament in
Niigata prefecture.
You won first place in Niigata
prefecture.
As a handicap for Keyakizaka, I would
like to compete with this variable table
tennis table.
Here it is.
In short, the width of this table is
twice the width of a normal table.
This handicap is rare, isn't it?
It's not rare.
It's pretty mean.
Thank you very much.
It's not just the table tennis table.
It's a hand-to-hand match between 20
people from Keyakizaka and 5 points from
Yokosawa.
Who is the most confident in table
tennis?
I happened to have a table tennis table.
I had a match with Risa Watanabe.
Who was the strongest?
I happened to win that time.
I'll say I'm stronger than you.
What about the length?
I didn't have any tools, so I used
slippers at home.
Let's start the table tennis match!
The first player is Izumi Imai.
She says she's not very confident in
table tennis.
Let's start!
What? What? What?
It didn't disappear!
You can do it, darling!
No way!
You got 1 point.
This is surprising.
That's amazing.
Have you done this before?
I used to lose at school, so this is my
first time winning.
I lost to someone who used to lose at
school?
This is too sad.
No way, Keyakizaka.
Will Donkisa Ozeki be able to continue?
That's good.
That was close.
Scary!
The third is super junior high school
student Hirate
Let's go
Why?
So close!
Scary!
Wasn't that a good rally?
In the end, he went to a nasty place.
He went to a nasty place to win, didn't
he?
I aimed a little.
You aimed a little, but it went in.
It was close.
However, after this, Koike.
Suzuboto.
Oda lost easily.
It's better for the loser to pick up the
ball.
That's good.
However, Uemura changes the flow here.
Please.
He did it.
Uemura wins the match.
I've been learning tennis for 3 years.
It's not tennis!
It's table tennis.
Table tennis?
You can play table tennis?
Amazing.
Now, the flow has changed.
Wait a minute.
Can I do it one more time?
Here, Nagasawa, the master of slipper
table tennis, appears.
Please.
What?
That was no good.
That was...
You got it twice.
I got it twice.
Twice.
I'm sorry.
After regaining her energy, Yokosawa
beats the Keyakizaka members one after
another.
And...
So close!
Sato Saki has a strategy.
What's your boyfriend's name?
Ah, it's Nacchan.
Nacchan?
Nacchan!
What's...
What's going on?
Nacchan!
So close!
The strategy to distract her from the
question is...
...a violent fist fight.
So, Harada also has a question.
Where did you confess your love?
Um...
That's not it.
So close!
That was so close!
This strategy is good.
In this way, Risa Watanabe.
Please.
This is a practice.
How much is your salary last month?
I'm sorry.
This is the price of living insurance.
This is amazing.
This is 13.4 billion yen.
How much is the remaining 1 point?
I didn't think it would be so intense.
If Miyakizaka gets one more point, he
wins.
Will Kobayashi be able to win?
Let's go.
Kobayashi-chan, it's a battle.
That was close.
It's Juice, right?
Juice
Will it be decided with this one?
The remaining two are Yonetani and Sugai
And so
Yonetani and Sugai-chan
Will be able to do a double
It will be decided with that serve
Do your best
When is the final kiss?
Oh, the final kiss
That's right
Oh, no
It would be nice if we could do it in a
good place
Oh, there it is!
When was the last time you did it?
That was close!
That's the end!
The winner is Yokosawa 46!
The third match is the ballet pirouette
showdown!
So, Yokosawa-san, you have experience in
ballet?
I started ballet when I was 25 years
old.
Recently?
I started ballet a year ago, and I
learned ballet with my wife in a very
elegant place.
So, in the second round, we will have a
competition to see who can spin the most
in pirouette, the basic ballet
technique.
The three members who will compete with
Yokosawa this time are those who have
experience in ballet.
Shiori-chan, I heard you've been doing
ballet for a long time.
I've been doing it for 11 years.
11 years?
You've only been doing it for a year.
You're kidding, right?
I got injured when I was in the 3rd
grade of junior high school.
Oh, you got injured.
I haven't been doing it since then.
I'm scared. I heard I'm doing it well.
Even if you're doing it well, you're
doing it with that weird old lady.
What are you talking about? I'm not an
old lady.
It's a silhouette competition.
Start!
Yokosawa is so slow!
Shiori-chan...
Those three are really amazing!
Their eyes are turning!
How fast are they?
Hey, old lady!
Their eyes are turning!
Amazing!
Those three are really different!
The place doesn't move at all.
5 seconds left!
They are turning!
Amazing!
They are continuing to turn!
Time's up!
Ma-san, are you okay?
If I do this, the old ladies around me
will laugh at me.
Kon-san, you're really good at this.
You didn't even hold your breath.
Wow!
Now, I'd like to announce the number of
spins.
Sugai-chan, 25 spins.
Harada-kun, 26 spins.
Amazing.
And Shiori-chan, 27 spins.
As expected.
Amazing
Can I change the side dish?
Yes
21 times
What?
But there were 21 times
I'll do my best.
However, he lost the first game.
The third game with the center.
The last game is...
Face performance battle!
I'll say it in English.
It's "Niramekko".
"Niramekko"?
It's a face performance.
Now, this is already...
It's the "Suttokodokkoi" phase of the
entertainment world.
"Suttokodokkoi" phase?
For the first time?
Natsuko Yokosawa is already strong.
This is advantageous.
I'm grateful to my parents.
You're grateful to your parents.
I'm grateful.
With these four people who are confident
in their strange faces,
if they can make Natsuko Yokosawa laugh
even once, it's a victory.
Shura-chan, do you have a strange face?
Do I?
Really?
Let's go.
You don't have that kind of image?
Not at all.
What about you, Himaizumi-chan?
I love a strange face.
You like a strange face?
Yes.
You have a strange face, don't you?
What kind of face do you have, Oda-mo?
Yes.
Oda-mo, you're good at it, aren't you?
No, I don't really want to show my face.
Why? Did it come out?
No, I don't want to.
Really?
Yes.
The first match is Yokosawa vs. Ozeki.
This time, we have a special rule.
You can talk while staring at each
other.
Do you have any plan?
I'll do my best.
I want you to do your best.
I want to be ugly when I put on makeup.
This mascara is really good.
Kozuki, attack him more!
Attack him more!
I can do it like this
Like this
This foundation
Welcome, Shirley!
The side of my nose is red
and I can't smile
That's because you got pimples recently
Stop it!
You're smiling
The second one is
Cool Beauty Shida
What is her strategy?
Fight
I have a little skill, so I'm going to
use it.
Yoko, do you have a strategy?
I'm going to do the face when Otomone
Owell praised his juniors for the first
time.
It's a performance battle. Start!
Oh, good job!
You're so good at it.
I'm glad.
If you don't laugh, you can change the
setting.
It's a game until you laugh.
Did you get it?
What is it?
You're good!
Yokosawa wins!
I'm so happy!
What's with that mouth?
It's the first time I've seen a mouth
like that.
It's so pointy.
This part is really...
Amazing.
This is it.
You can do it?
You can do it right away.
It's like 3 mouths.
The winner is Yokosawa.
As expected, Yokosawa is strong.
Can Imaizumi, who loves Engao, make
Yokosawa laugh?
What kind of person is Imaizumi?
I like to make wrinkles on my face.
You like to make wrinkles?
It's like a facial exercise.
Oh, I see.
Are you confident?
Yes.
I'm from Shinjuku Lumine 2.
I'm a clerk with an ugly smile.
Oh, you're from Shinjuku Lumine.
A clerk with an ugly smile.
Let's start the face performance battle.
Ready, start!
IMAIZUMI
That's amazing.
Imaizumi, you're good.
Imaizumi, you don't have to do it.
Yokosawa, you just did it.
You look like that when you're eating.
Stop it.
That's not it.
It's messed up.
It's terrible.
What are you going to do?
The winner is Ibaizumi!
No way!
I lost?
Oda-san!
One more time!
I'll do it, I'll do it.
You'll do it?
No, I'll jump, I'll jump.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Now, the final battle between Yokosawa
and Oda.
Oda-chan, what do you think of Hengawa-
dan?
My older sister and father often tell me
about it.
Tell you about it?
It's like "Isshi-souden".
Yes.
There's a story about it.
It's like "Hokkoshin-ken".
Tell you about it.
I'd like to show it.
Oh, the whole Oda family loves Hengawa-
dan.
Yes.
It's like "Unagi-no-tare".
That's the only thing you bring home.
Ok, Yokozawa-sensei.
The face of a cell phone shop clerk in
Ikebukuro.
I got it.
Ok, start!
What is the result?
FACE PERFORMANCE final battle between
Oda and Yokosawa
Who will win?
Why?
Have you seen that face before?
No way.
It's the first time I've seen it.
Don't tell the same members.
So, the winner of the face performance
battle is Keyakizaka46!
It's a draw.
And so, the 2nd season of Yokosawa
Center is over.
No, please.
No, you can't.
Please.
Speed is important.
You should apologize as soon as
possible.
I want to dance with you.
Are you positive?
Yes.
I want you to dance with me.
I even prepared a uniform.
Then, what kind of competition is it?
Let's try "Two-people season".
Thank you very much.
After this, Hirate and Yokosa will
perform "Two-people season" of "Double
Center".
In addition,
Girls talk in pajamas.
Care room.
Here is an announcement from the show!
KIA BINGO 2 will be available on the
online video streaming service "Hulu"
and "Nikkei On Demand"
and will start streaming on the internet
after the broadcast!
For more information, please go to the
show's homepage!
After this, Yokozawa Natsuko 46 will
have a season with Keyakizaka!
But before that...
KIA BINGO!
This time, let's look back at all 12
episodes of KIA BINGO 2!
You were the No.1 boyfriend in the final
round.
Do you have any impression?
I think Manaki is really ugly.
No, I kept pushing her.
That's right.
I kept pushing Manaki.
I loved her.
Hirate also kept pushing Manaki.
But in the end, which one did I choose?
When I was wondering which one was
cooler,
I thought I was Manaki.
But I was wrong.
I didn't vote for her.
I voted for Manaki.
It's amazing.
It's 3,000 yen.
Ah, 3,000 yen.
What's that?
Ah, that's right.
I gave it to Peetan as a gift.
Where is it now?
Did you lose it?
Where is it?
Hey!
The perfect version of the shocking
confession of Wadana Melika will be
broadcast on Hulu after the broadcast!
Now, it's Yokosawa Natsuko 46 featuring
Keyakizaka46.
It's a two-person season.
Here you go!
Two-person season, two-person season
Falling in love in the spring and summer
In the autumn and winter, right away
The season we spent together
Don't you regret it?
Two-person season
Even in the weeds that are in full bloom
I forgot that I had a name
Even if I'm born without being noticed
I won't scream, I won't
When I talk to someone, I don't care
I was pretending not to hear
You suddenly took off my earphones
What did you say now?
Before the sun comes back
I'm sure I'll meet someone important
It's not worth missing
Don't refuse love
Two-person season, two-person season
Falling in love in the spring and summer
Make your daily life shine
The scenery of yesterday and today
Don't forget
Looking up at the cherry blossoms inside
the flowers
There was a day when I thought
I have to go out
I can't see my dream
The window of my heart
Two-person season, two-person season
Falling in love in the spring and summer
The excitement I felt for the first time
My two-person season
It's my heart.
How was it, Hirate-chan?
It was amazing.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
But there were some dangerous parts.
There was a part where I thought,
"Hirate-chan, you're going to fall
over."
But I avoided it naturally.
I thought everyone was dancing so hard.
When I was making the mountain, Shida-
san...
No way!
Shida!
He did it!
He did it.
See you next time!