On April 6, 2016, they made their debut
with "Silent Majority."
They sold 261,580 copies in the first
week of release,
and made a shocking debut.
On August 10 of the same year,
they released their second single,
"Sekai Ni Wa Ai Shika Nai."
They were also used as the theme song
for the main drama,
and grew up with more momentum.
To be continued...
That's how Keyakizaka 46 released their
3rd single "Futari Sezon" on November
30th of the same year.
In addition, the first one-man live was
held at the Ariake Coliseum on December
24th and 25th with that momentum.
In this program, we look back on their
dramatic year of 2016 from their debut.
Keyakizaka 46, where will they go in
2016 and 2017?
Tokyo
Pre-Opening
In 2019, Shizuoka University entered the
Tokyo Olympics.
"Tokyo Olympics" is held at the Tokyo
Olympics, and will be used for the first
time in 2 years.
The Tokyo International Olympic Games
will take place on June 31, 2019.
The Tokyo Olympics are being hosted at
Shizuoka University.
On April 6, 2016, the debut single
"Silent Majority" was released.
Their revolution began here.
Where do you go at the intersection
where there are so many people?
Wearing clothes that look like they've
been washed away
With a similar expression
Please!
As if I'm lost in the crowd
I'm walking without stopping
What are you hesitating about when
you're different from others?
People who go ahead look back and say,
"Don't cross the line."
I read the rules, but those eyes are
dead
There are many people who can't lip-
sync.
This is my first experience, so I don't
know what I'm doing right now.
Actually, you don't have to make a voice
when you're doing it.
Actually, the way you make a voice and
the way you move your mouth will change
your facial expression.
If possible, I want you to sing with
your voice out.
Then, you'll be able to see the real
voice, even the tremor.
So, including that, I want you to be
able to see everything.
You have to do it with the intention
that you want to use all of your cuts.
Are you okay?
Don't let your voice go down to your
ankles.
Let's practice only your ankles.
OK, let's do it.
It's hard to make a debut.
This single was a big obstacle for them,
who had never danced before.
I think it's going to be pretty intense.
Let's do our best.
Shining, shining, shining, OTP!
Fight!
Their first challenge.
A new trial awaits.
It's the same. Everyone's height doesn't
change, right?
The ball is flying a lot, isn't it?
You have to put your feet in to make it
look high.
So you have to take care of that.
Please look forward to it.
The debut single "SILENT MAJORITY" sold
260,000 copies.
It was the largest sales record for a
female artist's debut single.
It became a record-breaking hit single,
symbolizing Keyakizaka46.
"Keyakizaka46"
The reunion was brought to you by
DREAMCATCHER and ONE PIECE.
On August 10, 2018, the second single
"Sekai ni wa ai shika nai" was released.
This single was also decided to be the
theme song for Keyakizaka46's first
starring drama.
When I ran up the sidewalk, the blue sky
of summer was right there.
I should have known that I would never
reach it, but I stood up and reached out
with all my might.
I can't just keep staring at you.
My feelings for you overflowing in my
heart are frustrating.
Thank you very much.
I want to make it look like JK.
Oh, it looks like JK.
I'm so excited.
- I don't think so. - I don't think so.
This is rare.
That's right.
- Some of the staff have never been
there. - That's right.
- I don't go there that often. - What?
I want to buy a year's worth of caramel.
Five, and six, and five, six, seven.
I'm trying to get rid of the dust.
That's why I want to express the feeling
of being captured by the music video.
This song was the first music video
shooting with all the members for NERU
in Nagahama.
The atmosphere was completely different.
It was a little cold in the delicious
air of Hokkaido.
We all ran at full speed in the air.
We all joined hands and danced.
It was so much fun.
The other side of the grassland was a
wide sea.
I was so impressed that we danced while
looking at it.
I'm so excited!
This is so much fun!
It's so cold.
But the view is beautiful.
We're on the edge of Hokkaido.
It's different from "Silent Majority,"
Samu-san.
My hair is crazy.
It was a dance that was beyond "Silent
Majority."
It was so intense, I was so surprised.
I couldn't speak.
I had a lot of muscle pain.
If we had a little more time, we would
have danced.
I had a hard time.
I want you to see it.
"Let's all go with just the two of us"
I'm not sure if it's good or bad, but
I'll keep doing it.
I'm glad to hear that.
"The End"
This day, the youngest center.
15-year-old Hirate Yurina is celebrating
her 15th birthday.
Congratulations!
When I turned 15,
I knew about Keyakizaka46 from the
moment I became a member of the group.
This year, I want to do my best to let
more people know about Keyakizaka46.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is bad.
Is he already here?
Really?
Nagahama Bell is in front of you, so
let's go to the stage.
On May 8, 2016, 11 people who passed the
Hiragana Keyaki were announced.
Finally, Hiragana Keyaki will start.
I was very excited and worried about
what would happen next.
I made a promise.
I'm very happy to be able to work with
them.
I want to make them a group that can be
on "Kohaku Uta Gassen".
I'm Shiho Kato, 18 years old, and I'm
from Tokyo.
I want to be as famous as I can be.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
Well...
Look at the camera.
I want to be an idol who can make people
smile.
Thank you.
I want to be like the sun.
An idol?
Zero.
Well...
I don't know.
That's all.
More?
Thank you very much.
Keyakizaka 46 released their first
single "Futari Sezon" and their second
single "Futari Sezon"
Keyakizaka 46 has been working hard
through various activities
The last single in 2016 became a
powerful, beautiful, and delicate work
that can only be expressed by them
The theme of this project is "impulse of
the heart".
When everyone has the same sense of
rhythm in their hearts, it becomes a
dance.
The theme of the music video is "impulse
of the heart".
It was really fun.
It was my first time to dance like this.
We've been waiting for you!
Why did you scream?
I'm sure it was in the last part.
I don't want to go back.
♪You appear before my eyes, you are the
center, you are the center♪
♪You make my day shine♪
♪A scenery different from yesterday♪
♪To live is to change, you are the
center♪
♪Oh, oh, oh, oh♪
Stand up.
Put your hands together.
Ready, go!
Spread your arms and grab each other's
hands.
Everyone, look up.
Wow, amazing!
It may have gotten a little bigger.
Thank you for your hard work.
One, two, three.
Keiaki Hiragana shot her first music
video with this song.
Everything was her first experience.
She was nervous and anxious.
Good morning.
It's amazing.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
rendezvous
- Good morning. - Good morning.
I'm excited.
It's been a while since I wore a high
school uniform, so I'm happy.
I feel like I'm back in the day.
I'm worried that I'll get burned.
I'm nervous.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous, but I'm looking forward to
it.
Good morning.
It's been a long time.
I've been eating all the time.
If you don't mind, please.
It's a live show.
3, 2, 1
Cut!
Ready, action!
It is very delicious.
I have a lot of head.
It is full of meat.
- I couldn't express it well. - That's
true.
I want to be able to do it more and
more.
This is what Raman-san is doing.
It's like the one in "Ten to Chihiro no
Kami Hyakushi".
When grandma goes to grandma's house,
there's a lamp that bounces like this.
It's similar to that.
- We're back. - We're back.
- I'm sorry. - She's crying.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
I can't dance without everyone.
Thank you very much.
I was seen by so many people.
At first, I couldn't smile at all.
It's hard, isn't it?
But didn't you have a good smile at the
end?
Yes, I did.
So, maybe...
No.2 was good.
No.1 was a little stiff.
I'm hungry.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
It's my first time doing this.
I don't know what's going on.
I had a lot of fun.
I'm glad I got to meet everyone.
Finally, the dance scene with all the
members started.
I'm sweating just by dancing once.
I think it was better at the rehearsal.
At first, I was nervous.
I didn't feel the same.
I don't know if it was because I didn't
want to do it, or because my dance was
not good enough.
Everyone has to show Hiragana
Keyakizaka.
I want to show everyone that I don't
want to be judged by my ability.
Yuka and Kumi always lead me.
She did a live performance before the
handshake event.
But everyone said, "Neru, you do it."
So I changed my mind halfway through and
did my best.
It was pretty tough, to be honest.
Cut.
It's all a little frustrating.
I looked at myself on the monitor, and I
thought, "I'm not there yet."
And your legs.
Let's do our best for the last three
times.
It was really hard.
I practiced a lot, but I was so
desperate.
This might be the last take of the
dance.
Let's do our best.
With a big jump
The wings of hope
The sun is shining
Believe in yourself
You can do
You can do it
A little more
Thank you very much
To make a music video
A lot of people are involved
With gratitude
The most
That's what I had in mind.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm glad I got to make a music video.
I knew I wasn't good enough.
I was so frustrated.
I cried.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I want to be the best group ever.
Today, I'm going to show you how to make
a simple and easy-to-make cake.
I hope you enjoy watching this video.
To be continued...
We will now begin the explanation of the
First One-Man Live.
Thank you very much.
We only have 1, 2, 3, 4 times to go, but
we'll do our best, so please look
forward to it!
Please look forward to it!
On Christmas, they had their first one-
man live as a group in 2016.
Keyakizaka46, who has been running up
and down since their brilliant debut.
What kind of girls will we be able to
see in 2017?