Translations & timing by u/onji, proofreading by u/TheThrawn and u/Shadeslayr, additional revisions and styling by u/wkvesey
Please wait a moment for the start of the broadcast
Hai! I'm Elementary School 6th grade student Hidaka Marin! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Hai! I'm Middle Sch... Ahh, everyone, are you ready?
Err... just now I was playing
an impersonation of Marin
Well... Everyone, are you ready?
Good... Ōganing!
Thank you very much! I'm Middle School 3rd year student and Education Chairperson Ōga Saki! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Hai! I'm Middle School 3rd year student and Talk Chairperson Shirai Saki! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Hai! I'm Middle School 3rd year student and Student Council President Isono Rinon! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Hai! Now we've started "Houkago! Manande Monday!" for this week. (Afterschool! Learning Monday!)
This week's Day Leader is I, Isono Rinon. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
In this program, we'll introduce you to the charm of Sakura Gakuin
which we can't show at a concert or an Open Class event. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Staff: Oh, you're fluent!
Today, the four of us will present this program, but Sakura Gakuin also has
Kurashima Sara, Kurosawa Mirena, Yamaide Aiko,
Today's Lineup:
Isono Rinon
Ōga Saki
Shirai Saki
Kurashima Sara
Kurosawa Mirena
Yamaide Aiko
Okada Megumi
Okazaki Momoko
Asō Maaya
Hidaka Marin
Fujihira Kano
Yoshida Soyoka
and
Mori-sensei
Okada Megumi, Okazaki Momoko,
Asou Maaya, Fujihira Kano,
and Yoshida Soyoka. All 12 of us are growing up cheerfully every day!
Well, let's have an opening talk.
Hai!
Staff: You're very down-to-earth.
Well, I did it in the minimum time.
Staff: Oh, I see. You're in a hurry.
I think we can go without it.
Oh, shall we omit the opening talk?
But, at least we should talk about today.
Oh, definitely!
Certainly!
Today, we went to a place... Do you know where?
Of course you know. You must know.
There is no way they could know!
I'm sorry... Well, Marin, go ahead.
Okay, today
we went to Tower Records Shibuya
to see the Sakura Gakuin Museum
together with all 12 of us.
It was awesome!
It's so fun!
There we could see several messages from Fukei-sans
left on a message board.
And today, we left our messages
on the same message board.
There were unexpectedly lots of messages of Fukei-sans. I was so pleased!
And we left messages on the small blank spaces we found.
So, please go and find our messages.
Honestly, I had hoped to leave my message at a noticeable place...
...but it was so full of messages. It was difficult to find a space to write.
There were some blank spaces at the top, but they were too high for me.
Our messages might be hard to find. Go and look for them, please!
Onegaishimasu!
Well, let's hurry, so as not to waste time.
We have a lot to talk about today.
Then let's invite our Homeroom Teacher, Mori-sensei.
Ready?
"Mori-sensei!"
Hello there! I'm Mori Hayashi, thank you for inviting me!
Let's keep talking fast!
You look very excited.
Excited? Yes, it's because I have too much energy left!
You must be careful of speaking, especially when you have too much energy
Err, only I didn't get tired.
Ah, I see.
I regret I couldn't get tired.
Anyways, today we'll talk about
the event which made a blast last night. All through this program.
We have a lot to talk about the event.
["M-1 Grand-Prix" is a famous TV program in which the funniest comedian-duo for the year is decided.]
Yes, last night was the "M-1 Grand-Prix"!
Everybody was so excited to watch the program on TV Asahi!
No! This program is for us, Sakura Gakuin!
What do you think about the new way to judge the participants?
Do you like the new way, or not?
No? Aren't we going to talk about the event?
Err... No, we are gonna...
Definitely not.
This studio is not for...
You know, Principal Kuramoto is one of the staff for the event in the other studio.
He is also responsible for OUR event!
I'm very pleased to be criticized in this fierce manner!
What are you talking about?
Well, last night, we had the 5th anniversary concert of Sakura Gakuin.
So, today, we want to review the concert in this program.
All right, Day Leader!
Rise!
Attention!
Bow!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Sit!
Well, well... You have a lot to say, right?
Yes, we do.
I do have a lot, seriously!
You're making me scared.
No, I don't want to make you scared.
You are really excited today.
It creeps me out.
As I've said, I'm not tired at all. I had almost nothing to do last night.
You're too loud.
You appeared for only a few minutes.
I felt really lonely these last two days.
Altogether, there were about four hours
and I was on the stage for only five minutes.
Yes, you were.
I had been waiting for eight hours and took part for only five minutes!
I think it's because you made yourself hoarse at the Festival.
Ah, it could be true. Oh, was it a penalty on me? Was my time reduced like Ōga's time was?
Yes, it's a penalty.
No, Ōga's time wasn't reduced. Mori-sensei got the first ban.
Oh I see. Anyway, there were really a lot of things happening
and I was watching all of them from backstage.
Now, let's have a review of Day 1.
This is the setlist for Day 1.
As it shows... it was full of a variety of things.
So many things.
We had quite a lot.
Well, let's review one by one.
The very first song was "Chime".
Right from the beginning, something happened. What happened?
At the performance of "Chime",
Megu made terrible "mistakes" in the choreo.
But it was as a lead-in to the next skit.
Yes, that was an introduction.
My mom took it as a true mistake of Megu.
When I went home, she said, "Is Megu-chan all right? She made terrible mistakes!"
Is that right? In fact, Okada made the mistakes on purpose. It was in the script.
Oh, we can watch the scene?
We can watch the footage.
I want to watch it.
It must be fun.
The scene was... In the script, there was only the line: "She makes a mistake."
She did great.
But, she made a LOT of mistakes.
She played herself making a mistake, trying to recover from it, and getting worse.
She played her role very well. The footage is ready?
Well, let's give it a look.
From this scene...
It's the last climax of the song.
Everyone is acting her role as a performer, and...
Oh, no...
I can't help laughing!
She is making a really terrible mistake.
Megu! You can't do that!
She is full of smiles.
Oh no! It's too bad!
She faced the wrong direction again.
Other girls are in good smiles.
It's awesome!
Megu, good job!
Were you acting your role?
Yes, giving a glance.
Glancing at her with a concerned look.
Oh! I didn't....
Hidaka, What's wrong?
I actually didn't notice Megu-chan making a mistake!
Unbelievable! You knew the script!
I knew the script, but...
Then, you had to be surprised that you didn't notice the mistake.
I was too focused on my dancing.
I was dancing the same choreo with Megu-chan's.
Ah, your choreo was symmetrical.
Yes, it's symmetric and...
I see.
I didn't notice Megu-chan making a mistake at all!
You are awesome!
You're the only one who didn't notice, among everybody in the venue!
Everyone but you was feeling anxious!
You are amazing!
But her acting was very realistic.
Just as Isono's mother was fooled.
Audience, were you fooled by the play?
Maybe.
It made me feel so good,
imagining the audience watching with anxious hearts!
And then, the skit began.
Yes, there was an atmosphere of encouraging Megu.
Oh, really?
Fukei-sans were trying to cheer Megu up.
Could you sense that kind of mood from the audience?
Yes, we could feel an "It's okay, Megu!"-like atmosphere.
Oh, I'm sorry they felt that way,
although that's what I was aiming for.
I see. Anyway, she made the terrible mistake because
she was "getting into a slump and was depressed."
The skit was...
usually we play a comedy in the Festival or in other concerts.
This time, we replayed the skit which we had performed in the 2011 nendo,
with revisions for the 2015 nendo.
First of all, there was an earnest playing of Isono
which was originally played by Mutō Ayami.
Yes.
Isono played a very sincere person.
It was really... I'm very bad at acting.
No, you did well!
Why not reenact those lines here?
You were acting with confidence.
Which lines?
It was very good.
"For the two of you, the 5th..."
Yes, those are the lines. I was very impressed with Isono's acting.
Give it a try.
Please try it now.
What, now?
To the camera...
Let's see your sincere performance.
OK.
It's possible performing this would get you invited to a prime-time TV drama of Tele-Asa.
No, I don't aim for that job!
Give it a try now.
OK. "For the two of you..." lines?
Yes, it's a good line.
It makes me laugh...
For the two of you, the 5th anniversary concert is very important, isn't it?
Having it in such feelings... I'm sorry for you... Please...
Cut! You are great!
You're awesome!
Too cool!
"For the two of you, the 5th anniversary concert..."
What? Stop! Why are you trying to make fun of her sincere acting?
"I'm sorry for you!"
Ok, if you want to play the lines, I'm gonna let you do it!
Show us your acting please!
You've tried to make a lot of fun, haven't you?
Oh, wait! Why not give it a try with your Shizuku-chan?
No. Please don't push me!
There is a "Murakami Shizuku-chan" character in the comedy part of the skit.
Yes, she is.
But I prefer the lines you were just playing.
I'd like to see Ōga play Isono's lines.  "For the two of us..."
"For the two of us..." and what?
Oh, I remember... Well, very earnestly?
Of course. In very earnest way.
Oh no! I can't...
You can't? You were just giving them!
OK, I'll give it a try.
Please go ahead.
For the two of you...
the 5th anniversary concert is very important... isn't it?
Giving it with such feeling...
What are you doing?
No... I can't play sincerely in this mood!
The mood doesn't matter!
Now you made Tele-Asa angry again!
Ehhh?!
It makes it harder for you to become an actress!
No more bantering like that!
Well then, Shirai played the role that Miyoshi Ayaka played.
You portrayed bantering.
Yes I did.
How was that?
It was very difficult.
to give a well-timed banter... and the way I speak... It was very difficult.
It was a hard time.
I thought you did well.
Really?
And then, Hidaka played someone placing an order telepathically.
I'm sorry, I can't describe it to those who didn't watch it!
The one like this.
Yes, give it a try now. Telepathically...
Look! Your face at this scene!
Scary!
What's this?!
Creepy!
I didn't do that!
You did it!
I didn't play this expression!
I can feel something weird!
Too scary!
Definitely I didn't play this!
I can see a girl like this in a midnight horror drama.
You are the person closest to a having a debut on a TV drama!
I agree. She can make a debut!
To play "Get out!" or something like that.
I can't believe it!
You were exactly like this. Why are you so surprised?
No way... I just acted...
But it's...
Wait! I guess this shot will be shown repeatedly.
I agree! This must be shown again and again.
To illustrate Marin's personality.
But, it was really good acting, to play a telepath.
She looks scary...
I read the old script again and found that Horiuchi had played the telepathic order.
Yes, I remember that.
Look! Now Shizuku-chan came...
So the old and the new skits have some similarity.
But this is a totally new character by Ōga.
Oh no! I hate this...
She didn't appear in the 2011 nendo skit... Ōga was playing her.
Marin: "I'm Dai-chan!"
Saki's voice was more powerful.
When she played Dai-chan at the transfer-in ceremony, the voice was very feeble.
Oh I see. Dai-chan is becoming grown-up?
This time, Dai-chan had a powerful voice.
Her voice has gotten bolder since the transfer-in ceremony.
I got it. But it's the least interesting growing-up in Japan for me.
Hasn't it?
I didn't know the doll gets bigger too.
Yes, she also grows up.
The doll also grows up?
It doesn't make sense.
Oh, I see. Its voice got bold.
Yes, the doll's...
Huh? The doll is getting bigger?
No, no! The voice of the doll...
Ah, its voice, I see.
By the way, she is NOT Ōga Saki!
She is Shizuku-chan!
Ah, I see. There is a complicated story about her.
And she is never YOU, right?
Never.
Then YOU didn't appear in the skit at all!
Right, I was left out.
I see. There was no Ōga.
And then, you performed several songs.
Are there any songs you want to review?
Wait! Can I suggest one?
"Planet Episode..."
Ah!
It was performed fourth.
Do you like the song, Mori-sensei?
There was a "happening" that occurred during the song.
Yes there was. It doesn't happen very often.
Can we see the footage?
No! I don't want it shown!
Well, let's give a look.
I want to look into each girl's face carefully
to see what expression they show at the exact moment of the problem.
Oh no, don't look at it!
I don't remember the moment at all.
We were facing backward.
Well, well, just after Kurosawa started her solo lines...
She is very enthusiastic.
Oh! It stopped. Why is the camera back on us?
Rinon: "It's a live performance thing."
Why is there a problem happening in this studio too?
What? What happened?
I've been possessed into the footage!
We have troubles in the footage and in this studio!
Rinon: "Don't...! Wait! Wait a moment!"
Well, let's watch it again.
Can we watch it without a pause?
I mean, I want to see the exact moment of the problem.
Shall we be silent for a while?
Yes. I want to take a serious look.
Serious?
We must learn.
Yes.
Oh I see. You want to learn something from the footage.
Yes, we must learn.
But it was really fun.
Was it fun?
Yes it was.
Why? Wasn't it a real problem?
It can only happen in a live show.
I tried to ask the audience to make some noise,
and I felt we got the biggest noise ever!
Really?
Oh! The Fukei-sans were also trying to overcome the trouble.
This time, there were some standees behind the seats,
and the standees were making a lot of noise.
True.
So, the problem united the audience?
Yes.
The standees were also copying the dancing.
By the way, you look super relaxed, leaning forward.
It's as if you were watching TV at home.
I'm sorry!
Oh, can we watch? Let's enjoy the footage.
Give it a look. It's sad to see her excitement.
At this point, the sound stopped due to unexpected equipment trouble!
Ah, it's edited.
Momoko!
Aiko: "Performing live is the best!"
C-chan: "It's an unexpected trouble with the sound system."
Momoko: "Let's have a talk with the Fukei-sans..."
Rinon: "Wait! Stop talking simultaneously!"
Multiple: "Right! Got it!"
Aiko: "Calm down."
C-chan: "At a time like this, we must wait for a green light from the teachers."
Multiple: "Yes, that's right!"
Mirena: "Tell me in advance, please!"
Rinon: "It's okay."
Rinon: "Well, why not ask Fukei-sans again to make some noise?"
Saki: "Yes, it sounds good."
Rinon: "This time, the venue is huge!"
It seems you are really enjoying it.
Yes, it was fun.
Mirena: "Very huge!"
Rinon: "Everyone on the third floor! Are you having fun?"
Ah, I see.
It looks great. Everyone was not...
Everyone was not confused, unexpectedly.
It happens every year.
Yes, it happens.
It's not so unusual, so...
Your words make the staff feel hurt... You make it sound like the trouble happens constantly!
No, but every year...
I see. You've had experience with the trouble and can handle it.
Yes.
But Hidaka has never had it. How did you feel?
When the music stopped...
the footage reminded me that...
I was making this pose for a while.
Ah, you danced in this pose.
I was at a loss what shall I do next.
I see. You had been giving an "OK" signal for a while.
No, this is my posing in the choreo!
I know that! Why on earth should you be giving an "OK" signal to the staff?!
You were at a loss for a while, and how did you feel when you found out there was a real problem?
Ah... something went wrong.
You were late to know... but you didn't get panicked?
Hai!
But it's interesting to see each girl reacted differently.
Sure.
Kurosawa was trying her best, as if she could still hear the music!
Yes she was trying hard!
She was singing very hard!
What did you think when the music stopped, Isono?
Well, I've had... two times?...
of having trouble with the PA.
You have experience.
In such a case, I remember a teacher said to us
that we had better start MC-ing
rather than try to keep singing with only hand-clapping.
I think she said that to us, so
I see.
I didn't get panicked.
I got it.
Even if we tried to keep singing with hand-clapping,
I was not sure if we can finish the song to the end!
Certainly!
Shirai was so calm as to realize
it's hard to finish singing to the end.
It was still the beginning of the song!
I see.
You saw a girl keep singing, and thought "No! Cut it out!"
Yes. We were only just playing the second planet!
Shirai was so calm, that she instructed everyone to wait for the green light of the teachers.
After the show, there was Iida... Iida Raura had been there, and she said
"Mori-sensei, we were very lucky to have Isono there!"
as if it had been her achievement!
"She has experience and that's why she could handle it so well!"
Rau-chan is someone who speaks that way sometimes!
Isn't she?
I knew she is someone like that!
She speaks proudly!
Yes, she speaks very proudly like "It's good for US to have her!"
I couldn't agree more!
You're making her angry!
I know. But Rau-chan won't take it bad.
Rau-chan, we're sorry.
What? Why we are sorry?
Rau-chan is very scary if she gets angry.
No worries.
Saki will apologize to her.
Please give my regards to her.
Well, is there anything more for Day 1?
Oh! There is!
You performed "Let's Dance".
Yes! We did!
Please explain it for those who didn't watch.
Yes. "Let's Dance" is a dance performance
without singing
Yes.
which we once performed at the 2012 Festival
as a "Dance Club" performance
just after "Motteke Sailor Fuku".
Yeah... It was a... difficult brainteaser.
Brainteaser? Was it a puzzle to solve?
I guess she wanted to say "a difficult problem."
You're right. It was a difficult problem.
But, it was very fun... What? Did I say something wrong?
No! You are right!
It's great that you had fun,
and many people praised it.
Really?
I felt it was cool.
Fukei-sans didn't expect that to come, did you?
I'm sure no one expected it.
Have you ever performed it before?
I performed it.
Isono and Ōga performed it. Shirai?
Only two of us... No, I didn't perform it.
Shirai performed it for the first time.
Yes. Only two members had experience
among the 12 of us.
There is some footage again. Let's give it a look.
I'd love to see it!
A bit embarrassing!
You look very at home.
Wow, it's cool!
Hidaka, what's wrong?
I performed it with an expressionless face.
That's the way this performance is supposed to be, isn't it?
To play it with a big smile makes you look strange.
It's cool!
Our mics are on now?
On, all right.
What was the most difficult part of this choreo?
At first, we couldn't find the exact timing to move.
Timing to move?
For the 1, 2, 3, 4 counts, each girl has her own choreo to dance.
Ah, each girl had to dance in different timing?
Yes, each one had to harmonize her movement with...
That sounds difficult.
Here, I'm getting quite a lot of weight on my back!
Too cool!
Ah, you are being pressed down hard?
I'm at the center of the circle, and I felt heavily pressed on my back.
Maybe someone was having a rest leaning on you!
Wow, you look sharp!
So cool!
I love the choreo where you make a sidestep while keeping the same axis.
Here, this choreo.
Ah, it's a good memory.
You only performed it yesterday,
it's too soon to feel nostalgic!
It reminds me of my first performance when I was a 6th grader.
I see, your first performance.
I feel nostalgia too.
Wow!
Oops, it suddenly switches to the studio when I'm into watching!
You must be careful! You'll look stupid!
I was off guard, and then the camera suddenly comes to me...
It's important. If Kurosawa was here, she would have looked into the camera with confidence.
Next time, after watching some footage, try to show your good face.
Let's take a practice to show yourself handsomely.
Anyway, the performance got a really good reputation.
Please tell me the most significant point for you.
Oh, I can't decide...
Hidaka! You're trying to talk a lot today. It's very good!
You're trying your best against the three seniors.
Yes, indeed.
Er... there is a choreo where only us four elementary schoolers dance like this.
I really love that choreo!
Oh, really?
Only the four of us got the spotlight.
I see. It's good to be spotlighted.
Certainly!
It's really... How can I say...
You're taking too much time!
Wow! Very strict! You're too harsh of a senpai, aren't you?
"I think it's been Hidaka's time"!
C-chan is very willing to talk.
You need to talk? OK, with a little English, please.
That part was... for me... too good and...
In English?
I see, it was too good.
So, I love that part.
I see.
Really, your dancing was very sharp.
Well, Shirai, now it's your turn. I'll give you a long time to talk.
She must say something very interesting!
Oh, everyone is strict today!
The part... how can I describe it...
it's like a heart beating.
I see.
A girl is stacked on top of another girl.
Megu and Saki (me) are in the center of the circle,
You were in the center.
and I got a pretty heavy weight on my back!
You already said that when we were watching the footage!
How can you repeat the same thing!
No, no! I want to say I was almost falling down!
Today, you are very harsh to each other.
Oh, you were almost falling down? With too much weight?
I tottered on my feet.
I see.
The "Office Lady" has weak legs, doesn't she?
I need to build muscle.
Because you have weak legs.
How was the performance, Isono? You danced very sharply!
I've taken a liking to dancing.
So I was pleased to get the chance to dance seriously.
Yes, you danced seriously.
You were really into your performance.
Focused on dancing.
It was good to see your serious expressions.
I hope you'll perform this dance again.
Well, let's go forward with the review.
Was there something significant for Day 1?
There were a lot of things! "The History of 5 Years" footage was great...
And we played a medley of good songs...
Ah! The new song!
Yes! We unveiled it!
OK, let's talk about the new song.
"Kirameki no Kakera".
Oh! VTR!
Can we see the footage? Then, let's see.
I'm excited!
We must show our handsome faces.
When the camera returns to you...not now.
Not now? I see.
The face Shirai showed now was very...can I see it again?
No way!
It was great...OK, when the camera returns, please show it again.
Please take a close-up shot of C-chan.
That face was really awesome. Well, let's watch the footage.
I couldn't help laughing at Shirai's face!
Well, this new song is
written by cAnON-san.
When you perform a new song, do you get nervous?
Yes, of course.
The audience also feels something unusual, and are focusing on listening to it.
Are there any highlights in the dancing?
Highlights? The climax will come soon.
The climax of the song is great.
Indeed.
Wait...I might have made a mistake...
C-chan!
You made a mistake?
This footage is from Day 1... then I didn't make a mistake.
Soon, the camera will return to us.
I got it.
Wait... were you really watching the footage?
I don't believe someone who was watching the footage can show such an expression.
I was watching!
How can you show that expression?
What feeling were you watching the footage with? You're amazing!
The climax of the song... did you see our sharp dancing?
Yes, it's very sharp.
I guess there'll be a good chance to see the song from now on.
So please remember the song and have a blast with the song.
Then, let's finish the review on Day 1, due to time constraints.
Although, I know there are more things to be reviewed,
like the Koubaibu performance, or the revival of "Wonderful Journey".
Now, let's take a look at tweets from the audience.
I want to hear some opinions on the show.
I agree. I still have not gotten opinions.
I want to hear your voice.
"The new song is just awesome!"
Yes, I feel that way too
"You are so lucky to have such a good song."
Yes, indeed.
"The new song is very stylish."
Oh, I see.
Look! "I love the pair of Marin-chan and C-chan."
Yeah!
At the "chō jūyōna suteppu" line, ("super-important step")
I see.
you two make a pair in the song, right?
There are lines which sing
"oikomaresō, nomikomaresō". ("being chased, being swallowed up (...by the drive to win)")
At that line, I hold hands with C-chan.
We hold hands like this.
Tightly.
Very firm.
We take firm grips.
Everyone is trying to place stress on Shirai, aren't they?
During the performance.
Saki (me) is also doing the same in return.
It seems everyone is trying to weaken each other.
Oh, that's why we felt so tired.
No, just kidding.
Well then, we proceed to Day 2!
The setlist of the Day 2 is like this.
Can you see?
Which camera?
[This board shows a wrong setlist. It's titled "Setlist for Day 2" but the right side is copied from Day 1.]
The show began with "Mezase! Super Lady".
It's the only part where Mori-sensei appeared.
I spoke nothing on the day. Just read the lyrics exactly.
Hidaka, what's wrong?
I have something to say.
You're very proactive today! It's great!
It's good.
Well, when we had the rehearsal of "Mezase! Super Lady",
Mori-sensei called the names of the girls one by one.
Yes, I call them.
At the time, Mori-sensei...
Er... we took the rehearsal three times...
Yes, we did.
And in all three takes he forgot my name!
Oh, no! You snitch on me? You are so willing to speak ill of me?
Ah... it's true.
You really couldn't call her name.
OK, to tell the truth,
you know, I call the roll at the bridge of the song, like "Middle School third years, Isono Rinon, Ōga Saki, Shirai Saki"...
Calling the roll. I see.
After I finish calling the roll—I'm done.
I feel like I've achieved something.
Oh, no!
I'm very likely to make a mistake right after that!
Yes, it's true.
So, when I call the name of Hidaka.
after I finish calling the roll with "Yoshida Soyoka!"
I'm already done and forget her name!
I feel very satisfied after I complete calling the roll.
You're mean!
But, I did well in the show.
Yes, you did.
That's the awesomeness of me!
It's so nice of me to not make a mistake in front of the audience!
It is expected to be able to do that!
Shut up! How come I'm the one being lectured by you?
The VTR footage is ready?
Do you want to watch it? I'm not willing to see "Super Lady".
OK, take a look if you want.
Let's see it. I want to see.
Ah, from my entrance...
It was really funny.
Why "funny?" You must say "cool"!
Sensei, you look a bit...
Yes, I got fat a bit.
"Attendance will now be taken!"
A tense atmosphere... It's enormous.
It's a pretty long solo shot.
It's pretty long.
I'm sorry for it. I apologize for letting live viewers see me alone for a long time.
I made it just in time.
It's super funny to watch it with your eyes on Mori-sensei!
Don't pay attention to me!
Look! Very funny!
I have some times when I have nothing to do,
so I'm trying to imitate your dancing as much as possible.
It's so funny!
You got a problem with that? I'm trying my best
while not affecting my memory.
Too much dancing makes me forget my own lines.
I'm telling Yamaide off...
for her having an ice cream.
Don't look at me!
You're making fun of me... terribly!
Oh, five seconds until the camera's back. Strike a pose!
5...4...
No, no, it doesn't make sense as a pose
after watching the footage!
Mori-sensei, you're too funny...
I did pretty well on the Festival
and still kept everything in my mind.
So, I was trying to duplicate your dancing, as far as possible.
Your duplication was too poor.
It's not so bad. I never miss dancing Isono's choreo.
The choreo everyone dances, like this!
I always dance that choreo.
From now on, we can't miss watching Mori-sensei.
Look! A Fukei is very pleased. I did it!
Shirai, was it really good?
It was... indescribable!
You should bring a copy of the footage back home.
Now I'd like to see the "Mori-sensei Version," the footage focusing on Mori-sensei!
No one wants it!
like a "Fan's-eye camera".
Yes, the "Fan's-eye camera".
No one needs it, definitely.
Well, well... This is not the time to disclose such things. We have little time left.
Yes! we must hurry up!
As for Day 2, we had that event at the ending.
Yes, there was a surprise event.
What was that surprising event?
This setlist shows... Is this for Day 1?
Which one is for Day 2? This one includes "Mathematica"...
That is the setlist of Day 1.
Before that, I have something to say.
Hmm? Hidaka?
At the performance of "Kimi ni Todoke",
at the interlude, I dropped my microphone!
Yes, that happened.
You're good enough to say it by yourself!
I am so sorry for what I did!
You learned something.
So, I want to give a message to a member... Sara-chan.
Give a message? Can you make it short?
There is a harsh senpai who is fussy about time—Shirai!
Yes, I am!
Well, go ahead.
Sara-chan, thank you very much for picking my mic up!
Oh, there was such an accident. Is there footage?
No footage? I see.
Please describe what happened. Hidaka, you dropped your mic?
Yes. I dropped my mic, and it rolled to the back of the stage.
Wow that's terrible. The mic is so precious.
I noticed a sound, something hitting the floor.
You noticed?
Yes, and I found a mic.
I kept singing with the pin-mic...
and Sara-chan held two... both...
Sara-chan's mic and my mic.
She was dancing with mics in both hands.
Wow! Amazing! She was dancing like a dual-sword wielder?
But listen! I heard Rinon-chan speak to Sara at the interlude,
when we were facing backward.
"Pick it up" or something like that.
I was wondering what they were saying, while we were facing backward.
Isono, did you suggest to Kurashima to pick up the mic?
Er... If Sara had left the mic at the back of the stage,
a Staff-san would have had to go pick it up at the encore.
In order to save the trouble,
Sara should have gotten the mic and kept it with her. So I told Sara...
Wow! Isono directed her to do so
while you were dancing. It's amazing!
Sara didn't hear me at all!
So I cried out very loud "Sara!"
Really?
That happened?
It's fun!
But it so happens that we danced that song with our fists tight.
It happened to be good to hold two mics,
So it didn't disturb her dancing.
Then, Kurashima was dancing with two mics in her hands,
as if she were practicing with dumbbells!
Yes!
It must have looked gallant. Kurashima is very handsome.
Anyway, it's good for you
that you could give an apology in this public program.
Thank you Sara-chan!
Well, then. At the end...
Let's talk about the surprise.
Hai!
When you were playing "message" at the encore,
this surprise took place. Please watch the VTR.
It's not starting...
What shall we do?
Glittering〜
What's that? Ōga-san, you're very proactive today!
Oh, it's coming!
Fantastic!
You're playing "message".
Here everyone is holding her mic properly.
She forgot?
No, I don't think so.
I think someone forgot.
Never.
You can see in the footage.
It seems that there were lots of troubles.
Well, here they come.
Look...
No, it's no problem.
Whoa〜
Don't forget it's on the air.
Awesome!
Kawaii!
I feel they emit a dreadful aura about themselves!
What do you mean!?
There's an aura of divinity about them!
I feel they try to emit that aura intentionally!
The aura comes out by itself!
I sense a "Finally, Miyoshi Ayaka has come all the way to see you"-feeling!
Why do you say that!
Well, Matsui is not bad, but
don't you feel something triumphant about Miyoshi?
You'll get in trouble!
Don't you sense an "I'm Miyoshi Ayaka. What about it?"-feeling?
You can't say such a thing!
I've had it! Ayaka-chan is really gentle!
Ayaka-chan is far more warm-hearted than Mori-sensei thinks!
I think I'm more knowledgeable about her!
Oh! You showed a good face to the camera!
Ah, I should have shown another pose.
Don't be shy, Isono... Huh? what's that pose?
It's Soyo's pose.
Too late.
It's not the time to open a small window.
Well, as you saw, there was an unexpected appearance of the graduates
Miyoshi Ayaka and Matsui Airi.
There was a meeting beforehand and you took a lesson with them.
How did you feel at their appearance?
They were so beautiful!
Right?.
Really?
They were beautiful, and the excitement of Fukei-sans was enormous!
I felt the audience were the most excited at that moment of the concert.
I can't believe it... but I know the appearance really surprised the audience.
To be honest, I think the audience was overwhelmed by their height.
No, it's impossible!
Is it?
Why do you think so?
When I saw them at a rehearsal...
you know, the members this year are all short.
Ah, that's true!
So, I thought "Wow, here come adult ladies!"
I guess the audience was overwhelmed "Wow! They are so tall!"
I think so, anyway.
They are our graduates, in a sense...
Why did you add "in a sense"?
You're harsher than me!
I made a mistake in my choice of words!
I know. "They were Sakura girls for only two years, but in a sense
they can be seen as graduates."
Ah, in a sense...
No! They are true graduates!
I was wrong.
Did you talk with them?
Yes I did.
As you know, I snitched on Mori-sensei to them.
It was a clumsy talk, wasn't it?
We must have a Review Meeting on it later.
And then, after the show,
I apologized to them for my speaking ad lib.
Ayaka-chan kindly said to me
"No problem. The atmosphere made you speak like that."
I see. You politely apologized and...
In short, Ōga said something off-script, right?
Yes.
And Miyoshi gave some harsh words about that.
But, at the backstage, she was kind.
Any other talks with them?
Before the show,
Matsui-san came to Rinon and said
"I don't remember the names of the transfer-ins!"
Yes, that's it!
How come you look so pleased?
I'm not pleased.
Oh, no!
Six of us transfer-ins gathered and
stood in front of Matsui-chan,
and asked who is who.
Ah, there was a meeting and she asked you to introduce yourselves?
"What's your name? Huh? Marin? Hard to catch..."
No, it's not that.
No? I see.
And, I remember she called me
"Momoko-chan!"
I see.
She was unsure of your name.
She tried to remember us.
But it's obvious that she lacks love for Sakura Gakuin.
She's had enough time to remember.
But honestly, Saki (me) couldn't remember all transfer-ins for about a month!
Unbelievable. You must remember at once!
I understand what you are saying, but this year,
You've been together with them!
there are too many with the initial "M",
and I'm fed up with "M"-people!
Stop it!
Here is a "M"arin person!
"Marin," "Mirena," "Momoko,"
"Megu," and also "Maaya!"
I feel like, "No more, please!"
What an evil senpai! Hidaka, she is thinking such things!
Terrible!
It's sad. She doesn't need "M"-persons.
It can't be helped. You can't change your name.
I remembered all the names the first day!
No, you’re lying!
He had been practicing a lot.
Don't expose my covert effort!
Well, I have something to say about them
which made me laugh.
Before the show,
the two of them spoke to all of you,
just before you make a huddle.
And first, Miyoshi spoke
for a long time. She took a really long time,
for about three minutes.
"To begin with, there are three floors. You must take care to reach the third floor..."
Like this, she started a very long instruction.
Every girl was anxious about the opening time,
but was willing to hear her senpai's words
Actually, she was saying good things...
Yes, it was good.
heartfelt and thoughtful things.
And she ended her talk,
and Matsui followed
with only one phrase "Let's have fun!"
and broke the ice.
That was exactly a "carrot and stick" approach.
Miyoshi hit you hard, and Matsui gave you a sweet carrot.
Didn't you think Miyoshi's instruction was long?
It was good!
She said really good things.
That was like...
Then, do you remember what she said?
Ayaka-chan taught us strictly what we need to think,
And Airi-chan calmed us toward the show.
The two of them made a good harmony.
Isn't this lip service? You're making a fishy face!
No, I didn't make a face!
The two of them are not watching this program. So tell the truth. Didn't you think Miyoshi's talk was long?
It wasn't long, was it?
Err...
Too hard to say?
No, you're wrong!
You know, we must be mentally prepared for the show,
I see.
and they are kind senpai who made us prepared.
Ah, Shirai is getting to speak sweet words.
Hm? Is there a group photo?
I want to see it.
The 12 of you.
Is it after the show?
Yes it is.
Well, I heard that
when a Staff of LoGiRL asked Isono "How was the show?"
she was so relieved to say "It's a big load off my mind."
I know how she feels.
It was really...
The load was that heavy?
How can I say... I'm the only one
who shared a time with the first graduates.
So I felt I must send gratitude on behalf of all the graduates.
I know.
So, I was very nervous.
Although, I feel nervous in every concert.
I see.
There was something grave... a sense of responsibility?
I understand.
So, there was something special, an unusual atmosphere.
It may be a bad remark, but you were haunted by the spirits of the graduates.
You were performing with spirits or wraiths on your shoulders!
The graduates sent us emails
Yes they did.
before the show began.
Such as, "I would be pleased if you give my gratitude to the audience for me."
That's a lot of pressure, isn't it?
Not at all.
As for Marina-chan's email...
Oh, what did she write?
I read it and forgot.
Wow! Read-and-forget?
Oh my...
I know Horiuchi is likely to spare you.
Yes, I thought it's OK if I'd reply later.
Everyone sent you emails and it's hard to reply to all of them.
Other than that, Shirai met... Was it Day 2?
Two of the Talk Chairpersons.
Yes, they came.
The first Chairperson, Sugisaki
and Notsu... now Honjo... Yunano.
Yes.
I know you felt pressure.
Actually, I didn't know they came.
They visited me after the show.
I wish I had known of their having been there.
I know they said something to you.
They said a lot.
What did they say?
Er... First, our MC-ing was pointless and lengthy.
Very harsh!
And as a Talk Chairperson
Saki (me) should have developed a topic more.
Wow, they are very demanding!
I got it. So today you vented your frustration on Hidaka!
The frustration you feel because you were told off!
It's scary!
No, that's not true!
Too bad!
Wow, I've found we have only a little time left.
Oh it's true.
I feel like talking more. Can I join the following program?
I want to talk with Chie-san, the hostess of the next program
about Sakura Gakuin.
I'm afraid you'd speak ill of us!
Well, now we've talked a lot
about the concert.
Anyway, we had fun, and could celebrate the 5th anniversary well.
Hai!
This program is going to end.
So, please...
We have some announcements.
We have little time left, so...
I know.
do it with your whole heart, but hastily.
Hai! We'll have Open Class events!
They're starting.
Yes! These are our first Open Class events in this... in the next year.
On Saturday, January 16th, 2016,
We'll have a "Study of Rhythmic Gymnastics",
inviting the Rhythmic Gymnastics Club of Tokyo Women's College of Physical Education as lecturers.
Great! I'm super happy!
And...
Why are you so happy?
I just now realize we invited members of the Rhythmic Gymnastics Club
Yes...
of a Women's College.
I have taken lessons in rhythmic gymnastics...
I'm super excited!
Listen! C-chan has just revealed something interesting!
I have experience in rhythmic gymnastics.
Shirai? Really?
For eight years.
Eight years!
This is the first I've heard of this!
But I still have a very inflexible body.
Unbelievable!
Well, we'll have another Open Class event,
The "Study of Rakugo" (Comic Storytelling)
[Saki mistakenly says "jūnanoka" for the 17th day (17日) of the month.  10 = jū,, 7 = nana,, 17 = jūnana, and day (日) = ka or nichi. The seventh day (7日) can be read as either "nanuka", "nanoka", or "nananichi", but 17日 can only be read as "jūnananichi".]
It'll be on Sunday, January "10 7th." (Jūnanoka)
Wonderful!
"Jūnanoka?!"
"17th!" ("Jūnananichi")
But Shirai won't...
Ah, that's right. I can't join the event because of a mock test of an entrance exam for high school.
You must prioritize the mock test.
Yes, I'm sorry!
We'll invite Mr. Tatekawa Shirano as a lecturer.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
I see, thanks. And...?
And! Tomorrow, on December 8th,
Our 5th Anniversary Video Single
"School days -2015-" will be released!
The photo of the jacket of this video single is
similar to the jacket photo of our debut single which was released in 2010.
We tried our best
to mimic the facial direction and the like.
Yes, we did.
So, please compare the two jacket photos.
Onegaishimasu!
Is that all?
No, not yet!
Wow! You have a lot of announcements!
And now, "Sakura Gakuin 5th anniversary Museum" is open
at the "SpaceHACHIKAI" on the 8th floor of Tower Records Shibuya.
I'm sure a Fukei must visit there.
Ah, I know.
Today, we were there
and we wrote our autographs
and wrote some messages on a message board.
So, even if you've already visited there, please go again
and find new features!
I see. There is something new.
And...
More!?
At the Tower Records Cafe Omotesando shop
you can enjoy three kind of collabo-dishes, which are Mini Pati collaborations.
They are re-makes of past Mini Pati dishes,
and also, you can see several photos of Mini Pati.
Please check it out!
Why are you laughing?
And more? You have more announcements?
It's the last announcement.
And, to commemorate the 5th anniversary of Sakura Gakuin, a wonderful story was produced!
[Synopsis: On the morning of Christmas, Marin wakes up and find herself in unfamiliar woods. She looks around and finds a small cabin in which several girls are having joyful chit-chats. And there come fairies and... It's a fantasy story which tells us the beauty of friendship, and the truth that there is nothing which can be wasted.]
Oh! Sounds great!
The members and five fairies weave a fantasy story
"ever after."
Here it comes! Thank you!
It came!
Then, Ōga, give it a try!
"evah aftah."
What the...!
Saki (me) can speak more fluently!
No no... Why on earth do you speak with a turned-up chin?
"evuh aftuh."
Now you can pre-order it at ASMART, the on-line shop
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
It sounds fun!
And I hear Hidaka is the featured actress.
Yes, she is!
I'm looking forward to seeing "ever after."
Well, we did lots of announcements in a short period this time, but
the next time will be our usual program.
We can't show you a trailer movie this time
because our talk took up all the time.
I hope you env... enjoyed our talk
Something wrong?
At the very last moment!
We must have a Review Meeting!
What did you say? OK, then, let me say something!
I think I must tell you off for your stumbling on your lines at the Day 1 show!
You made a lot of terrible stumbling, do you remember?
I'm so sorry!
OK! That's all!
Hai!
Well, after this program, from 8pm, the "Spir-log" of Mystery Hunter Chie-san will begin.
Chie-san, thank you for waiting!
We've warmed up the atmosphere for you!
Well, that's all! Day Leader!
Rise!
Attention!
Bow!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!
Everyone, show your good face, your good face!