Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Video camera
Please use the contents of the recording machine for shooting.
Please be aware of the use of cell phones in the seats.
On the top of the phone, there is a setting for the banner mode.
Please be careful not to make any noise.
Photo shooting inside the passenger seat
The number you have dialed is not available at the moment.
It is forbidden to smoke inside the venue.
Please have a look at the location of the restaurant.
If you have any questions or other problems, please post them in the comments.
The act of stealing things towards the stage is...
I think you know this.
It will be a nuisance to other customers.
絶対におやめください
See you!
Towels, sketchbooks, paintings, etc.
Please raise your arms to the height of your chest.
Video recording
There will be a camera for streaming and photography.
The number of customers is increasing, so please be aware of it in advance.
本日演出の都合上
I would like to give a speech at the top, the bottom, the top, and the bottom of the hall.
Please take a look at the exit in front of you.
Please wait for a while until the end of the show.
Today is...
KURASAKA 46
Welcome to the Sports Municipal, Supported by ION CARD.
Thank you very much.
We would like to take this opportunity to ask you a few questions.
Thank you.
Video camera
Thank you for watching.
Please do not use your mobile phone in the audience.
The mobile phone is on the top of the manner mode.
Please make sure there is no sound.
Let's take a picture together.
I used an ultrasonic telescope at the end of the day.
Thank you.
If you have any comments, please leave them in the comments section.
It's a corner where you step out of your seat and run forward.
The act of throwing things towards the stage is...
I think you can do it.
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
Thank you.
Edge Look, Uchiba, etc.
Please raise your hands with your chest open.
Broadcasting and...
There is a camera for photo shooting.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. Please be seated.
Today, at the Eiffel Tower...
It is a situation in which an emergency light, a guidance light, a light bulb, or a light bulb are used in the city.
Please check the exit near you in advance.
We will continue until the end. Please look forward to it.
Today is Sakurazuka 46 Sports Festival
Thank you for coming to supported by ION CARD.
I'm Matsutarina from Sakura Tokahou T6
I'm Ten Yamasaki.
I would like to ask for your guidance.
Camera, video camera at the venue
Please refrain from using a recording device such as a video recorder with recording function.
Please do not use your mobile phone
The theme of the mobile phone is...
Please make sure that the sound doesn't come out of the settings.
Recording and recording actions using a photo camera with a recording function are not allowed at all.
The performance inside the venue is...
Thank you for watching!
If you want to eat, please go to the place you are supposed to eat.
The act of running away from the seat and running forward, the act of throwing things towards the stage, etc. are very dangerous.
It will be a nuisance to other customers, so please be sure to stop.
See you!
Please raise the towel and the sketchbook at the height of your chest.
There will be a camera for video recording, streaming, and photo shooting.
There are times when the audience's appearance is reflected, so please be aware of it in advance.
Due to the convenience of the production, today there is a case where the emergency light, the guidance light, the light bulb, or the light bulb are used.
Please make sure to check the exit in advance.
And so...
Buddies, everyone!
We'll do our best to cheer you on!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for the amazing view!
Thank you very much!
Wow, amazing! Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Sakurazaka 46 SPORTS FESTIVAL supported by ION CARD
I will be the MC today.
This is Tadano Buddies Grand Toyama!
And as always, I'm Kanada, the only Buddy and the only Hange.
Cheers!
Thank you very much!
As long as I'm happy!
Yeah, this is...
With us, the radio, the live broadcast, and with Sakura-chan
That's right, in commemoration of the release of the Blu-ray, we will be doing a special broadcast on Sakurazaka's official YouTube channel!
Even though there are no members, only the two of us will do it
Yes, we will do it
Thank you very much for the event at such a big and wonderful venue!
Thank you so much! The view is amazing!
Yeah!
What do you think of this amazing 360 degree view?
We might not be able to confirm who is sitting at the top, but Mr. Tanaka!
First of all...
Aren't your lips too red?
It's not too red
It's almost the same color as the jacket
It's a great event
It's a retro atmosphere
It's like Osaka Banpaku
There is no moon stone.
It's a story from 1970
It's a quiet Toyota.
The air is amazing.
It's the quietest car I've ever seen.
Today's event starts here.
From now on, it will be a sports festival
That's right
Please look forward to the last part
Please look forward to it
Warm-hearted Buddies, thank you very much
Once again, to all the people who came here today
They are Buddies who are limited to ION CARD members
Once again, thank you very much
Everyone, are you using your ION card?
All of us
I'm using all my energy
Please continue to support ION CARD
And please continue to support Sakurazaka and ION CARD
Today is Sakurazaka's first sports event.
The members are divided into two teams
We will be competing in various competitions
It will be a team battle
Yes
Mr. Ion, you did your best, but...
It's rare to see an event like this
You might have seen it through the screen
It's right there
I'm sure the members will come as soon as they run or something like that.
That's amazing.
I want you to look forward to it.
What kind of event is it?
That's right.
Well, it's a sport.
Sakurazaka 4DX, of course, the dance is wonderful
Yes
But in regards to the movement, it might be something like that
For example, throw a ball to the catcher and hit it on the mound
You might be able to see it today
Maybe...
There are people like that
There are
There are people who simply can't ride a bicycle
So what kind of competition are we going to have today?
There might be a bicycle game like that
But the 4th generation has a Super Athlete
That's right
It's in Sakurazaka
I hope everyone can look forward to that
Let's call it right away!
Even if we're talking, it's already...
Everyone, please call them in.
Are you ready?
Right?
If we don't have a little more support, we might not be able to come out.
We're counting on you, everyone!
Yes
Wow! Amazing!
Well then!
I would like to call them in. First of all,
Rina Matsuda
Team!
ZETTEI KATSU is here!
Time's up!
What's the name of this team?
Katsura Rina!
Osaka
Takemoto!
Thank you for watching!
I'll definitely win!
Alright, here we go!
Yamazaki Tenhikiru
Team!
What do you mean by losing?
NON-YOU-JO!
Thank you!
1st place
Thank you for watching!
Give them a big round of applause!
First of all, since both teams are here, both teams, please...
Thank you, Buddies!
Please go ahead, Captain Matsuda.
3, 2, 1
This is Takarazuka46!
Team ZSK and Mazda Captain
First of all,
Can I ask you to tell us how you feel?
Yes, after all, we have a team name.
We gathered the members who had a very strong feeling.
Today, I really won't lose. I will definitely win.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
By the way, what is the team name of this team?
Who decided it? Did you talk about it with everyone?
In my own group
Me!
In the group
How do you feel, Yuzuki-chan?
I think it's a nice team name.
Really?
Yeah, it's true.
I see.
I feel like I forced myself to say it.
No, no.
I definitely want to win, regardless of whether I'm good at sports or not
With my soul, I want to win today
With your soul!
Thank you very much!
What are you going to do if the opponent team loses, Ten-chan?
First of all, how do you feel today?
Do you want to fight?
We don't know how to lose, so I don't think we're going to lose today.
I think we're going to win!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
Let's go! Let's go!
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work.
Now that we've heard your enthusiasm, I'd like to inform you once again that Meguro Hiiro-chan is not feeling well today.
I hope you'll be able to recover soon.
Thank you for your hard work.
And this time, as a supporter of each team of BUDDYZ at the venue
We are waiting for you to join us today!
That's right!
I would like to divide the audience into two groups
So from here, from the middle, it's from this side, right?
From the middle, then...
Yeah!
Could you turn the penlight to red, please?
Thank you for watching!
We have towels for the members of the winning team.
There may be some people who think that we are pushing them, but we will do our best to support them.
We will do our best to support them.
That's right, it's already too early to talk.
The other side is going to be blue
Yes
That's the rule
That's what we're going to do today
Yes
We look forward to working with you
Thank you very much!
That's right.
Let's say a few words to the supporters of ZETTEI KATSU and the leader of BUNSTER CAPTAIN.
Can I take a picture?
Yes, of course.
Everyone, let's go!
Thank you for watching!
Wow, Haki is amazing!
I definitely want to win today!
Wow! Amazing! It's pretty big!
That's it!
Let's do this!
Nice!
That's right!
When you get excited, you become like a rapper
Yes!
Like, let's go, let's go!
Ten-chan, you can't lose
Please say a word to your supporters
Everyone, thank you very much!
The supporter's voice is louder
Let's do it one more time!
Amazing!
Thank you everyone for your support!
Well then, let's start!
In the first match
Let's go!
The first competition is...
This way!
If the song is played, it won't be surprising, right?
Dancin' Good Miley!
Everyone who wants to participate in this game, please get ready
If you want to do it, you have to stand in front
If you don't want to participate, you can sit on this bench.
That ticket is already...
It could be 88,000
It's pretty close
The best team is
Kousaka, Moriya, Nakashima
Mukai, Murayama, Katsumata
Nakagawa, Matsumoto
And the losing team is Endo, Inaguma, Tamura, Masumoto, Yamasaki, Mato, Yamashita, Yama, Kawato
Thank you very much.
That's right, rule!
Basically, it's just a ball
Next!
A song from Sakurazaka 46 will be played.
Yes.
Then, everyone, please stand in a line.
Dance as hard as you can in the circle!
Please dance to Sakurazaka's song
When the music stops, they all go back to Tama-ire
Once the cherry blossom song is played, dance again.
This is a repetition of this.
Of course, there were a lot of balls in the time limit. The team won.
Let's hear it from Kanata-san!
I'm at the scene.
Kana-san, are you there?
Let's listen to their enthusiasm.
Mr. Murayama, are you ready?
How do you feel?
Of course I want to be cute, but I also want to show how cute I am when I dance.
Right here, right in front of you
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching.
Yes
Mr. Tamura
Are you ready?
I said that about Murayama
That red...
It's a red team!
All the supporters, let's make it a blue team!
If you make this part all blue...
There will be a rule
It's going to be a mess, but...
Please stop it, please stop it, please stop it!
Please don't do that
It can't be helped
We can see the dance here
Yes
Are you ready?
SAKURA SAKA's song is dance, TOMARU and TAMAIDE
Let's do it until the time limit is full!
Here we go!
Dancing Tamaide
Yoi!
Start!
Let's go!
You're good at this, right?
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much!
How many songs is this going to be?
Everyone is busy!
Are you okay?
Not bad!
I used up a lot of energy
Everyone, you must have used up a lot of energy in the first round
Alright, then!
As far as I can see, it's not that big of a difference.
I don't know.
Did one fall?
No, it didn't.
Team representative, please go to the basket.
Ten-chan and Burayama-san?
From now on, let's take out two at a time since there are quite a few
Two at a time?
Yes, two at a time
Are you ready?
I'm pretty tired. It's okay, right?
Here we go.
Let's count the numbers.
Touch!
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
There's still a lot left. 32!
I love you!
YEONJUN!
42!
Thank you for watching!
Ryo-chan!
Right?
Thank you for watching.
Go Jooyoung!
Let's do it again, 56!
Thank you very much!
Rokuzi!
Good luck!
Thank you very much.
No.68
Let's do it one by one from here.
Let's go!
It's not as big as I thought it would be
I was surprised too
There's quite a lot in there
It might have been better if it was 5 each
From here, one at a time?
From here, one at a time.
I see.
Yes, it's volume 61.
Let's start from 69.
69!
70!
71!
Thank you very much.
Seventy-two
Seventy-three
7th week 4th week
Please give us lots of love!
Seventy-five Seventy-six
One, two, three!
Seventy-seven
Seventy-eight
GG!
79, 80, 81, 82
Team MAKERU
Thank you for watching!
I don't know how to drink
Kanama-san!
If you lose, you can ask for help from one person.
Now!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy to win from the first competition. I'll do my best after this.
And unfortunately, it was disbanded
The team that will definitely win!
Thank you.
Mokai-san, you look like you're having a hard time.
I don't know if I was dancing or throwing the ball.
I was like a ball in the middle.
It's frustrating. It was fun. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Once again, the winner of the first match, Team MAKERUTTE, is...
We're getting ready, so everyone, please go back to your seats.
There was a lot of excitement and a lot of excitement
Matsuda Captain!
Yes!
Unfortunately you lost
I lost
But it's only the first match
There's still a chance.
I don't feel like I've lost.
Shin-Emi-chan
It's a song!
Like from the chorus
Yes
Isn't it?
Can you dance from the chorus?
Pop!
It was surprisingly difficult. Actually, Mukai was stopped.
As far as I can see, Itoha wasn't able to dance the dead end at all.
That's right. She was standing in the middle of the dance.
It was surprisingly difficult.
Itoh-chan, was it difficult in the middle?
My head was all white and I danced a lot, but I was like, what?
It was my first time dancing. I was surprised.
It was your first time dancing?
I don't think it was your first time.
Everyone went to drink water right away.
You have a lot of stamina.
It's still the first battle.
It can't be helped if you keep your stamina.
That's right.
You have to go get it.
Stop!
Are you ready?
The next battle is...
Here it is!
Let's get into BUDDYZ!
Giant MaruHakobi Contest!
Here it is.
It's huge!
Everyone, please take a look at this giant balloon!
The balloons have come out
From now on, the members of BALLOON and the BUDDIES of the venue will cooperate
Who will be able to reach the goal as soon as possible?
Let's have a battle
Actually, the balloon will go to the top of the stage
The towels and panels might have to be taken down
The starting point is over there
From the members
Pass it to the BUDDYs at the south stand
Everyone in the southern stand, this is important
And then like this
On both sides
We went to both sides and went to the north side.
We were all carried around by the Buddies.
When we fell down on the way, the members pushed us back.
And then, from the north, in the middle, the members...
Catch it
Bring it all the way here and compete for the fastest
This is...
The other members understood it, right?
Yes, it's fine.
Yes, they did.
But then...
The supporters on the second floor have no choice but to drink and watch.
Please cheer for us!
That's right!
The captain is amazing right now!
The focus is on him!
We look forward to your support!
It's like a sense of unity.
Also, there's a possibility that it might break.
Yes, it did break a while ago.
Yes.
Then...
Replace it?
Replace it.
Simply, everyone will be surprised and replace it.
Yes, we will replace it.
I see.
It's a loss time.
I don't know what kind of sound will come out.
Yes, if it breaks, it will be quite a loss, so it is possible to make a big comeback.
OK.
I'll do my best.
First of all, the team that lost earlier will definitely win.
Hikaru-chan.
What do you think?
Do you have any plans or intentions for this match?
That's right. But BUDDIES will also cooperate and carry it together, so I think that if the voices of BUDDIES support us, we will be able to come back soon.
I want to do my best while cheering for each other.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best!
Tono-san, you have a microphone, right?
How do you feel about this competition?
Our team is lined up in a row,
efficiently, and so fast that you can't see the ball.
I want to send the ball to him.
That soon?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please.
If he can't see it, there's a possibility that he'll get injured.
No, but...
Yes.
I'm in a safe position.
You're in a safe position.
Got it.
Thank you for your cooperation, Buddies!
Thank you very much.
Let's get ready
Let's get started.
Are you ready?
Yes.
So, how are we going to do this?
From the lift, it's quite deep
Let's pay attention to this part
Are you ready?
Thank you.
Let's go!
Second battle!
Bring in the Buddies, bring in the giant balloon, and get ready for the match!
Start up!
Stop!
Wow, amazing!
Oh, it's a one-on-one.
It's getting popular! The red team will definitely win!
Stop!
The place has changed!
Are you okay?
Is it a violation of the rules or is it a violation of the rules?
This is...
This is a violation of...
Thank you very much!
The absolute winner is Shiba!
It's the other way around!
Zettei Katsu doesn't go at all!
Zettei Katsu is this way!
He just has to make it spin!
That's not it!
Thank you for watching.
Give it back to Disney!
It's coming back!
It's perfect!
Thank you for watching.
The crowd is going crazy!
Thank you for watching!
It's close!
It's so different from Buddies!
Thank you very much!
I was cli-
Oh, that's good.
What do you mean you're going to lose? It's fast!
Good match!
And this is out!
He's coming back!
It's really close!
It's really close! Everyone, look closely!
It's a very good match with the members.
Thank you for watching!
I can't hear you.
It's a really good match.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
That's it!
Watch out!
Here it comes!
Thank you very much!
It's a bit off, isn't it?
You can do it, Katsu!
The red team is on their way to the north.
It's going to be a fun fight.
He's coming back!
The blue one is back!
ICHIGI!
Ichigiri, properly to the center!
He's serious!
Thank you very much.
You're the best!
Let's go!
You can do it!
It's over!
I'm still doing my best!
She came over here once, but I think she came all the way to the center.
She's so good!
She's so good at protecting us.
That's too much sportsmanship!
You can do it!
Thank you for watching!
Let's cheer for them till the end!
The spirit of fair play!
Fair play!
subs by maro!
Almost 1 person
The fire is burning out!
It's amazing!
Thank you!
In the middle, in the beginning, there's no absolute number
There was a time when you were just spinning on the top of the screen
What do you mean by losing? Did you just put it back?
It was falling down and I couldn't move forward
Pretty much
Ah, that means you lost quite a bit, right?
That's right.
I see.
Yes.
Even though you were doing well at first, right?
Then, once again, this competition is the team's absolute victory!
Yes!
It was good.
We lost.
In the beginning, it looked like Karin-chan didn't participate at all.
Yes.
Did you participate?
Wait, what?
It was perfect.
Was it perfect?
You were acting like a director.
I was a supporting role.
Oh, you were a supporting role.
I see. Thank you.
You're sweating a lot.
When it comes to water supply,
Well then, it's 1 win 1 loss!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
I thought the people in the back were going to come, but they didn't.
That's sad.
Next time
Are you prepared to come to the front?
But it was a big event
It's great to be able to compete with Buddies
It was so close, everyone!
That's right.
It's good, it's good.
And Maru didn't break either.
I'm glad we managed to do it
We're going to get some water right away
This is Sakurazaka 46 Sports Festival!
After all, it's a sports festival, so today is a day to get a lot of water.
Everyone, please take a good amount of water.
We would like to ask for your support.
So far, one win, one loss.
Honnaki-chan
How was it? It was one win and one loss, but he was able to catch up.
But there are still a lot of games left, so I hope we can get back on track from here.
Everyone, please support us!
Let's do our best!
Yu-chan, this is the end.
What do you think?
The excitement of BUDDYZ is really great
Everyone is excited
Yeah!
I might have caught you off guard
Good, good
Come on!
Well then, with one win and one loss, let's move on to the next match!
The next match is...
Here!
Basket! Shoot!
The third match, the basketball shoot match
That's right
This time the venue is, of course, the Toyota Arena
Thank you very much
The home arena of the pro basketball team, Alvark Tokyo, so to speak, the holy land of basketball
So, from now on, everyone will be facing each other at the basketball court.
This time, each team will have 5 players to compete in the shootout.
Thank you. Now, Kanata-san, please explain the rules.
Each team has 5 participants, and each of them will shoot one at a time.
However, the score will change depending on the shooting location.
The three-point line is 5 points.
The free-throw line is 3 points.
And by the way, I think there's a stand over there.
There's a red stand, isn't there?
We specially prepared it this time.
Lucky Otachidai
If you put it in from above, it's one point.
It's close, so it's advantageous.
The winner will be decided by the total points of all the participants.
If you are cornered, you have no choice but to aim for 5 points.
First of all, it may be important to go one step at a time.
Well, there are also members who are good at it.
That's right.
Because Sakurazuka is a basketball club.
Yes.
Once again, he belongs to basketball.
I'm a member of TENSHI.
Oozono-san, Murai, Yuu-chan, Ishimori, Rika-chan, the three of you are...
He's been showing his basketball on YouTube and other platforms.
Furthermore,
According to this information, Wako Matsumoto of Team ZETTEI KATSU
Mo!
I was on the bench of a minor high school student
What? That's not something to laugh about!
That's enough!
I feel like I can do it.
Feelings are important.
I want to do my best today.
That's what I was aiming for.
That's good.
Because the school around us was strong.
How many years have you been doing this?
Everyone is good at basketball.
There were about five people.
I'm sorry, I was going to ask about the history
Oh, there are 15 people!
You can make 3 teams!
There are quite a lot!
15 people!
You can make 3 teams!
It's a great idea!
Wonderful!
Then, basketball club members, please come here
Yes, yes!
Is that okay?
Yes, thank you!
But this is for each 5 people
Let's do it!
Team Zeddei, Katsuwa, Roko-chan, Yuu-chan, and of course Basket
That's right, I'm really excited
The one who did this hairstyle today is Alvaro Kutokyo-san's official character, Luke
It's a cute and favorite character
I tried the ears of that bear, and I'm really excited
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Did you do it yourself?
Yes!
Did you do it?
Thank you!
No, I did it myself!
You did it yourself!
I did it!
You did it!
You're a good girl who doesn't lie!
I'm looking forward to it.
Next is Odo no Rei-chan.
Yes!
Of course, basketball
Basketball, actually I've seen it in the seats over there
In the actual match?
At this venue?
Yes
That's amazing
Wait, wait, after dropping the kogera...
It hasn't even been three months.
That's right. So shooting at the spot I was looking at was...
I think it's a proud thing to do, so I'd like to finish it while tasting it.
Wow, what is this?
Let's go!
I think there is a strategy, but I want to aim for 5 points.
I want to aim for 5 points.
From 3 points to 5 points.
And Ishimori-san, have you already played basketball?
I was in the basketball club.
How confident are you?
After all, I am very excited to be standing in this Toyota Arena.
I also want to do my best while receiving everyone's support.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you for watching.
So, as I said earlier, it's a 5 vs 5 match.
It's called a battle
Both of you have been chosen, so there are three people left.
Well, you have to choose, but this is not an exaggeration.
No, you can nominate a player from your opponent's team
I see
I'm not good at this.
It's like Pongkotsu-chan
This person is the one who can't get in
I see.
You point out the person who is not good at it.
That's what we're going to do
First of all,
Team ZETTEI KATSU
From now on!
First of all, I would like you to choose the player of the first round of the opponent team, Yu-chan and Wako-chan.
Who is it?
I will announce who will come
What will it be?
Yamashita Shizuki-chan!
I'm getting a lot of emotions
I did it!
Shizuki-senshu!
She didn't look very satisfied
What did you do, Shizuki-senshu?
Is it okay if I do it?
You're being too strong.
I don't have confidence in myself.
First of all, Yu-chan
Why did you choose Shizuki-chan?
No, it's Shizuki. Well, that's the reason.
Can you do it?
I'm already laughing.
That's what they say, but what do you think?
Well, it's a bit frustrating
I don't think I can lose to a bear
Shizuki-chan, over here
You're going to do it from now on, aren't you?
That's right!
Basketball is here.
I want to see your level.
For example, can you dribble over there?
The camera is very strong.
Well then, please go to the other side with the dribble!
Please!
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh!
What?
Don't you think so?
I was wondering if he was going to lay up like this
How was it?
It's quite fun.
They're having fun!
They're having fun in this huge venue, amazing!
Then Shizuki-chan
The place to shoot is 3
You can choose from 3 places
That's important.
Which part do you think is better?
To the same G.O.B. mate
Let's take a look.
I knew it!
I think it's the red special stage
First of all
It's just one point.
It's not a competition at all.
First of all,
I think so too
1 point is 1 point
Shizuki-chan, there's a saying that it's better to stand on one side
That's what I think too
Did you really think that?
You were so determined
Really?
Well then, let's start from the top.
Please do your best!
The performance is also difficult.
Isn't that too close?
It looks like you can go in
Thank you very much.
Is it better to have support or is it better to be quiet?
Shin-chan, which do you prefer?
Thank you for your support!
E
Isn't it good?
It's bigger than I thought, and that's the pressure.
You can do it!
Are you ready?
It's OK.
It's like a real tournament
Let's go!
Yamashita Shizuki
Daito, please!
Now, Shizuki-chan!
Yes!
How do you feel now?
It's the best!
It feels good, right?
First of all, congratulations on 1 point!
Thank you very much!
This is...
It might have been more exciting than the Albuquerque-Tokyo match.
It was a great match.
It might have been the best match of the year.
And now we have a winner.
Wonderful!
Kaisen
Well, but it's still 1 point.
That's right.
Next, from Rei-chan and Rika-chan.
The first one is Shimei!
Everyone is looking away
Uh...
And then...
He's being pulled out.
Karin-chan, be careful with your facial expression.
Thank you.
It's a lot of pressure.
But they all have confident faces.
Yamashita-san put in a lot of pressure just now.
That's right.
I've decided.
Chii-tan!
Thank you, Kagawa-san!
Here we go
Here you go.
Thank you for watching!
But for me...
Lately
When I was in high school, I played basketball, so I'm a high school student, so I'll do it.
Wonderful!
Thank you for watching.
Let's take a picture here.
By the way, Rei-chan, why?
That's why I chose Jiro.
I was looking at the opposite side
You were looking at the opposite side
So I chose it
But there's a possibility that it's a fake performance
It's real
It's a good idea
It's okay, it's okay
Let's take a look at Dribble's ability
It's a trial Dribble
Please
You can do it!
Let's calm down
It's a no-count at the basket count.
First of all, you've already got one point
Where do you shoot from?
Yes
What should I do?
Mayonnaise
First of all, you have to be able to catch up.
Then, let's do Otachidai!
Otachidai!
On a day off!
Otachidai! Otachidai!
Let's do Otachidai!
Let's do it!
I'll definitely give it to you!
Ah, by the way, is it better if it's complete or not?
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
Are you ready?
Simulation, start!
Thank you very much.
I think I can do it.
Are you ready?
OK!
Thank you for watching.
E!
Chihiro Nakagawa
Basket shoot challenge!
Please!
Thank you for watching!
Do your best!
Thank you very much!
Chihiro-chan, how was it?
Yes, it was an easy win
Really?
Alright!
That's good. I'm relieved.
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Well then, let's change the course and continue from Yu-chan and Wago-chan
We have to welcome them with a sense of unity.
What should we do for the second round?
Let's do it together.
Next is...
Inaguma Hina-chan
Thank you very much.
Oh, your legs are too heavy.
This way, please.
Why?
Inaguma Hina-chan's mission
I've heard that she's not very good at sports, so if you've seen her athletic nerves, you'll know what I'm talking about.
I think I know the reason why I chose it.
I'm being underestimated, but...
Um...
I would like to ask Mr. Kanada, who is from the same Aichi prefecture, to cheer for me.
Yay! I am from the same Aichi prefecture!
Please cheer for me from the same Aichi prefecture!
How about the people from the same Aichi prefecture?
That's quite a lot
I will support Aichi prefecture!
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Inazuma, please come here
You can do it!
Do your best!
I'm the type who wants to choose the ball.
Ok, let's do a test dribble
You can do it, you can do it!
It's really good!
It's wonderful!
Isn't it good?
Did you have a good time in Naginata?
Hina-chan, it's 1-1 so far
1 point, 3 point, 5 point. From where will you shoot?
Eh?
It's hard to choose.
I want to go to Otachi University
I want to go to Otachi University too
Thank you very much!
Do you want to go?
Let's do our best!
Thank you!
Go for it!
Do your best!
It's okay if it's perfect. It's better if it's not perfect.
That's right!
Kanata-san, can you do it too?
Inaguma-chan, you have to do your best!
I couldn't hear you!
I couldn't hear the most important part!
Are you ready?
Let's start the second round!
Hina Inaguma
Do your best!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
Thank you very much!
Hina-chan, congratulations on your great shoot!
Thank you very much.
Everyone in Aichi Prefecture,
Thank you so much for your support!
I will support Todokan and all Todokan
I will support you until the end
Thank you for watching!
Once again, Hinae-san, congratulations on your wonderful win!
Congratulations!
2 vs 1
Everyone has decided
It's going to be a competition
It's about time
But it's a strategy, so it's okay
It's amazing, under this pressure
Next, from Rei-chan and Rika-chan, the second person!
C-man
Let's do it
Okay, let's do it
Everyone is looking straight ahead.
It's decided!
Who wants to go first?
Eh?
It's Jyot-san!
Jyot-chan!
That's good!
I'll put it in.
She's laughing.
She's putting in Karin-chan.
Why did you choose Karin-chan?
Yes, somehow.
Somehow?
It means you won't be able to enter
Ma ma ma ma ma ma
You can't really see Karin-chan's face, can you?
No, that's not it. I wanted to see Fujiyoshi-san playing basketball.
Ah, that's good. That's a good way to say it.
She's talking with a lot of choice of words.
Let's show them, Karin-chan.
Now, Karin-chan has been told.
Honestly, my heart was beating so fast
Your heart was beating so fast?
It's okay if it's Rin-chan
Yes, I will do it.
You can do it, you can do it.
Do you want to support me?
Yes, of course.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
This is rare. So we can watch the dribble too?
Tameshi dribble
Please support us!
Have a good one!
It's cool!
Now, Kanin-chan, it's 1 vs 2.
Yes
However, 1 point, 3 point, 5 point, from where do you shoot?
Thank you for watching!
Ah, there's a voice that says 5 points.
5 points!
Please stand up.
That's right!
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi
Huh?
It's getting hard
We might get angry too soon
Karin-san, it's not moving
It's not moving
Oh, it's moving
Free throw
Karin-chan, can you do it?
How was it? Let's listen to it again after you've done that.
I see.
It's Ota-jidai
Ah, it's a part time job after all!
The blood of Kansai is flowing.
A flow of new moves.
Ok then, please make a decision.
There is no such thing as a perfect match.
Are you ready?
If you're ready, please
3 out of 3
Let's go!
What do you want me to do?
Fujiyoshi's parry shoot challenge, please!
I mean...
Thank you.
You don't look like Fujiyoshi Karin!
That was the best!
You can't say sorry, can you?
I couldn't watch it myself.
This is a bit pathetic.
It's so embarrassing
It's embarrassing
You were trying to keep your distance
I tried to keep my distance
It's embarrassing
I didn't want to see you being so slow
It's embarrassing.
Unfortunately, 0 points!
You can do it! You can do it!
Good job!
On the contrary, everyone was amazing.
It's precious today. I've only seen Ujiro like that.
I was able to see a valuable appearance.
Now, it's 2 to 1.
That's right.
The losing team won by 2 points.
Next, Yu-chan and Ago-chan will be the finalists.
Next is Tenshan Yamazaki!
Tenshan!
Me?
I can do it!
ZOZOMARIN STADIUM
He's going to jump to the left, so it's okay.
I'm sure it's going to be like that.
That's right, a little bit of that.
It's basketball.
I'll help you.
That's right.
I'm weak in the real game
That's right
I've seen it
I don't want to hear such words before the match
But what is losing?
I think it will go in.
Let's put it in.
Well then, here is the ball.
Ten-chan, you chose it, didn't you?
Please go for the curry with the dribble!
The trial dribble!
Why?
I didn't want to see it!
I don't want to get carried away
I was trying to get through the gap
It's good, isn't it?
And Double Dribble.
I found it!
Double Dribble is amazing.
Yes, Double Dribble.
That's why he's leading right now.
Ten-chan!
They're leading with a 2-1 lead, but they're all in the lead so far.
Where will they shoot from?
Eh? Which do you think is better?
Which do you think is better?
Isn't it better to attack?
Go! Go! Go!
Let's stand up.
What do you think?
3 points.
3 points?
Yes.
You can do it.
3 points.
As expected of Ten-chan.
I'll give it a try!
Is it good enough?
As expected of Yamazaki-kun!
No, it's amazing!
If you put this in, it's amazing!
If you put this in, it could be a victory.
You have a good face.
If you're ready, let's go!
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
Yamazaki Ten's 3 point challenge
Please!
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
But after this, everyone in the basketball club
I'm sure you're waiting for it
Please don't
The real one
I'm going to show it to you
That kind of pressure
It's okay, it's okay.
The pressure now is on the other team members as well.
It's true.
I'm frustrated.
But you gave a big round of applause to Ten-chan who challenged.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Well then, with this...
It's the end of the third round.
Yes.
Let's go to high school
Mika-chan is the third person
So far,
I'm winning.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Who wants to go first?
With Yui-chan
Go! Go!
It's a legend, isn't it?
Yappa!
There was also a story about the inauguration ceremony, so I thought I'd take a look at Yui-chan's.
That's right.
Because you're on top, you throw it.
Do you still drag it down?
It's like you're still being rubbed.
Do you still do it?
Yes.
Well, it's a game of hitting the ball down.
No, no, no.
Ah, it's not that kind of game.
Basketball.
It's a game of hitting the ball down.
I see.
That's what I'm good at.
What do you mean?
I'm good at it.
There's no such thing.
There's no such thing?
The rules were wrong.
Then it's wrong.
I'm interested in putting a little shoot.
Oh, was it a shoot?
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll have to go.
I have no choice but to go.
I understand.
Yu-chan, this is your ball.
Please go.
You can do it!
I might be good at this!
It's good to put it on your head.
It's a picture of that time.
That's not it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
No, that's not it.
That's the end of the 9-jouju.
Goal!
It's a good song.
It's very light.
Keep going, keep going.
Where is it coming from?
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Now, where does the shoot come from?
Eh, but well, Ten-chan, who was in the same dormitory, got 3 points, so I'll start from the same place.
Oh, what? That's good.
Go for it!
If this goes in, it's a big one.
If it goes in, it's 3 points.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't think we're friends.
I'm sorry.
Do your best! Do your best!
Please do your best!
You can do it, Yui!
Is it completed or not?
It's completed!
It's completed! Everyone, please do your best!
Thank you for watching!
If you enter, you'll have to turn around.
Team 3, clear!
We can do it! We can do it!
Let's have a look at Yui Takemoto's 3 points
I just want you to think it's amazing
It was the first time I was able to throw it up. Thank you very much.
Because it is not
But I think everyone in the basketball club after this will do their best for this round.
Please!
First of all, let's give Yui-chan a big round of applause!
Wow, amazing!
As long as you don't get beaten, you'll grow.
He's doing it on purpose, that's for sure
Up to here, 1 vs 2?
Yes
Oh, I see, I see.
The team that loses is the leader.
Yes, that's right.
Then, the top and bottom teams will remain as they are.
Is that okay?
Well then, let's continue from Rei-chan and Rika-chan
Ah, that's right, from now on
It's a basketball team competition
Do your best!
Thank you.
What's the order?
Please make your decision.
I see.
What are you going to do if you lose?
Which team will go first?
I'll win.
I see.
Let's start with the losing team.
Here we go!
If you win 2-1 and Rei-chan goes, it's okay!
You can do it, Rei-chan!
By the way, what do you think? 1 point, 3 point, 5 point?
Well, it's all thanks to everyone's support.
That's right. Well, we won, so...
I'd like to go with Ampere, but I'll go with 3 here to make it look cool
3.7
That's cool!
You're going to lose 1,000 points
I'd like to open the test
Got it
We'll do our best!
It's going to be a lot of pressure.
Do your best!
Thank you very much.
3 point declaration
From now on, it's KK's turn.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you push the button and just stand still, there might be a pattern for everyone to make fun of you.
But I'm used to it.
I don't want to see this
Oh, that's it
They're not the same
OZ's words are not the same
That's not the same
Oh, I see. There's an angle, too.
Wow, that's cool.
But the angle is 3 points, so it's fine, right?
There's also a position where you want to go from the angle of 45 degrees.
That's right.
Let's go from here.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Thank you!
Ready!
Let's get started! The 3 point challenge, Oozono Ray!
Please!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
It's good!
Don't you think so?
It's not in the video.
Oh, it's in the video.
Oh, I'm so frustrated.
Wow, I'm so frustrated.
It looks like this side entered the corner.
It was a bit far.
I don't like it!
Rika-chan is still here today, so I'd like to leave her to you.
There was also a challenge from a cool angle.
Thank you for your hard work, A-chan.
You're winning.
Yes, I'm winning.
After all, he has a good position.
Well then, the absolute winner will be in the position of being behind.
Who is going to be the 4th person?
Wako-chan and Double Maiko-wako will go
Yes
Why?
It's an election activity
Let's do it at the same time
So far, he's lost.
That's right, but I saw how cool the seniors were shooting from the three-point line, so I...
Let's do our best for 3 points!
Sounds good!
I wonder how it will turn out.
Let's do our best!
Let's go. 3 points.
Bring the ball here.
Yes
You can do it!
Thank you for watching!
Yes.
3 is for everyone.
I want to see some dribbling
Good job!
Thank you for watching!
It's too fast!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You can do it!
Face to the front.
There is no such thing as perfection
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
Please let us know when you're ready.
OK!
OK! That's good!
Well then, let's go in!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Oh yeah!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Let's go!
But it's too bad for Mako-chan!
It's a little off. I'm frustrated.
Thank you for your warm support.
Yes, but...
Are you frustrated?
Mr. Murai...
I want to leave the rest to Murai-san.
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm so glad
It's really hard
If you hit an apple, you can't say anything, right?
No, I can't.
So far, 4 people have finished, 1 vs 2, the absolute number is 1 point, if you lose, of course, it's 2 points.
Then, as it is, the last one.
If Shibori Rika-chan goes to the 5th person, she has no choice but to go.
One point difference!
1 point, right?
So...
This is just the beginning
That's right. What should we do?
What should we do in order to prevent the opponent from choosing 3-5 after this?
What should we do to make it more stable?
No one has done a free throw yet.
I see, no one's playing the blues
Good morning.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
What should we do?
You suddenly became the tone of the dressing room.
No, this was bad.
Yes, but I want to do my best.
Do your best!
What will you do, Ichi-san?
1,3,5
In terms of score, it's a free-throw.
See you in the next video!
As I thought, it's 5.
It's pretty risky!
So cool!
Well, that's right. We're aiming for an absolute victory.
We're aiming for an absolute victory.
If it goes in, it's a win.
That's right. If you get in, you win.
Oh, I see.
I don't think you can do it.
That's a problem.
But Cody.
I'll go with 5.
Okay, got it.
You can do it!
It's perfect.
Thank you.
Well, first of all,
It's a test drive.
You can do it! You can do it!
That's cool!
5.1
Thank you for watching!
Ineosu!
Let's do it here.
Yes
I got 5 points.
I'll give you 5 points.
Good luck!
There will be a completed version as well!
Everyone, please give us a big round of applause!
This will decide it.
If you decide, you will win as it is.
Thank you very much!
Once again, please give a big applause!
Are you ready?
With that, he gets 5 points!
Ishimori is the last!
Shoot Challenge, I love you!
Thank you for watching.
Let's go!
AAAAAAAA-
Thank you for watching.
This is amazing!
How do you feel right now, Rika?
It feels good
Wow, the last one!
The last one!
It's like a three-way battle of slam dunk
5 points!
You!
Even if you score 5 points
But Yu-chan, what do you think about the shooting scene?
I want to see it!
It's not even possible to turn the tables, what should we do?
Please.
Eh?
Please!
Please
If you score 5 points, you get 6 points
But if you score a little behind, you get 100 points
100 points!
How about that?
You can do it!
How about this?
Everyone!
I'm OK with that
Only Odakura-san is getting a round
Then it's OK
Ok, then it's OK
It's OK
Odakura-san is OK
A little bit more than 100 points
I'm a little bit pressured
Then let's go with 100 points
It's OK
How about you?
To be honest, I'm under pressure
We'll do our best.
We have no choice but to do it.
Thank you very much!
First of all, please get closer to the dribbler.
It's a little behind, isn't it?
It's over!
Nice!
Thank you for watching!
Point guard!
Good! Good!
Let's imagine
That's right.
This is way too long!
Where should we start?
Here!
Eh, Mr. Murai, are you planning to go from there?
What?
That's right.
Thank you for watching!
Please give her a round of applause!
He's got a good face.
Thank you for watching!
Go for it!
If this goes in, Mundo Muneo will be defeated!
Murai Yu's last challenge!
PLEASE!
Thank you.
Let's go!
I'm glad I watched it.
I can't believe it!
Too far!
It was really good
Amazing
How did you feel when you got 3 points?
It's hard to bring up to that level of power.
That's right, it's a bit...
I'm so frustrated, but I could have done it if I had done it one more time.
If you had done it from 3 points, for example, was there a possibility that you could have done it?
No, I could have done it.
Oh?
Isn't it too sweet?
Let's do it one more time.
One more time?
Let's do the last challenge.
Is that okay?
What does that mean?
But after all, the members of Buddies...
We'll just do it
It'll be just a demonstration
But that's fine
It's an exhibition match
Yu-chan seems to be satisfied with it.
This will be the last shoot of the basket, so please be prepared for the next one.
Last challenge, Murai!
Congratulations on the shoot, but Yu-chan's team loses!
That's too much!
Please give a big round of applause for NICE WHITE!
It's amazing to be able to put that kind of pressure in there.
Please return to the stage, Future.
It's been a long battle, but the team that loses is the winner!
It was a good match
Now we have 2 wins and 1 loss.
The losing team is in the lead.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ok, let's get ready for the next match.
Do you guys want to drink some water?
Yes.
Please look forward to it.
Wow, it's so intense!
It was so much fun!
I was so excited!
It was a good match.
Let's watch the replay
What do you want to see now?
I want to see it no matter how many times I watch it.
2 wins and 1 loss
This is it.
We still have 2 more wins to go.
Everyone
BUDDY's supporters, how are you? Are you feeling well?
Oh!
There's still more to come.
The absolute winning team is now in the lead.
Everyone from ZETTEI and Team Supporter, once again...
Please give a big round of applause to everyone sitting on the second floor.
1,000 yen is a lot of money
But no matter what team I lose to, I'll do my best to not let any of my supporters down!
Let's move on to the next match.
Everyone, let's give them a big round of applause!
It's a dodgeball battle!
It's a win-win!
Each team has 8 players
Everyone over there, please come to the court.
Let's start!
Let's go!
Well, the winning team is getting more and more excited.
The absolute winners are Takemoto Fujiyoshi, Matsuda Morita, Enriko Murai, and Sato Yamada.
The losing team is Oonuma Yamazaki, Ishimori Odakura
Egoji, Konnagi-chan, Taniguchi, Asahi, Naguma
That's what it is.
Let's go!
This is simply dodgeball.
There are 5 people in NANIYA.
Gaiya 3 people
Of course, if a member of NANYA wins, he will go to GAIA.
There is no return from the outside to the inside this time
Once it's over, it's still Gaia.
Of course, if the last person is hit, the team loses.
Thank you very much.
Let's go! Matsuda Captain!
What kind of 8 members did you choose?
I chose a member who has a very strong shoulder.
It's a member who is too good at acting and too good at acting.
You look good, Hikaru-chan.
No, you look strong.
You look strong.
Your shoulders look strong.
Everyone seems to be good at running away
It's true that it seems to be fast, but it seems to be fast, isn't it?
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Run away and throw! I'll do my best!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!
Ten-chan team, what kind of members are they?
As expected, Oonuma Akiho
I'm here
The cannon is about to fly.
With that girl's cannon
I want to wipe them all out.
Oonama-san, how do you feel right now?
So much that you can't even see it with your eyes!
I'll do my best!
Yes!
Can you throw a ball?
I've never heard of it.
I'm looking forward to it.
The jump ball man is in the center.
Okay, up.
This is just the beginning.
Team ZETTEI KATSUWA
Akashimu won't be able to drop this
Let's get into it.
Mamamoo Mito Onuma's Jump Ball.
Thank you very much.
It's a real dodgeball match.
Yoi!
Start up!
Thank you for watching!
Asahi-san!
Thank you very much.
It's good!
It's like a mountain.
Turn it around, turn it around properly
There's an emergency
It's okay, it's okay
Ah, no one's shooting!
It's dangerous!
Everyone is excited.
Oh, the catch of the cap.
Wow!
Karin-chan is not going to take it at all.
Okay!
Chas!
Yuu-chan!
Okay!
That was close, Ooguma-san!
Let's go!
Here it comes!
Oh!
What was that?
That was close!
Uwabou!
Mr. Nayakawa, you're so fast!
Thank you very much!
Yeah!
Oh, he's throwing a good ball!
Oh, that was close!
How is it?
Oppa!
Thank you for watching!
Wamba Wamba Wamba Wamba
Sate-chan!
It's a rare way to cry
Let's call the police!
Thank you for watching!
Yama-
Makiyu got out, but he got caught
And...
Yes
Stop!
Oh, great! That's a great way to avoid it!
Now it's 4-3! Oh, it's 5-3!
That's enough!
Thank you very much!
4-3-4
It's sandwiched! It's sandwiched!
It's sandwiched between the two of them!
Odakura 07, Ashi no Motsure!
Ah, he's giving the rice balls to the person over there!
Sportsmanship!
Great!
Whoa, watch out!
I can't do it!
Fujiyoshi Kariyama doesn't look at the ball at all.
Every time the ball is handed to him.
Are you being targeted?
Thank you for watching!
Catch ball!
It's a catch ball!
Watch out!
Oh, it's Hikaru Morita!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Ohohohoho!
Naguma-chan is amazing!
He's a good catcher!
It's the start of the catch ball again!
Wow!
What do you think?
He missed again!
See you in Shimorinika!
Thank you for watching!
Turn it properly
I got it, I got it, I got it!
The winner of the giveaway!
He's definitely the winner!
You have to attack soon!
You have to attack!
Shin-chan, you can do it!
Go Asakura has a chance!
Let's attack!
That's it!
It uses a lot of energy
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
We're running out of time!
Thank you.
I'm not good at this!
Thank you very much!
Amazing! The combination is amazing!
I have to do my best to win!
But the opponent is one person, Ken-chan is one person!
Alright!
Thank you very much!
Until the match is decided!
Shin-chan!
That was close!
Thank you for watching.
Well, how is it? Turn around, turn around.
OK!
Morita Hikaru from the inside!
This is the result of tension!
Wataru!
Peach! Peach!
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Hikaru Morita was able to hit the ball
Nice!
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute, Ten-chan is the only one left!
It was so scary!
It's really really big!
I was really scared
But I knew Gaia was strong, so I wanted to leave it to them, and I was desperate to run away.
But...
Thanks to everyone, I was able to win.
That's wonderful!
Thank you!
Rika-chan and Sai-chan did a great job in the first half
Yes, a little...
I was also nervous, but I was able to decide because I was good at turning the ball.
That's great.
It was exciting.
And Hikaru-chan is the only one who stayed for a long time at the end.
I'm already thirsty.
I feel like I've been locked inside of me
Everyone's eyes are serious
Yes, it was scary, but it was fun because it reminded me of when I was a student.
Well, that's good.
Even though you were a top student at first.
Once again, the team that loses the dodgeball match is the winner!
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the center again
Was it in a straight line?
Yes
So far we've had 4 matches
What's the result?
Kanata-san, we just finished
Ah!
As far as I can see from the monitor,
Do you want to see it?
Thank you very much.
It's coming out
It looks like it's coming out
The Genzai!
What does it mean to lose?
The current team has won the match
3 wins
The team that will definitely win will have 1 win and 3 losses
So today, we're going to have a 5 on 5 match
Oh!
Huh?
Next, the last one!
First of all, I would like to announce the final competition.
Gochisosamadeshita
Last but not least, Jay-Z!
See ya!
Yes, of course, everyone will perform, everyone will be relayed, and of course, the one who won first place will be the winner.
It will be simple.
Meguro-san has a day off today, so which team will lose?
You will have to run twice
Who will go?
Kira-chan!
Hi!
Half a lap x 2, so it's one lap per person
That's right, originally my legs were fast and I was famous
Famous? Where?
What is it?
It's famous, isn't it?
In elementary school, it was famous for having fast legs
You answered correctly
Because it was SPYSTER
Yes, because it was SPYSTER
I'm looking forward to seeing SPYSTER live
We'll do our best
It's really close
He's going to race next week, but...
This is...
At this point,
Ten-chan, you already won with 3 wins.
What are you doing?
Even if the winning team wins
Well, it's 2 wins, so 3 vs 2 is the only thing that doesn't change.
You can't win.
That's right.
You!
What do you want me to do?
It's an aurora.
Next time if this team wins, I'll give them points for what they didn't do enough.
How many points do I need? I can't calculate right now
It's 3 to 1, isn't it?
Well, it's strange.
I want 100 points!
I want 100 points
If you win next time, I want 100 points
I see
How was it?
Isn't that great?
That's kind of you!
It's been a long time since I saw her like this.
Kind?
Kind! Good child!
Is it okay?
Normally, if you do this, there's something you can forgive, right?
It's okay if there's nothing, right?
I think I will lose
Ah, I see
Yes
We will win
So if we win, it's good
Yes
I think it's totally okay
I won't lose
The winner of relay competition is 100 points
Yes
That's right
Thank you
Let's eat!
It's half a week, half a week
Half a week!
At the end
It was strong
From here, from this line, it goes like this
Yes
A real relay with full speed
I'm serious.
It's amazing to see them running at this distance.
I don't think there's any other venue like this.
If it's a work of art, it's amazing.
But it's a recording.
Bake it, okay?
That's right.
He's running on the cherry blossoms.
Everyone, please be careful not to get hurt.
This is the first round.
The winning team is...
What?
Yawada Moumi-chan is the top?
Yes, I'm the number one
Not an anchor?
I won against Masumoto-san
I connected from there
I want you to score a goal in the first place!
Go for it!
Amazing!
By the way, how many seconds is 50 meters?
The most...
The fastest is about 7.3 or 7.2
7.3 or 7.2
It's really fast.
So you want to win by winning the top?
Yes, just like that.
While we were talking about that, the losing team kept talking about the strategy.
That's not true!
Even if I run after hearing the beep, I get called a flying team.
That's why...
I want to know if I should run after I say the beep or run after I hear the beep
I see
Ready, get set, go!
So I think it's good, the moment you hear the beep, it's good
Do you want to run after the beep?
No, no, no, I always run after listening
Listen carefully
I see. You don't have to finish the song.
The moment I heard the sound of the drum, I immediately said it.
You said it?
No, it's normal.
I said it.
You've been doing this for hundreds of years.
It's normal.
What?
The moment it sounded.
I will do it.
Momomi, that's enough, right?
Yes.
That's normal
That's right
Let's do it
You can do it!
Let's do it seriously!
What about in-course and out-course?
Is this okay?
Is it okay?
Kira-chan, I think there are various things such as in, out, and etc.
They gave me the one that was more advantageous
Ah, the one that was more advantageous
Honest
The two of them had an agreement
I didn't know that
Yes, it seems that this one is more advantageous
It's kind
Because it's an inn, you can take it
Because you're an expert
No, no, I'm sorry, please hold it
I'm sorry
That's fine now
It's not here
It's fine to hold the mic now
It's our job
Yes
Momomi-chan, are you okay on the out-course?
Yes, it's okay
I have to win because I gave it to you
Cool
It's okay to enter the inn, right?
Yes
I think it's okay
Cool
Thank you very much.
Is Kira-chan going to be okay in the battle?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
What are you trying to say?
I was wondering if he was standing in front of me all the time
Ah, the cameraman!
That's not how it works!
It doesn't go like this!
You can't go like this in a race!
Isn't it too fast?
No!
It won't start at all!
I'm sorry, I'll do it!
You can do it!
Good luck!
Do your best!
Please support us!
I won!
Hold on!
The winner is...
Let's hear it for Kanada-san!
Aizu
Yoroshiku Onegai Itashimasu!
The first place goes to...
Hey!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I didn't do it at all!
It's good! It's good!
Yeah, yeah
Why did you say that?
Was it that late?
I got it.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I got carried away.
It's okay.
That was a strategy.
Ah, I forgot to put my hand on it.
It's difficult!
Thank you for watching!
Is it okay to be at the top?
It's okay
Team B
Team B's team
Okay, here we go
Let's do it again
1st place
K! K! K! K!
I can't believe it!
How is it?
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
This is for real!
Thank you very much!
It's dangerous!
It looks like it's going to melt, but it's opening up more and more.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Dona Gontara!
It's okay!
I don't get it! I don't get it!
From here...
Come on!
Sawa Naka Naka
Yui-chan, come on!
Wow, that's pretty good!
Thank you very much!
It's fast!
Thank you for watching!
Good! Good!
Start!
He's coming from the left!
Will he be able to escape like this?
Fighting!
Thank you for watching!
It's fast!
Last!
Let's go!
Fast! Fast!
It's the last round!
Murai-chan is fast!
That's right!
It's fast!
Mako-chan is fast!
Her form is cool!
Let's go!
It was so exciting!
It was so much fun!
Everyone, please go back to your seats.
No, no, no!
First of all, let's give a big round of applause to everyone!
Thank you for watching!
Everyone was amazing.
The team that won the first round was the one that won the first round.
They were leading the first round.
That's right.
The distance was gradually getting closer.
Yes, it was getting closer.
The same!
I was on the side, so I thought we were going to pass each other, so I made a mistake in the in-course and out-course.
There was that kind of feeling too
Miyawaki-san worked really hard to run
It was wonderful
You did a good job
I'm glad that we were able to communicate with each other
It was hot
And no matter what team they lose to, they turn the tables.
Thank you.
Yes!
That was a wonderful dance!
What do you mean by losing?
As a result...
That was the result, indeed
And the anchor was Kira-chan?
Yes, Kira-chan ran at the beginning and the end.
Kirei-chan's run on the anchor was great, how was it?
Did you see that?
Eh?
I just kissed the mic
Report
Everyone, Kira-chan just kissed the mic
No, that's not it!
This is amazing!
This is the first time I've heard an idol's kiss declaration!
In front of the fans, in front of the Buddies
It's wonderful
That's it!
Once again, the team that won the first Sakurazaka 46 Sports Festival is...
Congratulations on becoming the loser!
It was a hot battle!
It was really hot today!
Ten-chan, as the leader, what did you think of this victory?
After all, the fact that we were able to win the first round...
I think it will lead to a lot of confidence in the future
It's all thanks to everyone's teamwork that we got this point.
I think it's because the supporters cheered for us that the umbrella became a color.
I'm very tired.
It's coming quite a bit, though.
Thank you very much!
Wonderful!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much
How was it, Hikari-chan?
That's right!
I'm really happy that I won, and the leader, Ten, gave me a name, so what does it mean to lose?
I think the winner was already decided from the beginning
I think it was a very hot battle
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
In the back, Airi-chan!
How was it today?
Yes, that's right.
It's like...
It feels very youthful
It was really fun!
It felt like a sports festival.
It really reminded me of a sports festival.
Like
I think I was able to enjoy it a hundred times more than before
It was fun!
The first Sakurazaka Sports Festival has ended with the team losing and Nani winning.
There's no time left!
It's been a long time.
Yes, it's been a long time.
It's time to say good-bye, Captain.
Eh?
Yup
Huh?
It's okay.
It's okay?
Yes.
What is it?
It's okay.
It's not the end?
It's not the end.
To all the Buddies who came today
The present is-
What is the present?
First of all, each member's autographed acrylic stand
5 pieces in total!
We will give it to 155 people!
155 people!
The lottery ends at 9 o'clock.
Yes, so after the end of this event, the seat number of the person who was selected for this monitor
We'll announce it after the show, so don't forget to watch it!
We're looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
And the winner is, after the show, Main Gate!
Please come to the main gate.
So, Captain...
Is that all?
No, it's not over yet!
There's more?
This is the signed game shirt of the members who are participating right now.
I'm sorry!
I'll give it to you as a present!
Thank you for watching!
Sorry
This is the box that came out just now, from now on
The 5 winners will be announced by lottery
First, the first person is...
Moriya Rena, come out!
Go go Rena-chan!
There are a lot of lottery tickets for one person, so you will be asked to play.
I don't think so.
Why am I so flustered?
You're not saying anything strange, are you?
Yes, I'm not nervous.
Are you nervous?
Yes, I'm nervous.
Everyone's feelings are on the line.
Well then, let's have them play seriously.
Yes.
Let's do it.
First of all, I'd like to cast a spell.
This is important.
What spell?
I'll cast a spell.
Everyone, please cast your own spell.
That's right.
Please.
The trainer is waiting for you.
Thank you.
I hope everyone gets it.
Moe moe kyuuu
I've never seen this before.
What did you do?
I'll drop a new joke here.
It's a new joke.
Moe moe kyuuu
I'm looking forward to your magic.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's our first time.
Let's cheer for them.
Here we go.
Everyone, please enter the ticket number.
There are so many tickets.
Here we go!
Ta-da!
Number 3!
3 times
3 times!
11th row
11th row?
353!
Where is it?
Are you here?
As expected!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you.
Let's move on to the second contestant.
Yamashita Shizuki!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Yes!
JUMMO!
I'm sorry, I thought you were playing a trick on me.
Nena-san!
Thank you.
That's better, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Do you have a microphone?
It's okay
It's for everyone
It's not like it's funny
Thank you for watching.
Seriously!
It has a meaning to do
I'm sorry.
It's already decided.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
You don't have to make it sound like you're an idol.
He's sighing.
I heard a loud noise
Here we go.
Omojinai!
Yeah!
Thank you very much!
It's on the floor!
Thank you for watching!
Helicopter! Attack Copter!
I didn't think it would roll!
Yonkai!
4th round, 2nd round
Thank you very much.
40?
It's number 49!
Number 49!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
The third person
Mato-no-san! Mato-no-mio!
Nice to meet you.
What's wrong with your face?
What is it?
Well, I'm glad I can do it.
Well, I'll do it.
Why are you being cornered?
Can I do it?
It's like a magic trick.
It's a joke, isn't it?
It's a joke.
That was Shizuki-chan's magic trick
It's everyone's wish to draw Miyo-chan's image.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go.
I hope I can hit your target
Wow!
Thank you very much.
It's like magic
Okay, here we go!
3 times
Open
18 rows!
Number 116!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Now, the 4th person
Asahi-san!
Asahi-san! Asahi Konami-chan!
No way, Asahi-san!
Ah, she's holding her head!
No way, in this order...
No, you don't need to be shy.
That's right.
I really didn't listen to it
Everyone really didn't listen to it
That's right
But I want you to say something that you really want to be hit
Yes, I understand
I'm going to answer questions, so I want you to answer something
I see
I'll do it
Is it your taste?
I hope you get it right!
Chirori Chirori
Churuchururin?
Churuchururin.
What is it?
The rotation is long.
It's a foreshadowing type.
I've been talking a lot.
It's really embarrassing.
Let's move on to the next one.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
What?
I can't see it.
It's okay.
4th floor
Wow, it's so fast.
10 rows!
Judy!
No.351
10-351
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Last but not least, Mr. Yamakawa!
YAMAKAWA
Yamakawa Uji
This is also...
Hey!
Since it's the 5th person, it's the last person
That's why...
If possible, I want a special magic trick
It's the last one, right?
That's right.
I'm sweating so much that I can't stop.
It's okay. It's just a spell.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
I understand. It's a spell.
That's right.
Are you ready?
Yes
Is that okay?
Thank you.
Ehehehe
Well then
This is your lucky star
Shou-kichi, Chu-kichi, U-un, Ui-kichi!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Why are you so fast?
4th place
I can't hold it, so I'll do it separately
Please announce it.
3 times
Rokuretsu
Number 7
Number 7, row 3, row 6, number 7
Oh, congratulations!
It's right in front of us!
Congratulations!
Once again, the five of you, please come to the main gate after the show.
Thank you very much.
Well then, the presentation of the present is over.
With this,
It's over, Captain.
Yes
We still have a long way to go, but we still have a long way to go.
Do you have time tomorrow?
I'm busy.
How about you, Matsuda-san?
That's right.
Let's go!
Let's do a special live!
Amazing!
What do you mean?
Thank you for watching!
Please get ready for the song.
Thank you very much!
It's already...
It takes about an hour.
Which one is the real one?
It was after I played basketball and did the Zebri delay.
That was a great goal!
Yeah!
It's a waste of time for us to shake hands.
Please do it over there
Please throw it over there.
No, but it's amazing. Relays that are hard to see.
You don't need Toyama-san's Moe Moe Cue
No, I said please give me a like.
No, I'm not a king.
You don't need an old man like this
It's embarrassing. I'm not a king.
Thank you very much.
Hey, don't say things like that!
Everyone, BUDDYZ!
Thank you very much.
ORE MO BUDDIES!
From now on, let's have the best Sakurazaka!
Let's all cheer for Moe Moe!
Thank you.
It's a strange space.
The old man is moe moe king and it's so weird
Eh?
I want to see Kanada-san's too!
I see.
Kanada-san's Moe Moe Kyun, or...
Can you show us a pose to show your gratitude?
Minamabalizu!
ORE MO BODY DUDE
Why am I kidding?
Let's go!
No
This is real!
It's a bit lower than my impression
Thank you very much.
You're saying you won't change?
This exhibition match is my victory.
Is that okay with you?
No, but...
That's enough!
Who?
No, no, more than that...
From now on...
What the...
What are you talking about?
I don't care about the old man
I'm going to watch it live
I know you want one more song, but we don't need one more.
We're not kings.
But the distance is so close
There's a lot of excitement today, isn't there?
We saw you at the sports event earlier
We've been watching your activities for a long time
It's our first time seeing something like today
I think it's really exciting
Isn't it really fun today?
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
This is the first time, but in the future, as Ten-chan said earlier
It's the first time that Sakurazaka Sports Festival is being sung
Maybe it's the second time
It might be helpful
It was a serious relay, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was a good relay
I don't want to part
Matsumoto-san was running in a really cool form
Oh, during the relay?
Yes
You don't know that, do you?
I'm very grateful to have the opportunity to see it live for such a long time.
Also, it's hard to see the three-point moment.
The two of them are really into it.
Since it's this year, it's already been a month since we started in 2026
From now on, there will be more events like today's Sakurazaka46
Recently, Sakurazaka has been busy
That's right, there's also April
Is there anyone who went to see the Fukuoka festival?
Wow!
Wow, what a great schedule!
Was it good?
That's great! There's a clothing festival, and there's also K-Arena
He went to see the live performance of HINATA ZAKA 46
Wow!
It's a busy place.
In March, a new single will be released!
Amazing
The song is called Growing Up Train
The track should already be on social media.
Who will start singing from there?
What kind of formation will it be?
And the songs that will be included, how will they be coupled?
Of course, the backing track is also the best!
Why are you saying that to me?
Why are you saying that to everyone?
Why do you keep saying that to me?
The single will be released on March 11th
And beyond that
April!
11-12
MUFG National Stadium 2 days!
I'm saying it like I'm going to do it!
Why do you say that to me?
Everyone, please say it
It's a national stadium!
That's amazing!
It's a simple calculation of 70,000 x 2, it's 140,000 people!
The ticket is being taken, Buddies!
Wow, amazing!
So everyone here will be able to walk
So what will happen to the March single here? Will it be released for the first time?
At what timing will it be released?
Furthermore, the 5th anniversary...
Anniversary!
It's really busy, isn't it?
This is Aasha!
Narsha for the national team
Perimetron Northlinger!
He came out again!
In a cherry blossom tree
Everyone sits in a row.
That's it!
Members
5 years have passed since then
We are happy to be able to stand there.
Mune ga odoru omoide ippai desu!
No, everyone is saying yay.
Thank you very much.
If you say something like that, it means you're ready
Thank you very much
Yes.
While we look forward to it, we would like to convey our feelings to the members once again.
From now on, it's time for the special live.
Once again, to the members...
Please come to this venue
You're going to show up?
Once again, the members, please come here
Thank you very much
Thank you for watching!
Are you all right?
With a big applause
I would like to get excited.
Let's enjoy it as a group
Let's enjoy from here
Let's go, captain!
Yes!
We'll hand it over to you now, so please take care of it!
From here on, it's a special live!
We would like to enjoy after this
First of all, our cute, cute Yonkisei-chan's performance
Are you ready?
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Yes
Thank you.
It was really fun today. Thank you very much.
Buddies, what did you think of today?
Thanks to all of you, it was a lot of fun.
Last but not least, Matsuda Cam
Please say a few words to everyone who is watching the live stream today.
Today, once again, everyone came to the venue...
Thank you for watching!
This is a sports festival.
Thank you for watching.
I think I was able to make this time with everyone in this venue and everyone watching the live broadcast, so I really...
I really want to challenge myself
Let's fight seriously with the Buddies!
Please!
My days are hot, so let's have a lot of fun with ION CARD from now on.
Thank you for watching!
This is the end of the show.
I lost the timing to shout
As a result of losing, the two of them stand up and kneel down.
Everyone, I think it's cold, so please be careful not to catch a cold.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet at the 2nd Sakura Naga Sports Festival!
Thank you very much!