Translations and timing by EmptyH2. Original chatsub and timing by Onji and Iwashi.
Please keep supporting the Sakura Gakuin Graduates.
Sakura Gakuin no...
Ganbare Fresh Monday!!!
Hai! I'm 6th grader of elementary school Tanaka Miku.
For this episode I will be your day leader.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Hai. This time we will have us 4.
Let's begin with introductions.
Miki first...
Hai, I'm 6th grader Yagi Miki!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Let's go everybody!
Kanonon! Kanonon!
Cheerful girl!
Thank you! I am 2year highschooler and performance chairperson Fujihira Kano. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Hai! It's middle school 3rd grader
and class president Shintani Yuzumi.
Yes. Last week...
What is it?
Did you see it?
I did.
There was Marin-potter.
So cute.
Kokona, right?
Kokona was like: Hey wait!
The hat and her hair were super cute.
The card trick was amazing.
Really...
Complicated.
I didn't get it.
Oh and...
I went out together with Aritomo Tsugumi.
Nice!
Where did you go?
Where?
We went to Harajuku.
Oh that's nice.
Miku and Miki went too.
Yeah we did, I wrote a diary about it. We wanted to eat rainbow cheesecake.
I thought the sauce on top was mayonaise and was a little surpised.
What were you doing in Harajuku?
We sang karaoke.
Isn't that hard?
Ari... Tsugu wanted to go.
Doesn't sound like her.
She always wants.
Every time...
We sang all the SG songs.
It was like a live: Everybody! Janken pon!
It's really fun.
Three of us, MikiMiku&Me, went to lunch together.
What did you eat?
Omuraisu.
Nice. I love Omuraisu.
What did you drink?
Drink ?!? I had a acai juice.
And you?
Mango juice.
Cuuute.
Everybody was having Omuraisu.
Today we have talkative members.
Well...
Let's call our homeroom teacher Mori-sensei.
Se... No... Mori-sensei!
Hey! Hello! Woohoo!!!
Today's members make a gentle mood.
From all the academy we took the most gentle ones.
So you sang SG's songs at karaoke?
Yes.
I thought you would sing other things in private.
We also sang some other songs from our favorite Idols.
Mostly SG songs though.
You want to do it too? That's troublesome don't you think?
Singing "Yume ni mukatte" in private too.
You are evil!
Okay. You look like you are enjoying this.
Well, let's go then. Day leader!
Attention!
Bow!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Have a seat please. Looks like fun, right?
You already heard what he have planned for today right?
Yes, please enjoy!
Let's begin our first segment with that mood.
Actually, we've invited a special teacher.
You know her right? Please welcome!
Wait a second... wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second!
Here!
Sit down.
So our first lesson will be this!
Hai. Fresh Monday Study of Manner.
But...
We heard something else...
Really? What did you hear?
I heard today's episode is just playing something.
We did!
No way... really?
No! This is work!
No playing around on here!
Shintani... what's wrong?
You guys know this sensei. She was at our open class.
Yagi-san. Who is she?
Uh oh... that is bad.
I know! I know!
Tanaka remembers?
Yes, I know, I know!
Everybody knows.
Well then Yagi...
Yagi... Yagi?
Everybody knows but Yagi.
Sunai Emi-sensei.
No cheating!
She was cheating! She is just the worst...
So this is Sunai Emi-sensei. Please introduce yourself.
Hello everyone, I am Sunai Emi.
Well... since you seem to remember.
What kind of teacher is she Shintani?
She is... well she... she taught us about manners.
What is it? You seem different than before...
Woohoo! Shintani! Woohoo! Yaaaaaay!
Yay.
Are you alright?
All good!
I know she is a very gentle teacher.
We will get along just fine.
So with her we will have our first lesson...
What are you doing holding hands?
Are you okay?
All good.
How about that manner-wise?
Well... it doesn't look like you are concentrating.
What about forgetting your teachers name?
I remembered...
Let's have fun today!
Let's have!
Right Shintani?
Yes!
Shintani really likes this teacher. You love her right?
Are you happy?
Yes!
And you Tanaka? What teacher is she?
She's a gentle teacher, and I look up to her a lot. She is a very good teacher I think.
Diplomatic... really diplomatic.
Hey... I really think so...
So anyways. She will be in charge of today's manner lesson.
A bit over here please.
I don't think they forgot my manner lesson.
I don't think so.
Okay everybody. Our first lesson... what was it?
The first one?
Bow.
Yes exactly.
Do you remember?
Nothing...
Stop it please.
...I'm fine...
Something you will need every day.
Important for your line of work too.
I assume they are good at it.
Yes, absolutely. I think so.
Important during their growth period.
*evil laughter*
What's wrong Shintani-san?
You forgot about the manner class? How do you feel?
... I'm okay...
She's crying.
Haha... Shintani... don't be impolite here.
She's just too moved right now.
She is happy.
Such a bad feeling...
Shintani? Give your feeling out...
With our sensei here. What is your feeling?
I was so surprised...
It was surprising.
We know nothing about this.
Well, let's get going.
So. For greetings... I told you about 3 types of bows.
You did.
Yes, Shintani-san.
Eshaku... I am sorry I forgot.
You know the other ones right?
Eshaku...
Eshaku and?
Tanaka?
I knew... but I'm like... I'm so nervous... give me a sec.
I knew, I knew, I knew...
Why are you so nervous?
I don't know... I was nervous because of the day lead...
Because of that... I see.
Yagi, Eshaku and?
Applause?
Eshaku and... I mean you can't do that in a temple.
Eshaku and clapping hands?
Clapping as a greeting... who does that?
Okay enough.
Eshaku, keirei and sai...
Eh? Saidei?
Eshaku, Keirei and sai...?
Saikeirei.
What angle do you make at each bow?
Let us see. Please turn towards this wall.
Stand back a little.
First, Eshaku. What angle do you think?
Go on.
Please.
Ouch!
Make an Eshaku, don't hit each other.
Stay like this. Yagi, what angle are you doing?
Um, 15 degrees?
You are lucky this is not math class.
This is not right... This is 90°.
And you Tanaka?
About 45 degrees.
Hmm... each girl is making a different bow.
Okay. Enough for the Eshaku. Stand up.
Eshaku is bowing at 15 degrees, right?
Fujihira and Shintani...
Was that supposed to be 15° just now?
Stop laughing... you are the worst Yagi-san.
And two of them made it properly.
The others were no good.
Shintani is correct! YAAAAY!
Okay Eshaku is done. Next one.
And how about Keirei?
Show us the angle please!
Keirei.
What is that angle Yagi?
90 degrees.
You like that, don't you?
This isn't 90° at all.
45?!
Around 45°.
It's 30 degree.
Shintani-san is doing good.
Thank god.
Are you trying to manipulate us with your tears?
Shintani yay!
Next. The last one. Saikeirei.
Saikeirei yes. Please show it.
Everybody bows really deeply. Is that 45°?
Yagi made almost the same bow each time.
It was a bit different.
That was no good everybody. You must learn this again.
We should send them to a training camp.
Well, that'll be after this class.
We have some more later.
Manners for visiting superiors.
Yes exactly. Since we don't have much time I'd like to see one person.
Who wants?
Correct etiquette when visiting a teacher. I will be the teacher.
You can do it.
I think that's something the senpai should do, right?
What a betrayal by the kouhai... really bad.
Tanaka trying her best to get out of it.
Maybe I should choose.
Ah yes of course.
Since she seems very hesistant I will pick Shintani-san.
Let's do this Shintani-san.
Shintani yay!
Yay.
Well well. So I'm in the teacher's lounge.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Excuse me.
What is it Shintani?
You seem to be very slow today. What is it?
I came to borrow a gym key.
A gym key? What do you need it for?
For basketball.
Something is weird. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Yes.
Okay. Here is the key.
Thank you very much.
Good bye.
WAAAAAAAAH!
Wow! Somebody screamed very loudly in the hallway!
So what do you think sensei?
How much do you think you will get out of 10?
3/10?
3/10? Close.
First, what bow do you give when you enter the room?
Eshaku.
You have to close the door properly. You did that.
Very good yes.
But... you're going to interrupt the teacher.
Such a nuisance.
So what do you say?
Excuse me.
Just excuse me?
"Please, may I have a moment?"
Yes I felt very annoyed by your intrusion... Somebody coming into my territory like that. How impolite.
How you left wasn't good either. No bow at all.
Absolutely.
You can't just bail like that after getting what you want.
After I gave her the key it was over.
The end wasn't good.
Yes. I felt very sad. Please work on that.
Yes.
She has teary eyes.
But now the others can do it properly.
Ok, that was the first class.
That was quick.
After the break, you'll have the 2nd class of manner.
We will be here for the next lesson.
Am I welcome for the next lesson?
Yes! Of course!
Anybody against this class?
Ah, yes good girls. I'm glad.
They take this seriously.
Let's take this more seriously.
Well, it's break time. Let's go.
That was really stressful.
What a surprise.
I was so nervous...
You gave your best.
Thanks.
I kinda wanted a prank during FRESH once, but not like this.
Yeah.
We were told we'd make a fun class with playing something.
We were looking forward to this.
Yeah... the script was lying.
True.
Why are you doing this?
It says we can do whatever we want... but it's not true.
*Girls going mental*
Where are the playing cards!?
Well, let's give our best in the second period.
Let's see the break theme.
Well... here.
Yuzu-chan?
The Road-to begins!
Yes.
It has begun!
That sucks...
It's too soon!
How many days are there left? 33?
Until graduation.
I thought you said 3.
No... but it's around that number.
It goes so fast.
I have this notebook and I keep track of the days... I'm sad for every passing day.
True.
Kano always says "We have xx days left...".
I watched the RTG 2015 video at home today... I was so sad at the ceremony.
But there are still some shows left.
We have 2 left.
Right. Okay, next.
"What phrase from Sakura Gakuin song left a strong impression?"
Phrases... there are so many. All of them.
All are precious.
Otomegokoro has "jinx" right?
At school, when you say the same thing at the same time, you say jinx!
Like... In Kokona's and my school you say "jinx" when two people say the same thing at the same time.
I enjoy that a lot.
We say it a lot, and it surprised me that it was in the lyrics.
You say"Jinx" to that?
Happy ice cream!
That's it. It's that one.
Whoever says it first gets ice cream.
Don't know this?
No.
Already... that was quick.
Oh no wait... ugh... I'm okay.
Why are you so emotional Shintani.
I'm fine.
Break time looked fun.
But we will have a fun class too.
Yes.
Looking forward to it? Today is great.
Well, please sensei.
So enjoyable.
Doing good Tanaka?
Yagi-san, which class do you like better, playing cards or study of manner?
Manner lessons are great.
This lesson is...
...the best.
Good thing we have this on camera.
Well. This is what we will do for the second period.
Next class is about "Visiting someone's home"
Sounds good!
Visiting somebody's home...
So much fun...
Much better than playing cards, right?
Today, you visit my house.
Eeeh? What?
What do you think of that reaction, sensei?
Well... impolite.
You see. You are impolite towards me.
Haha... Fujihira is annoyed.
Ah, did you hear Miku?
She rather wants to visit my home.
Me too. I don't wanna go to Mori-sensei.
What about next Sunday.
Really? I think you'll get severe teaching at the entrance of her house. (?)
Well. So we have the entrance on set here.
With some flowers next to it and slippers.
Actually, we even have a living room.
Yes, we have a living room over there.
Do we have to go there, too?
Yes, you will be invited there.
Ok, you now visit the house of your teacher Mori-sensei.
Enter at the entrance and then go to the living room.
Yes, please.
Well... who goes first?
Who goes first?
I think Yagi want to play first now.
Because you enjoy this the most.
Yes...
Me? First?
This is probably for the best.
Let's move the slippers a bit over here.
Here we go! Start!
Oh, there she is.
Excuse me.
Oh, Yagi. Thank you for coming.
It was far... no... it wasn't.
Which is it?
Only 30 seconds.
30 seconds sounds a bit low.
Please come in.
Here?
Yes, there.
Who are you talking to?
Ah... sor... excuse me.
Wait...
Quick. Wear the slippers.
Why...
You are a fun student.
So embarrassing!
You can see it even with the slippers.
It's okay.
It's nothing.
You idiot.
No... It's from the last live.
Sensei...
Yes?
This is a little present.
Oh you brought something? Thanks.
Thank you for coming. Please follow me.
I just tidied up.
Oh very pretty.
Really? Thank you.
I will make some tea. Please sit down.
Sit down, sit down.
*mumble* which? *mumble* here?
*mumble* eh? *mumble* eh?
This?
Excuse me.
Cut!
Yes. Yagi-san please come back.
Okay... now... now... the results.
I want to see other girls first.
We go with the next student? Okay.
Okay, who's next.
Who wants?
Well... Fujihira.
You should have an advantage after seeing Yagi.
I feel nervous. When you are here you get nervous.
It's my home, take it easy.
Yes, well, go!
Who is there? Oh Fujihira.
Excuse the intrusion. It's me Fujihira.
Just a little something.
You seem different. Thank you.
How was the travel? Long?
Yes a bit. I feel a bit tired.
Is that so. Well you can rest now.
Excuse me.
I've never imagined you would come to my house.
I'm surprised myself.
How is Sakura Gakuin?
A lot of fun.
Please come in.
So, this is my place.
Amazing.
Thank you for coming. Sit down I will prepare some tea.
No, please. Let me take care of that.
Ah, no... I don't want you in my kitchen. Sit.
Where should I sit?
What kind of a question is that?
Which one do you prefer.
Whatever... please sit.
Excuse me.
Cut!
It's two things to be polite and to say something you feel.
Very suspicious.
Well... next one.
Who wants?
Who goes?
Shintani or Tanaka?
Both is okay.
Tanaka who?
Well Shintani then.
Okay let's do this.
Okay. Shitani's home visit aaand action!
Somebody came. Come in.
Good evening.
Hai, Shintani.
Sorry to bother.
Why are you here?
Um... to bring a souvenir.
I went to Hokkaido and I brought a souvenir.
That's nice. Come in.
Sorry, sorry...
Where in Hokkaido.
I went to Hakodate.
What did you do?
I ate ramen.
It is good, right?
Please come.
What?
Sorry.
Thank you.
Ah, no problem.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
I will make some tea.
What?
What is that?
A souvenir.
From Hokkaido? What is it?
Um... cookies.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Cut!
Well...
All have been a little different.
The gifting was different.
After entering the room.
Okay next and last: Tanaka.
I hope you learned from you senpai.
Wait, my legs are shaking.
I can hardly move.
She is the most scared one.
Like in the open classes...
I was shaking the entire time.
Tanaka, what makes you shake?
I don't know.
Why?
I'm nervous.
About what?
Eh... eh... eeeh?
I don't know exactly.
Yes, well. Let's do this, nervous Tanaka. Ready!
Action!
Oh... yes?
Excuse me.
Oh! You arrived Tanaka!
Thanks, come in.
Well, well. Where are you coming from?
From Oita.
How long did it take?
How long?
About two hours by plane.
A long travel. Thank you.
Please come in.
Here's a souvenir from Oita.
Wow! Thanks! What is it?
Oita citrus cookie.
All those cookies will make me fat.
Come in.
mhm... I see...
*whisper* excuse me
Follow me.
Excuse me.
You must be tired. Sit down for a while.
Thank you.
I will get some tea.
Yes.
Cut!
That was all of them. Tanaka return to your seat please.
I was super nervous.
I hardly noticed.
...so nervous.
Well, yes.
We started with Yagi.
Yes Yagi-san...
First...
You had a little problem... with your socks.
That was funny.
Not very super lady like.
And when you took off your shoes. The placing is important.
Yes, very important.
Do you remember?
Entering... then...
Wait, who was the last?
Tanaka.
Who put the slippers there?
They should face the other way.
Ah yes, when you leave... that is important.
Sensei is strict.
Where did you stand?
Ok, you should not step on the entrance after taking off your shoes.
Okay Shintani. Show us where you were standing.
Eh... wait.
Shintani-san took off her shoes while showing her back to the teacher.
You have to talk to your sensei first and then take of your shoes..
Was somebody correct?
If you show your back while taking of your shoes that is impolite.
I felt really bad when she did that to me.
It is a weird thing to do.
It's okay. Be careful from now on.
And everybody placed the shoes near the flowers.
The flower place... it's kamiza.
You know that? Kamiza?
What is that?
Are you okay?
Kamiza and Shimoza.
So on which side do you put the shoes?
Shimoza.
You all choose to put your shoes in the Kamiza position.
The place with the flower is the most beautiful of the room... so the shoes must be on the opposite side..
So after entering and putting away the shoes...
Your teacher invited you into the living room.
Before that some of you gave the present.
Who gave me the present here? 3 people.
Only Shintani gave it in the living room.
Where is the right place?
Congratulations Shintani-san.
It's Shintani.
I'm so happy!
You don't give the present in the entrance hall.
Right? Why is that so Shintani-san?
Yes?
Ko...ko... I don't know, because you have to give it properly after talking?
When I get tea?
Are you trading this for tea?
That's wrong.
You give the present after a proper greeting.
You are greeting here and have a little talk, like that you came from Hokkaido.
So no giving presents in the entrance hall... are you listening?
The looks... are you guys okay?
Please pay attention. Where do you give the present?
Living room.
After entering there, yes.
Very good Shintani.
Thank you.
Yes, but...
Nobody took the present out of the bag.
So the proper way to do it is to take the present out of the bag.
You give the present with the ribbon facing up. That is the polite way.
Giving it like that is a bit...
Yes... here look at my fingers.
I know.
Being a sensei is though.
Remember that.
Before giving it you...?
...take it out of the bag.
But it was still good Shintani.
After that, one more point... where you should sit, right?
Nice isn't it. The first time we use this room.
Where did you sit Shintani?
There.
Who also sat there?
Why back there?
Like... it's the farthest...
I thought the near place is impolite.
Why so?
Like... because it's nearer?
Shintani-san... what do you see there?
Aaah... what? what?
A flower.
That was a hint.
Next to the flower is?
Next to the flower is... kamiza?
Kamiza... the good seat.
Also another thing. Besides the flower the entrance is important.
The place near the entrance is Shimoza.
You came through here.
So where do you sit? In the kamiza or the shimoza seat?
Shimoza.
The guest sits in the shimoza seat.
So the near seat is the correct one.
Who sat there?
Look at that...
So Tanaka and Fujihira picked the right seat.
Of course it's Yagi and Shintani who would do this to me.
Not true.
Thank you Fujihira. For letting me sit in the good seat.
So that visit was not very good everyone.
Regrettable.
I'll await you on Sunday at my house... with the Hokkaido souvenir.
We'll have the archaeology of songs in next Sunday.
Oh right we have a teacher on Sunday.
That's also important.
Okay. You can wear your shoes now.
So now we did the visit... who was best?
Well... who should I pick...
It's a though decision.
So besides the back turning and the seat.
Hmm... I think Shintani-san did well.
She gave the present in the living room.
Yes?
I'm happy.
I'm relieved!
And who was bad? Who is?
Fujihira made said: "Just a little something".
I was pretty sure it would be Yagi.
Me too.
What did she do?
How did you feel when she said: It's nothing, when giving the present.
Really? That's impolite?
Such a humble saying is not good. It's better to say something like: "I brought you something delicious."
I see. Something like: "I brought a cookie from Hokkaido."
Give him the feeling it's a present handpicked for him.
You don't have to downplay it...
That's how she is... terrible... a monster.
What's with the smiles? Did you like the lesson?
Their eyes aren't laughing.
Let's move on.
You have an announcement to make.
Here, sensei.
For you to remember.
This is my book...."The world-finest manner".
For people that want to improve, want to become a super lady.
This is the bible.
Yes. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
One more... my next book "How to send your feeling" for elementary school girls will be in sale from the 5th of March on.
It's mainly for elementary school kids but also contains important things for older kids.
These two books... you must buy.
Should be in your bag all the time.
Yes, that was a really good lesson today.
Right? Thank you. I enjoyed it very much.
Yes, that was manner teacher Sunai Emi-sensei.
Well... thank you very much.
Hm? What is it?
What is it with this feeling?
You liked it didn't you?
What's up Tanaka? What's up?
I was so so nervous.
So nervous. That's funny.
And you Yagi-san?
I mean... look... like... yeah...
You really look like an old lady!
I wanted it to end.
How come?
Nothing to say?
I won't say anything.
You Fujihira?
I can't say anything.
You made last place.
What did you learn today?
I shouldn't bring a "Narashimono"...
I meant "Tsumaranaimono"
You guys were no good.
Shintani found her smile again... how was today?
It became good.
You must not forget what you learned at the open classes. Okay?
Yes.
That was it for today's lesson.
I can't even stand up.
That was something right?
Unbelievable.
It was, wasn't it?
But you picked the right spot with the present.
Another thing I remembered. Finger bowl. That thing to wash your hands.
I remember Yagi played something funny with the finger bowl.
Yeah we didn't have the finger bowl today.
Ok, let's give some announcements.
Yes! The 2018 Sakura Gakuin Festival Live video is now on sale.
During the skit I was so nervous... one moment...
It has the skit with Shintani and this nendo's version of Fairy Tale... oh there it is.
Fairy Tale... um... Fairy Tale...
...and things from the "Wonderful Night" show...
and we have... um... wait a second...
...2018 nendo...
You didn't do any rehearsal today huh?
We gave our best...
This is a straight 0.
We worked so hard on the blackboard too.
It's okay Miku, its okay.
There are lots of thing on there...the wonderful night show... the audition for the Sakurademy awards. Please check it out!
It okay... all good.
I'm okay... I'm okay.
The pack looks like this.
Simple but cute.
I already saw it... so check it out please.
Absolutely.
Check it out everybody please!
Okay... On the 26th of March the "Road to Graduation Let's Standing Live" will be held in the Tsutaya O-East arena.
The show is already sold out, please look forward to it.
And on the 30th of March the "Road to Graduation 2018 Final" with the Graduation ceremony will be held in the Kanagawa Kenmin Hall.
This will be the last live with me and the other 2018 graduates.
Please look forward to my graduation ceremony.
On the next day there will be a live viewing event of the graduation in cinemas nationwide.
I'm happy to celebrate my graduation with all of you. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Shintani, that came from your heart.
Yes, and... on the 3rd of March the Sakura Gakuin 2018 nendo studio album "Life Iro Asenai Hibi" will be released.
There will be a Sakura edition and a Gakuin edition.
There will be different bonus material on there like the Year End Test.
*evil laughter*
Something to look forward to.
It was very enjoyable this time.
Yes, the rank order is very interesting.
Here it is.
We had a blast at the photo shoot.
It has a nice ocean view.
Such a good time.
Please check out the album.
Well... so that's... wait we have some more.
And, we'll have the Archaeology of Songs on March 3 in the Hamagin Hall via Mare.
There will be our principal Mitsuru Kuramoto.
Thank you! The tickets are sold out!
It's sold out.
Thank you very much.
This is one of the shows that we are the most nervous about... please be nervous with us!
Please be nervous ?!?
The first class can visit Sunai-sensei after having the class. There should be plenty of time.
I'm in the first one.
Me too!
The others can go before their class.
No... we have to prepare.
Yeah exactly... preparations.
Sorry... seems like they can't come.
Also... this...
...the first graduation photobook.
No not the first, it's second time.
...oh...sorry...
The three graduates did a special photoshoot.
It's a photo album with a lot of memories.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Yes, please look forward to that.
Okay, was that all?
And next weeks episode will be something special. Asou Maaya's Lonely Monday, right?
Last week we had Marin Potter and this week...
No it's good... its all good.
Sunai-sensei was very gentle, right?
It was wonderful.
Okay anyways... next week will be Asou Maaya's Lonely Monday.
Please watch it and give her your support.
The theme will be "trouble consultation"!
Please send lots of consulting letters to Asou.
You can send letters and cards to this address.
Please do.
After this we will have a "purchase Club" message.
Please stay tuned for that.
And there will be another thing, right?
There will be a MV of Carry On after this.
The one from the album.
And that concludes today's broadcast. Day leader.
Attention!
Bow! Thank you very much!
Asou, give your best!