Support the official stream @ freshlive.tv/sakuragakuin
Translations by amadiGW2
Nonaka Kokona
Fujihira Kano
Hidaka Marin
Shintani Yuzumi
Mori-sensei
Line-up:
Good evening everyone
Sakura Gakuin's homeroom teacher,
Mori Hayashi here
You might be wondering
what's happening right now
Well, this is actually a pre-recorded video
This is not live
Or more accurately, this video right here is currently being broadcasted live
Why, you ask?
Today is Obon so we'll be doing
a ghost-themed episode
So we're thinking of pranking the girls
You might've already gotten used to seeing only them getting pranked, and so, for this episode...
we'll be having this person as the instigator
Hello! Stand Out! Chairperson,
Hidaka Marin here!
You sure are standing out today as well
Today's episode is produced by you, right?
She thought of various ways
to spook the other girls
Unveil them, if you please
Here's what I've come up with for this episode
It's quite packed
First set-up.
Flashing a ghost photo on the studio monitor.
Aah... That's a classic one
We're trying to make it seem like
this studio is haunted today, right?
Second set-up.
A girl's voice can suddenly be heard.
This is a really scary one
Super scary
Even during recording, when the manager suddenly play something through our headphone...
everyone would scream
Hopefully they'll do so in front of camera
Yeah
Third set-up.
The light flickers when Hidaka says something like "My head hurts from pushing myself too hard."
I see, I see
You'll be doing this throughout the show, right?
Yes
As many times as you like?
Just say "My head hurts."
Right
Fourth set-up.
When Hidaka says "My shoulder hurts", Mori-sensei will feel a back pain.
Do I shout it?
It's so painful that it'll make me
shout "OUCH!" all of a sudden?
Make it subtle
This will be hard!
It'll be hard but I'll try
I'll leave it to you
Fifth set-up.
When Mori-sensei claps his hands,
Hidaka will do some mysterious action
I'll be the trigger for this one, right?
Yes
I'm not sure if I can do it naturally
What is this mysterious action?
For example...
Or acting like I had been
possessed by something
Don't get exposed!
We also prepared our best prank right at the end
so just enjoy the show without worries
The actual show is about to start
Everyone must've thought
there was a technical problem
Well then, please enjoy the show~
[Staff] 9... 8...
[Staff] 7... 6...
[Staff] Starts in 5...
[Staff] 4... 3...
[Staff] 2... Bell's about to ring!
[Staff] Starting in 9... 8...
[Staff] 7... 6...
[Staff] In 5...
[Staff] 4... 3...
[Staff] Sakura Gakuin's show begins
Sakura Gakuin's...
Ganbare!! FRESH! Monday!
Good evening everyone!
Good evening!
The day leader this time-
I'm the Stand Out! Chairperson,
Hidaka Marin of middle school 3rd year!
This time, I'll be in charge of... of....
Of...
Being!
...being the day leader!
Please bear with me!
Please do!
These four are the line-up for today
Please introduce yourself
I'm Nonaka Kokona of middle school 1st year!
Pleased to meet you!
Kokona!
I'm the Student Council President,
Shintani Yuzumi of middle school 3rd year!
Pleased to meet you!
Yuzumi!
It's been awhile so here I go!
Ready?
Kanonon! Kanonon!
Genkina ko! (Cheerful girl!)
Thank you!
I'm the Performance Chairperson,
Fujihira Kano of middle school 2nd year!
Pleased to meet you!
Anyway, we had the Art Open Class yesterday
Yeah, it's been awhile since we had an open class
It really has been and I enjoyed it
Since orientation
It's art, you know... Art
It was really fun!
It was like "Art is an explosion!"
We played around a lot in second period
How was the third period?
The third period is... well...
I'd say that it was very unique
It was Yuzumi and the elementary schoolers
Ohh, it's the first period
The paintings at the back are quite something
They drew portrait of themselves
Looks great
Oh yeah, none of them are here today
You're right
Only second and third period members
Who's that?
The one with twintail
Twintail and pink scarf
They look similar in appearance
Indeed
They do
All of them wore pink scarf
Kawaii
How was the second period?
Right at the end of the second period
when we were doing live painting,
I splashed the paint around quite a lot
and ended up making a bit of a mess out of it
Because of that, I got scolded yesterday and even today by the teachers
It's fine, you were just 'standing out'
You got paint around here
Around there, yeah
Some even got on our hair
and our face too
It was pretty tough but it was really fun
To move around this much in an open class is a first for me
Even though this is the third art open class event,
it's a fresh experience for me since it's my first
This picture is... something else
Third period!
Seeing Yuzumi and the elementary schoolers
It's amusing!
Miku's face looks quite surprised
In the third period, I...
Well... Lately, I'm often seen as an elementary schooler
I was often told that I'm like an elementary schooler
Rest assured, you're a senior
Yes, but I was told that a lot
Now, now
It's fine, it means you're youthful
Thanks
Well then, now's a good time to call Mori-sensei out!
Here we go
Ready?
Mori-sensei!
Hello there!
Here I go everyone!
Mori-sen! Mori-sen!
A guy with back pain!
Hello!
Excuse me!
Mori-sen! Mori-sen! Are you okay?
I do get back pain once in a while
Well, it's probably because of the open class
and I was a bit too festive during Gekidan Prestage's final show after-party
[T/N: Mori-sensei was the scriptwriter for Gekidan Prestage's play this year]
Lots of things happened
The heck you're doing!
I'm sorry if I let out a groan
Don't worry about it
It's a ticking time bomb
Oh yeah, from art class yesterday... Can you see this?
Pink!
It's pink here because of Hidaka!
Hidaka~
It's fine if you all got your overalls dirty
But this is my one and only vest and it is now stained with paint
Later- It's not something to yay about!
Yay!
The paint won't come off our hands
Yeah, it won't!
Well, you did use your bare hands to paint after all
But in the end, there wasn't improvement in your drawing
Is this really okay?
Hear me out!
Marin wrote "Yuzumi" just now
But she got the "zu" wrong!
Even though you're in the same grade!
She wrote "su"!
Isn't that awful?
Kano pointed it out, but she was like "It's fine~"
Let's move on!
What do you think?
Alright everyone! Take a seat-
Oh wait, no
It's day leader duty. Sorry
Alright then, day leader!
Attention!
Bow!
Please treat us well!
I'm sorry!
No worries!
Alright!
Yes, yes!
Don't you think...the line-up feels peculiar this time?
What do you mean?
It just somehow felt like that
It feels great, doesn't it?
The air feels strange right from the start
Yeah, it does
Well, it somehow felt like you were putting up a brave front
Here's what we'll be doing in the first period
FRESH! Monday Supernatural Entities Quiz~!
Fresh! Monday Supernatural Entities Quiz!
Perhaps because you all knew that it's gonna be somewhat related to ghost,
I feel like you were forcing yourself to be excited
Are you bad with these, Shintani and Fujihira?
I'm super bad with these
I know
I know that your reactions will be great
How about you, Nonaka?
If Kano-chan and Yuzumin starts crying,
I might ended up getting scared too
If they break down in tears, you'll join them?
Let's cry together!
Shintani seems like she gets scared living in dorm
I really can't stand these
She checks every parts of her room
like the toilet and under her bed
Stop it Marin! Don't tell them!
What did you check for?
She's so scared
Wouldn't it be bad if something's there?
It would!
The space under the bad is scary!
Sorry to tell you this but this is a true story
Stop it! That's enough
There are lots of "things" in that dorm
STOOOOP!
No! Just no!
Have you heard about it?
I'm currently living in a single room!
Hold it! I shouldn't be laughing!
But it's so fun right now!
I'm honestly scared~
I'm really scared!
It's really scary, isn't it?
During shower as well
Really scary!
While using shampoo...
Or when washing my face
I'm like "I know you're there..."
What's going on with you, Hidaka?
My head hurts...
What's up with you! You're also acting a bit weird!
You're not afraid of them?
I love yokai
[T/N: Yokai is a broad term that encompasses various supernatural beings so I'll leave it untranslated]
You love them huh? But that makes you more sensitive-
The heck is this!
Were you scared for real just now?
I was!
I'm seriously scared!
Well, never mind. Let's move on
Let's move on to the quiz!
What just happened?
Well then, we'll now have you challenge a quiz on supernatural entities
It is said that psychic phenonemon
are prone to occur during obon
and this is how the quiz related to that will be like
They are divided into different categories and points
Spirit
Yokai
Drawings
and you'll each have the option to choose one
For instance, if you choose Spirit 10 points, it'll be a somewhat easy question for Spirit
Same with Drawings. The question gets increasingly harder for higher points
So take that into consideration and then make your choice
So, who wanna go first?
Shintani who is the most fearful can go first
Let's see...
You're even scared to choose?
Then... Drawings!
How much points?
20!
Here's the question!
The Big Three Yokai of Japan are Kappa, Tengu and the last one is? Please draw your answer.
Ready... Start!
Drawings??
Drawings Quiz
20 Points
The Big Three Yokai of Japan are Kappa, Tengu...
and the last one is? Please draw your answer.
Yes, since we just had an art class!
The theme of your drawing is "Dynamism"
[T/N: Mori-sensei is referencing the theme from the Art Open Class]
What was it again...
Inner eye
Do you even remember?
What did you learn, Nonaka?
I learned about "Concept"
The term "Concept", right?
Inner eye!
Yes, that was taught in the third period
What kind of teaching was it again?
Mechanism?
No, it's not! It's cubism!
It's cubism!
Are you watching this, Yamashita-sensei? They've already forgotten it!
You learned cubism but you said mechanism
Are you done yet?
20 points question
Kappa, Tengu and what's the other one?
It's quite famous
Just draw something
Who knows? Maybe It'll be correct
Don't stop, keep thinking
What could it be?
It is one of the major yokai
A scary one
Nonaka is fast! Your drawing is looking good
Done
Done? In what way?
Are you just completely done with this quiz?
I'm done...
Wanna have a go?
Yes!
Let's take a look at Fujihira's answer!
Ta dah!
What's this?
Kappa, Tengu and?
Sadako
How modern!
Modern!
But yeah, it is quite a major one!
Your depiction of Sadako is surprisingly good
Yes, her hair!
Hair coming out of it, right?
Were you scared from just drawing her?
Scary
Seriously. Like, really scary!
Even just by saying her name too
Sadako is that-
This mood right now is scary
Yeah, and if you say "Sadako", she'll come for you
(Monologue: This @#$&*%!)
Ahh! That scared me!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Nothing
Nothing??
Alright! Oh, looks good!
Who'll go next?
Can you go?
Shintani!
I don't know the name
Just show your answer first. Go!
Yamamba!
What's its name?
Ahh! Yamamba (Mountain Witch)!
Yamamba?
It's not Namahage, but instead Yamamba?
I see, I see. It is indeed scary
Yamamba!
It does have some dynamism to it especially the hair
Alright, next one
Ohh, that looks artistic
Well, can you go next, Nonaka?
Okay
Alright, reveal your answer!
Hitotsume-kozo (One-eyed monster)
It looks lot like Medama no Oyaji
(character from GeGeGe no Kitaro)
I love it!
He seems like he'll say "Hey Kitaro!"
I love Kitaro~
You drew it well with a cloak and all
Does it wear cloak?
That's highly unlikely!
Why would a Japanese monster wear western clothing!
Well, it could be wearing furoshiki
But it does look good
Lastly, Hidaka!
Show it
Do you know?
What is this?
It's Karakasa-obake
That got dull rather quickly
Kappa, Tengu and suddenly, Karakasa-Obake?
The last yokai is so weak!
But you did drew it well
I love it
Well, here's the correct answer!
Answer: Oni (Ogre/Troll)
It's Oni!
Is it a yokai?
It is also a yokai
So, Fujihira- wait no.
Shintani's answer could be correct at first
Oni! Oni! Oni!
No, it's not! That's Yamamba!
It's Oni!
You said it was Yamamba!
Anyway, no one answered correctly!
Alright, moving on
You can pick the next one, Nonaka
Spirit, Yokai or Drawings. Which one?
20 points under Yokai
Why 20 points though?
What is the characteristic of "Rokurokubi"?
This is one of the major yokai as well, and it's worth 20 points
Everyone knows this
Do we just write the answer down?
Yokai Quiz
20 Points
What is the characteristic of "Rokurokubi"?
Yes, though it is also okay to draw
But you can just write them to save time
Show your answers at once
This is a easy-peasy
Oh you guys can even draw it
Have you ever seen it?
No
No, huh?
In anime
In anime, yes!
They say it often appears in Harajuku...
That's what I hate about you!
That's such an old man thing to say!
You're purposely scaring us!
There's none in Harajuku! I'm sorry!
I got carried away
But it is there in the dorm
OH COME ON!
I SERIOUSLY HATE YOU!
I HATE YOU!
I'll apologize later. But even so, it's there
Well then, show your answers at once!
One, two!
Okay, starting from Hidaka!
A woman with a long, growing neck
Nonaka!
Its neck can grow (long)
Next, Shintani
Its neck can grow...
What's wrong with you?
Next, Fujihira!
Its neck can grow...
Well, here's the correct answer
Answer: Its neck can grow
It's neck can grow. Everyone answered correctly!
I hate this!
Awesome! Even my backpain is going away!
You're looking really scary there, Shintani!
Alright, let's move on!
You can choose next, Fujihira
30 points under Spirit
Ohh you've done it now
Here it is!
The leading ghost story teller has countless first-hand experience with psychic phenomena
and has moustache as his trademark look. Who is he?
Write it down. He's quite famous
Spirit Quiz
30 Points
The leading ghost story teller has countless first-hand experience with
psychic phenomena and has moustache as his trademark look. Who is he?
Moustache is his trademark
People often do impression of him
I got it!
He used to be a "reaction geinin  (entertainer)" during our times long time ago
He was, right?
He has such a wide range of talent
So... No idea?
I don't know!
Then, Shintani
I only know his first name
First name only? Alright, let's see it
Jirou-san
Jirou-san huh?
How does he tell his ghost story?
He's like "It's scary... It's scary..."
That's Jirou-san huh?
Ehh? Who is he?
Calm down Shintani! What's wrong?
Is that how Jirou-san looks like?
His trademark moustache isn't even there
Fujihira seems like she's done
Nonaka can't stop drawing. She's really into it
Done, Fujihira-san?
Alright, show it!
It's Hiiiii~Muuuuu~
Excuse me, but the question is asking about who  the person is
It's Hiimuu
Hiimuu-san?
He has moustache and ghost are like "Muuuuu~" in ghost song, aren't they?
Ghost song?
I know what you mean!
Right?
It goes like "Muuuuu~"
I don't get it!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I don't get it at all! Hiimuu?
Hiimuu!
Hiimuu huh? How does he speak?
Like that huh?
Alright, next person!
Hidaka wrote her answer confidently so let's look at hers!
Gushiken!
Gushiken??
Perhaps it's Gushiken Jirou?
It could be!
It might be Gushiken Jirou
Combine the two names
The guy with the curly hair, right?
That curly-haired guy is known for telling scary stories, right?
Yes
Next, Nonaka!
Let's take a look at her answer!
But it's definitely wrong
Read it please
Kaidou Jirou-san
Kaidou Jirou-san?
It could be Jirou-san and either Gushiken or Kaidou as his last name
It could also be Hiimuu Jirou-san
It's only Jirou that's the same
Let's see the correct answer!
Answer: Inagawa Junji
Inagawa Junji-san!
It's Jun-JI!
It "J", right?
I was imagining him in my head!
Yes, can you do an impression of him again?
"It's scary... It's scary..."
Only the "Ji" of Junji came to mind
Yes, yes, yes
Gushiken-san is a former professional boxer
That's right
Doesn't he come to mind when talking about moustache?
That's true but he doesn't tell ghost story
He seems likely to do so
No, he doesn't
Let's move on to the last question!
You can choose the last one, Hidaka
Let's see...
30 points under Yokai
Here's the question!
What do you call the Yokai parade that begins in the dead of night when people are sound asleep?
Start writing your answer now
Yokai Quiz
30 Points
What do you call the Yokai parade that begins
in the dead of night when people are sound asleep?
What was it again?
I've heard of it
Right?
This is probably the hardest question
Even I couldn't think of the answer right away
It may be difficult
Well, it's a term that sometimes comes up in the ghost story that children reads
Hint, it's made up of four kanji characters
No way
Hidaka doesn't seem like she could only write four kanji
Mine's wrong!
You got this, right?
So it's made up of four kanji?
There's a possibility that it's not as well. Believe in yourself!
You've already wrote your answer after all
What is the parade called?
Got it?
Do your best everyone!
[T/N: Poor Mori-sensei. Marin didn't pick up the cue. lol]
Do your best!
You can move just fine
No, no, no!
It's extremely painful if I bend my back this way
Do your best!
What do you call the Yokai parade that begins in the dead of night when people are sound asleep?
Wanna have a go, Fujihira?
Yes!
Show your answer!
Sleep paralysis
Sleep paralysis huh?
So they're doing the parade while also making you unable to move huh?
That's a rather interesting drawing
How are the others doing?
Anyone done?
What could it be?
Think harder Hidaka
You seem knowledgeable in this matter
I don't know the kanji
I don't know what's what
Ehh? Gimme a sec
Ohh!
Nonaka has once again included a drawing.
Let's have a look at it
Done?
Well...
Let's see it! Show them!
Jinyokoushin (lit: PeopleNightParade)
It does sound like it could be that
Exactly as it is
The Yokai parade that begins in the dead of night when people are asleep, or in short, PeopleNightParade huh?
You just cut most of the words out!
Don't you laugh at it, sleep paralysis girl!
Are you done, Shintani?
Alright, show them!
Reigun Mikkai (lit: SpiritArmySecretMeeting)
That seems likely!
Scary!
Sounds possible, doesn't it?
It was hit or miss but it's still a very educated guess
Yes, yes!
Sounds possible... Maybe
Finalize yours too, Hidaka
What have you been looking at??
Nothing
That's scary!
I'm scared for my back
Yeah! Super scary
What?
Even in dorms, I'm scared for my back so I'm always leaning against the wall
Huh?
The mirror is scary!
Afraid that something could be behind you?
That's why I'd touch my back
I know!
What do you mean??
Like this! Yes!
So, if "something"  were to hug you-
Please stop! For real!
I wasn't even trying to scare you at all just now
Well, let's take a look at Hidaka's answer!
Hidamashii Youyuku (lit: FlamingSpiritsMovement)
The heck is that!
FlamingSpiritsMovement participated by Yokai
Well, it's something like that
Here's the correct answer!
Answer: Hyakki Yakou (Night Parade of 100 Demons)
It's Hyakki Yakou
I didn't know!
I've heard of it!
If you don't remember this, they'll come for you
Huh??
I have to make a note
But you can't take this back home!
I'll tear the notes off
Anyway, since everyone has 20 points,
It's a draw!
The only thing that you guys knew were Rokurokubi
Is it over already?
Yes!
The final result is a draw!
That's the end of the first period!
Enjoy the break time everyone!
Okay
Now then!
Time to read... the postcards!
Thanks!
All yours!
Shall I?
Sure, go ahead
Such a wonderful mountain
Oh wow!
How wonderful~
I'll read 'em now
Wonderful!
"Good evening to everyone in Sakura Gakuin,
Mori-sensei and the staff!"
Good evening!
"Without further ado, I'll now introduce my annual summer tradition to you. "
"My friend who is a fukei living in Tokyo goes on a trip to my hometown, Hokkaido..."
"...during summer holiday to do some mountain climbing."
That's awesome!
"Once we reached the top, we enjoyed the view while listening to Sakura Gakuin songs."
Thank you~
"Listening to MagiMelo while in the midst of the grand nature is the best."
Magic Melody... Got it?
"Have you ever went to Hokkaido before?"
"Although it's still hot, please do your best during lesson!"
From Asariba
Thank you!
Kano wants to go to Hokkaido!
Yeah, me too!
I wanna go to Hokkaido
Yeah!
Same!
It's vast
I wanna eat the Hotate (scallop) there
Me too
Who here has climbed a mountain?
Me!
Amazing!
We went mountain climbing for training camp every year in my elementary school
Really? Wow!
We climbed non-stop for like five hours
It was really fun
Wow~
Sounds fun!
It was so exhausting during climbing
But there's a technique for mountaineering
Always keep the gap between your steps the same
You said it before
If you do that, you won't get tired as easily
And also, if you keep a steady continuous pace, you won't get tired at all
A mountaineering expert taught me that
Really? Wow!
That's amazing!
Yes, it's true that the climbing is a struggle
but the moment you reached the top and see this scenery
I wanna see it!
it makes you want to climb the mountain all over again
You won't understand unless you climb huh?
Yeah
I wanna climb!
It feels like you're on top of the world
That's so cool!
Wonderful
I'm glad to hear that they listen to Sakura Gakuin songs on top of the mountain
I know right?
Thank you!
Let's read one more
May I?
Sure
"Good evening to everyone in Sakura Gakuin,
Mori-sensei and the staff!"
Good evening!
"Thank you for making my Monday awesome every week!"
"Well then! This week's theme is summer break."
"I don't really have any summer break but I go surfing in summer every year."
Amazing
"It's also one of the events in Tokyo Olympics so I'll be glad if you'll keep an eye on it."
"Are there any marine sports that you want to try out?"
"Enjoy the last summer of Heisei period!"
From Toki-san
Thank you!
"It's Aritomo-san!" written here
Aritomo-san!
Ohh wow!
Kawaii!
Sorry I'm not Aritomoto
Marine sports huh?
Kano wants to go surfing
Really?
Don't you wanna try it even though it seems hard?
I wanna try riding on a banana boat!
Sounds fun, doesn't it?
We'll definitely fall
Right? We'll lose balance
I wanna try out the water jetpack that makes you fly
The one that makes you hover?
I want! Good balancing skill seems essential for it though
I wanna go surfing
I know right! Same with me
Ride the wave
Right? I wanna go to the beach
I wanna go with everyone
Everyone in SG
Let's work even harder and then request the teacher to let us go there
Request!
"We wanna go to the beach!"
Please~
Thank you Toki-san!
So many dreams for summer break
And yet they always end up unfulfilled though
Now that you're the president, you should take command and organize a strike or something!
Be like "We won't practice unless you fulfill them!"
Alright! Moving on to the second period!
FRESH! Monday, Ghost Storytelling in Midsummer !
FRESH! Monday, Ghost Storytelling in Midsummer!
This is where we get down to today's main topic!
You'll be reading some ghost stories
Being skillful at this is also crucial to becoming a Super Lady
So do your best to frighten the viewers with your storytelling
For this, you'll be in a group of two
and read your story together
Both groups are clueless about the other's story so there's a possibility that you'd be scared by it as well
How will the team be divided?
Marin-chan and me
Kokona and me
So Nonaka and Hidaka,
and Shintani and Fujihira
Are you two gonna be okay?
No, we won't! We're always scared!
You even get scared from reading it?
Really scared!
There's candle now...
Why? Something wrong with it?
Are you scared, Hidaka?
Yeah...
I'm not feeling well today
The fact that Marin is not feeling well is scary
That's a sign, you know
The heck is happening!
I really hate this! I can't! I'm sorry...
Was that a pr-
Oh well, whatever. Let's move on
Let's see... Who'll go first?
I guess we'll start with team Hidaka and Nonaka first
Ready... Start!
Wait! Will it stay like this?
I guess so
Isn't it too dark?
Okay, nevermind
It's your groan that's scary
Let's move over there a bit
Okay
Wait, Kano doesn't like the gap here
I'll follow
Hurry up!
Go ahead
Okay
"Present"
PRESENT
This is a true story
Eiko-san who is an office worker at a neighbouring company
has been harassed by a stalker since around a week ago
As for the harassment...
She finds weird things inside her mail box every morning
First, a shoelace
Next, a belt buckle
The next one is...
a shirt button
Then, on the next day, there was a beanie inside it
However, because there hasn't been anything else since then,
EIko-san didn't inform the police despite feeling eerie about it
On a morning a few days after the last incident,
while thinking "What on earth was all those about anyway",
Eiko-san went to her mail box to pick up the newspaper
As she opened her mail box, she found a letter instead of a newspaper
The content are as follows
"Sorry to have kept you waiting for so long."
"I gave you presents that represent my feelings starting from my feet."
"But, before long, I reached my head already."
"I thought about what I should do next."
"A good idea came to me though it took me quite awhile."
"Look forward to it from tomorrow onwards."
Eiko-san immediately dropped to the floor in terror
"It must be him..."
Eiko-san was scared to stay at home that day so she stayed overnight at a friend's house
On the next morning, Eiko-san went back to her home for a change of clothes
She wondered about what might be inside her mail box
Despite the fear, she opened it
What she found inside was...
a bloodied toenail
Next to it was another letter
The letter reads as follows
"After my clothes, I'll now be giving you parts of my body from the bottom up."
"Oh! But it would be bad if you stay at your friend's house."
"Cause I like visiting you when you're sleeping at home."
"If you sleep at your friend's house again, I might do the same things to her."
"Telling the police won't change a thing as well"
"Look forward to tomorrow as well, okay?"
Eiko-san trembled in fear and felt completely helpless
"I can't escape him anymore"
Eiko-san took a leave from work
and shut herself in her home for hours on end
Unable to sleep... All she did was tremble in fear at the corner of her room
And of course, she couldn't check her mail box
Then, on a morning several days later, her front door bell rang
"I've been on leave for days so it could be someone from work who's worried about me."
Thinking that...
She went to open the door
However...
There was no one outside
Then, as she was about to close the door
The things that caught her eyes were
Fingernails scattered on the ground...
Hair...
And lastly...
Eyeballs
Eiko-san's phone rang
She fearfully answered it
"Why didn't you accept my presents?"
"I prepared lots of them for you,
and yet, you accepted none."
"Ohh I see! You're already satisfied with all the presents, right?"
"If so, why don't you give me your presents then?"
Eiko-san threw away the phone
and ran outside barefooted
However, Eiko-san became exhausted after not eating for days since leaving her home
She became unable to move right then and there
"What kind of present will you give me?"
She turned around and a bloodied man who is without his hair, fingernails and both his eyes was standing there
"Since I gave you that many presents, it's fine if I ask you to give me what I want, right?"
KYAAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!
After that, Eiko-san's whereabouts became
unknown and she remains missing to this day
Wait... Can you zoom in on Shintani-san's face?
What...
What... What kind of expression is that?
You were the most frightened
How was it?
It was really good, wasn't it?
This is a segment where you try to scare others after all
Seriously, what's wrong with you Shintani??
Please say something!
She only screamed because it's written there, right?
I CAN'T STAND THIS!
You...
What is it?
I'm not really frightened by this.
It's the dorm that I'm scared of
Dorm??
That's it!
What should I do if that person comes to our dorm?!
Don't worry! You're well-protected
He won't come to your dorm
He will, right?
She said it!
Are you okay, Hidaka?
Hey now!
I'm fine
Sorry!
Well then!
Nonaka was great just now, wasn't she?
Her expression for example
What's wrong with Hidaka?
Hidaka was talking the whole time in the dressing room
Is that so?
Who was she talking to?
She's talking to herself
Can you stop acting so scary?
We'll honestly get scared if you continue
Seriously
You're doing it to the wrong bunch
Yeah, what's wrong?
Next up! It's Shintani's and Fujihira's turn
It'll be fine, we're just reading them. It's not scary at all
That's true
That scream just now was so unexpected, wasn't it?
That's the scariest part!
The story wasn't as scary
It's the scream that gets you
Did you improvise that or was it written?
It's written
You deserve a perfect mark for reenacting the scream
Yes...
It's frustrating but you have to agree
Yes... Yes...
Amusing!
You're really amusing, Shintani!
Even us got scared after reading the story
The story choice is a bit too scary
I'm always called for this...
What's wrong?
Always!
I wonder why
Every single time!
Now then!
Here's Shintani and Fujihira reading their ghost story
Ready?
At a certain junior high school, there was a ghost story that had been circulating since long time ago
It was rumored that if you go to the music room at night,
the ghost of a woman who committed suicide will appear
This is a story of Eiko-san, a student who went to that school and had actually experienced it
Music Room at Night
It happened in the middle of the final exam period of the second semester
Eiko-san was doing some last minute cramming for the exam
When the night comes, she realizes something
"There's an exam tomorrow."
"But I don't have my Science textbook with me. I'd fail my paper at this rate."
And so, she decided to go to the school at night to get her textbook back
She arrived at the school's guard post
However, there was no one there
"I'll run out of time to study if I don't hurry!"
Thinking that, she decided to sneak into the school
Eiko-san walked cautiously through the dark hallway
Despite the eerie feeling in the air, she climbed the stairs and found her way to her classroom
She went inside and found her textbook in her locker
"Phew! Thank god!"
"I have to hurry back home and study."
Just as Eiko-san was leaving the classrom while saying that, something happened
She could hear the sound of piano coming from the music room
"Who could it be, this late at night?"
Eiko-san became curious and couldn't hold herself back
She made her way to the music room one step at a time
As she gets closer to the music room, the piano sound steadily gets louder
Whatchu want??
"There must be someone there!"
She plucked up her courage and opened the door
However, there was no one inside
The piano sound disappeared as well
"I must've misheard it due to the lack of sleep from all the cramming."
She told herself that and left the room
However, as soon as she closed the door...
She could hear the piano being played again
"Someone's making fun of me!"
She hurried back to the music room
She then looked in front of the piano and
around it but there was no one to be found
The keylid was closed as well
Unable to comprehend what's happening,
Eiko-san opened the keylid and tried playing them
However, it didn't make any sound
No sound were made no matter how hard she pressed the key
Then, the moment Eiko-san pressed
the keys with both her hands...
KYAAAAAHHHHH!!!!!
Her hands were caught in between the lid and the keys
Blood trickled down from her hands
Unable to move, Eiko-san screamed until she lost her voice
The music room became dead silent
Then, she heard a voice coming from behind her
"What are you doing with my piano?"
She nervously turned her head around
and there was a woman smeared with blood
Eiko-san was silenced by fear
Then, the bloodied woman said this to her
"Since you played my precious piano without my permission, I guess you don't need those fingers anymore, do you?"
Eiko-san was absent from school on the next day
The next day...
And the days that follows...
She never turned up to school
Scary
There we have it
Umm... Well...
Shintani's scream fell flat though
You wanted to return the favor but they didn't really fell for it
Wait a sec
At such a crucial part-
Anyway, let's first go back to our usual setup
With lights and all
Now then
Shall we move forward for now?
Alright
Let's hear your thoughts about this segment
Come forward
You okay?
I'm scared of Hidaka more than anything
Ehh??
Ehh?? What??
Let's umm... Let's just line up in the middle first
Anyway, the ghost story lesson...
She okay?
Umm... Yeah
Well uhh.. Alright, understood
What's your thoughts about this, Nonaka?
Scary...
It really was scary
Which part scared you?
I was still fine during the quiz but the talking alone...
Oh! Yuzumi-chan's scream was scary
Really? Really?
So that scared you after all
Why are you looking glad after hearing just that?
Really? I'm so glad
But yeah, both teams were great
Did you see Nonaka's expression just now? I guess you didn't
I didn't...
You were clinging to each other the whole time
Fujihira kept looking behind while reading
I was really scared
It really was scary
How about you, Shintani?
Scary...
Scary?
Which part was scary?
It's not the story, but rather the thought of it happening in real life that's scary
Yes, yes, yes
I see, I see
Yeah, when we get back to our dorm...
Yes... Ahh! I won't be able to sleep today!
I see, since you'll be remembering all these
Absolutely!
I absolutely cannot
Today...
What? What? What? What?
What's happening!
What is it?
Ehh?? What's this??
Hey!
Where have you been!
The heck is this!
It's Sadako!
You guys!
Sadako is here!!
I was worried about you Marin!
Take a look!
No! It's not that I was scared!
I was just worried about Marin!
You were here??
I thought you were sick or something!
Oh no!
Alright!
I wasn't scared! I was worried about Marin!
You were worried huh?
Sorry!
Shintani!
She has been acting strange ever since we were in the dressing room! I was so worried!
She got you worried huh?
However... Tell them the truth Hidaka
It's all an act!
All of it!
I've been acting ever since we were in dressing room today
She was acting so strange!
Alright everyone, let's uhh...
Fujihira-san too
You okay Shintani?
No, I'm just worried!
How kind!
You were worried more than you were scared!
It's all fine!
Nothing wrong with me
I'm so relieved!
This somehow turned out to be a disaster!
Nonaka kept checking on Hidaka
whenever she was acting strange
I was so scared
Nonaka kept on comforting her the whole time she was looking distressed
I really thought she was sick or something...
You must be thinking like
"Don't joke around while I'm reading my story!"
"And yet, I had to keep on reading!"
Actually, you know that we started 3 minutes late, right?
Since then?
Eh? No way!
I HATE THIS!
Yes, those 3 minutes
I HATE YOU!
Thank you!
I'm glad! I'm so glad!
While the staff was-
During the 3 minutes, a pre-recorded video of me and Hidaka
revealing this set-up was broadcasted
Flashing a ghost photo on the studio monitor.
I saw it! I saw it!
A girl's voice can suddenly be heard.
Was this played?
I didn't hear it
The light flickers when Hidaka says "My head hurts"
I'm more worried about her head hurting!
Since she kept saying that, it's like...
She made you worried?
Her acting was too good then
Too good!
Fourth, when Hidaka says "My shoulder hurts", Mori-sensei will feel a back pain.
That too?
I forgot about this
I kept my backpain acting going the whole time
So that's why!
I started off with saying that I have
backpain just because of this!
I've been worried about you since before we started
Man! You're so kind!
I was so worried!!
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry Shintani!
As for the reason why we went with this line-up,
the teachers chose based on who gets scared the most
Seriously! I'm always chosen for this!
And it was decided that it'd be the three of you
The teachers asked me who among the members get scared the most
And I told them
So, it's Hidaka's choice of members, right?
Yes! That's true!
Fujihira is the main choice every time!
(Yeah...)
It's always me that had to sit near the door!
I really hate this!
I didn't expect you to hide under this desk!
What a waste! We wanted to see your reaction too!
I didn't expect Shintani to be this surprised
Next, fifth set-up
When Mori-sensei claps his hands,
Hidaka will do some mysterious action
I was continuously getting ignored
Yeah
Did you remember?
I clapped so hard just now
I didn't know
I clapped unusually just now, didn't I?
Didn't know!
And yet, Hidaka didn't react!
You didn't clap hard enough!
I was clapping really hard!
I also made it obvious like "Hidaka! (Clap)"
I noticed your cue during the ghost story and did it.
But other than that, I didn't remember at all
I see, I see
The one where a girl's voice can be heard, was it played during break time?
They said it was
I didn't hear it
You didn't? That sucks!
You wanted to show your reactions, right?
Surprisingly, you were quite calm. Were you scared?
You won't be picked for this anymore, y'know!
So which is it! Are you glad?
I am glad
What is that you're glad about?
But yeah... Oh! Let's move on to the announcements
We did a lot and went a bit overboard today
Well, please do the announcements
Announcements please!
Next week, on August 20th,
Sakura Gakuin's Ganbare!! FRESH! Monday will be a Maaya special!
Solo!
Do your best! Seriously!
It'll be a live broadcast too
Today's episode was produced by Hidaka
Huh? Really?
That's right
Oh wow!
No way!
Well of course, that's what we had been talking about!
Why do you only realize it now!
I get it now!
Next week will be handled by Asou alone
Send her lots of postcards!
Please do!
Questions perhaps
Or Maaya-related
It'll be like when I did my solo episode with a radio-like set-up
Having those postcards will help to motivate her
Do your best!
Since she'll probably be really anxious about this
We'll be watching!
Do your best Asou!
Let's move on
Next!
On September 7th, "Manners Lesson" will be held!
Yesterday... I forgot her name
You did, and what's worse is that she was there
Seriously!
We greeted her after the show...
Her name was written on a piece of paper here, right?
That's the worse manner!
Honestly!
I messed up
I already remember it!
The lecturer will be Sunai Emi-sensei!
We still don't know what we'll be doing
But please look forward to it everyone!
Please do!
Is there more?
On the same day as the Manners Lesson, this show, Ganbare!! FRESH! Monday...
will be broadcasting a pre-recorded video at 9 pm
Be sure to watch this too after you finish watching the Manners Lesson!
Please do!
How thoughtful!
Even those that goes to the 3rd period can watch this right after
Please look forward to this as well!
Well then- Oh there's more huh?
Next, it's regarding Sakura Gakuin's Ganbare!! FRESH Monday, 2017 Nendo Outdoor School
That's last year!
It's 2018!
You weren't there!
It's 2018
It'll be broadcasted in two parts which will be on August 27th
and September 3rd so be sure to watch them!
Please do!
FRESH Monday is also having tons of interesting development
We really went all out today, didn't we?
Though I do feel like I owe Shintani tons of apologies!
And of course, towards Fujihira and Nonaka as well
Let's praise Hidaka for her acting too!
She was really good!
She's really amazing!
I believed her!
I honestly believed her!
She was so believable when we were in the dressing room!
When she said her head hurts, I thought she was sick
She has been acting since then
That said, I was walking like this since then as well
We didn't know!
Too bad there was no one around!
How sad!
Anyway, let's cheer for Asou next week!
Yes! We'll be watching!
I hope she'll succeed! Talk Chairperson!
Talk Chairperson!
Please do your best!
Now then! Please- Oh yeah!
We're accepting postcards as well!
The theme will be "Summer Plan"
Summer plan!
We'll appreciate it if you would send them!
Those who have their letters read will be given a sticker
What will be shown after this again?
Well, it's the outdoor school trailer
I forgot! I'm sorry!
Hidaka is on fire!
It's all right
Outdoor school!
Thank you
The trailer video will be shown so be sure to watch it!
Well then, that's all for today! Day leader!
Attention!
Bow!
Thank you for watching!
Thank goodness...
Thank goodness! Honestly!
See you next week!
I'm glad everything's fine!
OUCHHH!!!
Bye bye!
OUCHH!!
No one's giving a damn! Ou-