Good evening, everyone. I'm Mori
Hayashi, an intern at Sakura Gakuin.
It's the first "Fresh Monday" in 2018.
Why am I here today?
I'd like to call you in with a little
momentum.
In 2018, I want to do my best as a
teacher who can express everyone's
feelings.
Thank you.
Now, I'd like to take attendance.
First of all, Aso!
Yes!
Yes, it's been 3 years since I became a
junior high school student!
Everyone is tough! 2018 Tendo!
No, no, go ahead, go ahead.
It's the second year of middle school!
I'm Tsugumi Aritomo, second year of
middle school. Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you!
Each of you will get a new badge.
You'll be in the middle school for 3
years.
Thank you!
Good luck!
I'm sorry for Aritomo.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for ruining your debut.
It's okay.
Let's keep going.
Next is Yoshida!
Yes!
It was small, but it's 12!
It was a battle!
And lastly!
I want you to do your best!
Don't worry, it won't start from me.
So, you just gave your name card.
It's your first time, right?
Yes.
How do you feel right now?
It feels weird. I feel like I haven't
become one yet.
You're still a trainee at a real school.
You're a 3rd year junior high school
student.
Really?
What? Is this some kind of prank?
The countdown has already started.
That's fast!
It's already started.
I'm getting nervous.
How is it? You're a 2nd year junior high
school student?
These two are 2nd year junior high
school students.
Are you really 2nd year junior high
school students?
You're trying to hide your age from that
age.
I'm 2nd year junior high school student,
Aritomo Tanaka.
Nice to meet you.
And Tanaka looks happy.
Your smile is intense.
No, it's not.
It's not proof.
How do you feel?
Thank you for watching.
I wish I was a little bit older.
Yeah, if you were a transfer student,
you might become a senior.
Are you okay, Tanaka?
But you've grown a lot in a year.
And today, we have a blackboard behind
you.
You all drew this, right?
Isn't the giraffe cute?
The giraffe is the biggest problem.
This is it, right?
You're giving up on your face.
I look like a bug.
You have a lot of bad feelings.
I drew a lot of Manji.
Don't do that.
There's a lot of Manji.
You can't keep up with your uncle, so
you're drawing a lot of Manji.
Manji, Manji, Manji, Manji.
It's a fresh start.
It's okay if you fail today.
It's like, "Let's grow from here!"
It's like, "This year has been a tough
year."
It's going to be a long story, but...
The moment I came in, I thought, "This
year is going to be tough."
All of a sudden, Aritomo came to the
dressing room.
She said, "Mr. Mori, there's a dropout
test."
All of a sudden, you brought out a test?
Yes.
It's in the west.
Mr. Mori doesn't know much about it.
This is bad!
Wait! Aritomo!
I don't understand this question!
I feel like I'm going to get fired this
year!
Please follow me!
This is bad!
I'm in a pinch since Sakura Nagumi
started.
Everyone, I'm sorry for the test.
You're in a hurry, right?
I'm in a hurry!
When I look at the answer and take out
my smartphone, Tanaka is already strict.
Tanaka is so strict that it's scary.
This will be released in the future,
right?
I'm looking forward to it.
Please don't hit me.
I'm begging you.
I'm already regretting it.
This is the start of my 2018.
Anyway, I want to have fun with
Freshman.
Let's start the class.
Yes!
Thank you for your time today!
These members...
I heard Okada's handover party is still
going on
But I heard he's feeling better now
So I think you can be at ease
So let's start right away
The first hour is...
Yes, 2018...
2018...
He's dead, he's dead
2018 Fresh Monday Meas Back Up!
I can't say it, I can't say it. It's
2018.
That's right.
We want to make it more exciting.
We have a theme for today.
I want you to shout it out loud.
There's only one theme.
A word you want to shout for 2018.
You can say, "This is what will happen
to me in 2018."
Or you can say, "I want her to fix this
this year."
Chikurin, too.
I'd like you to shout out what you feel
this year.
Who wants to go first?
This is the first time this year.
Let's start with Yoshida.
Let's cut her lips.
I'm scared of Yoshida's baseball bat.
Yoshida's baseball bat is traumatic.
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you want to say to Yoshida in
2018?
Mori sensei, Mori Mori is too much!
I'm fine because Momoe is there at the
time of the announcement!
"I can do it too!"
I'm sorry about that!
Is there a part where you only rely on
Yoshida?
Like "Yoshida, please!"
You keep putting pressure on him
That's fine
That's fine?
I get it, I get it
There's a lot of that, right?
I was talking about this at the press
conference yesterday
I have a feeling that if I don't say
everyone's name, someone will get mad
After the graduation ceremony, the
graduates will be like "Why did you say
my name today?"
"Eh, is that so?"
Sato will get really mad at you
Yes, that happens
I get it, it's me all of a sudden
I get it, it's Yoshida
Let's continue
Let's go with Tanaka
Yes
Tanaka is already
It's my first time
It's Miyasu's first time
Tanaka you were noisy today
I was fine
You were so excited
You're going to be a good age
Alright, go!
Miku and Miki, the last letters are a
bit different
Fujihira is the best
I make mistakes every time
I don't think I've ever called Miku
"Miku"
Yuzu and Tsugu made a lot of mistakes
Yuzu was like this
Yuzu Yuzu Yuzu
It's true, it happens every year, Miki
and Miku
I'll call you by your name so it's fine
Are you called Miki?
I'm called Miki
Fujihira
There's no one else but Fujihira?
No
There are times when everyone makes a
mistake
But the one I'm particularly curious
about is
Kano-chan
Fujihira
Yesterday at the voice recording session
Fujihira's shocking video
If you haven't seen it, you might be
able to see it someday
It's a video of Fujihira linking with
chimpanzees
It was amazing, it was interesting
I hope we can see it someday
That's good
Okada was being teased until now
I want to find a new Measubako Queen
You can talk about Okada this year as
well
Ok, let's go
Aritomo, you have a lot of things you
want to say in this show
I have a lot
Let's go
I can see both of you
Yuzu, please show us the front of the
stage
"I'm scared of moving" or "They're
aiming at me"
"I'm too scared"
What's that?
There's a moving thing on the stage
"Are they aiming at me?" or "I'm scared"
They're all aiming at you!
You can't leave them in the dark!
I'm really scared
"I'm really scared, so come this way!"
If that's the case, you might have to
make it pitch black
You're not used to it yet, are you
surprised by the lighting?
I'm really scared
You're from the countryside, so you know
Let's move on to Aso
Aso is pretty scary
No, no, I'll do it
Aso, you're a bit nervous right?
I'm nervous!
You're the only top student here
Let's go!
They give it to me.
They give it to everyone.
It's because she eats a lot.
While I was eating a lot of what Soyou
gave me,
I realized that this is it.
Thank you for watching!
If you give it to Maya, she'll
definitely eat it!
It was delicious!
That's a bit of a trap, isn't it?
You're trying to give it to her, aren't
you?
I thought I'd have to give it to her.
But Aso is the one who eats the most,
isn't she?
Everyone eats a lot.
Everyone eats a lot, but...
We add snacks and buy them.
We buy new things at the convenience
store.
It's a little funny, but...
It's an important year for me, too.
It's going to be a funny DVD when you
graduate.
Be careful, Yoshida-san.
I'll keep accepting more and more.
Let's go, Aritomo.
You have one, Aritomo.
I do.
I have one, but...
That's good.
It's someone's...
I said, "Where did my notebook go?" and
he said, "Oh, Suu ate it."
What kind of strategy is that?
But the one who's looking for it is
pretty desperate.
What do you think about that?
But it's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
"Oh, did you eat it?"
It's like that.
But isn't it irritating?
When you're desperate, what is it?
It's okay to go down that way.
Why are you suddenly making a fantasy?
That's comforting.
It's quite healing.
What was that comment about Yoshida's
food?
I don't know.
How did you feel when you said that?
It's popular among me now.
I'm sorry if I ate it.
It's fun to say that.
Do you want to continue?
Yes.
Be careful, there are people who are
really desperate.
There might be people who are like,
"Don't step on my contacts!"
If you eat it, it might be like, "Don't
eat it!"
Okay, let's move on to the next one.
Do you want to play a game? Yes.
You have eggs, right? Yes.
You've been eating a lot for a year.
Until now, you might have been wearing a
cat.
In front of your seniors.
Let's go. Go ahead.
Misaki sensei!
It's Yamaide's fault. Yamaide said it
with a funny smile, so she forgot the
mic.
Yamaide, be careful!
It's not your fault!
But the moment she said it, Tanaka
looked at me.
I was surprised.
I thought I was able to follow her.
I thought I could hear Tanaka's loud
voice.
That was the worst.
It would have been better if you didn't
say anything.
I'm sorry, Tanaka.
You can do it until you're in 9th grade.
Is that okay?
No, I can't. I'll do it this year.
I'm really sorry about that.
Let's continue.
Let's start with Aso.
Yoshida and I are really popular right
now.
Chikurare? Chikurareri? That's crazy.
Chikurareri.
What should we do?
Oh, I see.
I want to sing a song.
I want to sing a song when I get sleepy.
You know, taking a bath makes you feel
better.
So, I want to sing a song to make me
feel better.
How long does it take?
One hour and a half.
It takes a long time.
Have you ever been bothered by it?
No.
That's right.
You don't have a schedule, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't know the standard, but how long
do you usually sing?
I don't sing for more than 10 minutes.
That's normal.
You're fast.
I sing for an hour.
Your family will be attracted to you.
I'm often told that I'm noisy.
You're noisy.
You're long and noisy.
I'm often told that I'm a nuisance.
Are you that loud?
Do you sing seriously?
You're noisy.
What kind of songs do you sing?
I sing Sakura's songs and songs that I'm
addicted to.
I sing songs with a loud voice.
It's a little embarrassing, but I don't
get stressed there.
What do you think?
If no one's bothering you,
then you can just eat your stress and
come to Flesh Monday with a face like
this.
What if the people in the neighborhood
say, "I can hear Maya's voice again."
I don't think Asou is bad at it, so it's
okay.
Isn't there a time limit?
It's at night.
Thank you.
If you don't feel like you can't
sleep...
I'm sorry.
You still have time, so you can take
turns.
Where's Yoshida?
Yoshida hasn't gone to the second floor
yet.
I want to go to the graduation ceremony.
I'm sure you'll get there today.
You're still watching, aren't you?
I'm sure you're watching.
I asked everyone what it was, but it was
returned before the graduation ceremony,
so I was a little sad.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. I think
you need to explain a lot.
What do you mean?
There's a 2015 Road to T-shirt, but that
T-shirt is gone.
Is that Yoshida's?
Yes, my Road to T-shirt is gone.
I asked everyone.
That's right.
Everyone was like, "I don't know!"
I was like, "There's no such thing?"
My mom got mad at me.
How many years ago was that?
It was in 2015.
When was that?
When she passed away.
You didn't tell anyone.
She passed away before Megu-chan's
graduation.
So she had it at home for 2 years?
That's crazy.
XS!
It's a really small one.
Megu-chan is tall, so I thought she
wouldn't be able to wear it.
But I found it.
I wonder when Okada realized that it was
Yoshida's.
Maybe there was a time when he couldn't
say it.
He might have said "I'm going to
graduate" or "I can forgive anything
now"
He might have said it at that timing
I read a letter from Okada
It said "Trick Yoshida"
He said "I don't mind if you trick
Yoshida this year"
I want to keep that kind of message
I don't want to
There are still people like that
I see, so Okada is the one who's missing
out?
That's right, there are a lot of people
who are missing out
So you're upset because you got scolded?
Yes
This is all Okada's fault, right?
It's also my fault for being sick
No, that's not it
No, it's the same
That's Mori-sensei's fault
Aritomo-san, can you stop being so calm?
Can you stop being so dry?
Okay, let's continue
If there's no more, it's fine
Ah, Aritomo, it's fine
Yes
Aritomo, you're amazing
Thank you
I'm going to do it
Soya's body is very soft, it's a bit
uncomfortable
That's fine
I want you to do it
It's not uncomfortable, it's a good
thing
When I want to do a warm up, I do this
Thank you very much
Are you ok?
I feel like my body is shaking
I don't like it
It's ok
My whole body is soft
Even my shoulders
I see
When you are doing warm up, your body is
already soft
Try doing it in front
It's very uncomfortable
I know that
Is this your first time?
Have you ever done it?
No
It's really uncomfortable
I really don't like it
But it's ok if it's this year's Yoshida
I'm ready to be teased
I'm ready
You can do it!
You're not going to do it?
I'm going to do it
Yoshida-san's flexibility exercise
I don't want to
What is it?
The whole body really loosens up
Just now?
It looked like this part was more
dangerous
But it's amazing!
It stretches a lot!
How did you get this softness?
I don't know.
How did I get this softness?
I learned gymnastics.
I learned how to use the bridge and my
legs.
You can do it like this.
Tanaka, you should try it too.
Tanaka can't do it.
Yoshida can't do it.
Do it side by side.
I'm sorry. I'll let Tsugu-chan do it.
Tanaka, you can't do it.
I don't know how to do it.
Say it clearly.
Yoshida did it because she didn't want
to do it.
Do your best.
To be continued.
Is there anyone who doesn't want to do
it?
Why? Why?
I don't know.
Do it like this.
Wave your arms.
Why? Why?
I don't want to do it.
It's not that you don't want to do it.
It's fine.
Really.
Unexpected rebellious period.
But this is disgusting.
If you look closely.
Also, there is a technique called
Garake.
Garake?
I don't do that.
Thank you for watching.
It's like you're folding your body.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
You put your upper body and legs
together like this.
And you do this with your hands.
Oh, I see.
It's like you're putting this behind
you.
Yes, it's like that.
Isn't it good for you to be alive?
That flexibility and softness.
It's a mat exercise test.
Thank you for watching.
You can do this exercise when you have a
stomachache.
I can't do this.
It's amazing.
Aritomo is strict.
It's good.
It's okay because I'm cute.
You are cute.
Don't say it like that!
It's not like that.
It's Mori-sensei's nose.
Mori-sensei's nose is the point.
That's fine!
What should I do with that?
Don't tell me to get plastic surgery.
So, we've talked about a lot of things.
Yes, we have.
You guys are passionate.
You have the energy of 2018.
So, that's it for the first part.
That was "Fresh Monday 2018" by Bear's
Box.
Now, it's time for the first break.
I hope you enjoy it.
I have something to say.
Yesterday, we did "Takoppa".
I'd like to ask everyone, but what would
be good to put in takoyaki?
Takoyaki is...
It's good to put cheese in it.
It's not just takoyaki.
You can put pancake mix in it.
You can also use it for Valentine's Day.
Since Sayo is from Osaka, I thought she
knew a lot of things.
I wanted to ask her.
For me, chocolate...
It's delicious.
Have you ever made takoyaki?
I've never made it.
I don't know.
You don't know?
I made it with red pickled ginger.
Red pickled ginger is delicious.
It's delicious.
You should definitely eat it.
I want to make takoyaki.
I want to do it.
All of us.
How fast can you eat takoyaki?
I don't know.
When everyone gathered, we made takoyaki
together.
I have a takoyaki machine at home, so I
made it.
I've been to Sakura Bukui about once or
twice.
I did it a lot when I was little.
I've never made takoyaki before.
I've made it once.
I didn't help at all.
I told my brother, "I want to turn this
over, so do that."
My brother wanted to make a really big
takoyaki.
I made it, but after that, I added more
sauce and made it really big.
I also adjusted the degree of baking.
This is mine. I'll eat it.
Don't eat it, Maya.
It looks fun.
It's really fun, so let's do it.
Let's do it.
I want to celebrate.
That's what it was about.
Then, let's go to the cutting board.
I'm looking forward to it.
Who's going to read it?
Miku?
Do you want to read it?
Do you want to read it, Miku-chan?
Which one do you like?
Whichever is fine.
This is cute.
Thank you.
Which one should I choose?
This one.
Here I go.
Everyone at Sakura Gakuin, Mori-sensei,
staff, good evening.
I have a question.
What do you want to wear at the Sakura
Gakuin fashion show?
Do you have one?
What is it?
I like the first uniform.
When we were in the shuffle unit, Megu-
chan was wearing the first uniform.
I really wanted to wear it. At that
time, I should have asked her to let me
wear it.
I touched it.
I want to wear the uniform of the tennis
club.
They are short and long.
These three girls are called "Sun
Girls".
Tanaka of "Ungirls" has a body like
hers.
She has long arms and legs.
But I'm not like that.
These three girls are definitely
different from me.
I'm not like that.
Not at all.
Let's dance!
If you can, please come to Flesh Monday!
I want to see everyone wearing it.
Thank you, teachers!
Please do your best in 2018! I'm rooting
for you!
This is from Sakura no Kinoshita.
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
One more!
Who's going to read it?
Mayu-chan.
It's fine, it's fine.
I can't read it.
You can read it.
Good evening, everyone!
And, please take care of me this year as
well!
Please take care of us!
This is a question, but since it's this
season,
do you all...
do you all do hanami?
Do you?
I've never done it, so if I did,
I'd like to know what's so attractive
about it!
That's what they say.
I used to do it a lot when I was little.
You've done it before, right?
Yeah, I've done it before.
I've done it before, but when I get
older, it's kind of annoying.
It's pretty, but you can see it on the
train, right?
Yeah, I can see it.
It's close to the train.
I'm satisfied with that.
I want to go to a shop.
I want to buy it.
I want to buy Jagabutter.
I don't think I've been there.
When I've been there, I've been to
picnics.
I've seen it up close.
Cherry blossoms are really cute, aren't
they?
The colors are a little different.
It's really fun to see that.
By the way, it doesn't matter.
I played with Momoe today.
I played with Momoe.
You were happy, right? You were like, "I
love you, I love you, what's wrong with
you?"
Yes, yes, yes.
Did you discover your charm?
I ate shaved ice, but it was really
cold.
I couldn't stop sneezing.
And my hiccups were like, "Ugh, ugh."
It was a bad memory.
That was the second dimension.
Here is the 20th dimension.
This is the first Hacchaki project in
2018.
There will be a variety of products.
I will be the customer.
Please sell the products to me.
I will decide the winner at the point
where I want to buy it.
There is a good vibe.
Right, Yoshida-san?
Don't you have confidence?
Haven't you seen this in the city?
You can buy it and sell it for real
You can cut it with a knife
At the supermarket?
Yes
If you go to the supermarket, you can
buy it
You can grill it and eat it
You can do it well
It's natural to be able to do it
Aritomo, you're not talking at all
Let's explain the points
It's a live broadcast
First, we'll start with a small talk
It's important to not make them nervous
If you get too close, it'll be hard to
refuse
And the point is to make it easy to hear
your voice
Tanaka, you've been doing well lately,
right?
Lately...
You weren't talking just now!
You were kind of blabbering just now
And point 3
Find out what the customer is looking
for
You can have a conversation
And point 4
The price is the last one
You can have a conversation
There are some people who say the price
is too high
But there are some people who say the
price is too low
I want you to use this as a reference
point and sell it to me
Let's do it! You can use any of the
products here
There are a lot of things but it's hard
to sell
I don't think you can buy this often
Who should we start with?
That's great!
Anitomo, that's great!
Akindo, show us your soul!
It doesn't matter what kind of person
you are or what kind of motivation you
have
It doesn't matter if it's a girl
Just choose a character that's easy to
sell
Someone that I can easily play
Thank you for watching!
It's difficult
Let's do it flat
Let's do it
Today is pay day so I have a lot of
money
What are you doing?
Come on
It's too scary
You're going to hit me?
I'm going to hit you
I'm going to hit you with my grandson's
hand
What is it?
Today is pay day
Did you hear about it?
Yes, I heard
Today is pay day
If you want to be extravagant
What kind of work do you do?
I'm a novelist
That means you do ego-searching
I do a lot of ego-searching
You do
I get hit a lot
In that case, you'll be quite depressed
Are you okay?
What is it?
She can speak
She can speak?
If I talk to her, will she answer when
she's depressed?
Can I try?
Yes, you can
I got scolded by the editor today
Is that so? Are you okay? Do your best!
I want to do my best, but how can I
write a good novel?
In that case...
Wait a minute...
Perfume...
What are you selling right now?
Two of them!
You're selling a lot!
I see.
Then, Kuma...
Kuma will comfort you.
What happens if you use this, Kuma-san?
If I use this...
This voice is tiring, so can I speak
normally?
No, no, no. Do whatever you want.
If I use this perfume...
It doesn't make me angry, and it sells
well.
Even if I look it up on Egosa, I can
only write good things.
This?
If you buy this?
Yes.
That's attractive. Wait a minute.
These two, right?
Yes.
How much is it for a set?
If you buy it on Amazon...
You're saying it in a small voice.
It's about 80,000 yen.
You can talk and it's good for your ego.
But if you buy it here, it's 79,000 yen.
You can buy it for 1,000 yen?
What should I do?
I won't buy it!
Wait a minute.
I did my best, but...
At first, I did this.
Normally, you don't talk to people who
come.
Normally, you get irritated.
What was your strategy?
I don't have a strategy, but...
You didn't decide.
No matter which one sells, you decided
to follow the person's mood.
I made time for everyone to think.
You made time for yourself.
I didn't do anything.
You did a great job as a top batter.
This kind of pattern is rude to say in
UR.
You can't say "I'm tired" all of a
sudden.
But it was fun to connect.
I understand.
You can add the effect on the spot.
Thank you very much.
I don't know if that was a good example.
From the perspective of buying it, I
would never buy it.
I swear.
Let me feel like I'm buying it.
Who's next?
Tadakai-kun?
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
This is a difficult one.
What should we do?
I don't really want to decide, but
please choose one.
A kind customer.
Please.
Let's do it.
Ready, start!
Today is my wife's wedding anniversary.
I feel like I want to buy a lot of
things.
So I came to the store.
Is there anything?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm looking for it now.
No.
Why don't you give this bear to your
wife?
My wife is the same age as me.
She is 40 years old.
She doesn't look like a bear.
Then what is this?
What is this?
It's hot these days, so if you wear
this, it'll be cool
Ah, this can be used as a fan
A fan?
It's not a fan
It's a little too flashy
No, today is a wedding anniversary
It's good to have a party with this
The bubble generation is a little young
But this flashy
Is there anything good about this?
I don't know
But isn't a normal one better?
If you put this on, you'll feel better
You'll feel better? Why?
How should I say this?
Who are you asking?
I don't know
But you'll feel better
I'll feel better
Just looking at it makes me feel better
What's the name of the product?
It's similar to what I used to use.
What should I do?
My wife might want something like that.
How much is it?
It's a wedding anniversary, so I'll make
it cheap.
Really? I'm happy.
Then, 300 yen.
I was worried but it was good at the
end.
It was good.
You made it cheap for me.
I was happy.
Yes.
You got many points.
I thought you were going to be quiet,
but it's good.
Which one should we do next?
Let's do Aso.
Let's do the one where Okayu takes the
lead.
I really want to go.
Do you have any requests?
I want to look like I'm tired from work.
I want to look like I'm not Mori-sensei.
Can I be a teacher?
Yes, you can be a teacher.
I don't want to be Mori-sensei.
I see.
Let's do it.
Welcome.
I'm tired.
Excuse me, sir.
You said your back hurts.
It hurts a lot.
I'm worried about my age.
That's rude.
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
Age is a part of age.
I'm tired of work.
I'm a teacher at a school.
Is that so?
I can't teach my students.
There's a lot of scary ones.
I have a recommended item here.
Really? For a person like me?
It's this.
It's that?
Why do you recommend it?
Actually, isn't this pretty old-
fashioned?
Old-fashioned? Well, yeah.
Compared to computer games, it's a bit
old-fashioned.
If you play old-fashioned games, your
heart will be...
It's like calming down.
I feel calm.
I feel like I'm back in the old days.
I think I can refresh myself.
You feel like a child.
That's right.
When I go home, I'm alone.
What should I do?
In that case, look at this.
How many do you think there are?
There are 12 of them.
You can play with the members of Sakura
Gakuin.
I know Sakura Gakuin!
You know?
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it's good.
There are a lot of cute girls.
I get a lot of courage.
There are 9 of us now, but if you look
back at the previous years, there were
12 of us.
What does it mean to become Sakura
Gakuin?
For example, I call her Maya-chan.
Yes, and Maya-chan kicks like this.
There is a ball here.
There is a teacher called Morihayashi-
sensei, who is a bad teacher.
Let's do our best with the image of
kicking him.
With the image of kicking the annoying
teacher
I can release my stress
Wait a minute, isn't it sad because
you're the same teacher?
It's a setting where the student is
forced to do it
That's right, but I can release my
stress
I see, but it's fun to do it alone
It's fun
Your heart is moving a little
How much is it?
The price is a little
You're tired, aren't you?
You want to refresh, don't you?
I do!
Sakura Gakuin was really good!
If I were Fukei-san, I would want to buy
it.
But I have Mori-sensei-ism somewhere.
I don't want to feel sad.
So it's better not to be Mori-sensei.
I'm the only one who can't buy it.
We don't have much time, so let's move
on to the last one.
Really? I don't want to.
Let's do it with my daughter.
Tanaka, Tanaka, Tanaka!
Thank you for watching!
It's like you're here as a parent and
child.
Let's enjoy the game!
I'll do my best.
You're not that tall!
What should I do?
How about elementary school?
It's fine as elementary school.
No, I don't want to
Then high school?
I want to go to high school!
You like high school, right?
Yoshida, are you sure you don't mind?
I'm fine.
Let's go!
The team is really modest.
Oh, Miku!
Today, I will buy you anything you want.
It's your birthday soon, right?
It's not my birthday.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
It's not your birthday.
But you know, I'm a really good dad.
Welcome!
What is it?
Miss, you're cute!
I'm a proud daughter.
You look like my dad.
Don't make a complicated face.
It's almost my birthday?
It's not my birthday, but I want to buy
something.
This is cute, isn't it?
It's really cute.
Is this cute?
It's cute, isn't it?
But it's still early in the afternoon,
isn't it?
I think this kind of childish feeling is
fine.
This one?
Wait a minute.
What is this?
I don't know.
It's a small face massage.
I'm getting used to having a small face.
My daughter already has a small face.
What are you talking about?
It's getting smaller.
It's going to disappear.
Do you have anything you're interested
in?
This is it.
Which one?
This one.
You want to use it?
I'll try it.
I think it's too early.
It's not early.
You want it?
You want it because you're a kid?
It depends on the price.
I don't care. If you want it, I'll buy
it for you.
This product is 10,000 yen, but today
it's half price.
5,000 yen.
Really?
Give me three of these.
I get a lot of compliments for having a
daughter.
I get excited when people say that I
have a daughter and she's cute.
Right, Tanaka?
How was it being sold to Yoshida?
It was kind.
It was kind, right?
Tanaka's daughter...
I can't get used to her.
There was a distance.
It's sad.
Mori-sensei...
I didn't know that my daughter would be
shocked by this show.
You don't have to be so kind.
It's all right.
Well, it's been a long time.
Well, that's it for today.
It was fun.
Let's do something like this. Something
like an etude.
I'm looking forward to it.
I feel like everyone can do it.
Please come to the front.
It's interesting.
Announcement!
The first announcement of 2018.
I would like you to decide on it.
The first live of 2018 has been decided.
Thank you very much.
The first live will be held on May 6th.
We don't know what will happen yet.
We don't know at all.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Thank you.
It's scary, isn't it?
It's amazing that you are scared of many
things.
Have you done something with the nine of
you?
Yes, we have.
A new song, a new position.
I see. It's a little difficult to
decide.
It's a little difficult.
I'll let you know.
Is there anything else you want to use?
Yes.
Sakura Rakuin 9th Live Video "The Road"
Graduation 2017 "My Road"
It will be released in July 2018!
I did a lot of things like live viewing,
but if you want to see it again at home,
it's already
You can watch it over and over again, so
please check it out!
That's great!
You're good at this kind of high-vibe
stuff!
That's great!
It's decided, it's decided.
So that's it?
That's it.
Okay, so we're going to continue to
collect the hagaki.
If you send it over here and read it,
we'll give you a sticker, so please send
it over.
You got some of the members, right?
Yes!
You got the ones that you sent over. You
got the ones that you got for free,
right?
Yes, I did.
Please read the hagaki.
But everyone got one.
Everyone got one?
Yes, everyone got one.
You don't have to get one. It's already
out there.
You don't have to read the hagaki.
Okay, so we got a feel for 2018.
I'm really relieved.
We got a feel for it.
We look forward to seeing you again in a
year.
That's all for today's lesson.
Be careful of the sun!