Boon, Boon, Hello, YouTube.
I couldn't keep up with you.
I'm Momoko Hachimoto from Takano Yonai.
I'm Hina Tahina.
Today, there are two of us.
Yes, there are two of us.
I'll tell you what we're going to do.
We're going to play a game.
It's the game we've been waiting for.
We're going to play "The Cursed
Digitame".
I'm scared.
That's what it is.
Did you know that?
Digitame?
No, not Digitame.
You know Digitame, right?
I know Digitame, but I don't know this
one.
There are many series, right?
Yes, there are many.
I've seen many series.
I've seen many too.
I'm looking forward to it.
You haven't seen this one yet, right?
I haven't seen this one.
It's a must-see.
It's around 9 o'clock at night.
It's Ushimitsu time.
Ushimitsu time?
No, it's not.
It's 2 o'clock.
I'm sorry.
I might not be able to control it, but
I'll try.
I've never played a computer game
before, so I don't have any complaints.
You don't?
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best together.
I'll do it.
You'll be the first one to control it.
I'm scared.
I'll do it.
Let's start over.
Huh?
It's on the right!
Oh, it's on the left.
What's this?
It's a park.
I think it's started.
I'll play Blanco by myself.
I'll show you.
From here to Blanco.
It's fast, isn't it?
Let's run!
What's this?
Isn't this a digital camera?
A girl died in a park near here the
other day.
Are you okay?
What's this?
Look for this girl.
I'm scared.
Since then, she's been suffering from
sleepless days.
Always, always.
You're scaring me.
This is important, isn't it?
The location of the 2nd and 8th park
after 3 o'clock.
Let's go back to the slide.
-Let's go back to the slide. -Oh, the
slide.
-It's a roller coaster. -Wait, I'm
scared.
-Don't look at me. -If I don't click, I
can't move forward.
She's still tied up like this.
-We have to release her. -Poor thing.
-What does this mean? Does it mean we
have to release her parents? -I think
so.
She's a bit of a bad parent.
-What's that? -Huh?
-What's this? Oh, I can see it. -Wow,
can you zoom in?
I can see it now.
"Welcome to the world of the strongest
photography."
"Right-click to choose a photo."
"This website allows you to see the
dead."
-Wow, that's an amazing website. -It is.
"You can see the dead on this website."
"Luckily, we got a special camera made
by a priest."
-Wow, that's fast. -It's digital!
"100 photos a day."
-60,000 yen. -60,000 yen? Why 50,000
yen?
-I don't know. It's expensive! -It's
expensive.
But if you can get your daughter to go
to heaven with 60,000 yen, it's not that
expensive.
-What's this? -Where is it?
"Hold the camera." "Hold the camera with
the space bar."
"Take a photo with the left mouse
button."
"Check the photo you took with the tab."
What's a tab?
Oh, it's talking.
"Interact with E."
Isn't it difficult?
E?
I'm pressing E.
Should I close it and press it once?
I did it!
What's interrupt?
Does it mean to open?
Is it a movement?
Run with left shift
Run, run!
What is left shift?
Isn't it this?
I took a picture!
This is a little difficult
I thought I had to run with this
Wasn't it run with W?
Was it wrong?
Move forward with this
What is this?
This is in the way
Thank you for watching!
You run with the left shift, right?
Yes, yes
Isn't this to push the doggy?
Ah, I see!
What are you doing?
That's too much!
What is this? Toilet?
This is the toilet
This way?
What is this?
It's Japanese style
What? What?
I thought someone was peeping
I was surprised
It says it's fine
Oh, I just close it
Oh, I see
Let's go this way
I was surprised!
There was someone!
Look again!
I'm scared!
There's no one
I'm scared
But I'm hurt.
I'm scared.
Ah!
Aaaaah!
I'm hurt!
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
Back, back.
Wait, the mouse is...
Oh, it's this way.
Look, it's looking at us!
Maybe it's a picture.
Maybe it's not a person.
What?
Should we take a picture?
Yeah, let's take a picture.
Let's zoom in.
It's taking a picture.
It's gone!
That's scary!
Why?
It's not here.
Try opening it.
It won't open?
Excuse me.
It's here.
No, it's not.
You took a lot of pictures.
The mouse is difficult.
Difficult mouse?
What do you mean?
Difficult mouse.
It's coming out.
It's a park.
You took a lot of pictures.
What?
-There's a phone ringing. -There's a
phone ringing.
-What is it? -I think it's...
-Isn't it this? -It's a phone.
-How do I dash? -What was it again?
-Shift and dash. -What was it again?
-It's a bit slow. -What was it again?
-It's shift. It says left shift. -Oh,
it's here.
-What is it? -Hello?
What do I do?
-It's ringing. -I can't press E, right?
I can't press E.
Please call me.
When are you coming back?
I'll be back around 5.
Is your head okay?
Are you coming back?
But my dad isn't here.
What's this? Don't talk at home.
No one's here.
-I'm scared. -Someone's here.
-It's so realistic. -Yeah.
-Someone's up there. -There's a kid.
Hi there.
-The park is so realistic. -Yeah.
-I think there's someone. -It's
dangerous to go through.
We should stop in the middle.
Huh? What's this? We can't go through?
Oh, we can't go through.
But there's someone behind us!
He's taking a picture!
-Huh? He disappeared! -He disappeared.
What's this?
It's gone.
It says 1/15.
Does that mean we have to take 15
photos?
I think so.
But there's no one here.
I don't think so.
The place where we can play is around
here.
Around here.
Behind us?
There's a weird face.
What's this?
I'm scared.
I saw Moco-chan's eyes.
It hurts. I'm scared.
It hurts.
I'm scared.
Is it going to appear again?
Really?
You can't miss the shutter chance.
But it's not here.
It came out just now.
Here.
Here it is!
It's here!
I got it!
Nice shot!
I'm going to be a cameraman.
Okay, thank you.
It's definitely here.
It's an elementary school nurse's
office.
What?
"Recently, there's been a case of child
abuse."
That's dangerous.
"It's dangerous to go out late at
night."
"Please be careful."
"I understand."
"This round is suspicious."
"It's definitely coming."
"I'm scared."
"What should I do?"
"Run!"
"Wait, wait. Isn't this still a
possibility?"
"Run! Run!"
"Let's go inside."
"What should I do?"
"I'm scared."
- I'm scared. Take a picture of me. - I
can't see you.
- It's pitch black. - It's pitch black.
I'm scared.
- How many did you get? - It's the third
one.
- It's a face! - It's a hand!
- It's a dog! - It's a dog!
Something came out!
- What is it? - It's a hand!
- Something came out! - It's a hand!
- It's coming! - Run!
- What is it? - Isn't it a dog?
- It's looking sideways! - What is it?
I don't know.
I'm scared!
- What should I do? - I'm scared!
- What should I do? - It's gone!
I'm scared!
It's a dog!
I'm scared! I can't get out!
What should I do?
- Is it useless to take a picture? -
What should I take a picture of?
I can't take a picture.
It's a hand!
- Isn't there something? - What is it?
- It's a dog! - It's a dog!
- Wasn't it a dog? - Wasn't it a dog?
- Why? - It's looking at us.
- I'm scared! - It's looking at us.
Let's take a picture.
- It's transparent. - It's shaking.
- I'm scared! - What is it?
It's looking this way.
I'm scared!
- I'm scared! - It just moved, right?
Don't look away! I'm scared!
- If we put it in camera mode, can we
zoom in? - That's true.
- It's there. - It is.
I'm in the frame.
Who are you?
I can't go home.
It's bright.
It's too scary.
I'm scared.
- I'm so scared. - I'm scared too.
- I was so scared. - I was so scared.
I was looking sideways, so I thought I'd
look sideways.
I'm so scared.
There's only one left.
What should we do?
I can't see anything.
- There's no shadow of a panda. -
There's no shadow of a panda.
Let's set up the camera here.
- I'm scared of the panda's face. - I'm
scared of the panda's face.
There's a human shape.
Let's take a picture.
There's a panda.
There's a dog.
- There's a dog. - It's moving.
There's a panda.
It's turning red. What should we do?
Let's go home.
What?
We don't have to go back to the park.
Please subscribe to this channel.
1 minute is too long.
This is the end.
I'm scared.
What?
It's a message from when she died.
She said she had something to say.
I think she's coming out.
What?
She's coming out!
Eh? Why? Why are you so close to me?
Gyaaah!
Eh? What?
Eh?
Someone's there! Someone's there!
Someone's getting closer!
What?
What is this?
Is that person still here?
- Is it still going on? - It is.
It's a house.
Isn't it here?
Isn't it in here?
It's kind of dirty.
The room.
Don't you want to open it?
It's not opening.
Wait, I'm scared.
Close the curtains!
It's scary at night!
There's a lot of them.
They're definitely in the bath.
Let's take a look.
Can I open the door?
I don't have a good reaction yet.
There's a washing machine.
The washing machine is moving.
But the washing machine...
It's open!
There's definitely someone in here!
A cockroach!
There's definitely someone in here.
There's definitely someone in here!
It's gone.
I think there's something behind us.
There's something.
I'm sure there's something here.
There's something here.
This is a shadow.
Take this.
See?
This is a shadow.
Isn't it huge?
I thought it was a cockroach.
I thought you were going to say, "What?
You're going to put that on? You're
going to put that on?"
Let's go inside.
- I can't take a picture. - I don't
think I can use it.
I can't open it, so I can't take a
picture.
- Is it broken? - Is it broken?
- Can you take a picture and tell me? -
I can't.
I can't react. I'm a monster.
Huh?
I'll ask you to stop.
- One more time? - One more time.
- Can I stop? - Yes, you can.
What if it starts from the beginning?
I'm scared.
Something scary is happening.
What? From the beginning?
What?
Something scary is happening.
This is the first time.
This is not good.
What if this is it?
Huh? It's not opening again.
I can't open it.
It's exploding at the same place.
Let's take a look.
It's not moving.
Huh? That's weird.
This is weird.
It's cursed.
It's a performance.
Maybe.
Where?
The entrance?
Let's go to the entrance.
Let's go to Mitsuka's room.
Can't we press E?
It's open!
This is the changing room!
Was this the changing room?
What was that?
You did your best!
It was fun, wasn't it?
- Did you use it? - Yes, I did.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
- I can't open it. - I don't want to.
It's too scary.
- It's moving! - It's moving!
- It's moving a lot! - It's moving a
lot!
- Where is the entrance? - Wait!
- Who is it? - Ouch, ouch, ouch.
- It's scary! - What?
- It's big. - It's getting dark.
I don't want to.
It's scary!
I don't want to!
- There's a dog! - I'm getting
goosebumps!
There's a dog!
Is it better to have a camera? I
couldn't take a picture without it.
You don't have to take a picture of a
dog.
- Isn't it brighter with a camera? -
You're right.
What room is this?
It's a bathroom.
It's bright.
My heart is pounding.
What should I do now?
I'm scared.
It's coming again!
Wait!
I'm scared!
It hurts!
It hurts! I'm scared!
I'm scared!
It's coming out!
I hate it!
I think he'll come back if he sees me.
I'm scared.
What should I do?
No! I don't want to pilot anymore!
I'm scared! I really don't want to!
I don't want to!
I like dogs.
I don't like dogs!
I'm really scared!
I hate them!
I'm angry.
What is this?
Don't get caught by a dog!
If you turn around, there's a dog.
It's coming out of the house.
Can't you get out of the house?
If you turn around, there's a dog.
It wasn't there.
It was there!
Why is it looking at me?
Should we do something without turning
around?
I don't know.
What should we do?
- Let's go this way. - Yeah, let's go.
I'm scared. I'm so scared.
I'm so scared. I'm so scared.
I feel like a toilet is going to appear.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
What is this?
What? I'm so scared.
What? Why is it coming out?
The picture doesn't look like that.
What is this sound?
I'm scared.
I'm going to check the toilet.
Let's do that.
I'm scared.
Hey!
- What's going on? - This is how it
works.
What's going on?
Maybe I shouldn't turn around.
- I should go around without turning
around. - Where do you want to go?
I don't know.
- It's coming! It's coming! - It's
coming!
What's going on?
- What's this? - Are we being chased?
But I can't run away inside the house.
What's going on?
I can't stop shaking because I'm scared.
Hurry up and come here!
I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
This way.
Did you go to the kitchen?
I'm sure he's here.
He's not here yet.
I don't know what to do.
I'm scared.
What is this?
What should I do?
Wait a minute, I have to find something.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm getting used to the dog.
I know the timing now.
Come on, come on.
I'll take a picture of you.
Leave it to me.
Come on, come on.
It's coming!
You took a picture of me, didn't you?
You want me to take a picture of you
every time?
Leave it to me, leave it to me.
Hey!
It's like a motorbike.
I don't have a passport for this
country.
It's raining.
It's fragrant.
There's a woman inside.
Isn't that Mitsuka-chan?
It's either Mitsuka-chan or a pervert.
- I'll go this way. - OK.
What's that sound?
It's too dark.
It's too dark to see anything.
My heart...
- Don't let go, Naoko-chan! - Stop it!
Don't let go of my hand!
She's holding something.
She's holding a chain.
Here it comes!
It's a failure!
Wait a minute.
It's too heavy!
It's coming!
Is it ok?
Which way?
Is it the other way?
It's not here.
It's coming!
I can't see the screen.
Is it over?
I can hear something.
Are you ok?
There are a lot of dogs!
There are a lot of dogs.
It's coming!
This is Mitsuka-chan's room!
It's Mitsuka-chan's room!
What is it?
Is there something?
Can I move it?
I can't move it.
Miki-chan!
Wait!
I'm scared.
She's a pervert.
Wait, I'm scared.
What should I do, Miko-chan?
What?
Trash?
Outside the house?
I can't get out.
I'm too scared to turn around.
Wait, what should I do? A dog is coming
out.
Something is shining.
It's shining.
Which one is it?
I don't know.
Let's go with the TV.
It's so scary.
It's not a TV.
It's a TV.
It's a cursed video.
It's a digital camera.
Something went in.
Did it?
It's coming.
I'm scared.
What did you do?
Don't come out!
It's the girl from before!
Do I just click everything?
I'm going to speed up because I'm
scared.
Please.
Ruler!
What's going on?
There was something we had to do within
13 days, right?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I don't get it, I don't get it
Where, where, where, where, where, where
We shouldn't have gone beyond 13 days
Kyaaa! I'm scared!
I'm sorry, what is it now?
What do you mean by 13 days?
What, what, what?
It says something, right?
"Photos must be taken within 13 days
after death"
Look, look, look
I'm going to call you.
I didn't know that I was violating the
rules.
You're already dead before the 13th.
What's this?
I'm violating the rules, so I'm doing
something scary.
I'm so scared that I can't stop myself.
What's wrong?
Where's the bathroom?
I'm pretending to be a cockroach.
I'm scared.
Hurry up.
Someone's here.
Don't peep.
I'm really scared.
Everyone...
It's Mitsuka-chan, it's Mitsuka-chan!
Mitsuka-chan, what should I do?
Mitsuka-chan, stop it!
Mitsuka-chan, stop it! What are you
doing?
Misaka-chan?
Don't look this way, Misaka-chan!
Don't look this way!
Tonta, are you okay?
No! No!
No!
Mitsuka, are you okay?
It's your dad.
Your dad is here.
What?
It's your dad.
Isn't this your dad?
It's my dad.
What?
What's going on?
He's moving!
I can't open the camera mode.
I heard something.
Listen.
Where is it?
Let's go this way.
Don't say it so easily, Moko-chan. I'm
scared.
I'm definitely scared.
I can hear it from here.
We were looking from here just now,
right?
That's right.
Isn't the entrance open?
It's open.
The entrance is open.
It's open?
It's open.
Then come on in!
Eh, the entrance is dirty.
Ah, it's dirty.
Eh, Mitsuka!
What?
Isn't that Yukari-kun's photo?
This is Mitsuka-chan's first photo.
What?
What should I do?
Don't send it to me.
I can't see it.
I can't zoom in on the camera.
Ah!
Manami-chan?
It's the first one!
Is it Manami-chan?
Where is Mitsuka-chan?
I'm scared. I can't do this.
Mitsuka? What's going on?
I can't see her. I'm too scared.
It's close!
What?
Where are you going?
Mitsuka, are you going in?
She went in!
Mitsuka!
There are more dolls.
You can do it by yourself.
I'll show you.
It's a TV.
TV?
Yes, it's a TV.
Is it on?
Yes, it is.
It's on, isn't it?
I got a call.
I'll be right back.
What is it?
Dad?
I'm sorry I called you.
I heard this on the radio.
What?
I'm so scared, I'm so scared.
I'm so scared.
Didn't we just make a phone call here?
Is that so?
Isn't this from Mitsuka-chan's point of
view?
I don't think so.
Look, it's here.
Look, it's Mitsuka-chan.
Is this Mitsuka-chan?
Isn't this Mitsuka-chan?
Stop it!
It's open, it's open.
There's a lot!
The wardrobe is open.
Blood?
I'm so scared!
Blood, blood.
Can you move it?
I can't move it.
I'm so scared!
I'm going to take a picture!
I can't take a picture!
Eh? Is Mitsuko okay?
What? What do you mean?
How do I get out of the bath?
I'm scared.
I can't move it.
It's coming closer.
I'm scared.
Why did it turn out like that?
And why is she wearing a swimsuit?
Wait, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
No, no, no, no.
I'm so scared.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
What was that sound?
I don't know.
What?
It turned purple.
Let's find it.
I can't move this.
What?
What is it?
Maybe I should make a call.
They're definitely coming this way.
Us?
It's us.
They're on our side.
I like Mitsuka.
Stop it.
Stop it, Mitsuka!
It's too scary!
I can't move!
Oh, no, it's a phone.
Maybe it's a phone.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
9, October
October
And then, the moment he tried to call
the police...
I'm scared, scared, scared, scared,
scared, scared...
What's wrong?
Um...
My dad...
He's not coming back?
What?
Madami-chan is being killed, Dad!
It's over.
It's over?
What does that mean?
Does that mean Dad is the culprit?
- I have no idea. - What's that dog?
It's my dad.
- What? - That dog is my dad.
Huh? There's an ambulance coming.
The police are here.
So this was all done in real time?
What is this piano sound?
Ending...
Scary...
I'm tired...
I'm so scared that I'm tired...
There's more, there's more.
There's more.
What's this? It's already started!
Where am I?
There's something here!
I'm dead!
I'm dead.
Did you jump?
I jumped. I don't know. I don't know who
it is.
There's something there!
It's Mitsuka-chan.
What are you doing?
Mitsuka-chan...
But I can't hear anything
Eh?
What was that?
My hand!
I'm scared!
Eh? Is it over?
Eh? I'm scared!
This is bad!
I'm going to die!
The cursed Digi-Kame.
I don't know what it was, but it was
scary.
I'm curious because I don't know what it
was.
I want to find out who it was.
I want to find out after this.
I want to do it again.
It was really fun.
It was the best.
I'm scared to think about it now.
Don't be scared.
I'll do my best to go home.
Everyone.
Please subscribe to our channel and give
us a high rating.
See you soon.
We are waiting for you at Motomachi
Shopping Street.
I-M-O
Imo?
Excuse me
We are an idol group called "Hello
Marushiko"
It's really delicious
Please subscribe to our channel and give
us a high rating
I did it!
Please press the good button!