[Music]
To be continued
I've been told that I'm not good enough,
and I'm really upset about that.
I'm really upset that I've been told
that I'm not good enough.
I want to stand on a big stage and do my
best, so I'm doing my best.
J-DOL audition, let's go!
We have decided on 7 members!
These members will debut at the Tokyo
Idol Festival 2022 Smile Garden Stage!
Let's become the world's best idols!
A.A.R.!
Nice to meet you!
I didn't expect such a famous person to
come.
I didn't expect to be an idol with such
a famous person.
I'm honored and excited to be in the
same group with the best idols.
A.A.R.!
I'll announce your group name.
Your group name is...
A.A.R.!
It's like "The Gossip Room".
The scenery is so nice.
I feel like I'm studying abroad.
After this, we will have an individual
performance evaluation.
We will divide the team into three teams
from A to C.
[Music]
I don't know your ideal
I don't want to be a toy
I don't want to regret
I won't cry for you
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
I love you
I can't control myself
I have passion
Hello
I'm Su. This is my first audition.
My dream is to become a top idol of
HoneyWorks.
I want a place where I can keep working
hard.
I want to sing on a tough stage.
I'm good at enjoying myself.
I have a brightness that I can't lose to
anyone.
I want to be a super idol who can make
many people smile.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was able to create a career leader.
Team A's temporary leader, Hina Ishii.
Team B's leader, Rika Tanaka.
Team C's leader, Hitomi.
Team A is Team A.
Team B is Team B. Team C is Team C.
The final judgment will be decided by
that group.
The leader of the team will be in charge
of that group.
I'm the leader.
I'm the leader of Team B.
I'm not good at being a leader, so I'm a
little worried.
But I'll do my best to lead everyone in
the right direction.
I want to lead them.
I'm alive.
Yes.
Let's eat.
I'm so full.
I'm so full from the morning.
I'm more energetic than yesterday.
I wasn't energetic yesterday.
I think I'm at my limit.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Let's start the second lesson.
Let's do it again.
The power is very weak, isn't it?
I may not be able to make it at this
speed.
What I want you to express is my
strength.
When I said I wanted to be an idol,
Some people may be against it.
I have a strong will to do what I want
to do.
That's why I'm here.
Let me hear you.
I want to be an idol.
I went to a vocational high school.
One day, I decided to make a work only
with my classmates.
I was told that I was an unwanted
talent.
So, I want to be on a bigger stage than
them.
Yes.
I never wanted to be number one in dance
school, singing practice, or school
tests.
I couldn't even pass the audition I took
in the past.
I didn't want to be like that, and I was
frustrated.
I couldn't pass the audition.
I want to get a pass.
I want you to put it on your song.
Let's give it a try.
(upbeat music)
(children cheering)
What kind of performance will they show
us next?
It's not the end when you learn it, it's
how you express what you've learned and
how you show it, so that's where it
starts, right?
I'll go with the sound.
Yes, please.
[Music]
One more time.
It's much better.
I'm sure you all know what I mean.
Let's do it again.
Yes, please.
[Music]
The difference between what I can do and
what I can't do is too strong.
Let's do it again.
You're not able to do what you said.
You're doing that in the chorus, so it's
particularly noticeable.
That's what happens when an incomplete
child steals the gaze of an incomplete
child.
You make a wrong move with a different
person, and you'll be noticed by the
wrong person.
Practice a lot.
I'm not sure if I can keep up with the
practice.
Thank you very much.
During this camp, I would like everyone
to level up a little more, so I have
invited a powerful guest.
The first day of the camp
Good morning!
I'm Anna Murashige from T48.
I'm going to be a judge tomorrow, so I'd
like to take a look at your lessons and
get motivated.
Thank you.
I was so happy.
My eyes were twinkling and I was like an
angel.
I was healed.
My eyes were like this.
It was so cute.
I didn't expect you to come to this
training camp.
My heart was beating so fast.
I was so happy.
I didn't expect to come to this training
camp.
I don't think I've done a lot of dance,
but I can't do anything in two days, so
I think it's a matter of feeling.
I don't think there are many idols who
don't seem to be confident.
I think the fans who come to see the
idol stage are the ones who want to do
their best and want to do their best
tomorrow.
I wonder how much courage and energy I
can give.
I think Murashige is an idol.
I want you to do your best so that you
can bet your whole life on today and
tomorrow.
I have no choice but to do my best.
[Music]
Let's go to J-Gala Audition!
Yeah!
[Music]
(upbeat music)
(soft music)
I'm so excited. I've never had so many
people like me.
I'm so happy that I didn't get to
participate in the audition.
You're a good dancer, aren't you?
Thank you.
You're like an older sister to me.
I like that about you.
I'm going to go now.
Thank you for watching!
"I won't cry for the sake of love"
"Come and tell me how you feel"
"I don't want to fight in my youth"
Everyone's emotions are really high.
The sound is not coming at all.
Especially the intro of March 1st.
Everyone is so fast.
I'm a little thirsty.
I want you to be a little more calm.
Let's be calm.
I've always been looking forward to
winning, but now I'm nervous for the
first time.
Thank you for your hard work.
I did my best.
I have no regrets.
Congratulations, you have been selected
as one of the 7 contestants!
[Preview of the next video]
I really wanted you guys to do your
best.
Let's be the best idols in the world!
A.A.O.!
This time, we participated as A-Group.
I felt that the strength of the group
was the same, so I wanted to carry that
feeling and aim for the top with all my
might.
I didn't think I would cry at the moment
I was called, but I was very happy to
remember everything that had happened so
far at once.
After all, I...
I think I'm a total beginner, so I'll do
my best not to leave my singing and
dancing to others.
I'm going to announce the name of your
group.
Your group name is...
I'm going to announce the name of your
group.
Your group name is...
Congratulations!
These 7 people have been chosen!
They will debut at the Smile Garden
Stage at the Tokyo Idol Festival 2022!
The photogenic "Smile Garden" will be
held in the Tokyo Idol Festival 2022!
I hope that everyone will come and enjoy
it!
I will do my best!
Everyone, the camera is here.
I'll try to take a picture.
I'll try to take a picture!
Excuse me.
I'm Hime Komiyama.
I'm Momoko Hashikawa.
I'm Honda Matsumoto.
Nice to meet you.
What do you want to say to your fans?
Well, I want to say to everyone.
Everyone is so wonderful.
When I auditioned for the first time, I
couldn't appeal myself so much.
Everyone was amazing from the beginning
and made me think that I had to do my
best.
I really want to do my best for this
group, so thank you.
Thank you.
I saw that the showroom judges and the
training camp were working very hard.
I also thought that I had to do my best.
From now on, we will work hard to aim
for the top together, so I hope we can
get along with each other.
Thank you.
I was able to feel that I could be
strong by watching everyone's
performance.
I also got a lot of energy, so I'm
looking forward to working with you.
Thank you.
I hope I can aim for the top.
Thank you for your support.
I was very excited.
I went to many events.
Thank you for your support.
I've been watching the audition program
since the beginning, and I've been
admiring you for a long time, so I'm
very honored to be in the same group as
you this time.
I'll do my best to catch up with you.
Let's definitely do it together!
(Laughter)
(Applause)
I don't know if I should do it or not.
What do I want to do?
I want to be an idol.
Honestly, I don't know what I want to
do.
I don't know if I want to be an idol or
not.
I want to be an idol.
After "LAST IDOL" was over,
I didn't feel like it was over.
I couldn't get out of "LAST IDOL" for a
while.
I've been watching videos and searching
for "LAST IDOL" on SNS.
After "LAST IDOL" was over, I thought
about "LAST IDOL" a lot.
After "LAST IDOL" was over,
I was asked to talk about "LAST IDOL".
I don't know if I should do it or not.
I couldn't put it into words.
After the activity,
When I was asked about my future,
I was told that I should continue to be
an idol
by my manager who has been supporting me
since I was 5 years old.
Since I had a chance, I decided to do my
best again.
I will continue to do my best.
They were so energetic and cute.
When I auditioned for the first time,
they weren't this cute.
They were so bright that I thought they
were idols.
I could see that they were working hard
for the training camp.
I felt like I had to do my best.
They were so energetic that I thought
they were idols.
When I lost my activity, I had more time
to think about myself while I was doing
the live streaming.
I was wondering what I wanted to do.
I've been doing it for a long time, so I
thought it was good.
Q. What are you looking forward to in
2021?
A. I'm looking forward to the time when
I can enjoy my favorite things.
B. I'm looking forward to being able to
meet my fans while enjoying my favorite
things.
A. I'm looking forward to the time when
my SNS has changed to my own colors
little by little.
When I announced that I would do what I
wanted to do individually, I was really
lonely that I would go my own way, but I
thought it was amazing that everyone was
doing their best to do what they wanted
to do, so I thought I wanted to do my
best as soon as possible.
When I was told that I would do what I
wanted to do, I was really grateful, and
I have a feeling that I want to do my
best with everyone from now on, so I
think I had the same dream of wanting to
be an idol, so I want to do my best with
everything I have here, so I want to do
my best with the same feeling from now
on.
I want to do my best with the same
feeling from now on, so I want to do my
best with the same feeling from now on.
I'm grateful to be able to be an idol
again.
I've been an idol for four years.
I want to devote my experience and what
I've learned to this new group.
I'll do my best to do what I can do.
First of all,
To be honest, I thought it was good to
be an idol.
I didn't know if I was suitable for
being an idol.
Of course, there were fun and happy
things, but there were also hard things.
Because I had experienced it, I was
wondering whether to be an idol or not.
I didn't intend to be an idol.
Please subscribe to our channel, give us
a high rating, and follow us on Twitter
!!
I thought I wasn't good enough to be an
idol even after "LAST IDOL" was
released.
Before I thought I wasn't good enough, I
thought I didn't want to do it because I
wanted to do it.
When I thought about it, I liked idols
who sang and danced.
I thought I wanted to do my best.
I was worried, but when I got on stage,
I thought I could do it.
If I can do it, I'll do it.
That's what I thought.
Good morning.
I'll do my best.
What was your group name?
I don't remember.
I haven't decided yet.
I'm still a group.
I have an announcement for everyone who
hasn't decided on a group name yet!
I'm not here to give you a present.
I'll announce the name of your group.
Your group name is...
Takane no Nadeshiko.
J is for Japan, and it means that we
will aim to become a representative idol
of Japan who is not inferior to the top
artists in the world.
I named it with the hope that I would
like to become a proud idol group with
the pure beauty and cuteness of Japanese
women, like Yamato Nadeshiko, who is
longed for by many people who cannot get
it like Takane.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best together!
I'm a sound producer, HANIMI WORKS.
I was more motivated by the name, and I
thought that I was expected.
I wanted to do my best more.
I'm very happy to receive the name of
HANIMI WORKS.
It's the first time I've done a
10-member test.
I'm very happy to have received the
name.
I'm going to do my best. Thank you.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's my first time.
It's amazing.
I didn't know there was a place like
this for shooting.
I was surprised.
I'm nervous to do what I've seen in the
video so far.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to take a look at the costumes
for the first time.
I'm going to do my best.
It's amazing.
It's pink.
It's pretty.
It's like a drawing.
I'm so happy to think that it was made
for everyone.
I'm going to do my best to make it.
It's my first time wearing such a formal
costume, so I'm really excited to be
cute.
Let's do our best on the show wearing
this!
Oh!
I've changed my clothes.
The sleeves and this part are lace.
It's really cute.
It's designed in detail, and I really
like it.
I'm really happy to be on stage wearing
this kind of costume.
It's my first time posing like this.
So, I'm thinking about how I should
pose.
Let's do our best!
I'm nervous.
I'm here because I have a strong will to
do what I want to do.
Let me ask you a question.
I'm...
When the screening started, I had a
fight with my boyfriend.
I told him that I wanted to quit my job.
[The story of a girl who was in love
with a man]
I used to think about which one I should
cherish.
That's what I've been trying to
remember.
I'm starting to feel like I'm gradually
being drawn into the world of idols.
It's really fun.
I'm starting to feel like I'm gradually
being drawn into the world of idols.
When I was little, my friends told me
that they wanted to be an idol.
I was laughed at.
Since then, I've been saying it more and
more.
When I was little, my friends told me
that they wanted to be an idol.
I'm going to be an idol.
I feel like I'm getting more and more
realistic.
realistic as an idol.
I don't know how it feels.
I feel like I'm getting more and more
realistic as an idol.
I'm really nervous.
I feel like I'm getting more and more
realistic as an idol.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
I really like idols.
I want to be an idol who makes fans
happy.
I feel very happy now, so I want to be
an idol who can cheer up the fans by
enjoying myself on the stage.
Bye!
I think it's very rude to those who have
been supporting me since I aimed for the
final.
I think it's very rude to support me
like this.
I want to be able to support those who
have been supporting me in my life and
support me from the bottom of my heart.
I want to be able to support those who
have been supporting me in my life and
support me from the bottom of my heart.
I thought I was doing it, so I was very
excited, but after all it became hard.
If you turn your face in the direction
of the light, you can't draw.
Mr. Hemini told me, so I did my best
with that in mind.
Nadeshiko Nakane, let's go!
Good morning.
I'm nervous.
I feel like my body is stiff and I can't
walk at all.
I'm so nervous.
I'm Nadeshiko Nakane.
I'm from Okinawa.
I want to show you my charm.
I'll do my best so that you can support
me.
I'll do my best.
The next video will be the last one.
They are getting ready for the next
shoot.
Please subscribe to my channel and
follow me on Twitter!
I'm so nervous.
I can't do my hair well, so I'm
panicking.
I'm not that nervous right now,
but when I get there, I'll be so
nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
I think this is the first time anyone's
seen us.
I hope they remember us just by looking
at our performance.
We'll do our best to show you a great
performance!
We're going to perform "SAVING" today.
I think that's how I feel.
This is my mom.
That's how I feel.
Thank you for your hard work today.
I was told, "Congratulations on your
debut."
I'm nervous.
I've been practicing a lot, so I want to
have fun.
Let's go, Nadeshiko Nakanishi!
I don't know your ideal.
I can't be your toy.
It's too late to regret.
I won't laugh for you.
I don't know your ideal.
I don't sing because I'm told to.
Don't compare me to a cheap woman.
An adult said, "Your knees are weapons."
It's cheap acting.
It's useless.
I'm always nervous.
I'm selfish.
What are you afraid of?
Coward.
I hate you.
I can't be your toy.
It's too late to regret.
I won't laugh for you.
I don't sing because I'm told to.
Don't compare me to a cheap woman.
An adult said, "Your knees are weapons."
It's cheap acting.
I don't sing because I'm told to.
Don't compare me to a cheap woman.
An adult said, "Your knees are weapons."
It's too late to regret.
I won't laugh for you.
I hate you.
Don't compare me to a cheap woman.
An adult said, "Your knees are weapons."
It's cheap acting.
I won't laugh for you.
I hate you.
If I can't do it, I can't fight
I don't know your ideal
I'm not a toy
Even if I regret it, love
I won't cry for you
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
I love you! I love you!
I can't get married
I can't be passionate
I can't laugh
I can't do anything
I can't dream
What is it today? I'm not feeling well
Is there something you don't like? Tell
me
There are times when I get angry
Thank you for always listening
You worry about my pain
You scold me with a sad face
I've noticed that this dream
It's not a real dream anymore
I love you! I love you!
I can't get married
I can't be passionate
I can't laugh
I can't do anything
I'm not a toy
Even if I regret it, love
I won't cry for you
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
I love you! I love you!
I can't dream
Words alone can't convey
With gratitude
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
I can't get married
I can't be passionate
I can't laugh
I can't do anything
I'm not a toy
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Thank you!
Let's do our best!
We will now cover one of the most
important songs.
Please listen to it.
Come on, Youth Train!
Youth Train
Train, train, let's start running
Train, train, train
Youth Train
Why do people's tears
have to be washed away?
If we pile up our memories
we'll end up in the hands of evil
Where are we headed?
We shouldn't ask
Let's go to the village
Don't let your passion get in the way
If you keep improving, you'll be
satisfied
It's fine if you're just dreaming
There's no need to get hurt
We've come to a place we want to go to
so let's move on
Even if someone punishes me
I have no choice but to go
The train I can't see, the bell I can
hear
What is it? It's the youth that lives in
the future
Train, train, what should I do?
Come on, train, train
I wonder if I'll grow up soon
Youth Train
Life is full of bubbles
It's a blue sky
Let's look back in the darkness
Come back to your senses
and walk on your own
No matter how many times you make a
legend
people will still stand up
What are you looking for
between ideal and reality?
You don't have to experience it yourself
Just pretend you want to
I was shouting from the train
at the sound of the train
Youth Train
Can't you get on?
Train, train, train
This is what it means to live
while dreaming until you die
It doesn't matter if it comes true
as long as you have something you're
aiming for
So that you can carry your luggage
without knowing where you're going
We're going to fly
on the train
Youth Train
Let's start running
Come on, train, train
What should I do?
Can't you get on?
Come on, train, train
Even if you die
you'll never grow up
It's over
Thank you
It was like a dream
I still can't believe
I had a lot of fun
Don't you want to do it again?
I've been doing it every day
After this stage?
It was fun
It was far brighter than I imagined
It was a wonderful stage
Before I became an idol
I used to dance alone at home
The fact that everyone was there
made my dream come true
It was like a dream
It's been a long time since I've been on
a stage like this, but I think it's fun
to be an idol, so I'm very grateful to
be able to stand on such a stage like
this again, and it was a lot of fun.
I was very happy that the fans from
RASAE came and brought the goods with
them.
[Morning of the 2nd day of the tour]
[The day of the 2nd day of the tour]
[The next day]
Good morning.
I'm scared! Why?
Are you scared?
I don't like this.
It's like a interview.
Please.
You've made it to the top.
To get to the top as a group,
I want someone who can put the group
together.
I think it's a difficult position to get
the members' opinions together.
I want to decide on a captain.
To be continued.
I would like you to do it once when I
talk to everyone.
It's very difficult to give up.
The reason is that it's simple and
solid.
I would like you to talk about your
experience in the previous group.
I will leave the contents to you.
I will leave it to you?
Yes.
What?
Is it impossible?
Yes.
[The day of the concert]
Good morning.
I'm going to sing "Hokkien" here.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10.
I'm going to give you a snack.
You can have it.
Really? Thank you.
I brought it.
Let's eat it.
Thank you.
You eat a lot.
I eat more than you.
Thank you.
Today, we finished TIFF yesterday.
We are going to work harder.
I'm going to do the same thing, and I'd
like to talk to you about various things
to do my best, so I called everyone
today, so I got a mission here.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It was a quiz yesterday, but it was
like, "Oh, I didn't say this, but my
friend said this."
It's like an environment.
Haru's friend came to see me from
Nagano.
What?
Four people?
Four people came to see me.
I got a message from the members when we
were doing "Last Lie"
"Good luck"
I got a message from Yu-chan
And when I read the tweets, Yume,
Kokoro, and Karin
They all said "Congratulations"
I'm glad that the members who worked
hard with me
Are blessing me with a new corner
I was happy and I cried a little
I'm glad that I cried a lot
Each one of us has a personal goal
It's okay to be like this
If you have a goal like this
I want you to tell me
In the first round
Even if it's a member or all of us
Even if it's a group
I want you to tell me
Music station
Like that
In a big music band
I want to be a lead vocalist
I want to be in the lead
I want to be on a big stage with a lot
of songs
In order to do that
I think we need support from everyone
Thank you
We want to be a group with a lot of fans
We are produced by HoneyWorks
We want to be a symbol of HoneyWorks
I heard a lot about HoneyWorks
Thank you so much for coming to see us
When I said "I'm looking forward to it,
I still can't believe it" to the people
who came to see us
They said "We are like a family"
I was like "Wow"
I was so happy
I want HoneyWorks to do better next time
Thank you so much
It's been a while since I've been to
Japan, so I want to go back to Japan.
I really want to go to the Olympics
someday.
I want to go to the Olympics from
overseas, and I want to go to the
Olympics in the U.S.
What do you want to say to your fans?
Finally, what do you want to say to your
fans?
I would like to set a goal as a group,
as a talent, as a disciple, towards that
one goal.
Well, I'm angry.
Ms. Suzukura.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Please.
I would like to be a blogger in about 2
years, but I'm 28 years old.
Oh!
More than 2 years!
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's get started.
The last one is Ohana.
I'm going to win!
Ohana!
That's cute.
I won!
Congratulations on your debut!
I think the team is a team that
encourages gratitude.
I've been watching you guys from the
beginning.
I think I started because I wanted to be
a pure idol.
I was talking about the feelings of the
fans who supported me.
I'm personally very happy about this
growth.
By doing my best for someone other than
myself,
I'm going to be needed by someone
seriously.
I'm going to be happy, and I'm going to
get bigger and bigger.
And Nadeshiko Takane is Takane, so I'm
looking forward to the future where I
can be a great person because I'm aiming
for the world's number one, which is the
highest rank in the world.
I think there are a lot of people who
support me now, so I want to do my best
so that I can repay them properly.
When I heard the comments, I felt that I
wanted to aim for the Everest with 10
people, so I want to do my best.
Good morning.
I overslept.
I'm going to shoot a music video today.
What time is it?
It's early in the morning.
Good morning.
It's my first time.
I'm nervous.
I was looking forward to it, but I'm
nervous because it's my first time.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous, but I'll do my best.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
I haven't seen anything yet.
I agree.
It's my first time.
Can I do it?
I did it.
Good morning.
I'm Tanishita.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm ZUMIKUN, the director.
I'm ZUMI.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The music video will be composed of
dance scenes.
First of all, I would like you to
express the strength of the instrument
rather than the smile of each one-shot
lip.
Yes!
The dance scene is a dynamic scene where
the lights move, and the last scene is
the TV scene.
This is the most unique scene in this
work.
This scene is a dynamic scene where the
lights move, and the last scene is the
TV scene.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous that everyone is watching me
because I'm a top model.
She is completely nervous.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous because I'm a top model.
I'm nervous that everyone is watching me
because I'm a top model.
I don't know the meaning of lip-sync.
While singing...
Don't cut it.
What?
Lip...
Was it lip-sync?
I'm sorry. I thought you were talking to
me.
I was explaining a lot.
I was surprised.
I was explaining while singing.
I didn't know I was being filmed.
I didn't know where to look.
Let's get started.
Yes, please.
I don't know the meaning of lip-sync.
I don't want to be a toy.
I won't cry for you.
It's beautiful on the screen.
It's like an idol music video.
It's cute.
I'm nervous.
I was surprised.
I took a lip-sync.
But I'm not used to it.
So, I was nervous.
If I can do it well, I'll be happy.
I took a lot of pictures for myself.
There was a wind behind me.
It was amazing.
I thought I was an idol.
When I was standing there,
The members I always talk to
I felt like I got a different name.
It was a fresh feeling.
I had a lot of fun.
It was really good.
That's why I don't know.
That's right.
Where can I see the glam?
I'm going to skip it.
How far can I go?
Really?
You went there.
Yes, I did.
It's amazing.
It's smoke.
It's smoking.
It's amazing.
They are...
The one who was in front of the door.
It's a little bit far.
I changed it a little bit.
It's 0.5m.
Even if it's 0.5m,
If there are two or three places,
It's confusing.
It's really confusing.
I don't know where I am.
(I got to the end.)
Let's do our best at the very end.
At the very end...
This...
Something like this.
It was really good during practice.
I want you to do that.
I thought I could do it, but it's pretty
hard.
It's not easy.
I think it's pretty close.
I'm about to fall.
I'm going to try again.
I did it.
I think it's cool to have a skirt that
looks like it's standing up.
It's a good point.
I'm nervous because the camera is
getting closer.
The camera moves really fast.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind
of movie it will be.
Wow.
There are a lot of TVs.
I'm here.
I can do it.
It's too close.
It's too funny.
It's too funny, isn't it?
It's too close.
I didn't know it would be this close.
You can see yourselves on the screen.
It is a performance that is closely
related to the theme of the song, such
as a confrontation or a conflict with
another person within oneself.
The long-awaited last scene
Cut!
1,2,3,4!
Great!
Cut!
That's all for the MV shooting. Thank
you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
"March 1" is a dark song, so I think you
can enjoy everyone's beautiful faces.
I often watched the making video, but
when I actually did it, I didn't know
how to do it.
I thought it was difficult.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind
of MV I can make.
There was a lot of content.
I had a lot of time, so I had a lot of
first experiences.
I'm running around, but I'm looking
forward to it.
This MV is amazing.
All 10 members dance like puppets.
They dance mechanically and express
anger and frustration.
I would be happy if you could focus on
that part.
The second day of the tour
Good morning!
Today is the third day.
Let's do our best!
We are going to Yokohama Arena.
It's a big stage, so I'm nervous.
But I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too!
It's our first time to have an indoor
concert.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's our first time to perform on the
stage.
So I'm nervous.
But I'll do my best to enjoy the
concert.
Let's do our best!
The third day of the tour
Yokohama Arena
I got it!
It's a gate.
It looks like Pokemon.
It's true. It looks like Pokemon.
Good morning!
The fourth day of the tour
I can't believe I'm in Yokohama Arena.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's the first time for us to have a
live show with the members.
That's right.
We were in a hurry to get ready
yesterday.
That's right.
We were in a hurry.
There were three people in blue, so I
was wondering who they were.
If it's blue, it's my person.
I'm glad.
It's a light pink.
I was wondering who it was.
I was thinking.
It's milky pink.
Isn't it cute?
Isn't milky pink good?
It's cute.
Let's go!
We'll do our best!
[The first day of the concert]
Let's get excited for the "@GEM"
Blueberry Stage!
Let's go, Nadeshiko Takazuna!
Let's go!
[The second day of the concert]
[The third day of the concert]
[The fourth day of the concert]
[The fifth day of the concert]
[The sixth day of the concert]
[The seventh day of the concert]
[The eighth day of the concert]
We're done!
Even though it was just the first day of
the concert,
there were so many colorful lights,
so I was happy to see my own color.
Thank you so much!
I was so happy to see my own color.
Each member's color was shining,
and it was such a beautiful scenery.
Thank you so much!
It was amazing!
[The first day of the concert]
[The second day of the concert]
[The third day of the concert]
[The fourth day of the concert]
[The fifth day of the concert]
[The sixth day of the concert]
[The seventh day of the concert]
[The eighth day of the concert]
[The ninth day of the concert]
I'm the only one who understands
It's okay, even if I'm alone, everyone
is here
Let's go!
It's time!
More!
Show me more!
The sound of love
2 steps!
One by one
More!
Show me dreams
So please, please, please, please
This is a special night filled with love
Let's have fun
Shout to the moon, again
Let's have fun, again
Don't forget
I hope it'll be a special day
Let's sing together, forever
Let's walk together, forever
Let's sing about love, together
L.O.V.E
One, two, three, four
More!
There's nothing I can't do
I'll leave you behind
Let's sing about love, together
One, two, three, four
More!
Let me see your eyes
I'll leave you behind
Let's sing about love, together
One, two, three, four
More!
Thank you!
We're done!
It was fun
It was fun!
The concert was great
Yeah!
Everyone was singing along during the
showroom
so I'm glad it was exciting
I was really nervous
but it was really fun
I've always been a fan of Uchikawa-san
so I was able to smile naturally
Thank you!
Okay!
Let's do it!
One, two, three, four
Ta-da!
This is it!
This is white chocolate
and this is chocolate
We're going to eat a lot of sweets
There's white chocolate too
I'm really looking forward to it
There's also white chocolate
It looks good
It's a cake
Thank you!
Wow!
Let's make it and share it with everyone
What is it?
Wow!
It's so cute!
I'm going to put a lot on
It's better as it is, isn't it?
I'll leave the sea as it is.
The rest is a little...
It's a happy time.
I'm so happy.
It looks so delicious.
I can't wait to eat it.
You're greedy, aren't you?
Thank you for the meal.
I'll eat white chocolate first.
It's so good.
It's sweeter than I thought.
I finished eating.
After you finished eating...
It's so sweet.
It's so good.
I'll eat it without leaving anything.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Each member will get an acrylic keychain
or an original sticker.
They are going to the shop.
What kind of products will they buy?
A lot of them.
Let's go to see them.
I'm going to MOKO in Sapporo.
I'm going to buy a lot.
What is this?
Yes!
I got it!
What is this?
Ta-da! Pandamic's
Ta-da!
Athletic camera!
Thank you very much!
I'm glad!
Let's go!
I'm going to put this in my pocket.
That's right.
It's a sticker.
It's cute.
It's a sticker of Atsumi-san and Stella-
san.
I got a sticker.
Thank you very much.
Pandamic's
I got a sticker.
Can I take a picture?
Yes.
It's a picture of me.
I got a sticker.
What?
I'm glad!
Thank you very much.
I'm going to put this in my pocket.
What?
It's a map.
Wow.
It's a family picture.
It's a map.
You are so funny.
That's amazing.
What's that?
What did you see?
That's all for today
Yeah!
Do you know about me? Do I look cute?
How is my singing? Do I sing well?
Do I look cute in a costume or make-up?
Do you like my choreography?
My hands are cold and my feet are
trembling
But I still want to fight, because I'm
an idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down upon
Don't say that I'm an idol
Don't say that I don't have a dream
Don't say that it's natural for me to
work hard
Don't say that I'm an angel
Don't say that I'm an idol
I hate it the most in this world
I'm always nervous and I keep giving up
But I still want to fight, because I'm
an idol
I'm a passionate idol
I'm a mischievous idol
I'm always looking for my love
I'm a living idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down upon
Don't say that I'm an idol
Don't say that I don't have a dream
Don't say that it's natural for me to
work hard
Don't say that I'm an angel
Don't say that I'm an idol
I hate it the most in this world
We would like you to announce the
results of the contest.
We have a letter for you.
A letter?
Yes, we have a letter for you.
Could you read it for us?
Yes, please.
I'm going to read it.
Yes.
To the members of Akane no Nadeshiko.
It's been two months since the group was
formed.
It's been two months since your debut on
the big stage.
(Announcement)
(Scream)
On August 26th, we will have a CD debut!
I'm sure you'll be surprised by the
sudden announcement.
This is a very happy announcement, but I
think everyone knows that this is not a
goal.
You are still a rookie idol.
As a step to this CD debut,
Give more energy to more people,
So that you can deliver songs
Aim for a proud idol from now on and
continue your efforts.
Let's aim for a higher goal.
Congratulations on your CD debut.
Thank you very much.
How about Matsumoto-san?
I really want to achieve one goal.
I'm really happy that I was able to
participate in the CD debut.
I will do my best as Takada Nanehiko.
I want to do my best so that I can aim
for a better future.
It's all thanks to everyone. Thank you.
This is a very important announcement,
but thank you very much.
We will continue to do our best for
October 26th, so please support us.
Thank you.
October 26th is the anniversary of the
end of the war between Japan and the
Soviet Union.
We will continue to do our best for
October 26th, so please support us.
Thank you.
October 26th is the anniversary of the
end of the war between Japan and the
Soviet Union.
We will continue to do our best for
October 26th, so please support us.
Thank you.
Please fall in love with me
I'll do anything for you
Be kind to me and let me fly
I found a job at a movie theater
I know better than anyone else
But it's okay, I can stand here
Let's go!
Please fall in love with me
I'll do anything for you
Be kind to me and let me fly
I found a job at a movie theater
I know better than anyone else
But it's okay, I can stand here
Let's go!
Please write me a letter
I'll call your name and talk to you
It's still too early to say goodbye
But I won't lie, I'll make a declaration
I don't want to be alone
I don't want to be a fool
I don't want to fight, I don't want to
lose
I'm here
Let's go!
Please give me more
Ah, the end is approaching
It's lonely, isn't it?
It's fun, but I'm about to cry
Next time, next time
We'll meet again, right?
I promise!
Words overflowing in my heart
Words of someone I don't care about
I need them, I need them
Always
Shout as much as you like
Have more fun
Don't forget
I hope it will be a special day
Let's sing together, forever
Let's walk together, forever
With love
Let's drink it all up
L.O.V.E
Let's sing together, one, two
More!
Look at me
Let's chase each other
I don't know if it's love
Let's keep going
Let's party
More!
Look at me
Let's chase each other
I don't know if it's love
Let's keep going
See you tomorrow
Let's do our best, let's do our best
Let's love each other
I can't do it
I'm passionate
I can do it, I can do it
Even if I'm laughed at
I can't do it
Let's make our dreams come true
I don't know what's going on today
What happened?
Tell me
There are times when I get depressed
Thank you for always listening to me
Let's worry about it together
You always scold me
I've noticed
I can't do it
Let's do our best, let's do our best
Let's love each other
I can't do it
I'm passionate
I can do it, I can do it
Even if I'm laughed at
I can't do it
Let's make our dreams come true
I can't say it
You look so happy today
Did you have a good day?
Tell me
I want to talk to you about anything
Because I love you, I want to tell you
We can make it happen now
Hard work allows for recognition
I'm not sure if I'll have the courage to
say it
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Yes, I love you!
The more I think about it, the more I
don't know
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
I'm not sure if I'll have the courage to
say it
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Yes, I love you!
The more I think about it, the more I
don't know
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Yes, I love you!
The more I think about it, the more I
don't know
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
Even if I'm made a fool of this year and
the next
I'll make it up to you, I'll make my
dreams come true
Do you know me? Do I look cute?
What do you think of my song? Do you
like it?
Do you like my outfit? Do you like my
nails?
Do you like my dance moves? Do you like
my dance moves?
I can't wait to see you, I can't wait to
see you
But I still want to meet you, because
you're my idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down on
Don't say I'm just an idol
Don't say I'm just a nobody
Don't say I'm just a normal person
Don't compare me to other people
Don't say I'm just an idol
I hate that the most
I can't see your private life, so I
don't think you know
Your personality seems to be bad, so why
are you screaming?
But I'm serious, I'm serious about you
Please fall in love with me, that's all
I can do
I know everything about you
But I still want to meet you, because
you're my idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down on
Don't say I'm just an idol
Don't compare me to other people
I hate that the most
I hate being looked down on
Don't say I'm just an idol
I can't work if I don't eat
I know everything about you, but I can't
live
Please wait until the day I regret
I know everything about you
But I still want to meet you, because
you're my idol
I know everything about you
But I still want to meet you
Don't compare me to other people
I hate that the most
I hate being looked down on
Don't compare me to other people
Don't force me to change my image
What is love?
I hate it the most in the world
[Music]
I don't know your ideal
I can't cry
It's too late to regret
I won't cry for you
[Music]
Don't compare me to other girls
I don't know your ideal
I can't cry
I always care about you
I love you
What are you afraid of?
Even if you don't like me
I don't care
A little
Come to think of it
I have to lose my youth
I don't know your ideal
I'm not a toy
It's too late to regret
I won't cry for you
[Music]
I'm not a toy
I don't want to be a doll
I'm not a doll
Don't compare me to other girls
I don't know your ideal
I love you
Even if you don't like me
I don't care
A little
Come to think of it
I have to lose my youth
I don't know your ideal
I'm not a toy
It's too late to regret
I won't cry for you
I'm not a toy
No matter how much I believe in myself
I can't live without getting hurt
I'm not a toy
I don't want to be a doll
I don't know your ideal
[Music]
Come to think of it
I have to lose my youth
I don't know your ideal
I'm not a toy
It's too late to regret
I won't cry for you
[Music]
I love you
Look at me more
Give me more
With a kiss full of love
[Music]
I'm not a toy
I'm smiling
I love you
Please love me
I'm not a toy
I don't know your ideal
It's too late to regret
I won't cry for you
I'm not a toy
I don't know your ideal
With a kiss full of love
I'm not a toy
Look at me more
Give me more
With a kiss full of love
I'm not a toy
[Music]
Please write me a letter
I'm not a toy
From now on
I'm smiling
I'm not a toy
I won't cry for you
Look at me more
Give me more
With a kiss full of love
I'm not a toy
From now on
We're over
I'm always lonely
I don't want this
I won't cry for you
Next time, next time
Let's meet again
Yay!
From now on, let's make our dreams come
true!
Words that are slowly fading away
Even the words of someone you don't know
It's necessary, it's necessary
Let's sing together
Shout to the moon, more!
Sing more happily, more!
Don't forget
I'm sure you'll be able to hear my voice
Let's sing together
We'll always remember
The words of love
Let's sing together
Shout to the moon, more!
Sing more happily, more!
Let's shout to the moon, more!
Let's make our dreams come true, more!
Don't forget
The words of love
Let's sing together
Thank you!