♪ Applicalbi, Applicalbi, Applicalbi,
Applicalbi, Applicalbi, Applicalbi,
Applicalbi!
Wow!
Squat! Squat!
Right, front! Right, front!
Ah-ha!
[This video was made with the support of
the Saka-Neko Touhou Project.]
[Sakaneko Tube]
[Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!]
I'm going to rush to Nonhiku's dressing
room.
I'd like to get her autograph on this
T-shirt.
So, I'll challenge myself to a battle.
If I win, I'll get her autograph.
So, I'm going to rush to Nonhiku's
dressing room.
It's my first time to rush to a dressing
room.
My fans might get mad at me.
I'm nervous.
Excuse me.
I'm Marisa Higashiyama from NADESHIKO in
Matakane.
Nice to meet you.
I'd like to get your autograph on this
T-shirt.
But I'm sorry.
My fans might get mad at me.
Please look this way.
If you win, I want you to sign here.
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won!
I'm sorry. Let's do it again.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Let's do it again!
I lost!
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
[Laughs]
[Music]
Stop
Once more
[Music]
Let's do it.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look over there!
I lost!
I'm so sad!
Thank you.
I'm going to do it by force.
One, two, three!
Can I have your autograph on this
T-shirt?
Sure!
Thank you.
I'm so nervous.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ta-da!
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
I love 2step.
They're always cute.
I love how they do it.
Is there a way to do it?
Yes, there is.
Let's try it.
Are you sure?
When you kick the ball,
put your foot inside the ball.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I can't do it.
I have to put my foot inside the ball.
Oh, you mean I have to put my feet
inside?
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Please take care of yourself.
I have to do some special training.
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
The special training is over.
Now, I'm going to go to the dressing
room of I LOVE.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I'm glad that I could come to the
dressing room.
So, I'd like to ask you a question.
Do you have any questions?
In September, there is a festival called
"Makuhari" in Takanako.
Do you do "Makuhari"?
I'd like to ask you how to shake
"Makuhari".
How to shake "Makuhari"?
I'd like to ask you.
Do you jump with everyone?
Jump?
Like "I'm an idol"
I see
And then
"Shake it"
Like an order
If you say "Shake it" like this
Everyone has to shake it
"Shake it" like an order
I got it
What are you going to do in this battle?
I'm going to shake hands
I got it
Do you like me?
I like you
I'm going to shake hands
Go, go
I was a bit weak
Thank you
Yes, I would like to enter the dressing
room of the collection from now on.
I think it's a little bit of a start.
Excuse me.
I'm Yusuke Nakazakawa.
Thank you for watching!
What is the content of the match?
The content of the match is to play "I
love you" game.
I've never played "I love you" game with
an idol, so I'm happy.
Are you happy?
I'll be the judge.
Ruru-san and Mikuru.
Let's play "I love you" game.
Are you ready?
I love you.
Who won?
Takaneko won!
I did it!
I thought I wanted an autograph, so I
used my experience as a judge.
I'm sorry.
Was it good?
Thank you very much.
Cute.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to enter the dressing room of
Tohoku Inari.
I'm nervous.
Do you have something?
No, I don't.
What are you going to do?
I heard that I was going to play a game
to get an autograph.
I was wondering what I should do.
I'm going to play a game called "Nanja
Monja".
Monja" which is a one-on-one game.
I'm looking forward to it.
Nao-chan lent me this.
It's a version with a smaller amount
than usual.
It's called "Jutan Bar".
I'm going to play a game called "Nanja
Monja" with this.
I'm going to play a game.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It's cute.
I bought this and came to play a game
because I wanted you to sign here.
Thank you.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
I'll go with this one.
I'm nervous.
Okay, then.
Kururin.
That's easy.
Okay, then.
Biyorin.
Biyorin, Biyorin.
Biyorin!
What did you say?
Biyorin, Biyorin.
You're Biyorin.
Wow!
That's a very similar name.
Biyorin!
Here we go.
Beans!
Biyorin!
Biyorin, Biyorin.
Can I get this one?
Yes, you can.
I might be wrong.
Biyorin, Biyorin.
Ta-da!
Kabi.
Kabi?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let's go with Kabi.
Kururin!
It's Kururin, right?
Beans!
Here we go.
Kabi!
Biyorin!
I gave up.
Yes, you did.
Let's go.
Beans!
I might get this.
Let's go for the last one.
Kabi!
Yay!
But we already have lots of autographs.
I know.
Thank you.
I have 7 Mejibana cards.
I have 12 Mejibana cards.
Thank you very much.
Don't open it.
I'm going to the dressing room.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm going to take the Nanka-Kinshi-
Seishuken.
Nanka-Kinshi-Seishuken
We say "Nanka" in conversation.
If you say "Nanka", you lose.
Nanka-Kinshi-Seishuken starts.
What did you eat today?
I ate crab rice.
Was it delicious?
What did you eat?
I didn't eat anything.
Did you eat something?
Let's practice.
Let's practice one more time.
I'm going to start.
What do you like about Aya-Yama?
You talked about it earlier.
Her costume is cute.
She is fluffy.
Her body is cute.
She is cool.
She is cute.
I won once.
She is easy to move.
She is cute.
Thank you.
She is really good.
I'm going to start.
Yorami is going to start.
Excuse me.
I'm going to start.
Banana.
Strawberry.
Orange.
Apple.
Blueberry.
Pomegranate.
Pineapple.
Banana.
Ramune.
I got it right.
I'm going to start.
Swimming.
Soccer.
Dance.
Baseball.
Basketball.
Softball.
Volleyball.
Cat.
Giraffe.
Rabbit.
Reese.
Fox.
Elephant.
Raccoon.
Giraffe.
Elephant.
Excuse me.
I'm going to start.
I'm glad.
She is kind.
She is cute.
Thank you.
I'm going to go to their dressing room.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to start.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
This game is to switch words and words.
For example, when you are told to go
forward, you go backward.
When you are told to crouch, you go
forward.
I'm nervous.
Forward.
Backward.
Right.
Left.
Jump.
Crouch.
Forward.
Backward.
Right.
Jump.
Crouch.
Forward.
I'm surprised.
It's a little different from the first
half.
I don't know anymore.
How was it?
I didn't pay attention to it.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Forward.
Backward.
Right.
Left.
Jump.
Crouch.
Smile.
Forward.
I'm sorry, but...
Takarago won.
I made a mistake.
Why?
I don't know.
She is cute.
She is good at it.
Thank you.
Please look forward to the next episode!
I'm going to the studio of STU48.
Nice to meet you.
I'm nervous.
Excuse me.
What game are you going to play?
I'm going to play Aburi Calbee.
Aburi Calbee?
It's a stupid game.
Aburi Calbee
I'll start.
Good luck!
Aburi Calbee!
[Abricalbi]
You got it!
I got it!
[Abricalbi]
I'm worried about you.
What should I do?
Don't lose!
Can I say it again?
She's nice.
You're good at this.
Let's try it again.
Let's go.
[Abricalbi]
Aburi Kalbi!
Wow!
I'm going to go to Shikoku.
Aburi Kalbi!
Wow!
That's cute.
Aburi Kalbi!
Wow!
[Aburi Kalbi]
I'll say it again.
Aburi Kalbi!
Wow!
That's cute!
[Kawaii-fu]
I'll say it again.
America the Beat
Now!
Huh?
There's a judge.
So I win!
I didn't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
Please use it.
I'll use it.
I think it's similar.
Is it similar?
That's good.
Thank you very much.
Now, we're going to the school.
Let's go!
I'll challenge the battle.
I'll do my best.
Excuse me.
I'm here to challenge the battle.
If Takane is good, I want her to sign
this T-shirt.
Nanami!
Let's do it together.
She's my classmate when I was a trainee.
We're going to play the Lost Game.
Do you know it?
No, I don't.
I said "2.0" and gave it to her.
2.0!
I'll protect you.
Let me protect you.
Dosukoi 2! 2 points!
Dosukoi A! Aichi!
Dosukoi B!
Dosukoi H!
Harami!
Oh, it's Harami.
There's a lot of meat.
I said "Happy".
Let's do it one more time.
Dosukoi B!
Dosukoi C!
What is this?
Dosukoi D!
Kitsune!
Wait, I lost.
I lost.
I lost, but both of them were good.
I'll take your autograph.
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
They are going to the dressing room.
We're going to the dressing room now.
Let's go.
I'll put it on.
I'll put it on casually.
I was going to put it on here, but I'll
put it on casually.
I'll put it on casually.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
How many times are you going to do it?
I brought a pram.
I'd like you to do it with me.
That's great.
I'd like to do it with Ame-chan.
Ame-chan is actually smart.
I'm weak.
I'm serious.
She's cute.
Then, please turn off your nervous
system.
If you hit it suddenly, you can win.
Oh, no.
Oh, it came out.
Hit it.
Please stop.
Oh, it came out.
It's not good.
I don't know.
Oh, no.
It's not good.
Did you forget Momo-chan?
Momo-chan.
It's not Momo-chan.
The costume is different.
It's good.
I've never seen this before.
What?
Wait, wait.
I'll take it again.
Here?
So cool.
So, Takaneko won.
Amazing.
So cool.
Can I have your autograph here?
Of course.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you so much.
I know it's a waste to leave this place.
But, I love you.
I love you too.
Hi!
Today,
I came to Ikebukuro Station.
So many birds.
Please subscribe to our channel and give
us a high rating!