Good evening, everyone. I'm Nonaka
Kokona.
Yaho!
Nonaka Kokona's REC Chuu.
This program is a talk variety show
where voice actor Nonaka Kokona,
who broadcasts once a month,
challenges various projects to make a
buzz video.
Last time, I challenged myself to do a
job interview.
There were various things.
As a result of various challenges, I
realized that this is the right way for
me.
I think it was a warm meeting with a
person who stayed in my heart.
First of all, please let me inform you
about the program.
I have already announced it on the
program homepage and program X.
Some of the functions of Nico Nico
Channel Plus are affected.
For more information, please check the
official Nico Nico account.
And for this situation,
today's live stream will be a free live
stream.
Please check the archive video of this
live stream from the summary column.
You can watch it by anyone,
but the comment function you are using
now
is your own comment.
If you can comment, please comment more
and more.
And if you can't comment, please post it
on SNS with the hashtag #Nuslog.
And so, this time...
This time's Nuslog is...
After this, we will have a guest.
The guest is...
I'm Izumi Fuuka-san!
Yes, that's right.
Izumi-senpai's fashion sense...
I've been saying this for a long time.
Her fashion sense is really good.
Also, her hair is really cute.
I'm growing my hair right now.
I'm growing it.
When I heard it, it's a little
fashionable.
How do I say it?
It's cute, but it's also good for the
outer hair.
It's also good for cool hair.
I'm saying it in front of him.
That's what I think.
Of course, we have guests this time.
He will also come to the first event of
this weekend's program as a guest.
Here is today's menu for welcoming Fuka
Izumi as a guest.
In the first half, we will talk with
Izumi-san about the announcement of this
weekend's program event "BuzzDemy Awards
2024"
And I would like to talk with Izumi-san
while reading your letters.
And in the second half of the program,
we will deliver a project with Izumi-
san.
First, Nonaka Kokona will challenge
Guinness World Records.
This time, Izumi-san and I will
challenge Guinness World Records.
Actually, I broke the Guinness World
Record in the last live stream.
So, I would like to challenge Guinness
World Records again this time.
And the main corner is Nonaka Kokona's
Buzz Rec.
Buzz Demi Award All Night Festival
I would like to enjoy a luxurious buffet
and enjoy a festival all night with a
party game.
And when you post about the program on
SNS, please add the hashtag #NasuRoku
Hiragana "Nasu" Roku-ga-no-Roku "Tesu"
And I'm also posting on TikTok
I took one earlier
So, I would like to post three reports
this time as well, so please check it
out
Then I would like to start the program
Please enjoy the 1-hour live broadcast
until the end
Nonaka Kokona's REC Chuu
Ready, action!
Thank you for waiting. Now, let's
introduce our guest.
It's Fuka Izumi.
I'm Fuka Izumi. Thank you for having me.
Thank you for bringing me eggplant.
I was an eggplant until a while ago.
That's right, until a while ago.
So, this time's guest is Fuka Izumi from
the same agency.
Nice to meet you.
I used to be a member of the agency's
YouTube channel.
That was about a year ago.
That's right.
It was really the first time.
It was the first time.
That's right.
I didn't know.
It was last summer.
That's when we met.
You came to see us at Mixed Juice.
That's right.
That's when you came to say hello to us.
It's the second or third time we've met.
Thank you for inviting me.
Everyone, do you know what this is?
This...
Hair?
Hair, right?
Do you know what I was talking about
earlier?
You've grown a lot.
You've grown a lot, haven't you?
Yeah, I've grown a lot.
I know, right?
Yeah, well...
Together...
On YouTube...
Yeah, yeah.
When I saw the picture, it was really
short.
Yeah, it was refreshing.
I didn't know my hair would grow this
much in a year.
Really, in a year?
Yeah, it grew a lot.
Yeah, it did.
So that's it.
With a fashion sense as great as
yours...
What kind of way of talking is that?
It's kind of embarrassing.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Anyway, we have Izumi-san as our guest
today.
As I said earlier, this time is not the
only time.
I would like you to come as a guest to
the afternoon of the first event of the
show this weekend.
So, let's get to the event and announce
it again.
Yes.
The first event of the show "Nonaka
Kokona's REC Chuu Buzzdemy Awards 2024"
will be held on Sunday, June 23rd at
Tokorozawa Sakura Town, Tokorozawa City,
Saitama Prefecture.
I'm sorry.
It will be held at Japan Pavilion Hall
B, Tokorozawa Sakura Town.
Fuka Izumi will be a guest on the
afternoon part of the 2nd performance.
I'm going to try it.
And as I said before, I'll also be
singing.
I'm looking forward to what kind of
event it will be.
And you can watch the event on the live
stream.
Here it is.
I've already announced it on the
official program X, but...
Due to some restrictions on the use of
Nico Nico's services, the distribution
platform has been changed from Nico Nico
Channel Plus to "Zaiko".
Please wait a while until the announcement of the distribution plan for those
who have already purchased a distribution ticket on Nico Nico Channel Plus.
If you can't come to the venue, please
watch the program event on the
distribution platform.
Let's introduce the goods.
Thank you very much.
Let's take a look.
It's cute.
It's full of coconuts.
There are four goods.
Nonaka Kokona Acrylic Stand A and B
Random Bromide
And this is the Random Bromide
This time we have prepared a real thing
in the studio
It's so cute!
It's so pretty!
Oh, it's nice. It's like today's
atmosphere.
It's active, and it's like a beautiful
announcer.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my.
But it's a little...
You can do both.
What is it?
Really?
Wow, this is...
Right?
You can do it.
Wow.
What are you going to do? How do you do
this?
At the very end, it's like a one-pose.
I was given this, and I thought, "Why
not give it a try?"
And that's how it came to be used.
Ah, here.
Everyone, be careful.
It's a common one.
Amazing.
But this is...
It's nice.
For example, if you make an axta with
this side,
you can do this.
You can do it.
It's amazing.
Everyone, you did it.
You did it.
It's amazing.
It's cute.
Which one is your favorite?
What do you like about it?
Me?
I like the casual look.
This is really good.
I had a lot of fun posing for the
photoshoot.
The casual look has a wide range of
poses.
It's really good.
It's really cute.
That's about it.
For more information about the goods,
please check out the show's website.
If you'd like to purchase the goods,
That's all for today's event.
Is it okay if I put this here?
Thank you very much.
I'd like to read your letters until the
end of the game.
I'm going to read them now.
Thank you for your name, Benny B. Bat.
Good evening, Nasu-san, Izumifu, and the
staff.
Nasu-san is from Nagasaki, and Izumifu
is from Aichi.
Why don't we try speaking in each
other's dialect?
Let's show off Nagasaki and Aichi!
I'd be grateful if you could try it out
in your dialect.
Show off?
Yes.
And this person is from Aichi
prefecture.
Oh!
I'm looking forward to it.
What should I show off?
Well then, we're looking forward to the
event.
Thank you for coming today.
Nagasaki sounds like a good place to
show off.
Eh?
First of all, isn't Aichi cute from its
name?
Ah!
Really? Ah, then I'll attack you from
there.
I'll give you one point for that.
But, how does Aichi's dialect sound
like?
There's not much of it, right?
Kansai...
Yeah, there might be a bit of a western
style.
But, if you put it into honorifics,
there really isn't much of it.
So, it's like, "Ah, I wonder what it
is."
Ah, I wonder what it is!
I wonder what it is!
I wonder what it is.
It's like a little introduction.
It's like, "I wonder what it is."
I wonder what it is.
It's like, "What is it?"
What is it?
What is this? It's so cute!
Huh? Who is this?
Isn't it so cute?
This is Uchibai.
Really?
It's so cute!
Uchibai.
It's so cute.
Nagoya, Nagoya.
Can you say it in Nagasaki dialect?
Nagasaki dialect?
In Nagasaki dialect...
I can say...
Izumi-senpai is...
Really...
She has a lot of sense.
I'm studying by looking at your photos.
Wow! That's cute!
That's great!
I also...
I often look at your pictures on X.
Really?
Yeah, I look at them a lot.
Your face is so cute.
The "like" button...
It's not displayed anymore.
Oh, it's not?
Yeah, the "like" button isn't displayed
anymore.
It's not?
Yeah, the "like" button isn't displayed
anymore.
I think I'll be able to "like" you a lot
from now on.
Yeah, that's what I think.
That's what I think, but...
I'm a little embarrassed.
You'll get caught, right?
Oh, yeah.
You'll get a notification.
Yeah, I'll get caught, so...
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
How should I say it?
Oh, right.
You said it like you were bragging.
Do you have anything to say?
Do you have anything to say, Aichi?
The fast bullet train stops.
But the scale is big.
The scale is big.
The bullet train stops.
And...
There's a lot of history.
Oh, that's great.
Aichi has a history, too.
That's right.
Nobunaga and Ieyasu, too.
Yeah, yeah.
Chida is the head of the Sengoku Busho.
I have a lot, too.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
See you.
I'll read the second one.
The name is Shin-san. Thank you very
much.
Nonaka-san, the guest, Izumi-san, good
evening.
Good evening.
The two of you belong to the same
amusement agency, right?
Yes.
The history of the amusement agency is
younger, but Nonaka-san is a little
older.
That's right.
It's a little interesting.
I'm a fan of Izumi-san.
Izumi-san actually...
I'm a sister who has an older sister, so
I often pick on people I don't really
care about, or do things I don't want to
do.
Can I say this?
To be honest, I'm quite a piece of shit.
What was that?
What did you say?
That's true, I'm curious.
But it's only the second time.
Yeah, it's only the second or third
time.
People say we get along well.
Are you a piece of shit?
No, I'm not.
But it's fine.
Thank you.
She's my little sister, so...
You're her little sister?
That's right.
She's my little sister.
Really? Does that mean she's reliable?
Yes!
You just made me say that!
How should I put it...
She's a very caring person.
Natsuta is a good person.
She's a good person.
But she's really...
She talks to me a lot.
She's so kind.
She's my little sister.
Please pamper me a lot.
I'm used to being pampered rather than
pampered.
That's right.
Then I'll rely on you.
I'll rely on you.
This is amazing. Four fish.
It's all packed.
The top is full.
I think it's a sister-like personality.
Is that so?
I'm looking forward to it.
Please do so.
Thank you for your letters.
We will continue to wait for your
letters.
There is a special form for letters, so
please use that.
We are also waiting for requests such as
questions for Futsuota and me, and
requests for videos like this.
That's all for the first half of the
program.
In the second half of the program...
You'll be able to watch all of it for
free, so please watch it until the end!
The second half of the program is Nonaka
Kokona's Buzzreck! Buzzdemy Awards 2024
Night Festival!
I'd like to have a party with our guest
Izumi-san!
Yay!
Well then, as usual...
Let's move on to the next one.
We've received a letter about how we'll
do our lines.
Thank you for your name, Tony-san.
As a guest, Izumi Fuka's favorite, Mendako.
Please say a word, Mendako.
Your vocabulary is rough.
Do you know, everyone?
Izumi-san's "X" icon and header.
That's right, Mendako.
It's Mendako.
Mendako...
I don't speak it, though.
Do you have anything?
Like a pose?
Like a pose.
Well, the fin is...
It's pretty close to here.
And, well...
I'm swayed by the waves.
I can't move as I want to.
Then...
Let's make a serious face.
Oh, yeah.
It's a little different if you don't put
your feelings into it.
Like this.
Okay.
When I say, "One, two,"
Like this.
I got it.
Put down your eye patch.
Oh, me too.
I was killed.
Here we go.
One, two.
Everyone, please watch the second half.
Well, well, look forward to the second
half.
Look forward to it.
This is Nonaka Kokona, I'm your
host, and our guest is Fuka Izumi.
Nice to meet you.
Let's get started.
We have a special segment for you.
Izumi-san, let's do our best together!
Yeah! Let's do our best!
The first segment is this!
Nonaka Kokona challenges Guinness!
This is...
It's already a mini-corner, a corner
where Nonaka Kokona can challenge the
Guinness World Record by herself.
This time, the guest Izumi-san and the
two of us will challenge it.
The official Guinness World Record
holder is not here this time,
but if the Guinness World Record comes
out here, it will definitely be a big
buzz.
I would be happy if everyone could see
it.
And here is the Guinness World Record to
be challenged this time.
"Pull out the Jenga blocks in 1 minute"
This is from Jenga in 1 minute.
It's a challenge to see how many blocks
you can pull out.
The current Guinness record is 22
blocks.
22 blocks in one minute.
So it's 60 seconds.
So it's 2 times 40, right?
So it's 4 seconds per block.
Am I right?
I think so.
So I want to aim for more than that.
The two of you will take out the blocks
and stack them on top of each other.
When you take them out, use only one
hand.
Oh, I see.
I'd appreciate it if you could turn the
other one to your waist.
Okay.
Well then, I'd like to get started right
away.
Let's move.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do our best, okay?
Then I'll hold it for a moment
Okay
So
This is the Jenga we'll be using for the
Guinness World Record
Okay
Then
Let's start
Before we start, let's play rock-paper-
scissors and see who goes first
Okay
I lost!
Then I'll go first
Okay
Here I go
Challenge Guinness World Records!
Jen pulls out a block in 1 minute
Ready?
Start!
Go for it! Go for it!
I'll let you pull it out
Wait! What should I do?
Let's go with the bold pull!
I'm going!
Is it good?
It's not good, not good
I'll let you pull it out
Go! Go for it!
Go for it!
It's bold!
It's cool
Kokona-chan, you're bold!
It's a little different
It's here
It's good
It's not good
I'm going! I'm going!
I'm just protecting
You're just protecting? Really?
It's not good
Let's go with this one
It's here
It's good
It's a giraffe
How many did you pull out?
Time's up
This one
Did you pull out about 10?
10!
Eh?
Isn't it too strong?
So that means
The Jenga blocks that you pulled out in
1 minute
are 10
So this is a Guinness record
I couldn't pull it out
This is a little difficult
It's difficult
I just couldn't pull it out
Let's just say it's good
So that means
It's good
Let's just say it's good
Yes
Next time, we'll be able to do it again,
I'm sure.
So, we're planning to do a Guinness
challenge at an event like this.
Let's do our best!
That's it for today's mini-corner,
"Nonaka Kokona's Challenge to Guinness".
I hear you knocking it over.
I'm knocking it over.
I'm knocking it over a bit.
So, let's move on to today's main event.
Let me introduce today's project!
Here it is!
Nonaka Kokona's Buzz REC!
Buzz Demi Award!
Congratulations!
This program is a talk variety show
where I try various projects to make a
buzz video.
This week's event is "Buzz Demi Award
2024 Night Festival".
I would like to have a party with
Yuzumi-san, a guest who will come to the
event.
Let's have a party game!
I've prepared a few, so I'm going to
play a lot of party games, but before
that...
I've prepared a meal for you, Cathy!
Yay!
Here it is!
No!
I was surprised.
I'll say it.
Buffet with sweets!
Ah, that's nice, Takahashi-san, isn't
it?
Yes, well, when it comes to parties,
it's definitely buffets, isn't it,
everyone?
Well, are there buffets?
Buffets?
Buffets...
Yeah, there are quite a lot of buffets
at the end of the year.
I see.
There aren't many private buffets, are
there?
No, there aren't.
It's the first time I've been to a
buffet like this.
Yeah, it's the first time.
But it's nice, isn't it? It makes you
feel nostalgic.
Yeah, it's nice.
This is just right.
Yeah.
I've never been to a buffet like this.
This time, we're going to do it with
sweets.
We've prepared a lot of sweets, so we're
going to put them on each plate.
Well, let's put them on nicely and see
each other's buffet sense.
I see.
Okay.
I really like Izumi-san's sense, so...
I don't know. I've been saying it since
before this project was decided.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
So, everyone, here it is.
You can only choose the amount that can
be put on this plate.
It's also important how to arrange the
sweets.
Well, we're going to play a party game
after this, so let's choose quickly.
Let's start with the sweets!
It's really a sense, isn't it?
There's a variety show like that, right?
What should we do?
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
Have you been to a candy store?
I have!
It's like the one in the anime.
It's like the one in the picture.
It's like a shop.
It's so nice!
There's a shop in the neighborhood.
I'd buy candy and take it to my aunt.
And we'd all eat it in front of her
house.
That's so nice!
It's amazing. It's because it's in the
countryside.
That's nice.
Wow!
Can I have some Morocco?
Sure!
I like Morocco.
I lost the one I was looking for.
Oh, there it is!
I found it. I love this mochi taro.
I'll put it in the main dish.
That's good.
I like it. It's delicious.
This is from Nata de Coco, right?
This is delicious, isn't it?
I'll have this, too.
There's one from Nata de Coco and one
that's not from Nata de Coco.
There's a normal one.
I'll have this one.
It's annoying, isn't it?
Which one is it?
I know which one.
There's something like this.
Black Thunder is also included in the
sweets.
I see.
Sudako.
It's good.
There's my favorite, Awawawawa!
There are two kinds.
Grape and soda.
Since it's always soda, how about
grapes?
I thought it was Awawawawa, but it's
not.
It's Awa.
The name is Awa.
But it says Awa here.
I thought this was the name, but it
wasn't.
It was Awa.
We're eating Awa.
I love this.
Do you know what it is?
I'm going to take more.
It's good. It brings back memories.
What is this? "Eight"
Yes, "Eight Chocolate"
Ah, good
This is good, it's a dessert
Ehh, what should I do?
I'm worried
Ehh
Ah, but
Ah
I'm worried
Something sweet and sour.
It wasn't like this, was it?
It was like this for me.
But, you know, it's like...
You know, it's like...
It changes.
It's more like...
That's right, time goes by.
Time goes by and the package changes
That's right
It's different, isn't it, everyone?
It's changed, isn't it?
I feel like it's changed
That's right, it wasn't packaged like
this.
It's a good thing that it hasn't
changed.
Hmm...
Do you want to exchange it?
Ah, it's juicy!
I love juicy.
It's delicious.
I found a really good one.
Calpas!
It was buried!
Calpas.
Is it okay?
Thank you very much.
I love Calpas.
I really like this one.
It's like a rice ball.
What was it again?
It's a carrot.
It's a snack.
So it's called a carrot.
Let's eat it.
Okay.
With this...
- Like this. - I'll take the juicy.
- Like this. - Turn end!
Oh, me too.
I'm getting greedy.
- Turn end. - It's over.
So...
Yes, it's done.
Well then...
Let's put them in order.
I'll also put them in order.
Okay.
Let's compare our buffets.
Let's start with Izumi-san.
I hope you can show it to everyone.
Ta-da!
Oh!
Oh, I see, I see, I see, I see.
This is the rice and...
The rice and meat...
Um...
Meal zone.
That's nice.
This is the meal zone.
And this is the dessert zone.
I see, I see, I see.
And this is the appetizer, or how do you
say it?
The appetizer?
The appetizer-like position.
Ah, like a spinach appetizer.
Yeah, like that.
Like a Namuru.
This is also a Namuru-like position.
Ah, that too.
This is like a salad.
Ah, salad!
Salad!
It's like a potato salad place.
Oh, yeah.
It says "flower garden."
Like a sweet carrot?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like a bento.
Like a school lunch box.
Like a lunch box?
That's right.
Now, please take a look at mine.
Here it is.
It's a carrot.
Let me say something, too.
It's really just right.
The size is just right.
This is my appetizer, and this is also
my appetizer.
This is like a chopstick.
Ah, I see.
A chopstick.
A cutlery.
Yes, yes, yes.
And this is the main course.
Ah, rice.
Yes, rice and chicken.
Ah, rice and meat.
Yes, rice and meat.
Like this.
That's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's very good.
So, let's eat it while eating this.
Let's eat.
Let me gamble.
Okay.
I'll start gambling.
I'll guess the sourest one.
Can you tell by the smell?
This one.
Here I go.
Sour!
This is sour!
You can't tell, can you?
It's sour!
I'm sorry.
I've never seen anyone guess the sour
one.
I've never seen anyone guess the non-
sour one.
This one is sour.
Just one bite?
You got it right.
I have a good nose.
I have a really good nose.
You got it right.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I'll do my best.
I made a mistake.
I made a mistake in the middle of the
show.
It's good.
I'm glad.
Eat it.
I'm eating gum.
I made a mistake.
Yogurt.
I've loved this since I was a kid.
I see.
I've never eaten it.
It's delicious.
It's crunchy.
Yogurt?
It's yogurt.
Oh, it's hard to open.
Ah, go!
Oh, it came out.
Itadakimasu.
Ah, was the deco spoon like this?
Mm!
This is it.
Ehh~
So that's what it's like.
I'll blow on it.
Fufufu
It's a new product.
It's sweet.
Yeah, it smells sweet.
It smells like yogurt.
It smells like a drink.
I used to use it when I was in
elementary school.
It's good.
Dagashi is good.
Put the gum in the right corner.
I'll eat it if it falls.
The mochi taro is good.
It's stable.
The gum has a good taste.
It's sweet and salty.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'll eat it.
The mochi taro is delicious.
I'll split it.
I made a mistake with the chewing gum.
But you're lucky.
You got it right.
I got it right twice.
I love it and I bought it a lot.
I can tell by the smell.
Amazing.
It's delicious.
It's a party.
There's no knife.
The potato taro is good.
Potato fry.
I thought it was something else.
It's good.
It brings back memories.
I don't eat snacks anymore.
You're great.
Didn't you eat a lot just now?
I ate gum.
I ate gum and Sapporo potato.
You ate them, right?
I thought you've seen them.
This is called "Dagashi"
I don't usually eat this much
It's good
We'll eat it later
So
Now, let's get to the main event of the
night festival.
We'll play a party game to liven up the
But it's not just a game.
It's an award-winning night festival
party,
so we've prepared a celebrity game.
A celebrity game.
So let's get started.
We'll be playing this game.
It's a nine-ball game with billiards.
Billiards are for celebrities, after
all.
Yes, I'm a celeb.
I'm a celeb.
So, I'd like to talk about the rules.
This ball is called a "te-dama" or
"shiro" in Japanese.
I'm sure you all know what it is.
It's a ball with a number 9 on it.
Is it "mato-kyu"?
"Mato-dama"?
There are a lot of words I don't know.
"Mato-dama"!
"Mato-dama" is a game where you drop a
ball into your pocket and the person who
drops the 9th ball wins.
This time it's a special rule, so if you
drop a mato-dama, you can continue to
play.
And if you don't touch any balls, you
can drop a free ball into your pocket.
If you don't touch any balls, you can
drop a free ball into your pocket.
But you can't return the ball that you
dropped into your pocket.
You can return the ball that you dropped
into your pocket.
Let's move to another place.
Yes, this is the billiard.
So, let's get started.
Let's do it.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Okay, I'll go first.
So, I'll start shouting.
Okay.
Here we go.
Billiard Nine-Ball Match.
Ready, start!
Okay.
Well...
No.1?
OK.
No.1 is impossible, isn't it?
What do you mean?
It's impossible to drop only No.1 so
far, isn't it?
Break the board for now.
I'll get closer.
I didn't drop it, but I touched it, so
I'll continue.
I see.
If I drop it, I'll continue, right?
If you drop it, you'll change.
Change?
You're aiming for the first one, right?
You're aiming for a difficult one.
You did it, Shiro-chan.
I'm going to go. Everyone, please excuse
me for a moment.
Ah, it's standing up. It's standing up.
Is that a free ball?
It's a free ball.
Can I put it where I like?
Ah, then...
Then...
What should I do?
If I put it here, if I drop 1, it's fine
if I drop 7, right?
Yes.
Here I go.
It's quite powerful, isn't it?
But, but, but, but...
It fell.
I dropped a 7.
But I can drop a 1, right?
Here I go.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, 1.
Ah, goodbye.
Let's continue.
I aimed for 2.
It's blue, I'll do it
You can do it, right?
I'll do it
Ha! Ah!
I did it
Then, what should I do?
I'll go with power.
Here I go!
Oh!
Eh?
How many did you drop?
I dropped quite a few.
That's amazing.
But there's two here.
Eh?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Can you do it?
I'm going to eat it.
9 is still alive.
Free ball?
Oh, then it doesn't matter where it is.
I'm going to drop the 2.
Did I drop the white one?
Ah, that's right.
Ah...
Then it's 5. Ah, it's 4.
Shiro-chan, come out.
Here you go.
Let's go with number 4.
It's number 4, the smallest one.
It's here.
Do your best.
Here I go.
Oh!
It's power.
There's a lot of power.
I'm going to be bold and decisive.
No way!
Isn't this really hard?
Why?
It's really hard, but what should I do?
What should I do?
It's that way, I think.
Eh?
No way...
Ah!
I can't do it!
This is hard.
Go ahead.
It's a d-ball.
But it's a 4, right?
It's a 4.
Ah, then it's...
Yeah.
Excuse me.
The balls are disappearing.
I'm going to throw it.
Eh?!
Why?!
It dodged it!
I'll decide who wins. I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
But you dropped it, so it's fine.
- I'll switch. - Switch.
- I'll put it where you like. - Thank
you.
I'll put it here.
- But I'll win if I drop 9. - Right.
Here I go.
Oh, beautiful!
- Amazing! - I did it!
I did it!
It's in an exquisite place.
It's common to hit it like this.
I see.
Here I go.
It fell beautifully.
It fell.
Is it a free ball?
It's a free ball.
I'll use this.
I have a winning spirit, don't I?
Yes.
Here I go.
Lightly, okay?
Be bold, Sensei.
Yes!
I won!
I'm so happy!
Be bold, Sensei.
I dropped a bunch of balls on the floor.
- I won. - You're really good at this,
aren't you?
I got it in the last round.
- I won. - Thank you.
- What a graceful game. - What a
celebrity.
- What a celebrity. - What a celebrity.
What a wonderful party.
- So... - Yes.
The winner of this celebrity game is
Izumi-san.
Thank you.
I won.
That's it for the billiards 9-ball
match!
Let's move on to another popular party
game.
Here it is!
Golf Putter Match!
Golf is a popular game.
It's true, it's only for celebrities.
It's a holiday.
That's right.
So, the rules for this time are...
We have prepared a golf battle, so...
Everyone, let's meet again later.
Please wait a moment.
Okay, so we're ready to go.
Now, I'd like to explain the rules of
the golf putter match.
This time, we'll be playing with this
golf putter.
Each player will hit one ball at a time.
If you hit two of the three red cups
first, you win.
It's a simple rule.
Even if you put it in a cup with a ball
in it, it's invalid.
If you hit two of the three red cups
first, you win.
We're going to take a break.
Are you looking forward to it?
Yes!
Well then, let's get started.
Do you want to go first or second?
Oh, go ahead.
I'll go first.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Okay, let's get started.
Ready, set, go!
I'm going to play it right away.
This is a real club, isn't it?
That's right.
It's pretty heavy, isn't it?
I'd like you to try it.
Here we go.
Oh, good.
Oh, close.
I want to win.
One game at a time.
Okay.
Have you ever played golf?
No, I haven't.
But I often play Anpanman.
It's a cute little game.
I see.
Here I go.
Please do your best.
It's not enough.
One more time.
It wasn't as easy as I thought it would
be.
Thank you.
But if you go straight, you should be
able to do it.
I was a little scared of the bunker.
Alright.
Well then, here I go.
Oh! Oh!
Nice! You did it!
Wow!
Amazing!
You're good!
I did it!
If you make two holes, you win, right?
I only have one ball left.
This is bad.
It looks like it's easy to aim at.
You've done this before, right?
I've seen it a lot.
It's a curve, right?
It's a curve.
Okay.
I'm going to show you how excited Riku
is.
A little stronger.
Here we go.
It didn't go in.
I'm sorry.
It's not "dews."
It's "riichi."
Riichi.
I'll go for the last ball.
The last ball declaration.
My ball is in the way.
I'll do it nicely.
I passed it.
Safe.
I'm taking a break, so if I get a light
blue or yellow card, I'll move on to the
next one.
I was strong just now, so...
The same place is over there!
But I'm taking a break.
Eh?
I didn't get a card, so I'm taking a
break.
Can I do it?
Can I? Thank you
It's difficult
It's golf
I think I can do it
I know
Here?
Here I go
I got over it.
This is difficult.
This is difficult. Can I get a little
closer?
The rules changed suddenly.
But it's okay.
I got to this line.
Here I go.
It's strong.
It's close.
It's close to the last one, but it
doesn't work.
It's not good.
It's hard.
It's a little difficult from here.
Do your best!
Close!
I thought it would go in!
Smoothly.
Okay, please wait
I thought I passed!
Good night!
Thank you
I'm going to collect the bullets
That's okay
The bullets are here
Thank you
Well then
I'm going to start.
I'm taking a break.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
That was close!
Was that a red ball?
You can do it in one go!
Isn't that huge?
Before you forget the feeling...
Go for it!
Go in!
Yay!
Amazing!
You're so good!
And so, the winner is Nonaka Kokona!
Yay!
Wow!
This is fun!
You're talented!
Wow, wow!
Should we put this back?
Yeah!
I don't want to let go!
This is my prize!
Amazing!
Wow!
If you try golfing...
It'll be fun!
It'll be amazing!
I didn't think you'd be able to do it.
I've never used a real one before.
This is amazing!
Yay!
Amazing!
So, that's it!
That was the golf battle!
That was fun!
Now that we've had a taste of how it
feels to be a celebrity, we've brought
you the party game for the Batsudemi
Award 2024.
I'm sure there are people who came to
the event and watched the stream.
We look forward to working with you.
We look forward to working with you,
too.
We look forward to working with you.
That's all for Batsu Demi Award 2024.
This is the end of Nonaka Kokona's live
broadcast.
Do you have any announcements?
Yes, please.
Madogushi Daria is a 2D TV anime.
I will be playing Luchia Fuano in
Madogushi Daria's Utsumukanai.
It will start airing on Saturday, July
6th.
I will also be playing the role of
Kokoshi Tantan in Shikanokonoko.
It will start airing on Sunday, July
7th.
I hope you enjoy both works.
Please look forward to other events.
We will let you know when we can meet
again.
I hope you come to see us. Thank you.
We also have an announcement from the
program.
We will release a bonus video for the
Producer Plan.
In the bonus video, we will talk about
what we couldn't talk about and what we
couldn't do.
The video will be released soon, so
please check it out.
I love you!
In addition, there are also off-shot
photos and handwritten messages, so
please look forward to them.
Yes, the bonus videos and off-shot
photos I showed you will be released as
soon as the Nico Nico system is
restored, so please wait for a while.
And the purpose of this program is to
buzz.
This time...
Well...
The Guinness record is...
Oh, right.
We couldn't film it, but...
But if you could record the pattern
success as a series of success,
it would be nice.
It's like a beautiful girl with great
talent appears.
I'd like to mix it up.
I think so, too.
Yes, that's it.
In addition, we also released a video on
the official TikTok program,
so please look forward to it.
And this week, June 23rd, a program
event will be held on Sunday.
Thank you for your support for Nonaka
Kokona's "REC Chuu! Buzzdemy Awards
2024".
In the afternoon, tonight's guest, Fuka
Izumi, will come again as a guest.
Tickets for the event are on sale at
ZAICO, so please take a look at the
program's first event.
I'd like to ask Ms. Izumi for a word.
I'm glad to be the guest of the first
event.
I hope I can help you have fun until
everyone gathers.
This is the first time I've been to
Saitama.
Sakuratown?
Yes, Sakuratown.
Where was it?
Tokorozawa!
It's my first time in Tokorozawa, so I'm
looking forward to it.
I'll be in your care.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And finally, here's the announcement for
next month's live stream.
Next month's live stream will be...
...on the show's homepage and X.
Until then, please look at today's
archive and the event's live stream.
Thank you to our guest, Fuka Izumi, for
joining us tonight.
Thank you.
Please look forward to this weekend's
event.
Yes.
Now it's time to say goodbye.
Our guests were Nonaka Kokona and...
Fuka Izumi.
Please join us.
Let's go.
Okay, cut!
Thank you for watching.