(Six months later)
[music]
Oh no
(crowd cheering)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music intensifies)
(crowd cheering)
(dramatic music)
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(singing in foreign language)
(speaking in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(singing in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(speaking in foreign language)
The fact that you wanted to see us, the
fact that you wanted to show us the best
scenery,
I'm really happy to be able to receive
such feelings.
And thank you for the best scenery.
I think there are a lot of anxieties and
difficulties in your daily life.
We are still small idols, but I want to
be a one-of-a-kind idol that can shine
on your world.
With that thought in mind...
I present to you this song.
Please listen to it.
"Idol Costume"
The first time I met you
I felt like I was in love
In the mirror, I was sparkling
After the failure, you always
let me cry
No matter what, we were always together
You made me special
I took a deep breath
It's okay to cry
You're the cutest on this stage
I want you to look at the stars in the
sky
I want you to see
You're the only one in the world
I'm your idol
Countless stars, shine on
I definitely want you to find me
I want you to see
I want to have a dream that will never
come true
"Idol Costume"
Your sleeves were loose
I was sweating on busy days
Even on a rainy day, I worked hard
I'm your flower, fluttering
You colored me
I had a bad time with that image
You cast a spell on me
I hugged you
It's okay to cry
You're the cutest on this stage
I want you to look at the stars in the
sky
I want you to see
I want to shine on the world
I'm a little idol now
When I'm shaking in the dark night
I definitely want you to look up
I want you to see
Like a star, I'll shine forever
Even if we're far apart on the stage
I'll take you to the future
I want you to look at the stars in the
sky
I want you to see
I'm a little idol now
I want you to look at the stars in the
sky
I want you to see
I want to have a dream that will never
come true
When I'm shaking in the dark night
I definitely want you to look up
I want you to see
Just like you, see, I'll always be
shining
"One Song"
One song is not enough
If only one voice could be by my side
I might be unable to sing with all my
might
Even so, I'll sing to the world
Come on, take my hand
I can love weakness
I can love failure and pain
Our feelings overlap and become a song
I can light up someone's heart
I'll stop
I don't care if it's hot
I don't care if it's cloudy
I don't care if I cry
I don't have to put up with it
It's alright, I'll be by your side
I'll sing to you
I want to sing about sadness and
loneliness
I'll decorate a fantasy of love
With the sound of children's voices
Last, your Story
It starts dancing with the beat of the
drum
A melody of infinity
It's a finale
I won't say goodbye
The happy moments are overflowing
I'm sure it'll continue
I was waiting for the night sky alone
I was throwing away my emotions alone
We know how to sing and shine
So let's sing to the world
Look, I have a passionate passion
I have a heart that won't break
Our wishes will become dreams
A night to light up someone's heart
I don't care if I fall
I don't care if I get hurt
I don't care if I lose
I just have to do it
It's okay, I'm on your side
A fanfare for you
Let's leave the fun, joy, and happiness
to the world
I'll decorate a fantasy of love
With the sound of children's voices
Let's write your story
With the sound of freedom
With the melody born from the heart
I won't say goodbye
The world is too beautiful
I'll dance with you
I'm sure it'll continue
I'll decorate a fantasy of love
With the sound of children's voices
With the sound of joy
A song for you
I'll decorate a fantasy of love
With the sound of children's voices
And the sound of joy
And the sound of summer
I'll organize it
With the sound of children's voices
And the sound of summer
This is your story
To the end
[Song title]
Congratulations.
The seven people have been selected.
Tokyo Idol Festival 2022
will debut on the Smile Garden stage.
I'm Hime Komiyama.
I'm a member of Hoshikawa.
[Song title]
It was far more brilliant than I
imagined.
It was a wonderful stage.
[Song title]
Congratulations.
The seven people have been selected.
[Song title]
I was able to do it perfectly.
Congratulations.
The seven people have been selected.
[Song title]
That's what I'm aiming for
I don't know, what is it that I'm
hiding?
I can't live like I'm tired, like I'm in
a trance
I can't let go of my breath
I don't know, what is it that I'm hoping
for?
I wonder if it's a work of fiction
I was told that my increasing body size
Is not necessary
I have to ignore my position and myself
I have to become someone
I have to be someone
Even if I cry, I want to show you my
rust-free soul
I'm not cute, I'm not pretty, I'm a mess
That's why I never get tired of mixing
colors
It's not fiction, it's not a lie,
there's a mistake
That's why my heart moves
So that I can be the person I want to be
I'm not cute, I'm not pretty, I'm a mess
That's why my heart moves
So that I can be the person I want to be
I'm not cute, I'm not pretty, I'm a mess
Isn't it okay to expose it?
If I have to kill my true self and work
Even if I'm worried, I want to show you
my rust-free soul
It's not ideal, it's not easy, it's a
dead end
Even so, I want to bloom a flower, I
want to be me
It's not logic, it can't be helped,
there's pain
Even so, I want to love you
So that I can be the person I want to be
Let's live proudly, beautifully
I'm not cute, I'm not pretty, I'm a mess
That's why I never get tired of mixing
colors
It's not fiction, it's not a lie,
there's a mistake
That's why my heart moves
So that I can be the person I want to be
Do you know about me? Do I look cute?
How's my singing? Did I sing well?
Do I look cute in my clothes and makeup?
Do you like my dance moves and my bad
habits?
I can't move my hands, I can't move my
feet
Even so, I want to fight, because I'm an
idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down on
The word "idol" doesn't even exist
Don't say it to my face
Sometimes I say "of course"
Don't compare me with your image
I hate the word "idol" the most in the
world
I don't think you can see my private
life
My personality is bad
Are you fooling me?
I'm serious, I'm serious
I'm just the way I am
If you like me, please push me
Is that still a lie?
Do you know about me? Do I look cute?
How's my singing? Did I sing well?
Do I look cute in my clothes and makeup?
Do I look like an idol?
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down on
The word "idol" doesn't even exist
Don't say it to my face
Sometimes I say "of course"
Don't compare me with your image
I hate the word "idol" the most in the
world
I cut my hair short
I'm a proud idol
Let's go for it
I can't act if I don't have support
I can't live if it's only my hobby
I'm always embarrassed
I love you, please wait for me
Even if I lose my confidence
Even if I get tired of it
I still want to be an idol
I have a lot of fans
I have a lot of love
I always have the love of my family
I'm alive
Idol
I hate people who make fun of me
I hate being looked down on
The word "idol" doesn't even exist
Don't say it to my face
Sometimes I say "of course"
Don't compare me with your image
I hate the word "idol" the most in the
world
I hate being looked down on
The word "idol" doesn't even exist
Don't say it to my face
Sometimes I say "of course"
Don't compare me with your image
I hate being looked down on
The word "idol" doesn't even exist
Don't say it to my face
Sometimes I say "of course"
Come on, let's make a revolution
Idol
Stand up
Now, let's make a revolution
Revolution
We don't want to be broken
We don't want to be killed
If you catch me with your unwavering,
loyal hands
I'll devour you
I'll send you to the sky
I'll shake you without being noticed
I'll make you smile and make you dance
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
If you can hear me, please answer
I was smiling
I was overflowing
I'm a worthless me
Even if you look down on me, it doesn't
hurt
No more noise
Are you ready?
I was born
I'll make a revolution
Follow me
Don't hesitate
Sit down with me
I'll make a revolution
I'll make you smile and make you dance
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
If you can hear me, please answer
I was born
I'll make a revolution
Follow me
Don't hesitate
Sit down with me
I'll make a revolution
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
If you can hear me, please answer
I don't want to be noticed
I don't want to be seen
No more noise
Are you ready?
I was born
I'll make a revolution
I'll make you smile and make you dance
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
If you can hear me, please answer
I was born
I'll make a revolution
Follow me
Don't hesitate
Sit down with me
I'll make a revolution
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
I was born
I'll make a revolution
Follow me
Don't hesitate
Sit down with me
I was born
I'll make a revolution
I'll shout from the bottom of my heart
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
I was born
I'll make a revolution
Follow me
Don't hesitate
Sit down with me
I was born
Thank you!
This isn't a game of rock-paper-scissors
More and more, let's go all out
Are you ready?
I was born
I'll make a revolution
I'll make you smile and make you dance
There's no reason to lose
Break out!
You can't live without challenging
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
Break out!
Let's overcome the limits of the present
chance
Break out!
There's nothing to be afraid of
I'll change myself
Break out!
The wound of defeat that began
Tears and flowers bloom
You can laugh and give up
I don't know such words
It's fun to keep chasing after your
dreams
There's no reason to hold back
Be a realist
Break through the limit
Break out!
You can't live without challenging
Even if you're cornered, I'll scream
Break out!
Change your emotions into strength
A brave heart
Break out!
A desperate dance
With a full heart
Break out!
I'll catch you
Hit, melt, and laugh
The wound on your knee becomes a medal
Even if you're cornered
I want to live with a victory
There's nothing to be afraid of
The strong wind blows
The blue flames gather
The dust that makes time
The road that leads to the top
Break out!
You can't live without challenging
The strongest, the most advanced
Break out!
The battlefield is a battlefield
Break through the limit
Break out!
There's a storm today
You can't be afraid
Break out!
Even if you're cornered
Do your best!
You can do it!
The wound of defeat that has begun
Tears make flowers bloom
Give up and laugh
I don't know such words
Even if you're cornered
I want to live with a victory
The wound of defeat that has begun
Tears make flowers bloom
Give up and laugh
I don't know such words
Thank you!
Fall in love with me more
Look at me more
I'll give you back
With a love-filled tearful kiss
It's not your fault
I'm right
I'll make a heart
Please fall in love
I'll do anything I can
Without NG
It's a big challenge
I found it in the picture
I know better than anyone else
But it's okay
Stand here
Everyone is here
Fall in love with me more
Look at me more
I'll give you back
With a love-filled tearful kiss
I'll show you a dream
Enjoy
A love-filled special night
I'll dance
Everyone, it's still not enough
Let's shout more and more
Please write a letter
I'll read it many times
I'll treasure it
It's still early for a scandal
I won't betray
I'll make a declaration
I won't lose to jealousy
I'll beat you with my mischievous
ability
So I won't stop
I won't lose
I don't hate you
I'm fine
Stand here
More
I won't sweat
I'll give you back
With a love-filled tearful kiss
It's not your fault
More
It's not enough
Accept it
A love-filled special night
Let's dance
Ah, the end is approaching
It's lonely
It's fun, but I'm about to cry
Next time, next time
I hope we can meet again
I did it!
I was able to come this far today
It's all thanks to the fans who have
supported me so far
I want to see a lot of scenery together
from now on
Please follow me
Words overflowing with kindness
Words of someone who has no heart
It's necessary, it's necessary
Let's be strong
Shout as much as you like
More
Have fun
Don't forget
I hope it will be a special day
Let's sing together
Forever
Let's walk together
Words of love
An exceptional L.O.V.E
Stand here
More
Look at me
Let's repay
With a love-filled grief
With a cry
More
Show me your dream
Have fun
A love-filled special night
Let's dance
Thank you very much
The next song will be the last
Thank you very much for spending this
time with Nadeshiko Takane
I want to continue with everyone here
And I want to move forward with these
nine people
I hope you will follow me from now on
I'll do my best to be able to do it.
Everyone, please take our best.
Please listen.
"Live Beautifully"
Even if I go to heaven, I can't reach
anyone's hand right away.
Noble and beautiful flowers are stupid
and useless.
I'm not going to give up!
There's no hesitation, there's no regret
I've lived for this day
If I were to decide on my own,
I'm sure I'd be the first
Life is fleeting,
so don't take away my youth
No matter what I do, I won't forget
I won't take away my dreams
I want to go straight to heaven
I don't want to reach anyone's hands
I'm going to throw myself
at the noble and beautiful flowers
I'm prepared to fight
I don't want you to come with me,
so I'm going to risk my life to bloom
I want to live beautifully
I want to be an idol
I want to be the best
I'll keep answering
No matter what, I won't stop
We don't have a day like that
Believe in me
I'm not prepared
I've lived for this day
If I were to decide on my own,
I'm sure I'd be the first
Whose life am I living?
Failure brings anxiety in an instant
Even if I give up, I'll keep challenging
I won't run away from my dreams
Even if I'm a thorn, I'll go straight
Even if I'm covered in wounds,
I'll bloom again
I want to be a flower that won't wither
The scenery I see when I'm alone
I want you to be by my side
I'll risk my life to bloom
I'll dye the world
I want to be an idol
I'll show you my growth
Who am I today?
If the result is everything,
I want to live in this world
Even if I'm hit, I'll shout out my love
Even if I'm ignored, I'll shout out my
love
Even if I'm told that I'm ugly,
I'll fight with my pride in my life
I'll raise my flag
I'll move towards my dream
I know that I'll advance
That times will change
But I can't change
My dream won't change
Even if I'm facing the sky, I'll go
straight
No one's hand will reach me
I want to be a beautiful flower
I'm prepared to fight
I want you to be by my side
I'll risk my life to bloom
I'll live beautifully
The scenery I see when I'm alone
I want you to be by my side
I'll risk my life to bloom
I'll awaken the world
I'll be an idol
I'll show you my growth
I'll keep answering
Even if I cry, I'll stop
We don't have time for that
Thank you very much for this wonderful
time today.
We are Takane and Nadeshiko.
Thank you very much.
Nakanishi, Nakanishi, Nakanishi,
Nakanishi...
(Chanting)
I want to make it a more wonderful song.
Everyone, please continue to support us.
Please support us.
Yes, and then, and then,
we have a new outfit!
Yay!
Everyone, is it cute?
It's cute!
Thank you! From now on,
I'm looking forward to performing in
this costume in front of everyone.
I have an announcement for everyone
here.
The first announcement is here.
It's a new outfit.
How does everyone feel about this new
outfit?
Thank you very much.
We have more announcements to make.
Here's the next one.
Takaneko Christmas Party 2025
Starting today, September 7th, at 9pm,
we'll be giving away free tickets to
FCs!
I'd be happy if everyone could spend
Christmas with us.
Please!
Here's another one.
Let's start with...
Akane no Nadeshiko x Docomo x Chojuudai
x Docomo limited Neko Utsurundesu 3rd
Anniversary Version Spendent Campaign
will start!
It will start!
It will!
Utsurundesu!
We took a lot of pictures in the
dressing room.
We did.
We might be able to send you the
pictures we just took.
Please apply!
We would like to take a picture with
TikTok on the back of everyone who came
today.
Staff, please.
Please.
What kind of pose should I do?
What should I do?
3.6?
Is this possible?
What?
What is it?
What? What is it?
What?
Ah, so cute, so cute, so cute
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
So cute
Ah, so cute, so cute
It's nostalgic
What? What?
Isn't it nostalgic?
Did you drop it?
It's nostalgic
Wow
So cool
Traffic jam
What?
What is this?
Let's go with the sound of the bell
Hokkaido!
Yeah!
Let's go with the sound of the bell
Let's go!
Wow!
This is not the time to take a picture
Let's stand up
Wait a minute
I was surprised
There were a lot of announcements
There was an important announcement
First of all, the first album will be
released!
The album means...
What is this?
I'm so nervous!
Are you nervous?
Does this mean that this costume is the
album?
Yes, it is.
The album is...
There's a lot of songs in this album,
right?
That's right.
Isn't it amazing?
You can make an album with a lot of
Takanero Nadeshiko's three-year history.
And it's from September 20th.
Will you come to Lily Bay?
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy to be able to hold Lily Bay
again this year.
We're looking forward to it.
And tomorrow...
The tour has been announced!
Speaking of February 14th, we had our
important one-man show this year, right?
From there, the tour will start a year
later.
In addition, we did a lot of ZEPP.
Anyway, the venue is wide and you can go
all the way up to Hokkaido.
I'd be happy if I could meet a lot of
people from all over the country.
It's all over Asia.
How many countries are there?
All over the world!
Also, on May 6th, the tour final will be
held at the International Forum.
It's so big, isn't it?
I still can't imagine it.
I'm nervous even though it's not over
yet.
Everyone, we have a lot of plans.
Will you make plans for Takaneko-chan?
Really?
You're not going to say goodbye today,
are you?
You'll come back, right?
I feel like it's getting less and less.
Why?
You'll give it to me, right?
Thank you very much.
I'm sure there are people who have been
supporting us for a long time.
I'm sure there are people who say, "I
came here for the first time today."
I'd be happy if you could come to the
tour and a lot of other big shows in the
future.
Thank you for making such a wonderful
announcement.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Let's take a picture.
What pose do you want to do?
I have a good idea.
I want to make a cat face on the 3rd
anniversary.
That's cute.
Everyone,
If I say "Takaneko", will you say
"Daisuki"?
Thank you.
Everyone, let's make a cat pose.
Takaneko!
Thank you.
Let's take a TikTok too.
Staff, please.
Let's do it.
Let's do it together with everyone here.
I've never heard of it before.
My darling, please.
Are you ready, everyone?
Really? Aren't you a little tired?
My darling, can you do it?
Yes!
Music, start!
I hate you.
Make a promise to me.
My darling, my darling, my darling
darling.
My darling, my darling, my darling.
Love is not a lie.
Thank you very much.
Please go back to your seats.
We've run through a lot so far, but this
is really the last one.
Can you all stand up?
Everyone, can you make a voice at the
end?
You've been waiting a long time, haven't
you?
That's not how you do it, right?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you all hit me harder?
Yeah!
We're going to sing our last song!
Please listen to us, "Magic of the
Feet"!
Look at me! Look at me! Look at me!
Ah!
Let's go!
Tell me what you like about me
Did you find something cute about me?
I want to be praised, I want to win
I love you, Bakunaka
Tell me what you like about me
Is there something gentle about me?
I want to be praised, I want to win
Tell me what you like about me
Listen to all my wishes
Don't let them go
Be grateful for being born
Love Chu Chu, Love Chu Chu
I'm so cute!
I want to be praised, I want to win
I love you, Bakunaka
Love Chu Chu, Love Chu Chu
I'm so cute!
I want to be praised, I want to win
I fell in love, I fell in love
It's okay, remember me
Steal away, steal away
Don't change the rhythm
The only city I loved
I'm aiming to be the champion
Please be my recovery magic
I love strong O.S.E.
The ball is in the castle, the wedding
is in the city, and the honor is in the
hands of the princess
I like this kind of me
What kind of wish is it? Listen to me,
don't reject it
I want to be grateful for being born
Love Chu Chu Love Chu Chu
I'm going to bully you
I fell in love, I fell in love
I'm going to cry, I'm going to cry
I'm going to run away, I'm going to sigh
There's something I want to say
What is it?
I want to tell you something, you're
cute
What is it?
I love you, I love you, I love you
I finally found you, princess
The reason I was born
What is it?
I met you after that
With you, my life
I'm the number one in the world
I love you, I love you
Everyone, you can still make a voice,
right?
Everyone, make a lot of voices
First, Momoko
Momoko, shout in a cheerful voice
One, two, Momoko
Momoko
Now, Nao
Yes
Nao, jump
Everyone, Nao
Shout in a loud voice
One, two, Nao
Nao
Thank you
Next is Mikuru
Yes, I'm Mikuru
Can everyone call me Mikuru?
Here we go
One, two, Mikuru
Mikuru
Next is So-chan
Yes
Can everyone call me So-chan?
One, two, So-chan
So-chan
Thank you
Next is Momona
Yes
Please call me Momona in a loud voice
One, two, Momona
Momona
Next is
Hina
Yes, I'm Hina
Everyone, please call me Hina
One, two, Hina
Hina
Thank you
Next is Su-chan
Yes, I'm Su-chan
I'll speed up Su-chan
I'll speed up
One, two, Su-su
Su-su
Thank you
Next is
Himeri-chan
Yes, I'm Himeri
Everyone, please call me Himeri in a
loud voice
One, two, Himeri
Himeri
Thank you
The last is Eiri-chan
I'm Eiri-chan
Everyone, please call me Eiri-chan in a
loud voice
Eiri-chan
Nao-chan, what will you do at the end?
I want you to shout "Takane-ko"
Let's shout "Takane-ko" together
Takane-ko
Thank you
Let's go until the end
Let's go
I fell in love at first sight
It was love at first sight
You stand out from the crowd
You're a cherry blossom
I'm an adult, I don't suit you
I know
I'm rumored, I'm exposed, I'm not
I'm an adult, I'm sorry I fell in love
During class, I had a dream
It was disgusting
Sometimes, you
Turned your innocent face to me
You ignored even the beads
I love you so much it's embarrassing
I love you so much that I'm about to cry
I'm glad I like you so much that I want
to forget
There's no way I could love you
There's no way I could go out with you
I can't even talk to you
I'm glad I like you
I'm sorry, I love you
I love you so much
I love you
This song is really the last song of the
day!
Everyone, let's get excited!
I was cleaning the pool in the afternoon
class
I heard a story
Let's study together in the morning
Let's play fireworks
You're being invited by a boy
I was looking at you with my side eyes
I'm not in your heart anyway
But suddenly
You look at me
You look at me and look at me
I'm sorry, I'm not in your heart anyway
But I'm still happy
I love you so much that I want to cry
I love you so much that I'm about to cry
I'm glad I like you
There's no way I could love you
There's no way I could go out with you
I can't even call your name
My love won't go away
I love you so much
I love you
I've never seen you in a school uniform
I can't concentrate
My throat is so dry
I'm a little nervous
Don't get jealous
I'll go with you
I'll walk with you
Are there people you like in your small
voice?
I said it unconsciously, I said it was
you
I thought I was hated for being a little
reckless
You walked in front of me and hid your
face
Sorry, I like you
Today, I like you
Always, I like you
I like you
No, I like you
Next, I like you
I like everything
I like you
Today, I was really happy to be able to
spend this time with these 9 people,
everyone in this venue, and everyone
watching the live broadcast.
From now on, Takane no Nadeshiko will
continue to aim for a more and more
proud idol group.
I hope everyone will continue to support
us warmly.
That's all from us, Takane no Nadeshiko.
Thank you.
I would like to go wave my hand to
everyone for the last time.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.
I can see you all, Takane-san.
Thank you.
It was fun, thank you.
Thank you for the second time.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.
Bye-bye.
Thank you all, thank you goods and
everything else too.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Bye bye.
Thank you so much everyone.
Thank you everyone!
Bye bye!
Thank you!
Come see us again!
See you again!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Let's meet again!
Thank you!
See you again!
Bye-bye!
It's a promise!
Thank you all for watching!
Let's meet again!
See you again!